<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geopolitical Tensions on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/geopolitical-tensions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Geopolitical Tensions on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/geopolitical-tensions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:1202
Chances: B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call discussed operational and financial results, including total gold production and performance highlights. B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 revenues increased year-over-year due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. B2Gold delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating a potential positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JPM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</guid>
      <description>score:818
Chances: JPMorgan Chase is expanding its presence and innovation efforts in India with the opening of two state-of-the-art facilities, enhancing service excellence and efficiency. JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s Advancing Black Wealth Tour aims to deliver financial education, workshops, and wealth-building seminars to Black communities, contributing to financial empowerment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:946
Chances: Intel Corporation&amp;rsquo;s decision to open an innovation hub in China to support local technology startups indicates a commitment to growth and innovation despite geopolitical tensions. Shares of Intel have experienced a 35% gain this year, recovering from previous losses and demonstrating positive momentum.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
