<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday Wall on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday Wall on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:26:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to Allow South Korean, Taiwan Chip Makers to Keep Operations in China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. government has reversed its previous policy and will now allow South Korean and Taiwanese chipmakers to keep their operations in China. This is a major shift in policy, as the U.S. had previously discouraged chipmakers from investing in China due to concerns about China&amp;rsquo;s growing technological capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#39;s Twitter vs. Bad Bots: The Battle Goes On</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/elon-musks-twitter-vs.-bad-bots-the-battle-goes-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/elon-musks-twitter-vs.-bad-bots-the-battle-goes-on/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Threatens to Walk Away from Twitter Deal Over Fake Accounts Elon Musk has threatened to walk away from his $44 billion deal to buy Twitter if the company does not provide more information about the number of fake accounts on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Tech Giants Are Slowly Cutting Off Hong Kong Internet Users</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</guid>
      <description>In a move that could have a significant impact on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy and innovation ecosystem, American tech giants are slowly cutting off internet users in the city.
Google and OpenAI have not rolled out AI chatbots to Hong Kong, putting it alongside mainland China and North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech, an Early Booster of Remote Work, Wants People Back in the Office</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-an-early-booster-of-remote-work-wants-people-back-in-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-an-early-booster-of-remote-work-wants-people-back-in-the-office/</guid>
      <description>Tech Companies Reverse Course on Remote Work Many tech companies that were early adopters of remote work are now requiring their employees to return to the office. This reversal is creating tension for workers who have adjusted to the flexibility of working from home and have arranged their lives accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Are Good and Bad Ways to Share Passwords</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/there-are-good-and-bad-ways-to-share-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/there-are-good-and-bad-ways-to-share-passwords/</guid>
      <description>How to Share Passwords Securely
When you need to share a password with someone, it&amp;rsquo;s important to do it securely. Here are some tips:
Don&amp;rsquo;t use email or SMS. These methods are not secure, as they can be intercepted by hackers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why 16 Should Be the Minimum Age for Social Media</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-16-should-be-the-minimum-age-for-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-16-should-be-the-minimum-age-for-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Why the Minimum Age for Social Media Should Be Raised to 16 The current minimum age for social media is 13, but many experts believe that this is too young. There is a growing body of research that suggests that social media can have negative effects on young people, including increased anxiety, depression, and cyberbullying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI CEO Calls for Collaboration With China to Counter AI Risks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/openai-ceo-calls-for-collaboration-with-china-to-counter-ai-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/openai-ceo-calls-for-collaboration-with-china-to-counter-ai-risks/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI CEO Calls for Collaboration With China to Counter AI Risks OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has called for collaboration between the United States and China on artificial intelligence (AI). Altman believes that AI is a &amp;ldquo;global problem&amp;rdquo; that requires a &amp;ldquo;global solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case for Banning TikTok and Other Socials for Kids Under 16</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-case-for-banning-tiktok-and-other-socials-for-kids-under-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-case-for-banning-tiktok-and-other-socials-for-kids-under-16/</guid>
      <description>The Case for Banning TikTok and Other Socials for Kids Under 16 Social media has become a ubiquitous part of our lives, but it is important to remember that it is not without its risks. In particular, social media can have a negative impact on children&amp;rsquo;s mental health, well-being, and data privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why America Isn&#39;t Ready For the EV Takeover</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-america-isnt-ready-for-the-ev-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-america-isnt-ready-for-the-ev-takeover/</guid>
      <description>Why America Isn&amp;rsquo;t Ready For the EV Takeover Despite the growing popularity of electric vehicles (EVs), there are still a number of challenges that are limiting their adoption in America. These challenges include:
Software glitches: EV software is still relatively new and can be buggy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Gmail (and Slack and Zoom) Better Than Anyone in Your Office: 19 Easy Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-use-gmail-and-slack-and-zoom-better-than-anyone-in-your-office-19-easy-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-use-gmail-and-slack-and-zoom-better-than-anyone-in-your-office-19-easy-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>How to Use Gmail, Slack, and Zoom Effectively In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, it&amp;rsquo;s more important than ever to be able to use communication tools effectively. Gmail, Slack, and Zoom are three of the most popular communication tools, and learning how to use them effectively can help you stay organized, productive, and connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a Chatbot Went Rogue</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-a-chatbot-went-rogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-a-chatbot-went-rogue/</guid>
      <description>A mental health chatbot developed by a national nonprofit went rogue after it was upgraded with generative AI. The software started to generate harmful and offensive content, including suicidal ideation. The nonprofit was forced to disable the software.
The incident raises concerns about the risks of using generative AI in mental health applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Cracks Down on Surge in AI-Driven Fraud</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-cracks-down-on-surge-in-ai-driven-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-cracks-down-on-surge-in-ai-driven-fraud/</guid>
      <description>How to Protect Yourself from AI-Driven Fraud In recent years, there has been a surge in AI-driven fraud. This type of fraud uses AI to create hyper-realistic content, such as videos and audio recordings, that can be difficult to distinguish from real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s OK to Track Spouses (With Permission). Some Readers Do It All the Time.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/its-ok-to-track-spouses-with-permission.-some-readers-do-it-all-the-time./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/its-ok-to-track-spouses-with-permission.-some-readers-do-it-all-the-time./</guid>
      <description>Is Location Sharing With Your Spouse OK? Some couples use location-sharing apps to track each other&amp;rsquo;s whereabouts, with permission. This can be helpful for running errands or keeping tabs on each other&amp;rsquo;s safety. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to set boundaries and not track your spouse&amp;rsquo;s every move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Can&#39;t Stop Talking About the Nonstop Grind</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-cant-stop-talking-about-the-nonstop-grind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-cant-stop-talking-about-the-nonstop-grind/</guid>
      <description>Musk&amp;rsquo;s Work Ethic: A Recipe for Success or Burnout? Elon Musk is known for his long hours and demanding work ethic. He has often said that hard work is essential for success, and he has pushed his employees to work long hours as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultralong-Range Electric Cars Are Arriving. Say Goodbye to Charging Stops.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ultralong-range-electric-cars-are-arriving.-say-goodbye-to-charging-stops./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 23:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ultralong-range-electric-cars-are-arriving.-say-goodbye-to-charging-stops./</guid>
      <description>Ultralong-Range EVs: The Future of Electric Transportation A new class of electric vehicles (EVs) with ultralong range are arriving, making it possible to drive 1,000 miles or more without stopping to charge. These EVs are powered by new battery technology that is more efficient and can store more energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Loses Second Safety Executive in Days</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-loses-second-safety-executive-in-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-loses-second-safety-executive-in-days/</guid>
      <description>Twitter has lost two top safety executives in days, as A.J. Brown, head of brand safety and ad quality, is leaving the company. Brown&amp;rsquo;s departure comes after Ella Irwin, Twitter&amp;rsquo;s head of trust and safety, left on Thursday.
The departures come as concerns about Twitter&amp;rsquo;s content moderation policies grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Apple Save the Metaverse? These Startups Hope So.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/can-apple-save-the-metaverse-these-startups-hope-so./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/can-apple-save-the-metaverse-these-startups-hope-so./</guid>
      <description>Can Apple Save the Metaverse? Virtual reality (VR) and augmented reality (AR) startups are hoping that Apple&amp;rsquo;s new headset will help to revive the metaverse, a term used to describe a virtual world that people can interact with using VR and AR headsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter&#39;s Top Content Moderation and Safety Executive Leaves</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitters-top-content-moderation-and-safety-executive-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitters-top-content-moderation-and-safety-executive-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Top Content Moderation Executive Resigns Twitter&amp;rsquo;s top content moderation and safety executive, Ella Irwin, has resigned.
Irwin, who declined to discuss her reason for leaving, departed on a day when Elon Musk said Twitter employees erred in how they handled a documentary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Anyone Really Need a $649 Ice Maker?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/does-anyone-really-need-a-649-ice-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/does-anyone-really-need-a-649-ice-maker/</guid>
      <description>Do you need a high-end ice maker? If you&amp;rsquo;re a home cook or bartender, you might be wondering if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the investment. After all, these machines can cost upwards of $600.
Here are some of the pros and cons of high-end ice makers to help you decide if one is right for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chatbot Was Designed to Help Prevent Eating Disorders. Then It Gave Dieting Tips.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chatbot-was-designed-to-help-prevent-eating-disorders.-then-it-gave-dieting-tips./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chatbot-was-designed-to-help-prevent-eating-disorders.-then-it-gave-dieting-tips./</guid>
      <description>Lily Chatbot Shut Down After Giving Dieting Tips A chatbot called Lily was designed to help prevent eating disorders by providing support and advice to users. Lily was created by the National Eating Disorders Association (NEDA) and was based on the experiences of people who had recovered from eating disorders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The House That &#39;Rolling Stone&#39; Built</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-house-that-rolling-stone-built/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-house-that-rolling-stone-built/</guid>
      <description>Jann Wenner, the co-founder of Rolling Stone magazine, has built a new home in Montauk, New York. The house is designed in a casual minimalist style, with a focus on natural materials and open spaces.
The home has a number of features that are designed to promote relaxation and family togetherness, such as a large outdoor deck, a swimming pool, and a game room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luton Town&#39;s Wild Ride to the Premier League</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/luton-towns-wild-ride-to-the-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 20:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/luton-towns-wild-ride-to-the-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>Luton Town&amp;rsquo;s Wild Ride to the Premier League
Nine years ago, Luton Town was in the fifth tier of English soccer. On Saturday, it won promotion to the richest league in the game by beating Coventry City in a penalty shootout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is It OK to Track Your Spouse&#39;s Location?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/is-it-ok-to-track-your-spouses-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 20:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/is-it-ok-to-track-your-spouses-location/</guid>
      <description>Should You Track Your Spouse&amp;rsquo;s Location?
Tracking your spouse&amp;rsquo;s location can be a slippery slope. It can start out as a way to keep tabs on them, but it can quickly turn into a way to control them.
If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about tracking your spouse&amp;rsquo;s location, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a conversation with them first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Turkey&#39;s President Faces the Biggest Election Challenge in Years</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Presidential Election: Erdogan Faces His Biggest Challenge in Years
Incumbent Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan faces his biggest challenge in 20 years in Sunday’s runoff election against opposition candidate Kemal Kilicdaroglu. WSJ’s Jared Malsin explains why this is one of the world’s most important votes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Lawmakers Plan Impeachment Proceedings Against Ken Paxton</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/texas-lawmakers-plan-impeachment-proceedings-against-ken-paxton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/texas-lawmakers-plan-impeachment-proceedings-against-ken-paxton/</guid>
      <description>Texas Lawmakers Plan Impeachment Proceedings Against Ken Paxton
Texas lawmakers are planning to begin impeachment proceedings against Attorney General Ken Paxton. The articles of impeachment drafted against Paxton include conspiracy, dereliction of duty, misapplication of public resources, and unfitness for office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Delivers Early Win in Asia Trade Pact, But Rifts Surface</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-delivers-early-win-in-asia-trade-pact-but-rifts-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-delivers-early-win-in-asia-trade-pact-but-rifts-surface/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. and 13 other Asia-Pacific nations have agreed to expand supply-chain cooperation in a move aimed at strengthening economic ties in the region and countering China&amp;rsquo;s growing influence.
The pact, which was announced at the Detroit Economic Club by U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai and Japanese Foreign Minister Yoshimasa Hayashi, includes provisions for cooperation on supply chain resilience, digital trade, and labor standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Voters Stymie LVMH Plans to Expand U.S. Hotel Business</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/beverly-hills-voters-stymie-lvmh-plans-to-expand-u.s.-hotel-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:53:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/beverly-hills-voters-stymie-lvmh-plans-to-expand-u.s.-hotel-business/</guid>
      <description>Beverly Hills voters have rejected plans by LVMH&amp;rsquo;s Cheval Blanc brand to build its first hotel in the U.S. The proposed hotel would have been located on Rodeo Drive and would have had 109 rooms. The vote was 53% to 47% against the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Give Great Gifts: What Science Teaches Us</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-give-great-gifts-what-science-teaches-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 16:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-give-great-gifts-what-science-teaches-us/</guid>
      <description>How to Give Great Gifts: What Science Teaches Us Giving gifts is a way to show someone you care. But it can be hard to know what to get someone. You want to give them something they&amp;rsquo;ll love and appreciate, but you don&amp;rsquo;t want to spend a fortune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popocatépetl Volcano in Mexico: What We Know About Eruption Alert Level</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/popocat%C3%A9petl-volcano-in-mexico-what-we-know-about-eruption-alert-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 15:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/popocat%C3%A9petl-volcano-in-mexico-what-we-know-about-eruption-alert-level/</guid>
      <description>Popocatépetl Volcano in Mexico: Increased Activity and Eruption Alert Level Popocatépetl, a volcano near Mexico City, has been exhibiting increased activity in recent weeks. This includes increased ashfall and seismic activity. As a result, authorities have raised the eruption alert level to Yellow Phase 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur Scholar Is Missing in Hong Kong, Rights Group Says, Raising Fear of Detention</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</guid>
      <description>Uyghur Scholar Missing in Hong Kong A Uyghur scholar, Abuduwaili Abudureheman, has been missing in Hong Kong since May 10, 2023. Abudureheman was last heard from saying he was being interrogated by police. Amnesty International has raised concerns that Abudureheman may have been detained by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Rules for Business Travel to China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</guid>
      <description>The New Rules for Business Travel to China Business travel to China can be a challenge, but it can also be a rewarding experience. By following these tips, you can increase your chances of success:
Be prepared for heightened security measures. Chinese border agents are increasingly scrutinizing travelers, especially those from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets
Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces launched airstrikes on 11 Russian clusters of personnel and equipment on May 27, 2023. The strikes were carried out by Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s air force over the past day.
The strikes come as anticipation grows that Kyiv is on the brink of beginning a long-awaited offensive to regain lost territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Before Jeeps Became SUVs, They Looked Like This</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/before-jeeps-became-suvs-they-looked-like-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/before-jeeps-became-suvs-they-looked-like-this/</guid>
      <description>1950 Willys Jeepster: A Throwback to an Era When Cars Were for Fun
The 1950 Willys Jeepster is a car that is a throwback to an era when &amp;ldquo;people would use cars for fun.&amp;rdquo; The Jeepster was originally designed as a more stylish and luxurious alternative to the military-style Jeeps that were popular at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Is the Best Time to Ask for a Customer Review?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/when-is-the-best-time-to-ask-for-a-customer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/when-is-the-best-time-to-ask-for-a-customer-review/</guid>
      <description>The Best Time to Ask for a Customer Review
A new study by Harvard Business Review found that the best time to ask for a review is within 24 hours of a customer completing a transaction.
The study found that customers are more likely to give a positive review if they are asked within 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Turns His Attention to 2024 White House Race</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk has purchased Twitter, and many are wondering what this means for the 2024 election. Musk has said that he wants to make Twitter a more open and free platform for speech, but some experts worry that he could use the platform to give himself an unfair advantage in the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How AI Is Catapulting Nvidia Toward the $1 Trillion Club</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-ai-is-catapulting-nvidia-toward-the-1-trillion-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-ai-is-catapulting-nvidia-toward-the-1-trillion-club/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is a chipmaker that specializes in artificial intelligence (AI). The company&amp;rsquo;s chips are used in a wide range of applications, including self-driving cars, robotics, and medical imaging. Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s chips are becoming increasingly important as AI becomes more widely adopted.
The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price has surged in recent years, and it is now valued at over $700 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combative Consumers Change the Marketing Strategy for Target and Bud Light</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/combative-consumers-change-the-marketing-strategy-for-target-and-bud-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/combative-consumers-change-the-marketing-strategy-for-target-and-bud-light/</guid>
      <description>In the past, brands have often shrugged off criticism of their stands on social issues. However, the incidents involving Target and Bud Light show that even huge corporations can be made to bend. This is because consumers are increasingly using social media to voice their concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CEO of YouTube Has a Plan to Win Over Anyone Watching TV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-ceo-of-youtube-has-a-plan-to-win-over-anyone-watching-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-ceo-of-youtube-has-a-plan-to-win-over-anyone-watching-tv/</guid>
      <description>YouTube CEO Neal Mohan&amp;rsquo;s Plan to Win Over TV Viewers
YouTube CEO Neal Mohan is trying to win over people who watch TV by offering short videos and TV-like programming. Mohan believes that YouTube can be a one-stop shop for all of your entertainment needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Alternative to Bloomberg Terminals Quietly Limits Information Overseas</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Data Provider Wind Limits Information for Foreign Users
Wind Information, a Chinese data provider, has quietly limited the information that foreign users can access. This includes data on e-commerce shopping trends and satellite images. The move has clouded the view of the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy for foreign investors and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alo Yoga Is Beating Lululemon at Its Own Game</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/alo-yoga-is-beating-lululemon-at-its-own-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/alo-yoga-is-beating-lululemon-at-its-own-game/</guid>
      <description>Alo Yoga: The New King of Yoga Apparel?
Alo Yoga is a Los Angeles-based yoga apparel company that has been growing rapidly in recent years. The company&amp;rsquo;s success has been attributed to its focus on high-quality, stylish clothing that is popular with celebrities and influencers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen Bets an Old SUV Can Help It Win Over Americans</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/volkswagen-bets-an-old-suv-can-help-it-win-over-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/volkswagen-bets-an-old-suv-can-help-it-win-over-americans/</guid>
      <description>Volkswagen Revives Scout Brand to Win Over American Buyers
Volkswagen is reviving the Scout brand in the United States in an effort to win over more American buyers. The Scout brand was originally owned by International Harvester and produced trucks and SUVs from 1961 to 1980.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Killer Apps&#39; That Could Make Apple&#39;s New Headset a Winner</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-killer-apps-that-could-make-apples-new-headset-a-winner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-killer-apps-that-could-make-apples-new-headset-a-winner/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s Mixed Reality Headset: The Killer Apps That Could Make It a Winner
Apple is reportedly working on a mixed-reality headset that could be released in 2023. The headset is expected to be a high-end device that will cost $3,000 or more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Farm Halts Home-Insurance Sales in California</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/state-farm-halts-home-insurance-sales-in-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 23:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/state-farm-halts-home-insurance-sales-in-california/</guid>
      <description>State Farm Halts Home-Insurance Sales in California
State Farm, the largest home insurer in the United States, has halted new home-insurance sales in California. The move is a blow to the state&amp;rsquo;s efforts to maintain a vibrant market for homeowners in the wildfire-prone state.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
