<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday Wall on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday Wall on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:50:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teens Can Now Ride Ubers Solo---With Parents&#39; Credit Cards</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/teens-can-now-ride-ubers-solo---with-parents-credit-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/teens-can-now-ride-ubers-solo---with-parents-credit-cards/</guid>
      <description>According to the Wall Street Journal, Uber is now offering a solution for parents who need help driving kids around by allowing 13- to 17-year-olds parent-supervised accounts for rides and food delivery. This is the first time teenagers as young as 13 years old will be able to have Uber accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Apple Headset Is Coming. Can It Be More Than a Nerd Helmet?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</guid>
      <description>Apple is rumored to be releasing a mixed reality headset as a precursor to their AR glasses. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we know so far:
The headset will allow users to switch between viewing the real world and virtual reality with a physical dial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is ChatGPT? What to Know About the AI Chatbot</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT: The Next-Generation AI Chatbot Revolutionizing Industries
ChatGPT is an AI chatbot that has caused a stir in the world of technology and is set to transform industries and the future of work. Built on a family of large language models (LLMs) known as GPT-3, ChatGPT can understand and generate human-like answers to text prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
