<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday Wall on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday Wall on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:49:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Stocks Picked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</guid>
      <description>BB (BlackBerry Limited) - SmallBlackBerry Ltd. is strategically pivoting towards profitability and operational efficiency through new leadership, business division separation, and strategic partnerships, despite the potential market indecision and competitive risks.
PCG (PG&amp;amp;E Corporation) - MiddlePG&amp;amp;E Corp. is navigating through the challenges of the energy sector and regulatory risks while focusing on sustainable and affordable solutions for its customers and innovative technologies for utility operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:186
Chances: RIVN shares surged after Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Cybertruck launch, showing growing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Stifel analyst initiated coverage on RIVN with a buy rating and a $23 price target, highlighting Rivian&amp;rsquo;s increasing brand awareness, partnerships, and potential for margin expansion. Rivian has a clear path forward and is capitalizing on interest in practical and desired electric options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:161
Chances: One Nasdaq 100 component, with a slew of competitive advantages, is cheaper than it&amp;rsquo;s ever been as a publicly traded company. Three historically inexpensive, brand-name companies owned by one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful investors are ripe for the picking in December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. NIO Inc. might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects Risks: Nio may undertake further job cuts after the company announced plans to cut 10% of its workforce last month Nio was pressured to slash prices, thinning its margins, in response to the price war that Tesla Inc ignited at the beginning of the year Score:-63 chances characters count - risks characters count = -1063</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:157
Chances: Pinterest is seeing a growing partnership with Amazon and strengthening advertising business, making it a standout stock for 2024, according to RBC. RBC Capital Markets analysts upgraded Pinterest to Outperform from Sector Perform and raised their price target on the stock, citing the company’s potential to benefit from impulse purchases and increased body representation on its platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:99
Chances: Aurora Innovation, Inc. has shown strong progress towards commercial launch with an Autonomy Readiness Measure (ARM) of 84% in Q3 2023. The company has announced the opening of the industry’s first lane for driverless trucks supported by commercial-ready terminals in Dallas and Houston, which could signify significant growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Sea Ltd. operates in the Digital Entertainment, E-Commerce, and Digital Financial Services segments, providing a diverse range of online gaming, marketplace, and financial services. The company&amp;rsquo;s Shopee mobile app and websites connect buyers and sellers, offering a strong potential for growth in the e-commerce segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:209
Chances: BlackBerry Ltd. is focusing on intelligent security software and services, leveraging artificial intelligence and machine learning, which aligns with the growing demand for cybersecurity solutions in the market. The appointment of John Giamatteo as the new CEO and the company&amp;rsquo;s decision to streamline its centralized corporate functions indicates a strategic shift aimed at enhancing profitability and cashflow-positive operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:177
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. operates in the power and sensing solutions industry, which is experiencing growth due to the electrification of the automotive industry. The company&amp;rsquo;s segments offer a wide range of semiconductor products that cater to various application functions, indicating a diverse product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-51
Chances: Many dividend stocks have sold off over the past year, offering attractive dividend yields. Realty Income Corp. is the 800-pound gorilla in the net-lease sector and looks like it is on sale today. These stocks offer generous dividend yields upfront and a good chance to receive growing payouts in the years ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: Shares of department store chain Kohl’s (NYSE:KSS) jumped 7.3% in the morning session after retail stocks soared in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s. Risks: The proposal from Arkhouse Management and Brigade Capital to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private could indicate increased competition for Kohl&amp;rsquo;s in the department store space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cere/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Cerevel Therapeutics has a robust neuroscience pipeline with multiple clinical-stage and preclinical candidates, presenting significant growth opportunities in the coming years. The acquisition by AbbVie will provide Cerevel Therapeutics with the necessary resources to expand its research and development efforts, potentially leading to breakthrough therapies in the field of neuroscience diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:-70
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China with a strong market presence. The company has announced plans to change the ratio of its American Depositary Shares, which could potentially lead to increased investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/edr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/edr/</guid>
      <description>score:199
Chances: Endeavor Group Holdings operates across multiple segments including sports properties, events, experiences, and rights, which provides significant growth opportunities through innovative deals and exclusive live events. The company has a strong portfolio of scarce sports properties such as UFC, PBR, and Euroleague, which can generate substantial growth through exclusive rights deals and events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: The FCC approval of the merger between Dish Network and EchoStar is a positive development for the company, easing debt worries and reuniting the telecom empire to tackle growing competition. Dish Network&amp;rsquo;s expansion beyond satellite TV into streaming TV and mobile telecom services shows potential for growth and competitive positioning in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:207
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corp. is helping customers make the holiday season sustainable and affordable with low-cost actions to trim their carbon footprint and energy bills. The company is exploring the usage of unmanned aerial systems for utility operations, which could improve efficiency and safety in their operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Hydrogen and fuel cell technology has the potential to play a crucial role in lowering emissions and providing alternative energy solutions. Sustainable transport stocks have reached new heights, making them prime investment opportunities for the future. Electric vehicle (EV) sales are skyrocketing, with projections showing a strong increase in global EV sales by 2026.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:203
Chances: CNH Industrial has unveiled its very first full-electric mini excavator model, showcasing their commitment to innovation and sustainability in the construction industry. The company&amp;rsquo;s T7 Methane Power LNG tractor won a Special Mention in the world-famous TIME&amp;rsquo;s Best Invention List, indicating their leadership in developing environmentally friendly agricultural equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
