<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday Wall on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday Wall on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:21:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Ban Signed in Montana, Paving Way for First Amendment Legal Battle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-ban-signed-in-montana-paving-way-for-first-amendment-legal-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-ban-signed-in-montana-paving-way-for-first-amendment-legal-battle/</guid>
      <description>Montana Bans TikTok, Setting Off First Amendment Legal Battle Montana became the first state in the U.S. to ban TikTok when Governor Greg Gianforte signed a bill into law on Wednesday afternoon. The law prohibits anyone in the state from downloading or using the app, and also applies to app stores that offer TikTok for download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Company New Relic in Talks to Be Sold</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/software-company-new-relic-in-talks-to-be-sold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 20:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/software-company-new-relic-in-talks-to-be-sold/</guid>
      <description>According to a report by the Wall Street Journal, private-equity firms Francisco Partners and TPG are jointly bidding over $5 billion to acquire New Relic, a software company specializing in analytics and observability tools [^1^][^2^][^3^]. The article did not provide any further information about the potential acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM, Google Give $150 Million for U.S.-Japan Quantum-Computing Push</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ibm-google-give-150-million-for-u.s.-japan-quantum-computing-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ibm-google-give-150-million-for-u.s.-japan-quantum-computing-push/</guid>
      <description>IBM and Google to Invest $150 Million in U.S.-Japan Quantum Computing Partnership IBM and Google have announced a $150 million investment in a joint quantum computing research program with the University of Chicago and the University of Tokyo. The partnership is part of an effort to preserve the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Apple Headset Is Coming. Can It Be More Than a Nerd Helmet?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</guid>
      <description>Apple is rumored to be releasing a mixed reality headset as a precursor to their AR glasses. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we know so far:
The headset will allow users to switch between viewing the real world and virtual reality with a physical dial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is ChatGPT? What to Know About the AI Chatbot</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT: The Next-Generation AI Chatbot Revolutionizing Industries
ChatGPT is an AI chatbot that has caused a stir in the world of technology and is set to transform industries and the future of work. Built on a family of large language models (LLMs) known as GPT-3, ChatGPT can understand and generate human-like answers to text prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
