<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday Wall on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday Wall on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:06:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/friday-wall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Is Spared a Search-Engine Switch by a Major Partner</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/google-is-spared-a-search-engine-switch-by-a-major-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/google-is-spared-a-search-engine-switch-by-a-major-partner/</guid>
      <description>Samsung Suspends Review of Bing as Default Search Engine Samsung Electronics has suspended an internal review that contemplated changing its smartphones&amp;rsquo; default search engine from Google to Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Bing.
The review was reportedly sparked by a desire to diversify Samsung&amp;rsquo;s smartphone software and consider new offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Tech Giants&#39; Results Reflect Lackluster Economic Recovery</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinese-tech-giants-results-reflect-lackluster-economic-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 06:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinese-tech-giants-results-reflect-lackluster-economic-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Tech Giants&amp;rsquo; Results Reflect Lackluster Economic Recovery Chinese tech giants Alibaba, Tencent, and Baidu all reported mixed results for the first quarter of 2023. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s revenue missed expectations, while Tencent and Baidu saw more marked upturns. The lackluster results reflect the broader slowdown in the Chinese economy, as well as the government&amp;rsquo;s crackdown on tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Creators Sue Montana Over State&#39;s Ban of Platform</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-creators-sue-montana-over-states-ban-of-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-creators-sue-montana-over-states-ban-of-platform/</guid>
      <description>TikTok Creators Sue Montana Over State&amp;rsquo;s Ban of Platform A group of TikTok creators have filed a lawsuit against Montana&amp;rsquo;s attorney general, alleging that the state&amp;rsquo;s ban on the social media platform is unconstitutional and violates the First Amendment.
The lawsuit argues that the ban is an attempt to censor speech and that it is based on unfounded fears about TikTok&amp;rsquo;s security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Says Microsoft May Have Violated API Policies</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-says-microsoft-may-have-violated-api-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-says-microsoft-may-have-violated-api-policies/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Accuses Microsoft of Violating API Policies Twitter has sent a letter to Microsoft alleging that the company may have violated its API policies. The letter, which was sent by Twitter&amp;rsquo;s general counsel, Vijaya Gadde, to Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella, focuses on Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s use of Twitter&amp;rsquo;s API in several products including some related to Xbox; the search engine Bing; and advertising and other tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Restricts Employee Use of ChatGPT, Wary of Leaks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/apple-restricts-employee-use-of-chatgpt-wary-of-leaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 23:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/apple-restricts-employee-use-of-chatgpt-wary-of-leaks/</guid>
      <description>Apple Restricts Employee Use of ChatGPT Apple has restricted employee use of ChatGPT, a large language model developed by OpenAI. The restriction is reportedly due to Apple&amp;rsquo;s concern that employees could use ChatGPT to release confidential data as the company develops its own similar technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Is Spending Billions to Wire U.S. for Fast Internet</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/att-is-spending-billions-to-wire-u.s.-for-fast-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 22:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/att-is-spending-billions-to-wire-u.s.-for-fast-internet/</guid>
      <description>AT&amp;amp;T Invests $42.5 Billion to Wire U.S. for Fast Internet AT&amp;amp;T is investing $42.5 billion to expand its network of fiber-optic cables. The investment will allow AT&amp;amp;T to reach an additional 30 million homes and businesses over the next five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Ban Signed in Montana, Paving Way for First Amendment Legal Battle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-ban-signed-in-montana-paving-way-for-first-amendment-legal-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-ban-signed-in-montana-paving-way-for-first-amendment-legal-battle/</guid>
      <description>Montana Bans TikTok, Setting Off First Amendment Legal Battle Montana became the first state in the U.S. to ban TikTok when Governor Greg Gianforte signed a bill into law on Wednesday afternoon. The law prohibits anyone in the state from downloading or using the app, and also applies to app stores that offer TikTok for download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Company New Relic in Talks to Be Sold</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/software-company-new-relic-in-talks-to-be-sold/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 20:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/software-company-new-relic-in-talks-to-be-sold/</guid>
      <description>According to a report by the Wall Street Journal, private-equity firms Francisco Partners and TPG are jointly bidding over $5 billion to acquire New Relic, a software company specializing in analytics and observability tools [^1^][^2^][^3^]. The article did not provide any further information about the potential acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM, Google Give $150 Million for U.S.-Japan Quantum-Computing Push</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ibm-google-give-150-million-for-u.s.-japan-quantum-computing-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ibm-google-give-150-million-for-u.s.-japan-quantum-computing-push/</guid>
      <description>IBM and Google to Invest $150 Million in U.S.-Japan Quantum Computing Partnership IBM and Google have announced a $150 million investment in a joint quantum computing research program with the University of Chicago and the University of Tokyo. The partnership is part of an effort to preserve the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Apple Headset Is Coming. Can It Be More Than a Nerd Helmet?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</guid>
      <description>Apple is rumored to be releasing a mixed reality headset as a precursor to their AR glasses. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we know so far:
The headset will allow users to switch between viewing the real world and virtual reality with a physical dial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is ChatGPT? What to Know About the AI Chatbot</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT: The Next-Generation AI Chatbot Revolutionizing Industries
ChatGPT is an AI chatbot that has caused a stir in the world of technology and is set to transform industries and the future of work. Built on a family of large language models (LLMs) known as GPT-3, ChatGPT can understand and generate human-like answers to text prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
