<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cost Cutting on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/cost-cutting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cost Cutting on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/cost-cutting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Charles Schwab experienced a successful weekend, converting TD Ameritrade clients and advisors, potentially leading to increased assets under management. Bond investors are showing confidence in Schwab after its cost-cutting measures, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health. Schwab&amp;rsquo;s trader survey indicates that recession fears are receding, suggesting positive sentiment among traders and investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Grab advances break-even timeline on boost from cost cuts, strong demand Grab Reports Second Quarter 2023 Results Grab Reports First Quarter 2023 Results Grab lifts revenue forecast, delivery business breaks even Grab targets Group Adjusted EBITDA breakeven by H2 2024 as it accelerates path to profitability Risks: Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Grab cuts 1,000 jobs to stay competitive Grab Holdings stock boosted despite falling delivery sales Indonesia’s GoTo Extends Stock Slump After Shaking Up Top Ranks Grab Sees Slower Growth While It Pursues 2024 Profitability HappyFresh Board Is Said to Hire Alvarez &amp;amp; Marsal for Review Score:12 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</guid>
      <description>score:1131
Chances: Tyson Foods CEO referred to the closures as an &amp;rsquo;efficiency play short term&amp;rsquo;, indicating potential cost-cutting measures. The closure of meat-processing plants is part of Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; efforts to address challenges in its chicken, beef, and pork operations. Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; assessment of beef price increases points to supply issues and herd liquidation, contributing to higher cattle costs and beef prices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
