<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Outlook on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-outlook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Outlook on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:33:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-outlook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: United Airlines&amp;rsquo; plans to resume daily flights between San Francisco and Beijing, as well as increase flights to Shanghai, could indicate a potential for increased revenue. Collaboration with TSA PreCheck enrollment provider IDEMIA Identity and Security for an enrollment initiative at Denver International Airport could enhance customer experience and convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CARR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/carr/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Carrier Global&amp;rsquo;s recognition for earning a Top Project of the Year Award indicates the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to deliver energy-efficient solutions in collaboration with its partners, which could positively impact its reputation and customer base. Strong financial results in the second quarter of 2023, along with raised full-year guidance for revenue and adjusted metrics, demonstrate Carrier Global&amp;rsquo;s performance resilience and its potential to capitalize on market opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line&amp;rsquo;s new ship, Norwegian Viva, embarked on its maiden voyage, which could attract positive attention and interest from travelers. Positive trends in the travel industry, such as increasing passenger numbers and strong demand for summer travel, could benefit Norwegian Cruise Line&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Nordstrom plans to open a new Nordstrom Rack store in Queen Creek, Arizona, expanding its retail presence. Nordstrom announces the date for reporting its second quarter 2023 financial results and provides an outlook for the year. Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s Relative Strength (RS) Rating improves, indicating improving technical performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
