<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>south africa on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/south-africa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in south africa on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:34:04 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/south-africa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Business Confidence in South Africa Falls to a Year Low</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/business-confidence-in-south-africa-falls-to-a-year-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:34:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/business-confidence-in-south-africa-falls-to-a-year-low/</guid>
      <description>Business Confidence in South Africa Falls to a Year Low Business confidence in South Africa has fallen to a year low, according to a report by the South African Chamber of Commerce and Industry (Sacci). The index compiled by Sacci fell to 106.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Supports South Africa in Hosting BRICS Activities, Xi Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-supports-south-africa-in-hosting-brics-activities-xi-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:42:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-supports-south-africa-in-hosting-brics-activities-xi-says/</guid>
      <description>China Supports South Africa in Hosting BRICS Activities China has expressed its support for South Africa in hosting various BRICS activities this year. The announcement was made by Chinese President Xi Jinping during a phone call with his South African counterpart Cyril Ramaphosa on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South African Current-Account Deficit Narrows More Than Expected</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/south-african-current-account-deficit-narrows-more-than-expected/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/south-african-current-account-deficit-narrows-more-than-expected/</guid>
      <description>South Africa&amp;rsquo;s Current-Account Deficit Narrows South Africa&amp;rsquo;s current-account deficit narrowed to 2.2% of gross domestic product (GDP) in the first quarter of 2023, from 3.2% in the fourth quarter of 2022.
The narrowing of the deficit was driven by a decline in imports, which fell by 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Africa May Turn to Burning Heavy Fuel Oil to Tackle Load Shedding</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/south-africa-may-turn-to-burning-heavy-fuel-oil-to-tackle-load-shedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:14:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/south-africa-may-turn-to-burning-heavy-fuel-oil-to-tackle-load-shedding/</guid>
      <description>South Africa May Turn to Burning Heavy Fuel Oil to Tackle Load Shedding South Africa is facing a severe power crisis, with rolling blackouts lasting up to 10 hours a day. The government is considering burning heavy fuel oil to generate electricity, as a temporary measure to ease the crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eskom Latest: Spar Retailers&#39; Diesel Bill at $35 Million</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</guid>
      <description>Spar Retailers Spend $35 Million on Diesel to Run Generators South African food and liquor retailer Spar Group estimates that its outlets spent more than 700 million rand ($35 million) on diesel to run generators in the six months through March. This is more than triple the amount spent on diesel in the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theft Shuts Key Railway Serving South African Iron-Ore Exporters</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/theft-shuts-key-railway-serving-south-african-iron-ore-exporters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/theft-shuts-key-railway-serving-south-african-iron-ore-exporters/</guid>
      <description>Theft Shuts Down Key Railway Serving South Africa&amp;rsquo;s Iron-Ore Exporters A key railway line serving South Africa&amp;rsquo;s iron-ore exporters was shut down due to theft of power cables. The 861-kilometer (535-mile) line is used to transport iron-ore and manganese from Kumba Iron Ore Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
