<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Buyback on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-buyback/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Buyback on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-buyback/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s AI platform, launched in April, is gaining traction with over 100 organizations and talks with more than 300 additional companies. Palantir raised its annual revenue forecast and announced a $1 billion stock buyback plan, indicating confidence in its growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Meta Platforms&amp;rsquo; potential involvement in a fight with Tesla&amp;rsquo;s CEO Elon Musk could attract attention and generate media coverage. The $1 billion stock buyback plan announced by Palantir might indicate a positive move for the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. The call to empower parents and require children to have explicit permission for social media accounts in certain states could benefit platforms like Meta, ensuring compliance and addressing privacy concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:1031
Chances: Alphabet Inc. is seeking regulatory approval to expand self-driving car services in San Francisco, indicating potential growth in this emerging market. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s strategic move to offer employee discounts to hotels on the Google campus as part of its return-to-office tactic could encourage employees to return to the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
