<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hong Kong on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/hong-kong/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hong Kong on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:35:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/hong-kong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>American Tech Giants Are Slowly Cutting Off Hong Kong Internet Users</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</guid>
      <description>In a move that could have a significant impact on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy and innovation ecosystem, American tech giants are slowly cutting off internet users in the city.
Google and OpenAI have not rolled out AI chatbots to Hong Kong, putting it alongside mainland China and North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Economy to Grow Faster, Singapore to Slow, Survey Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hong-kong-economy-to-grow-faster-singapore-to-slow-survey-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hong-kong-economy-to-grow-faster-singapore-to-slow-survey-says/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Economy to Grow Faster Than Singapore in 2023 A recent survey of economists by Bloomberg predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy will grow by 4.6% in 2023, up from a previous estimate of 3.4%. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy is expected to grow by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur Scholar Is Missing in Hong Kong, Rights Group Says, Raising Fear of Detention</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</guid>
      <description>Uyghur Scholar Missing in Hong Kong A Uyghur scholar, Abuduwaili Abudureheman, has been missing in Hong Kong since May 10, 2023. Abudureheman was last heard from saying he was being interrogated by police. Amnesty International has raised concerns that Abudureheman may have been detained by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
