<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aerospace on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/aerospace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aerospace on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/aerospace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:113
Chances: Delta Air Lines is expanding its flights to tourist-friendly destinations in Latin America and the Caribbean, indicating potential growth in those markets. The commercial aerospace recovery is expected to continue in 2024, making it a good sector to invest in. American Express and Delta Air Lines are revamping their co-branded credit cards, offering new rewards and benefits that could attract more customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:210
Chances: RTX has a golden opportunity to restart a 40-year-old missile business. Raytheon, with its recent contract with the U.S. Airforce, is set to expand its footprint in the missiles defense market. RTX&amp;rsquo;s Raytheon is set to expand its footprint in the global radar market, with the GhostEye MR contributing to the needs of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RKLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Rocket Lab USA, Inc. has been selected by the Space Development Agency to design and build 18 Tranche 2 Transport Layer-Beta Data Transport Satellites, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s continued growth and expansion in the aerospace industry. Rocket Lab&amp;rsquo;s stock soared after winning a U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
