<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aerospace on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/aerospace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aerospace on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/aerospace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: RTX has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. Despite all the doom and gloom, the stock still has a value case, and the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RYCEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rycey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rycey/</guid>
      <description>score:91
Chances: Rolls-Royce Holdings reported underlying operating profit of £1.6 billion on a surge in sales that were above-forecast The Civil Aerospace segment offers commercial aero engines and aftermarket services, which indicates a strong potential for revenue generation The company operates in multiple segments including Civil Aerospace, Power Systems, Defense, and ITP Aero, which provides diversification and potential for growth in different markets Risks: The first Rolls-Royce mini nuclear reactor will be built in Europe instead of Britain if ministers fail to accelerate decision-making, indicating potential geopolitical and regulatory risks The company depends on military aero engines, naval engines, and submarines for its Defense segment, which could be impacted by changes in defense budgets and policies Score:91 chances characters count - risks characters count = 91</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Spirit AeroSystems&amp;rsquo; strong position as a key supplier to Boeing and Airbus gives it a significant chance for long-term growth and stability. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on quality and safety will be crucial in regaining the trust of regulators, customers, and the public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
