<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:06:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cl/</guid>
      <description>score:-71
Chances: Colgate-Palmolive (CL) has started to reconfirm growth expectations after strong quarterly results. Analysts are seeing more sales growth ahead for the company in addition to growing opportunities in emerging markets. Risks: Investors need to consider the recent recall of approximately 200,000 Tesla vehicles, which could impact the overall market sentiment and consumer spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:99
Chances: Comcast Corporation (NASDAQ:CMCSA) beat earnings expectations, with reported EPS of $0.84 compared to expectations of $0.8. The company raised its annual dividend and announced a new $15 billion stock buyback, indicating confidence in its future prospects. Nielsen reported that older content from media libraries, such as NBCUniversal&amp;rsquo;s Suits, garnered significant views in 2023, suggesting potential value in licensing out older but popular content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Investors seeking high dividend-yielding stocks may find New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) attractive The joint venture between Blackstone and CPPIB winning a stake in the commercial property loans portfolio is a positive development for NYCB Banco Santander&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a 20% stake in a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: First Horizon Corporation has reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended December 2023. The company has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), indicating growing optimism about its earnings prospects. The Board of Directors has authorized the repurchase of up to $650 million of the Company&amp;rsquo;s common stock, reflecting confidence in the Company&amp;rsquo;s financial position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: U.S. Steel Corp. has the potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Nippon Steel Corp. made an aggressive all-cash offer for United States Steel Corp., indicating potential for a high acquisition price. Risks: The acquisition bid from Nippon Steel Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson beat fourth-quarter expectations with strong performance in the medtech segment. The company reported adjusted earnings of $2.29 per share, up 11.7% year-over-year, beating the consensus. Sales increased by 7.3% year-over-year to $21.4 billion, surpassing the consensus. Risks: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s stock tumbled after the company reported lower profit margins in the medical device and technology unit last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: AppLovin has been hot, and the run higher might have some momentum. AppLovin (APP) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Risks: It&amp;rsquo;s always important to assess the risk involved in investing in a company, especially in the volatile tech sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
