<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:-297
Chances: Peloton Interactive, Inc. Announces Participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference Peloton&amp;rsquo;s return to positive cash flow hit by bike recall, shares slide Peloton Interactive, Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year Fiscal 2023 Financial Results Peloton and the University of Michigan Announce Partnership Reaching Students, Athletes and Alumni Risks: Is Peloton in Trouble?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oln/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oln/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Olin Corp. announces shakeup in C-suite Olin Announces CEO Transition Plan Olin (OLN) Acquires White Flyer Targets to Grow Winchester Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Julie Piggott Appointed to Olin&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors Risks: Why Olin Stock Is Down Today Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Olin (OLN) Misses Q1 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Olin (OLN) to Close Epoxy Facilities in Restructuring Program An Intrinsic Calculation For Olin Corporation (NYSE:OLN) Suggests It&amp;rsquo;s 49% Undervalued Score:-43 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: KE Holdings Inc. Announces Upsizing and Extension of Share Repurchase Program and a Special Cash Dividend KE Holdings Stock Sees Rising Market Leadership; Earns 83 RS Rating Beike Joined &amp;lsquo;1t.org&amp;rsquo; China Action Even though KE Holdings (NYSE:BEKE) has lost US$1.9b market cap in last 7 days, shareholders are still up 24% over 1 year Bears are Losing Control Over KE Holdings Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer Bob Bakish to Participate in the 2023 Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference PATH Launches Limited Edition Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem Bottles in Partnership with Paramount Consumer Products Paramount Global Drops Plan to Sell BET Media S&amp;amp;P 500 Gains and Losses Today: Index Falls as Tech Stocks Lose Ground Risks: Paramount global debt cut to just above junk by Moody’s Hollywood strikes, subscriber churn, sports rights: Big media woes Americans are canceling more streaming plans as prices balloon Traditional TV &amp;lsquo;past the point of no return&amp;rsquo; as viewership hits record low Trouble in Tinseltown: 3 Entertainment Stocks to Sell Before the Curtain Falls Score:36 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Implied Volatility Surging for Nu Holdings (NU) Stock Options This Unstoppable Fintech Keeps Crushing Analyst Estimates Nu Holdings Ltd. (NU) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Buffett-Backed Nubank Bets on Mexico for ‘Pivotal’ Growth Wall Street Bulls Look Optimistic About Nu Holdings Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</guid>
      <description>score:-58
Chances: Positive Q2 2023 earnings call transcript. Lloyds Banking Group beats profit forecasts. Lloyds Banking Group raises dividends. Investor returns of 47% over the last three years. Expansion of banking sector and market recovery. Risks: Challenges from bad loan risks and economic fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/asx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/asx/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: ASE Technology Holding achieves the best overall performance on the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. ASE&amp;rsquo;s Bumping Factory in Kaohsiung, Taiwan inducted into the World Economic Forum’s Global Lighthouse Network. ASE announces advancements under the VIPack™ Platform. ASX reports positive Q2 2023 earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
