<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: RTX has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. Despite all the doom and gloom, the stock still has a value case, and the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WDC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wdc/</guid>
      <description>score:72
Chances: Western Digital stock saw a rise after an analyst at Rosenblatt Securities upgraded the shares, citing optimism about memory demand and the company’s pricing power. Evercore ISI analyst initiated coverage of Western Digital with an Outperform rating, indicating positive growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LEVI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/levi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/levi/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Levi Strauss posted first-quarter earnings revealing revenue in line with expectations and raised its full-year adjusted earnings per share forecast. Risks: Levi Strauss reported a 7.8% decrease in revenue year-on-year, indicating potential challenges in the market. Score:40 chances characters count - risks characters count = 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line (NCLH) has been making smart ROI-driven investments and digital innovations to maximize guest satisfaction and operational efficiency. Oceania Cruises, a brand under Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings, has announced a free pre-cruise hotel stay offer for guests, potentially attracting more travelers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NARI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nari/</guid>
      <description>score:93
Chances: Inari Medical (NARI) reported strong two-year interim results from the CLOUT registry, showing significant improvement in patient&amp;rsquo;s post-thrombotic syndrome and lower rethrombosis-related events. The company generated revenue of $132.1 million in Q4 of 2023, up 22.6% over the same quarter last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:-182
Chances: Palantir is expected to rapidly expand earnings per share over several years. The company is taking a visionary leap The path could be wide open for Palantir stock to climb even higher from here on out. Risks: Will generative artificial intelligence boost Palantir stock in the commercial market amid slowing revenue growth for the company?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOVO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 09:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Sovos Brands, Inc. delivered strong earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended December 2023, indicating potential for future gains The company&amp;rsquo;s strong volume-driven growth and margin expansion in fiscal year 2023 show promising signs for future performance Risks: The pending merger with Campbell Soup Company may introduce uncertainties in the near term The recent 52-week high may lead to potential profit-taking by some investors, causing short-term price volatility Score:63 chances characters count - risks characters count = 63</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: GoodRx beat Q4 estimates and issued strong guidance for 2024, indicating positive growth potential The company&amp;rsquo;s new stock buyback program valued at $450 million demonstrates confidence in its future performance GoodRx CEO Scott Wagner&amp;rsquo;s emphasis on industry innovation and the company&amp;rsquo;s leadership in AI technology bode well for future success Risks: Although revenue increased by 7%, the company encountered a net loss, indicating potential financial challenges The healthcare industry is subject to regulatory and market volatility, which may impact GoodRx&amp;rsquo;s performance Competition in the digital health sector poses a risk to GoodRx&amp;rsquo;s market position and profitability Score:23 chances characters count - risks characters count = 23</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agl/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: Medicare Advantage Growth Soars as Company Adjusts to Rising Medical Costs The headline numbers for Agilon (AGL) give insight into how the company performed in the quarter ended December 2023 The firm&amp;rsquo;s agilon Platform, provides healthcare for seniors across communities throughout the United States Risks: agilon health, inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oke/</guid>
      <description>score:-59
Chances: ONEOK Inc reported higher fourth quarter and full-year 2023 results and provided optimistic 2024 financial guidance. The company plans to make investments in the range of $1.75-$1.9 billion in 2024 to strengthen its operation. ONEOK&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings are likely to have gained from fee-based contracts and the completed acquisition of Magellan Midstream Partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARDX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</guid>
      <description>score:112
Chances: Strong commercial performance of IBSRELA and XPHOZAH drive revenue surge for Ardelyx, Inc. The positive outlook for the U.S. economy and widespread analyst upgrades across various sectors reflect confidence in the economic backdrop. The global biotech market is set to experience exponential growth, providing a unique opportunity for savvy investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wes/</guid>
      <description>score:119
Chances: WES announced multiple divestment agreements that could lead to improved financial performance The strong earnings results for Q4 2023 indicate positive momentum for WES The upcoming UBS Global Energy &amp;amp; Utilities Conference could provide WES with an opportunity to showcase its potential Risks: The potential divestment of assets could impact WES&amp;rsquo;s future growth potential Any fluctuations in the energy market could affect WES&amp;rsquo;s operations and financial performance Score:119 chances characters count - risks characters count = 119</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:237
Chances: DoorDash stock received an upgrade to Overweight from Equal-Weight at Morgan Stanley, signaling positive sentiment from analysts The company continues to deliver peer-leading and better-than-expected consumer spend and gross order value results, indicating strong performance across its expanding platform DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Community Impact Report demonstrates positive impact on merchants, consumers, and Dashers, showing the company&amp;rsquo;s positive influence in the community Risks: DoorDash struggles to return to pre-pandemic levels of growth, trailing behind leading competitor Uber in key metrics The company missed on earnings expectations for Q4 2023, reporting an EPS of $-0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: PPL&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings are better than estimates and the company continues to make substantial investment to further strengthen its existing operations. Robust Capital Investment Plan and Dividend Growth Announced PPL&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$20.44 based on Dividend Discount Model Risks: PPL Corporation misses on earnings expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALKS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alks/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Alkermes stock saw its Relative Strength Rating improve from 69 to 75, indicating a potential rebound in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenues outpaced estimates in the fourth quarter of 2023, driven by strong growth in proprietary products. Robust revenue growth and strategic focus are likely to propel Alkermes into 2024, indicating positive prospects for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:135
Chances: ImmunoGen has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months,ImmunoGen (IMGN) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects ImmunoGen Announces Inducement Grants Under Nasdaq Listing Rule 5635(c)(4) Risks: AbbVie Inc. announced its plans to acquire ImmunoGen in an all-cash transaction valued at roughly $10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings report indicates a stable performance, with revenue climbing 15% and operating income surging 37% The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend history, yield, and growth rates show potential for sustainable returns for investors The Food and Support Services United States (FSS United States) segment continues to offer food, hospitality and facility services for various institutions and venues, indicating a steady revenue stream Risks: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2024 earnings call is approaching, and it&amp;rsquo;s essential to closely monitor key metrics and compare them with Wall Street estimates and year-ago numbers for any potential areas of concern While the company has seen decent share price growth, the economic environment can significantly impact its performance, posing a potential risk The company may face challenges related to specialized dietary and support services provided by the Food and Support Services International (FSS International) segment Score:-74 chances characters count - risks characters count = -74</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: The stock price of Liberty Energy Inc. (LBRT) is up by 14% this week, indicating positive momentum. The company announced full year and fourth quarter 2023 financial and operational results, suggesting potential growth and stability. The Board of Directors has increased its share repurchase authorization to $750 million, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: U.S. Steel Corp. has the potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Nippon Steel Corp. made an aggressive all-cash offer for United States Steel Corp., indicating potential for a high acquisition price. Risks: The acquisition bid from Nippon Steel Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson beat fourth-quarter expectations with strong performance in the medtech segment. The company reported adjusted earnings of $2.29 per share, up 11.7% year-over-year, beating the consensus. Sales increased by 7.3% year-over-year to $21.4 billion, surpassing the consensus. Risks: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s stock tumbled after the company reported lower profit margins in the medical device and technology unit last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
