<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: The mean of analysts&amp;rsquo; price targets for General Motors Company (GM) points to a 26% upside in the stock. General Motors Company (GM) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately, indicating strong market interest. If you are looking for stocks that have gained strong momentum recently but are still trading at reasonable prices, General Motors Company (GM) could be a great choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co. (VRT) is expected to report positive fourth-quarter performance due to strong demand for its products and high-margin recurring revenue business. The company has an impressive earnings surprise history and solid growth attributes. Risks: The overly optimistic recommendations from Wall Street analysts regarding the stock&amp;rsquo;s average brokerage recommendation raise questions about its effectiveness and potential risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:105
Chances: The price-to-sales ratio indicates promising value for stocks like FHN FHN&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenue surprises suggest potential for stock growth First Horizon (FHN) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), indicating growing optimism about its earnings prospects FHN possesses the right combination of key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report Risks: FHN isn&amp;rsquo;t among the 30 most popular stocks among hedge funds It&amp;rsquo;s important to compare FHN&amp;rsquo;s key metrics to Wall Street estimates and previous year actuals to gauge its performance The stock is incurring losses or in an early development cycle, which poses some risk Score:105 chances characters count - risks characters count = 105</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: The stock price of Liberty Energy Inc. (LBRT) is up by 14% this week, indicating positive momentum. The company announced full year and fourth quarter 2023 financial and operational results, suggesting potential growth and stability. The Board of Directors has increased its share repurchase authorization to $750 million, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Investors seeking high dividend-yielding stocks may find New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) attractive The joint venture between Blackstone and CPPIB winning a stake in the commercial property loans portfolio is a positive development for NYCB Banco Santander&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a 20% stake in a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: U.S. Steel Corp. has the potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Nippon Steel Corp. made an aggressive all-cash offer for United States Steel Corp., indicating potential for a high acquisition price. Risks: The acquisition bid from Nippon Steel Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson beat fourth-quarter expectations with strong performance in the medtech segment. The company reported adjusted earnings of $2.29 per share, up 11.7% year-over-year, beating the consensus. Sales increased by 7.3% year-over-year to $21.4 billion, surpassing the consensus. Risks: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s stock tumbled after the company reported lower profit margins in the medical device and technology unit last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: AppLovin has been hot, and the run higher might have some momentum. AppLovin (APP) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Risks: It&amp;rsquo;s always important to assess the risk involved in investing in a company, especially in the volatile tech sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
