<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:05:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:209
Chances: Southwestern Energy (SWN) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. On a daily basis, however, output over the past six days was on track to drop by 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: PPL&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings are better than estimates and the company continues to make substantial investment to further strengthen its existing operations. Robust Capital Investment Plan and Dividend Growth Announced PPL&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$20.44 based on Dividend Discount Model Risks: PPL Corporation misses on earnings expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRIP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/trip/</guid>
      <description>score:79
Chances: Tripadvisor&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter results exceeded Wall Street estimates, showing significant growth in the Experience segment The company&amp;rsquo;s stock increased significantly by 45% over the past quarter, indicating strong market performance Tripadvisor&amp;rsquo;s platform provides contextually-relevant booking links to travel partners, which is a competitive advantage in the online travel industry Risks: The online travel industry is highly competitive and constantly evolving, posing potential challenges for Tripadvisor in maintaining its market position The company&amp;rsquo;s performance may be impacted by external factors such as economic downturns, changes in travel regulations, or disruptions in travel patterns Score:79 chances characters count - risks characters count = 79</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gtes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gtes/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: Gates Industrial Corp PLC&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Ivo Jurek, has increased the insider&amp;rsquo;s stake in the company by purchasing 20,492 shares, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s potential growth. The company has been recognized as one of America&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Workplaces for Diversity 2024, showcasing its commitment to diversity and inclusion, which can enhance its reputation and attract top talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALKS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alks/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Alkermes stock saw its Relative Strength Rating improve from 69 to 75, indicating a potential rebound in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenues outpaced estimates in the fourth quarter of 2023, driven by strong growth in proprietary products. Robust revenue growth and strategic focus are likely to propel Alkermes into 2024, indicating positive prospects for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:135
Chances: ImmunoGen has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months,ImmunoGen (IMGN) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects ImmunoGen Announces Inducement Grants Under Nasdaq Listing Rule 5635(c)(4) Risks: AbbVie Inc. announced its plans to acquire ImmunoGen in an all-cash transaction valued at roughly $10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings report indicates a stable performance, with revenue climbing 15% and operating income surging 37% The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend history, yield, and growth rates show potential for sustainable returns for investors The Food and Support Services United States (FSS United States) segment continues to offer food, hospitality and facility services for various institutions and venues, indicating a steady revenue stream Risks: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2024 earnings call is approaching, and it&amp;rsquo;s essential to closely monitor key metrics and compare them with Wall Street estimates and year-ago numbers for any potential areas of concern While the company has seen decent share price growth, the economic environment can significantly impact its performance, posing a potential risk The company may face challenges related to specialized dietary and support services provided by the Food and Support Services International (FSS International) segment Score:-74 chances characters count - risks characters count = -74</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: The stock price of Liberty Energy Inc. (LBRT) is up by 14% this week, indicating positive momentum. The company announced full year and fourth quarter 2023 financial and operational results, suggesting potential growth and stability. The Board of Directors has increased its share repurchase authorization to $750 million, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Investors seeking high dividend-yielding stocks may find New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) attractive The joint venture between Blackstone and CPPIB winning a stake in the commercial property loans portfolio is a positive development for NYCB Banco Santander&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a 20% stake in a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: U.S. Steel Corp. has the potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Nippon Steel Corp. made an aggressive all-cash offer for United States Steel Corp., indicating potential for a high acquisition price. Risks: The acquisition bid from Nippon Steel Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson beat fourth-quarter expectations with strong performance in the medtech segment. The company reported adjusted earnings of $2.29 per share, up 11.7% year-over-year, beating the consensus. Sales increased by 7.3% year-over-year to $21.4 billion, surpassing the consensus. Risks: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s stock tumbled after the company reported lower profit margins in the medical device and technology unit last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: AppLovin has been hot, and the run higher might have some momentum. AppLovin (APP) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Risks: It&amp;rsquo;s always important to assess the risk involved in investing in a company, especially in the volatile tech sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
