<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: CVS Health announces additional responsibilities for executive leadership team members, indicating strategic expansion. CVS Health survey finds that more than two-thirds of Americans plan to get a flu shot this season, which can boost revenue. CVS Health launches Cordavis to target the biosimilar market, tapping into a potentially lucrative sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Permian Resources announced a $500.0 million private placement of senior notes due in 2032, indicating its ability to raise capital. The company is set to acquire Earthstone Energy in an all-stock transaction, creating a $14 billion premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P, which may lead to growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vst/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Vistra Corp. (VST) is receiving positive attention from analysts and investors, making it a potentially favorable investment. The company has reported strong earnings and results in the second quarter of 2023, which could attract investors seeking growth. Vistra Corp. is expanding its energy storage system, positioning itself for the growing demand for clean energy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fti/</guid>
      <description>score:160
Chances: TechnipFMC has clinched a significant contract for the Girassol Life Extension Project, indicating growth potential in the oil and gas sector. The company announced the initiation of a quarterly dividend and an additional $400 million share repurchase authorization, which may attract income and value investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</guid>
      <description>score:55
Chances: Avantor has partnered with Tobin Scientific to provide comprehensive solutions for research lab services, showing commitment to innovation. The Avantor Foundation supports high school students pursuing STEM careers, which may contribute to future talent development. Avantor earned a Bronze Medal from EcoVadis for sustainability performance, indicating a commitment to responsible business practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings has shown resilience despite market challenges. Consumer demand for travel experiences remains robust, which is positive for the company. The company reported strong second-quarter 2023 financial results and improved its full-year guidance. Risks: Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings faced a 25% drop in stock price in August, indicating market volatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Marvell&amp;rsquo;s AI revenue is showing promising growth, which could be a positive sign for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. Despite a recent pullback, institutional shareholders have seen a 7.2% return over the past year, indicating some level of confidence in Marvell. The company beat Q2 earnings and revenue estimates, which may suggest its resilience in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Opendoor Technologies Inc. has shown significant growth potential, making it an attractive stock for investors. The company could be one of the market&amp;rsquo;s biggest winners over the next decade, indicating long-term growth prospects. Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s stock performance has been impressive, with a more than 200% increase in value this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Lufax Holding reported Q2 2023 earnings that topped estimates, indicating potential growth. Despite recent earnings declines, Lufax Holding could bounce back, as public companies are its largest shareholders. Lufax Holding Ltd successfully listed on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong, which could open up new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: C3.ai is off to a strong start with significant traction across its business in Q1 2024. Ark Invest predicts that the AI industry will add $200 trillion to the economy by 2030, making AI stocks promising. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s Q1 loss was narrower than expected, and revenues rose year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: GSK&amp;rsquo;s value is being questioned, but it may be undervalued, making it an attractive investment option. GSK announces availability of AREXVY, its Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) vaccine, at all major US retail pharmacies. Settling the first Zantac cancer lawsuit could soothe investors and impact GSK&amp;rsquo;s stock positively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Huntington Bancshares is paying out a dividend of $0.155, which may attract income-focused investors. The bank&amp;rsquo;s focus on transforming medical billing with software could lead to revenue growth in the healthcare industry. Huntington National Bank ranks No. 1 among regional banks in the J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Lucid CEO mentions that Air EV price cuts were well received, indicating positive market response. Lucid announces final production specifications for the Lucid Air Sapphire, enhancing its product portfolio. Rivian, another EV maker, raises production targets, signaling potential growth in the EV market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Nio is pioneering the EV revolution, suggesting growth potential in the electric vehicle industry. Analysis on NIO Inc. from BestGrowthStocks.com may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. There are catalysts expected for Nio stock investors in 2023, indicating potential opportunities. Goldman Sachs includes NIO Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: CEOs of major Brazil lenders see a &amp;lsquo;unique opportunity&amp;rsquo; for the local economy, suggesting potential growth. Amazon is set to launch a credit card in Brazil with Bradesco, which could open up new revenue streams. Banco Bradesco&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call transcript may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:-297
Chances: Peloton Interactive, Inc. Announces Participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference Peloton&amp;rsquo;s return to positive cash flow hit by bike recall, shares slide Peloton Interactive, Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year Fiscal 2023 Financial Results Peloton and the University of Michigan Announce Partnership Reaching Students, Athletes and Alumni Risks: Is Peloton in Trouble?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oln/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oln/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Olin Corp. announces shakeup in C-suite Olin Announces CEO Transition Plan Olin (OLN) Acquires White Flyer Targets to Grow Winchester Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Julie Piggott Appointed to Olin&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors Risks: Why Olin Stock Is Down Today Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Olin (OLN) Misses Q1 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Olin (OLN) to Close Epoxy Facilities in Restructuring Program An Intrinsic Calculation For Olin Corporation (NYSE:OLN) Suggests It&amp;rsquo;s 49% Undervalued Score:-43 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer Bob Bakish to Participate in the 2023 Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference PATH Launches Limited Edition Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem Bottles in Partnership with Paramount Consumer Products Paramount Global Drops Plan to Sell BET Media S&amp;amp;P 500 Gains and Losses Today: Index Falls as Tech Stocks Lose Ground Risks: Paramount global debt cut to just above junk by Moody’s Hollywood strikes, subscriber churn, sports rights: Big media woes Americans are canceling more streaming plans as prices balloon Traditional TV &amp;lsquo;past the point of no return&amp;rsquo; as viewership hits record low Trouble in Tinseltown: 3 Entertainment Stocks to Sell Before the Curtain Falls Score:36 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Implied Volatility Surging for Nu Holdings (NU) Stock Options This Unstoppable Fintech Keeps Crushing Analyst Estimates Nu Holdings Ltd. (NU) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Buffett-Backed Nubank Bets on Mexico for ‘Pivotal’ Growth Wall Street Bulls Look Optimistic About Nu Holdings Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/asx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/asx/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: ASE Technology Holding achieves the best overall performance on the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. ASE&amp;rsquo;s Bumping Factory in Kaohsiung, Taiwan inducted into the World Economic Forum’s Global Lighthouse Network. ASE announces advancements under the VIPack™ Platform. ASX reports positive Q2 2023 earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
