<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:787
Chances: BP&amp;rsquo;s earnings and profits have been impacted by falling oil and gas prices, but energy prices could rebound in the future. HSBC reported a profit jump in the second quarter, indicating positive economic trends that could benefit BP. The wind business, including offshore projects, is considered key for meeting climate targets, which could lead to opportunities for BP&amp;rsquo;s green energy initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Pipeline giant Kinder Morgan (NYSE: KMI) is a high-yield dividend stock with a yield of 6.2%. Kinder Morgan has spent the last eight years reviving its image after dividend cut in 2015. Kinder Morgan&amp;rsquo;s ability to secure high-return expansion projects to grow cash flow is a positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:1055
Chances: Coterra Energy reports strong Q2 2023 financial and operating results, exceeding production expectations. Positive stock performance with an 11% increase in share market value. Announcement of a conference call to discuss Q2 2023 financial and operating results. Retirement of two Executive Officers of Coterra Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:1153
Chances: Cenovus Energy&amp;rsquo;s positive Q2 earnings aided by higher contributions and lower expenses. Earnings and revenue surprises for Cenovus Energy in the second quarter of 2023. Beat in profit estimates due to higher downstream throughput and better production margins. Strong cash generation and funds flow for Cenovus Energy in Q2 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Lufax Holding&amp;rsquo;s strong financial results for the first quarter ended March 31, 2023, with earnings and revenue surprises, indicate positive performance and potential growth. Notable upgrades by analysts suggest positive sentiment and market response to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial results, potentially boosting investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mo/</guid>
      <description>score:942
Chances: Altria&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings beat expectations, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to maintain its cash cow business model and deliver positive financial results. Despite industrywide challenges, Altria has managed to hold up well, showcasing its resilience against headwinds in the tobacco industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
