<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:17:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1121 GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:1121
Chances: The back-to-school season shopping is projected to hit $135 billion, which could benefit Gap, Inc. (GPS). Gap, Inc. will report its second quarter fiscal 2023 financial results, presenting potential opportunities. Gap and LoveShackFancy announce a limited-edition capsule collection, merging Gap&amp;rsquo;s iconic styles with LoveShackFancy&amp;rsquo;s vintage-inspired florals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1116 IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings show an encouraging adoption of the sole-marketed drug Elahere. ImmunoGen delivered better-than-expected earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company announced a multi-target license and option agreement to develop next-generation antibody-drug conjugates. ImmunoGen made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) momentum stocks list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1032 INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:1032
Chances: Infosys&amp;rsquo; first-quarter results reflect the benefits of strong demand for cloud, data analytics, IoT, and security products amid the ongoing digital transformation wave. Easing odds of a recession in the US and the emergence of artificial intelligence as a potential new source of revenue drive a rebound in Indian IT companies&amp;rsquo; stocks, including Infosys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1035 RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: Alison Rand has been appointed to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Financial Corporation announced an increase in its dividend from last year&amp;rsquo;s. Higher NII on the back of decent loan demand and rising rates supported Regions Financial&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 AES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aes/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: AES&amp;rsquo; Q2 revenues of $3,027 million beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 5.2%. The AES Corporation reported financial results for Q2 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s GF Value suggests that it&amp;rsquo;s modestly undervalued. AES declared a quarterly common stock dividend of $0.1659 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0923 BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:923
Chances: BP stock raised its dividend by 10% and announced a new $1 billion buyback program. HSBC&amp;rsquo;s profit jump in the second quarter may have positive implications for BP as well. BP reported a surplus of $2.3 billion, and its stock is near an early entry point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 AVTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Avantor achieved a Bronze Medal from EcoVadis, placing it in the top 50% of assessed companies, which reflects positively on its sustainability efforts. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion plans and focus on creating customized workflow solutions may provide growth opportunities for Avantor. Avantor&amp;rsquo;s culture of development and commitment to aligning associates&amp;rsquo; growth could contribute to a positive work environment and potential business growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 IPG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: The Interpublic Group of Companies Inc (IPG) gained 4.25% daily, indicating investor interest in the stock. The company&amp;rsquo;s Earnings Per Share (EPS) of $2.41 adds to the positive sentiment among investors. As one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest advertising holding companies, IPG generates revenue from various advertising services, including traditional and digital services, which could potentially lead to future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0993 ENB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enb/</guid>
      <description>score:993
Chances: Enbridge reported higher second-quarter profit due to increased oil volumes, which could positively impact the stock. Enbridge&amp;rsquo;s favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season suggest a potential opportunity for the stock. The company reaffirming its 2023 financial outlook indicates confidence in its future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Flagstar Bank, a subsidiary of New York Community Bancorp, successfully completed its MortgageTech Accelerator program, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering innovation in the mortgage technology sector. New York Community Bancorp delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which could signal positive prospects for the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1027 CNK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnk/</guid>
      <description>score:1027
Chances: Cinemark beat analysts&amp;rsquo; earnings and revenue expectations in Q2 2023, indicating strong financial performance. The movie theater chain achieved the highest domestic box office month of all time in July 2023, which could positively impact its future performance. Cinemark is seeing favorable earnings estimate revision activity and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season, suggesting potential upside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0871 MP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mp/</guid>
      <description>score:871
Chances: MP Materials beat analysts&amp;rsquo; top- and bottom-line expectations in Q2 2023, indicating strong financial performance. The company reported refining small amounts of rare earths in California, a milestone that bodes well for its future. Shares of MP Materials rose by 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1116 APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: AMC Theatres achieved its highest single-week admissions revenue in the Company&amp;rsquo;s entire 103-year history, signaling a positive performance and potential for increased revenue. AMC Entertainment posted its best-ever week of admissions revenue, fueled by a surge in cinema-goers eager to catch back-to-back screenings of &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Oppenheimer,&amp;rsquo; indicating strong demand for its films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1299 MTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mtch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mtch/</guid>
      <description>score:1299
Chances: This stock has been hammered by economic headwinds but could rebound big-time if analysts are right, indicating potential for a recovery in the stock. Match Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in Tinder and Hinge, suggesting positive performance in its key products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1459 FLR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flr/</guid>
      <description>score:1459
Chances: Shares of Fluor gained more than 15% after the company easily surpassed Wall Street expectations for the quarter and upped its full-year guidance, indicating positive performance. Fluor&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefited from a higher contribution from Energy Solutions and Urban Solutions segments, suggesting potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1005 NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Evergy&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings are better than expected, which could indicate positive performance for utility companies like NextEra Energy. IDACORP&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings benefited from customer additions and plans to add more hydropower generation to its portfolio, which might also be favorable for NextEra Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1053 OUT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/out/</guid>
      <description>score:1053
Chances: A rise in billboard revenues and transit and other revenues could indicate growth potential for OUTFRONT Media. OUTFRONT Media&amp;rsquo;s diverse portfolio of advertising sites and strategic investments for digital-billboard conversions augur well for the company. OUTFRONT XLabs winning awards at the Cannes Lions Festival of Creativity may boost its reputation and potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1020 MCW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mcw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mcw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Mister Car Wash delivering positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023 may boost investor confidence. The surge in artificial intelligence names and the tech industry could potentially benefit companies like Mister Car Wash, Inc. Mister Car Wash being the nation’s largest car wash brand could indicate a strong market position and growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1045 U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1045
Chances: Unity Software&amp;rsquo;s revenue rose 11% YoY on a pro forma basis, exceeding analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations, indicating potential growth opportunities. Unity Software Inc. delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, suggesting positive financial performance. Steady demand for Unity Software&amp;rsquo;s software solutions, expanding client base, and the launch of AI services may have contributed to its Q2 performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0873 PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:873
Chances: Pinterest reported a monthly active user (MAU) base of 465 million, up 8% year over year, indicating potential growth opportunities. Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s increasing user base, strength in emerging verticals, AI integration, and enhanced monetization may drive revenue growth in the second quarter of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1162 F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:1162
Chances: Ford reported second-quarter revenue and adjusted diluted earnings per share that beat Wall Street estimates, which could be positive for the stock. General Motors&amp;rsquo; plans to boost employment for electric vehicle production may have a positive impact on the automotive industry, including Ford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: DraftKings stock soared after blowing away Q2 estimates and raising its revenue outlook for the second quarter in a row. Shares of DraftKings surged as the company reported second-quarter sales that beat estimates and raised its full-year forecast. The sports betting company posted strong Q2 revenue, beating expectations, indicating potential gains for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0784 OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:784
Chances: Opendoor Technologies reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, with positive clues for the stock&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s shareholder letter indicated that Opendoor exceeded the high end of its financial expectations, showing potential growth prospects. Risks: Opendoor Technologies missed earnings expectations for Q2 2023, which may impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1179 PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:1179
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s strong prospects in the field of artificial intelligence could boost its stock in the commercial market. Palantir&amp;rsquo;s multi-year enterprise expansion with WesTrac Pty Ltd to deploy Foundry across core operations indicates potential growth opportunities. Analyst Stephen Guilfoyle&amp;rsquo;s positive view on Palantir&amp;rsquo;s stock and its surging AI spending could be favorable for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1193 AAPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</guid>
      <description>score:1193
Chances: Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s Berkshire Hathaway reported net income of $35.91 billion for the second quarter, boosted by stock holdings such as Apple. Tech giant is working on compressing language models to run efficiently on iPhones and iPads, which could benefit Apple&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1244 AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:1244
Chances: Amazon.com, Inc. beats earnings expectations with an EPS of $0.65 compared to the expected $0.34. The e-commerce and cloud-computing leader, Amazon.com, showed strong growth and gained over 8% in stock value after reporting quarterly earnings. The outlook for e-commerce players, including Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 06:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>Chances: Dominion Energy&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings per share were better than its guidance range due to lower operating expenses, which may indicate positive financial performance and efficient cost management. The Coastal Virginia Offshore Wind project progressing on budget and on track for completion in late 2026 could signal potential growth opportunities for Dominion Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
