<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:02:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:97
Chances: The brand is optimistic that the sports drink will win over health-conscious consumers and fill a key void in its portfolio. Coke (KO) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:141
Chances: Uber Technologies (UBER) closed at $63.12, denoting a -0.83% change from the preceding trading day. The company will hold its quarterly conference call to discuss its fourth quarter 2023 financial results on February 7th. Steadying interest rates and a stronger-than-expected economy are contributing to positive sentiments regarding the Internet-Services industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:154
Chances: First Horizon Corporation (FHN) has an impressive earnings surprise history Regional banks tend to report early in the earnings cycle When the Federal Reserve starts cutting rates, it will be a positive for the regionals Higher-for-longer rates are still going to slow the economy, which will take a toll on the sector Banks that have strong capital ratios and loan portfolios will fare better during downturns Risks: The recent rally in regional bank stocks might have limited upside The Fed may not cut rates as soon as what the market is predicting Higher-for-longer rates could have a negative impact on the economy The slowing economy may take a toll on the banking sector Score:154 chances characters count - risks characters count = 154</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. signs agreement to acquire assets of a distributor of storm drainage products, indicating potential for expansion and growth in their offerings. Shares of Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. have more than doubled, up 107% this year, showcasing strong performance and investor interest in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
