<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cybersecurity on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cybersecurity on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CRWD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Shares of cybersecurity company CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) jumped 5.4% in the afternoon session after Morgan Stanley analyst Hamza Fodderwala upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Equal-Weight (Hold) to Overweight (Buy) and raised the price target from $203 to $304.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Cybersecurity stocks underperformed in 2023, but cloud security companies may be better positioned as corporate budgets tighten. Institutions&amp;rsquo; substantial holdings in Fortinet implies that they have significant influence over the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The technology sector will continue to be one of the sectors for investors to buy in 2024, with a focus on AI and semiconductor stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: The cybersecurity industry has been experiencing rapid growth, with increased demand for advanced technologies like AI for tackling next-generation threats. Risks: There have been significant insider sell transactions in SentinelOne Inc, which may raise concerns about the stock&amp;rsquo;s future performance. Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = 20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:351
Chances: VF Corp. (VFC) shares fell over 7% Monday after the owner of the Vans and North Face shoe and apparel brands warned that the company’s business operations were disrupted by a cyberattack. VF said in a regulatory filing Monday that the hacker encrypted some IT systems and stole data, including personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
