<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cybersecurity on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cybersecurity on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:04:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:478
Chances: The emergence of generative AI and new corporate products and services could boost Zoom stock but Microsoft looms. Top 15 value stocks to buy for 2024 picked by Joel Greenblatt. Analysis of 13 most profitable Robinhood stocks. Cisco Systems released their annual Purpose Report, reflecting progress towards an inclusive future for all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: Fortinet Inc provides a comprehensive suite of cybersecurity solutions catering to various businesses including enterprises, communication service providers, and small businesses. The company operates through multiple segments including Network Security, Infrastructure Security, Cloud Security, and Endpoint Protection, Internet of Things and Operational Technology, indicating a diversified product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: SentinelOne&amp;rsquo;s joint go-to-market program with Secureworks is expected to accelerate organizational cyber resilience and simplify risk management. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent rebound in stock price, positive financial results, and strong third-quarter earnings indicate a potential upward trend in the market for SentinelOne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
