<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:20:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1169 GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:1169
Chances: Gen Digital Inc experienced a 6.44% gain recently, with a positive Earnings Per Share (EPS) of 2.12. Q1 results reflect strong customer growth and benefits from global business expansion and the Avast acquisition, leading to year-over-year growth in revenues and bookings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1118 S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:1118
Chances: SentinelOne is a company helping to counteract the increase in cybersecurity threats by employing its own AI technologies to identify and stamp out threats. SentinelLabs announced a stellar lineup of speakers for LABScon 2023, the premier cybersecurity research conference, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s expertise in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1146 CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:1146
Chances: Oliver Tuszik&amp;rsquo;s appointment as the next President of Cisco Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) could bring stability and growth opportunities to the region. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s scheduled conference call to announce its fourth quarter and fiscal year 2023 financial results indicates upcoming updates on the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1056 NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Cloudflare reported second-quarter results that topped estimates, and the company raised its full-year 2023 outlook, which may attract investor interest. The company&amp;rsquo;s solid demand across its security portfolio amid work-from-home policies and escalating cyberattacks could benefit Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s financial situation is getting better, which may be seen as a positive signal by investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1321 PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1321
Chances: Palo Alto Networks is a global cybersecurity leader, which positions the company to benefit from the increasing demand for cybersecurity solutions amid growing cybersecurity threats and attacks. The announcement of Palo Alto Networks&amp;rsquo; financial results for its fiscal fourth quarter and full year 2023 on August 18, 2023, could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance and growth prospects, potentially impacting the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0995 MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:995
Chances: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s strong cloud business is expected to support its growth and revenue generation. Cybersecurity shares often outperform other tech stocks during economic downturns, which could benefit Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity offerings. The overall stock market has staged an extraordinary recovery in 2023, and this positive sentiment could have a favorable impact on Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0400 FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:400
Chances: Fortinet beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, reporting an EPS of $0.38, surpassing the estimated $0.34. This positive performance may attract investors interested in companies with potential for reversing their fortunes. Risks: A warning about slowing sales from Fortinet spooked investors, which could create uncertainty and potential downward pressure on the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
