<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:06:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: Micron (MU) closed at $85.75, indicating a -0.48% shift from the previous trading day. Investing in cybersecurity and semiconductor stocks can be a great way to ride the AI boom. AI chip stocks are on a tear amid investor optimism. Risks: The stock of Intel plunged nearly 12% after releasing disappointing sales forecasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:249
Chances: Gen Digital Inc. has a strong focus on consumer cyber safety through its business solutions, which could be highly beneficial in the current digital landscape The partnership with Dan Levy to raise awareness about cybersecurity through Norton Genie shows a commitment to public education and could positively impact the brand&amp;rsquo;s reputation The release of fiscal 2024 third quarter financial results and hosting a conference call could provide insight into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and future prospects Risks: The potential for lower interest rates creates a general risk for all companies, including Gen Digital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: SentinelOne (S) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Shares of SentinelOne (S) jumped 5.2% in the morning session after BTIG analyst Gray Powell upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Neutral to Buy and assigned a price target of $30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:129
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) has been gaining attention from investors and analysts, indicating potential for growth in the stock&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The announcement of the industry’s only integrated secure networking solution with Wi-Fi 7 and the launch of a new access point and 10 Gigabit Power over Ethernet switch demonstrates Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and staying ahead in the cybersecurity market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRWD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Shares of cybersecurity company CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) jumped 5.4% in the afternoon session after Morgan Stanley analyst Hamza Fodderwala upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Equal-Weight (Hold) to Overweight (Buy) and raised the price target from $203 to $304.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:351
Chances: VF Corp. (VFC) shares fell over 7% Monday after the owner of the Vans and North Face shoe and apparel brands warned that the company’s business operations were disrupted by a cyberattack. VF said in a regulatory filing Monday that the hacker encrypted some IT systems and stole data, including personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
