<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>growth potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in growth potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:331
Chances: Discussion of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s potential as an e-commerce business compared to Amazon&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory. Upgrading of CPNG shares by TheStreet&amp;rsquo;s Quant Ratings service. Coverage of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and its financial performance. Explanation of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s quarterly profit streak and factors contributing to improved margins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Strong quarterly results indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to perform well in the healthcare sector. Doximity&amp;rsquo;s leading digital platform for medical professionals positions it well in the telemedicine and healthcare technology industry. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show positive performance and potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:939
Chances: Discussing the impact of higher interest rates on Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s business valuation and the changing outlook. Reviewing Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and the missed earnings expectations. Analyzing the performance of renewable energy stocks, including the impact of interest rates and EV market strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1061
Chances: Discussing the top stock picks of ARK Invest and Unity&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the portfolio. Reviewing Unity&amp;rsquo;s latest quarterly update and evaluating its potential as an AI stock investment. Highlighting the year-over-year improvement in Unity&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results in terms of revenue and earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/riot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/riot/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Riot reported a new all-time record hash rate capacity of 10.7 EH/s, strong revenue of $76.7 million, and an expanded execution of power strategy, which suggests positive growth potential. Bitcoin production and operations updates for July 2023 show Riot&amp;rsquo;s continued commitment to expanding its Bitcoin mining capabilities and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Alibaba reported solid quarterly results that exceeded top and bottom line expectations, with strong revenue expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance is being compared to Amazon, Meta Platforms, and Microsoft, indicating positive competitive positioning. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s return to growth across all main divisions is a positive sign of a potential comeback after a period of malaise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Booming demand for AI chips could drive AMD&amp;rsquo;s growth in the second half of the year. AMD&amp;rsquo;s technology in the AI space, while not on par with Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s, still holds a strong position and is considered by many clients. AMD&amp;rsquo;s focus on AI technology aligns well with the growing popularity of the AI revolution in the business world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
