<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>growth potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in growth potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:235
Chances: Despite the significant decline in market capitalization, Lucid Group Inc. (LCID) has shown signs of a potential comeback, with its stock bouncing back by over 25% in a short time frame The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality electric vehicles, as evidenced by the selection of the Lucid Air to Car and Driver&amp;rsquo;s 10Best list for 2024, is appealing to investors Lucid&amp;rsquo;s production and delivery totals for the last quarter indicate a significant milestone in its growth and expansion Risks: The stock price of Lucid Group (LCID) has declined by over 30% year-to-date, driven by underperformance on certain key metrics The company has faced challenges such as unexpected declines in stock value and potential red flags in its operations Score:235 chances characters count - risks characters count = 235</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.4451, compared to expectations of $0.37. Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. and Plains GP Holdings LP combined Earnings Call indicates positive outlook for future growth in crude production in the Permian basin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
