<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: Toast has been growing rapidly in the last few years. Both Baidu and Toast have significant growth potential. These stocks represent the future of their industries. The stock is poised to see upside as the company gains market share and expands into new areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: With Grab&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in Southeast Asia and its success in various sectors like e-wallets, food distribution, and financial services, there is a significant chance of continued growth and success for the company. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent financial results for Q4 2023 indicate positive growth and improved profitability, which bodes well for its future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:223
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper (KDP) is on a growth track, thanks to its brand strength, innovation efforts, resilient category trends, market share gains, and significant pricing actions. The company has a strong product portfolio running broad across the beverage space, including soft drinks, coffee pods, and chocolate milk staple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:211
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) has released the latest version of its operating system, FortiOS 7.6, along with updates to its cybersecurity platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio includes network security, secure access service edge, enterprise networking, security operations, application security, and operational technology, indicating a diverse and comprehensive offering for its customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rum/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Rumble Inc. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $-0.14 compared to expectations of $-0.22 Full Year 2023 Revenue Increased 106% to $81.0 Million Achieved Company’s Largest Milestone To-Date with Public Launch of Rumble Cloud The current market’s volatility is ripe for momentum investing Risks: Rumble Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BROS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bros/</guid>
      <description>score:-455
Chances: Up-and-coming drive-thru coffee chain Dutch Bros delivers exactly what younger generations want. Drive-through coffee chain Dutch Bros. (BROS) announced a public offering of its Class A common stock. Dutch Bros stock: The coffee leader is breaking out past a new buy point on the stock market today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.4451, compared to expectations of $0.37. Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. and Plains GP Holdings LP combined Earnings Call indicates positive outlook for future growth in crude production in the Permian basin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
