<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth Potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth Potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:31:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: Wall Street analysts see a 27.77% upside potential in KE Holdings Inc., indicating optimism about its future growth prospects. KE Holdings Inc. recently announced an upsizing and extension of its share repurchase program and a special cash dividend, which may attract investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: Sea Limited reported strong Q2 2023 earnings with revenue growth, which may attract investors looking for growth opportunities. Despite recent setbacks, some analysts believe Sea Limited has significant long-term potential and could rebound in the future. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s focus on growth over profits signals its commitment to expanding its market presence and capturing opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Chewy, Inc. announced strong Q2 2023 financial results, beating earnings and revenue estimates, which may attract investors. Chewy&amp;rsquo;s CEO mentioned that helping customers with ease drives loyalty to the brand, which could lead to sustained growth. Some Wall Street analysts believe that Chewy has significant growth potential, with projections of over 50% gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Opendoor Technologies Inc. has shown significant growth potential, making it an attractive stock for investors. The company could be one of the market&amp;rsquo;s biggest winners over the next decade, indicating long-term growth prospects. Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s stock performance has been impressive, with a more than 200% increase in value this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates, showing growth year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s valuation remains relatively cheap and attractive for passive income investors. Positive signs of tech-led business reimagination using AI. Better than expected Q2 2023 results reported by eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Selected by Farmers Insurance Federal Credit Union for personal lending. Potential for significant upside due to AI technology in the financial sector. Stock&amp;rsquo;s impressive rally of over 400% since May 2023. Strong performance among the best performing stocks in the last 3 and 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docn/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Strong quarterly earnings results announced. Positive price performance and RS rating improvement. Expansion of AI footprint indicated after acquisition. Strategic bet on AI with a significant investment. Potential for growth as an AI-driven cloud services provider. Risks: Unexpected drop in stock price due to CEO transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) could benefit from a bullish trendline that might drive its stock price closer to record highs. The auto and industrial chip sector&amp;rsquo;s potential for accelerating growth and profit expansion in the coming year could positively impact ON Semiconductor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Strong quarterly results indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to perform well in the healthcare sector. Doximity&amp;rsquo;s leading digital platform for medical professionals positions it well in the telemedicine and healthcare technology industry. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show positive performance and potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
