<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>growth potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in growth potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:04:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: SoFi Technologies is diversifying its business operations beyond lending, which could lead to new revenue sources The company&amp;rsquo;s financial results have been impressive, indicating strong potential for growth Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s continued interest in the stock suggests a positive outlook for investors The thriving digital banking sector presents a lucrative opportunity for SoFi Technologies The technology platform segment of the company is poised for growth and increased revenue Risks: Investors may remain cautious about the company&amp;rsquo;s transition away from its core lending business The market&amp;rsquo;s perception of SoFi Technologies as a real, chartered bank may impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s valuation Shorting hot stocks like SoFi Technologies may carry significant risk due to market irrationality The transformation in traditional banking may pose challenges and uncertainties for the company Competition in the fintech and digital banking space could affect SoFi Technologies&amp;rsquo; market position Score:-20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.4451, compared to expectations of $0.37. Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. and Plains GP Holdings LP combined Earnings Call indicates positive outlook for future growth in crude production in the Permian basin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
