<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:04:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Keurig (KDP) is on a growth track with strong brand strength, innovation efforts, resilient category trends, and market share gains. The company&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio runs broad across the beverage space, providing opportunities for growth and disruption. The incoming CEO, Tim Cofer, brings experience in running companies at scale and understands consumer preferences, positioning the company for future success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:-39
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$35.37 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity LYFT is set to thrive in the growing rideshare market, buoyed by competitive pricing and cost-cutting measures Lyft shares more than doubled over the last year, indicating strong potential for growth Risks: Shares of ride sharing service Lyft fell 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rum/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Rumble Inc. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $-0.14 compared to expectations of $-0.22 Full Year 2023 Revenue Increased 106% to $81.0 Million Achieved Company’s Largest Milestone To-Date with Public Launch of Rumble Cloud The current market’s volatility is ripe for momentum investing Risks: Rumble Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BROS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bros/</guid>
      <description>score:-455
Chances: Up-and-coming drive-thru coffee chain Dutch Bros delivers exactly what younger generations want. Drive-through coffee chain Dutch Bros. (BROS) announced a public offering of its Class A common stock. Dutch Bros stock: The coffee leader is breaking out past a new buy point on the stock market today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.4451, compared to expectations of $0.37. Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. and Plains GP Holdings LP combined Earnings Call indicates positive outlook for future growth in crude production in the Permian basin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
