<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>growth potential on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/</link>
    <description>Recent content in growth potential on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-potential/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates, showing growth year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s valuation remains relatively cheap and attractive for passive income investors. Positive signs of tech-led business reimagination using AI. Better than expected Q2 2023 results reported by eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNOW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snow/</guid>
      <description>score:-46
Chances: Snowflake&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings top estimates with 36% sales growth. Analysts remain bullish on Snowflake stock despite recent challenges. Positive outlook for growth and market movers. Continued interest from Warren Buffett and insiders. Snowflake&amp;rsquo;s potential in the cloud computing and AI sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Selected by Farmers Insurance Federal Credit Union for personal lending. Potential for significant upside due to AI technology in the financial sector. Stock&amp;rsquo;s impressive rally of over 400% since May 2023. Strong performance among the best performing stocks in the last 3 and 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: KE Holdings to report Q2 2023 financial results. BEKE listed in Forbes&amp;rsquo; Global 2000 for the first time. Analysts believe BEKE could rally 42.95%, potential upside. BEKE&amp;rsquo;s P/S ratio is on the mark. Promising growth potential in the Chinese real estate market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docn/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Strong quarterly earnings results announced. Positive price performance and RS rating improvement. Expansion of AI footprint indicated after acquisition. Strategic bet on AI with a significant investment. Potential for growth as an AI-driven cloud services provider. Risks: Unexpected drop in stock price due to CEO transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sea Limited reports strong revenue growth despite missing estimates. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and upside according to Wall Street. Investing in Sea five years ago would have delivered a significant gain. TikTok signs payment pact with Atome for Malaysia e-commerce. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s intrinsic value is potentially 50% above its share price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Grab advances break-even timeline on boost from cost cuts and strong demand. Grab reports positive second quarter 2023 results. Initiatives to achieve zero packaging waste by 2040 show Grab&amp;rsquo;s sustainability focus. Positive revenue forecast and achieving break-even in the delivery business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: Opendoor announces inducement grants under Nasdaq listing rule. Positive signs for Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s business and growth potential. Trending stock with potential growth opportunities. Opendoor beats revenue estimates despite reporting a Q2 loss. Strong stock performance and potential for growth in the real estate sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) could benefit from a bullish trendline that might drive its stock price closer to record highs. The auto and industrial chip sector&amp;rsquo;s potential for accelerating growth and profit expansion in the coming year could positively impact ON Semiconductor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Strong quarterly results indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to perform well in the healthcare sector. Doximity&amp;rsquo;s leading digital platform for medical professionals positions it well in the telemedicine and healthcare technology industry. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show positive performance and potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
