<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend payment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-payment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend payment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-payment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Aramark recognized as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Companies for Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion&amp;rsquo; Positive movement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating. Strong performance in Q3 2023 results. Upcoming spin-off of Aramark Uniform Services (AUS) as an independent public company. Dividend payment announcement for August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: Encouragement for homeowners and contractors to call 811 for utility line marking. Dividend payment of $0.6675 scheduled for September 20. Second-quarter earnings per share better than guidance due to lower operating expenses. Coastal Virginia Offshore Wind project on budget and track for completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sirius XM&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results reflect improvement in average revenue per user amid declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which could provide insights into the stock&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend payment announcement and trading at a specific price level could attract investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: Barclays&amp;rsquo; appointment of James Edmonds as Global Head of Sustainable Project Finance demonstrates commitment to sustainability. Europe&amp;rsquo;s biggest banks announcing new share buybacks worth $5 billion could benefit Barclays&amp;rsquo; market position. Barclays&amp;rsquo; dividend payment announcement reflects its commitment to shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
