<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend payment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-payment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend payment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:41:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-payment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:-245
Chances: Huntington Bancshares Incorporated&amp;rsquo;s announcement of a dividend payment per share could attract income-focused investors. The appointment of Marcy Hingst as General Counsel might contribute to effective legal management and oversight for the company. Strong demand for commercial loans and optimism around a modest economic slowdown could positively impact Huntington Bancshares&amp;rsquo; financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Sirius XM&amp;rsquo;s improvement in average revenue per user and strong second-quarter 2023 results reflect positive trends in the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend payment and consistent performance in the music streaming industry could be seen as positive signals for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: KeyCorp (KEY) is a regional bank holding company, and its stock price has suffered a significant decline this year. Value stocks are expected to perform better, and KeyCorp could potentially benefit from this trend. KeyCorp&amp;rsquo;s Community Development Lending and Investment (CDLI) initiatives showcase the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to affordable housing and expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Aramark recognized as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Companies for Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion&amp;rsquo; Positive movement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating. Strong performance in Q3 2023 results. Upcoming spin-off of Aramark Uniform Services (AUS) as an independent public company. Dividend payment announcement for August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: Encouragement for homeowners and contractors to call 811 for utility line marking. Dividend payment of $0.6675 scheduled for September 20. Second-quarter earnings per share better than guidance due to lower operating expenses. Coastal Virginia Offshore Wind project on budget and track for completion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
