<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Estimate on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Estimate on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Paramount Global (PARA) has witnessed a jump in share price and strong trading volume, suggesting potential upside. The company has received multiple acquisition offers, indicating strong interest from potential buyers. Risks: The latest trend in earnings estimate revisions for the stock doesn&amp;rsquo;t suggest further strength down the road, signaling potential risks for future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Gen Digital&amp;rsquo;s fair value estimate is US$38.03 according to the 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity analysis. Avast, a brand of Gen Digital, blocked an unprecedented 10 billion attacks in 2023, which shows the company&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in digital security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpc/</guid>
      <description>score:131
Chances: Marathon Petroleum Corp. reported strong yearly net income of $9.7 billion amidst strong cash flow generation, indicating a robust financial performance The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on cost reduction and margin enhancement projects, as well as a 10% reduction in standalone capex for 2024, suggests potential for improved profitability Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and a positive Zacks Earnings ESP indicate potential for positive earnings results in the upcoming report Risks: Uncertainty in the global oil market and geopolitical events may impact the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and profitability Fluctuations in crude oil prices and refining margins could pose a risk to the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and financial stability Potential regulatory changes and environmental concerns may affect the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and profitability Score:131 chances characters count - risks characters count = 131</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Credo Technology Group Holding Ltd has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months. The company is an innovator in providing secure, high-speed connectivity solutions that deliver improved energy efficiency as data rates and bandwidth requirements increase. Risks: Notable insider transactions involving the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) may raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
