<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Us on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Us on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Stocks Picked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</guid>
      <description>IMGN (ImmunoGen, Inc.) Small ImmunoGen shows strong potential for growth in the biotech sector with positive industry outlook and earnings prospects, despite inherent market risks and volatility.
PDD (PDD Holdings Inc.) Large Despite potential risks, the Chinese e-commerce market offers opportunities for growth and innovation, and PDD Holdings is well-positioned to take advantage of these opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-59
Chances: Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s talks with France&amp;rsquo;s Blue Solutions for joint development of solid-state batteries could open up new opportunities for QuantumScape Prototype batteries from QuantumScape exceed design targets, showing potential for success in the solid-state battery market QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s stock saw a surge in November and early December, indicating investor interest and potential for growth Risks: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s stock is currently 70% below its market debut three years ago and 95% below its all-time high, signaling financial concerns and long-term challenges There are delays in the development of solid-state electric car batteries with Volkswagen, which may impact QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s growth and market potential Profitability at scale remains unproven for QuantumScape, raising concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to sustain long-term success Score:-59 chances characters count - risks characters count = -59</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: HPQ is well-positioned to benefit from the growing demand for personal computing and other access devices. The company&amp;rsquo;s division into HP Inc. and Hewlett Packard Enterprise has allowed for focused growth and strategic acquisitions. Risks: The potential merger of Hewlett Packard Enterprise with Juniper Networks could introduce integration challenges and uncertainties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-53
Chances: Coupang, Inc. is underfollowed on Wall Street, but has immense growth potential. The global e-commerce market is expected to reach $6.3 trillion for 2023, indicating a strong uptrend in e-commerce adoption. Emerging markets are likely to grow faster than most developed markets through the decade, presenting multibagger opportunities for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co. continues to show positive trend in veterinarian practices and support for U.S. veterinarians and support teams. The FDA approval for expanded use of Keytruda in combination with chemoradiotherapy to treat advanced cervical cancer is a significant development for Merck &amp;amp; Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:97
Chances: Tencent Music Entertainment Group (TME) has renewed a multi-year strategic licensing agreement with Universal Music Group (UMG), demonstrating a commitment to creating value for artists and enhancing experiences for music lovers. Risks: The resignation of Mr. Lixue Shi, the Group Vice President of TME, may raise concerns about leadership stability within the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s work in developing new drugs and breaking into the obesity market shows potential for future growth and innovation. Pharmaceutical executives are plotting to break into the lucrative obesity market, indicating a potential opportunity for Pfizer to expand its product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</guid>
      <description>score:79
Chances: Efforts to bolster fee income, dependence on domestic loans and digitization of banking services will keep supporting ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s (IBN) financials. ICICI Bank (IBN) looks promising on the back of its digitization efforts, high dependence on domestic loans and revenue strength amid the current macroeconomic backdrop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:105
Chances: Cisco Systems, Inc. continues its efforts to address the digital divide through a new research collaboration Technology is transforming our lives, changing the way we learn, work, interact with others and get access to all types of services Risks: Negative news from analysts about Cisco Hewlett Packard Enterprise&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Juniper Networks may impact Cisco&amp;rsquo;s market position Score:105 chances characters count - risks characters count = 105</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:68
Chances: Manhattan Associates and Shopify team up to help retailers deliver better shopping experiences. Monster and Shopify look poised for bull runs in the new year. The deal between Manhattan Associates and Shopify to create exceptional customer experiences at every step of the sales journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corporation Foundation offering STEM scholarships to support education and future talent in Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) disciplines. Risks: Inflation and higher natural gas prices are impacting utility investors and may lead to increased costs for customers. Score:40 chances characters count - risks characters count = 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:145
Chances: China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce landscape is still showing promising signs of growth and potential opportunities for investors. PDD Holdings has built a strong network of capabilities that support its underlying businesses, positioning it well for future growth in the digital economy. The introduction of new policies by Chinese e-commerce players may raise concerns, but there are still opportunities for growth and innovation in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Nokia&amp;rsquo;s launch of Nokia Federal Solutions (NFS) demonstrates a strong commitment to the U.S. federal government, which could lead to significant contract opportunities and revenue growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s patent licensing business and successful 5G patent agreement with Honor showcase the potential for generating substantial revenue from intellectual property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: Sea Limited operates in the digital entertainment, e-commerce, and digital financial services segments, providing a diverse range of offerings in the ever-growing online marketplace. The recent price movement of Sea Limited indicates a positive trend in the stock value, suggesting potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: The release of the E100 5G Enterprise Router by Cradlepoint indicates a potential growth opportunity in the enterprise router market, especially for retail and small office applications. ODIDO&amp;rsquo;s selection of Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s billing system for upgrading its infrastructure shows confidence in Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and presents a promising revenue stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:97
Chances: Coke (KO) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. If we want to find a potential multi-bagger, often there are underlying trends that can provide clues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: Oracle Corp. continues to expand its offerings and capabilities, especially in cloud services and enterprise applications which can result in increased revenue and market share. The company&amp;rsquo;s leadership in retail planning platforms and operations management solutions indicates strong potential for growth and profitability in the retail and consumer goods sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docu/</guid>
      <description>score:80
Chances: DocuSign saw a significant share price rise of 65% in the past couple of months on the NASDAQGS. DocuSign is at a pivotal point in its history. DocuSign shows rising price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating from 78 to 89.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: The stock yields 9% with a growing distribution Energy market is one of the most investable space in 2024 Sunoco LP announced the release of its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial and operating results Energy Transfer LP plans to release earnings for the fourth quarter and full year 2023 Concurrent offerings of senior notes and junior subordinated notes by Energy Transfer LP Risks: Energy Transfer LP closed at $13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:155
Chances: ImmunoGen has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months. The company belongs to a strong industry with growing optimism about its earnings prospects. ImmunoGen made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) momentum stocks list. ImmunoGen has announced inducement grants under Nasdaq Listing Rule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: The temptation to ride along with Uber Technologies stock is strong after its powerful rally in 2023. The company’s prospects for the very long term are strong as it&amp;rsquo;s a market leader. Uber Technologies offers ridesharing and delivery services. The average brokerage recommendation for Uber is equivalent to a Buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Toast received an upgrade from &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; by Goldman Sachs analysts There is optimism about the restaurant software provider&amp;rsquo;s ability to gain market share in 2024 Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies Risks: Etsy stock declined after Goldman Sachs downgraded it from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Charles Schwab shares came under pressure after a downgrade from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Elena Gomez, CFO of Toast Inc, executed a sale of company shares Score:16 chances characters count - risks characters count = 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RKLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Rocket Lab USA, Inc. has been selected by the Space Development Agency to design and build 18 Tranche 2 Transport Layer-Beta Data Transport Satellites, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s continued growth and expansion in the aerospace industry. Rocket Lab&amp;rsquo;s stock soared after winning a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Kenvue Inc. is poised to benefit from the favorable court ruling in a product-liability case, which has resulted in a nearly 5% increase in the company&amp;rsquo;s stock price. The Self Care segment, including cough, cold and allergy, pain care, digestive health, and smoking cessation, presents a strong opportunity for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Credo Technology Group Holding Ltd has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months. The company is an innovator in providing secure, high-speed connectivity solutions that deliver improved energy efficiency as data rates and bandwidth requirements increase. Risks: Notable insider transactions involving the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) may raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bti/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bti/</guid>
      <description>score:122
Chances: The U.S. Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s decision to decline R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company&amp;rsquo;s challenge to California&amp;rsquo;s ban on flavored tobacco products is a positive development for British American Tobacco, as it protects their market in the most populous U.S. state. Investors may find comeback stocks trading at 10% of their 52-week lows with a moderate buy consensus as potential opportunities for investment, offering growth potential in the face of market uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:162
Chances: Shares in enterprise software maker Salesforce rose amid an upgrade from Baird, which expects upside for CRM stock from price increases. For the most part, analysts are optimistic about Salesforce’s growth prospects in 2024. Amazon partners with Salesforce to integrate Buy with Prime into the latter&amp;rsquo;s Commerce Cloud platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/exc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/exc/</guid>
      <description>score:130
Chances: ComEd was recognized for its outstanding emergency recovery and assistance efforts in 2023 by The Edison Electric Institute and the Midwest Energy Efficiency Alliance. Exelon has been providing incentives for the development of energy-efficient affordable housing units across northern Illinois, showing a commitment to sustainability and community support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Fortinet has shown a positive change in stock price, indicating potential momentum in the market. The company is set to collaborate with global leaders and experts, offering strategic counsel on fundamental principles driving trust in cybersecurity. Risks: Cybersecurity stocks, including Fortinet, have underperformed in the past year and may face challenges in tightening corporate budgets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: Walmart is integrating generative artificial intelligence to make it simpler for shoppers to find what they&amp;rsquo;re looking for and streamlining associates&amp;rsquo; workflows. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s stock reached $161.29 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.24% change compared to its last close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-193
Chances: Chinese car exports are set to grow, predicts UBS. Tesla is dominating the EV market in the US and gaining ground in the overall market for cars. General Motors Company stock closed at $36.70, indicating a +1.97% shift from the previous trading day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Equitrans Midstream is the IBD Stock Of The Day, with a run of more than 50% in 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s operational results for the third quarter of 2023 show a 12% transmission pipeline throughput growth. Risks: Equitrans Midstream is reportedly considering a sale, which could potentially impact the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Realty Income Corporation has declared its 643rd consecutive common stock monthly dividend, showing a consistent and reliable track record of dividend payouts. Risks: With approximately 200 REITs on the market, it is important to carefully consider the relative strength and performance of Realty Income Corporation compared to its peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:-57
Chances: CNH Industrial NV is streamlining its leadership structure, which may lead to improved operational efficiency and strategic execution. Risks: The delisting of CNH Industrial NV shares from Euronext Milan and the transition to a single listing on the New York Stock Exchange may introduce additional market volatility and uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:218
Chances: Pinterest (PINS) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. With healthy fundamentals, Pinterest (PINS) appears primed for further appreciation. The top social media stocks of 2023 saw much relief, with many clocking in high double-digit percentage gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:55
Chances: The new law regarding the gig economy from the Biden administration may lead to increased employee classification for gig economy workers, potentially improving their rights and protections. DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s exclusive early release of the new Golden Carolina BBQ Tenders as part of their partnership with Cracker Barrel Old Country Store may attract more customers and drive sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:154
Chances: First Horizon Corporation (FHN) has an impressive earnings surprise history Regional banks tend to report early in the earnings cycle When the Federal Reserve starts cutting rates, it will be a positive for the regionals Higher-for-longer rates are still going to slow the economy, which will take a toll on the sector Banks that have strong capital ratios and loan portfolios will fare better during downturns Risks: The recent rally in regional bank stocks might have limited upside The Fed may not cut rates as soon as what the market is predicting Higher-for-longer rates could have a negative impact on the economy The slowing economy may take a toll on the banking sector Score:154 chances characters count - risks characters count = 154</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. signs agreement to acquire assets of a distributor of storm drainage products, indicating potential for expansion and growth in their offerings. Shares of Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. have more than doubled, up 107% this year, showcasing strong performance and investor interest in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline (PAA) has shown consistent performance with no significant change in stock price over the past few trading days. The oil and gas midstream market is valued at $27.5 billion, indicating potential growth opportunities for companies like PAA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRWD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Shares of cybersecurity company CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) jumped 5.4% in the afternoon session after Morgan Stanley analyst Hamza Fodderwala upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Equal-Weight (Hold) to Overweight (Buy) and raised the price target from $203 to $304.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Gap Inc operates as a global apparel retail company with a strong presence in the market. The company has a diversified product range catering to men, women, and children, under various segments like Gap, Old Navy, Banana Republic, and Athleta. Strategic plans for revitalizing the business with a new CEO at the helm and a marketing background may lead to positive developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has entered into an agreement to acquire a worldwide license to Precision BioSciences, Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Azercabtagene Zapreleucel (azer-cel), an allogeneic CD19 CAR T cell therapy program for autoimmune diseases. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: Pure Storage Inc. is set to replace another company in the S&amp;amp;P MidCap 400 index, which could lead to increased visibility and potential investment from index funds. The company&amp;rsquo;s all-flash storage platform is being leveraged by Toss Bank in South Korea, indicating the adoption of Pure Storage&amp;rsquo;s technology by a fast-growing financial institution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has a strong platform used by developers, artists, and designers across various industries. The company has a large user base, with over 1.1 million game creators relying on its software toolkit each month. Risks: Unity Software Inc. plans to lay off about 25% of its workforce, which could impact its operational capabilities and future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters reported strong growth in fourth quarter-to-date revenue, with the American Eagle segment growing in the high single digits and Aerie growing in the low teens. The company raised its fourth-quarter revenue and operating profit outlook, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Clarivate Plc has been consistently releasing new reports and products, indicating a strong focus on innovation and meeting the evolving needs of the healthcare and research industries. Risks: The company operates in a highly competitive market, and its success depends on the adoption of its products and solutions by academia, government, life sciences, and healthcare organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:294
Chances: AGNC Investment (AGNC) is a wise investment option at present due to an active portfolio-management strategy, decent liquidity and an attractive ROE. MPLX should have plenty of fuel to continue growing its big-time payout. Compared to this past year, 2024 is expected to be much better for the economy, and that means it will look even better for the stock market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: Permian Resources Corp. is engaging in an underwritten public offering, indicating a potential increase in capital and growth opportunities. The company&amp;rsquo;s consistent focus on responsible acquisition and development of crude oil suggests a sustainable approach to driving returns. The declaration of quarterly cash dividends reflects a commitment to delivering value to shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YUMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Yum China (YUMC) has been ranked number one globally for the Restaurant &amp;amp; Leisure Facilities Industry in the S&amp;amp;P Global 2023 Corporate Sustainability Assessment, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability. Yum China&amp;rsquo;s KFC unveiled its 10,000th store in Hangzhou, indicating strategic growth and solidifying leadership in China&amp;rsquo;s dynamic restaurant market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Gold producers are raising bets on copper through deals and investments, indicating potential growth opportunities. Expectations of interest rate cuts and a weaker dollar have fueled the rise in gold prices, presenting a positive outlook for gold mining companies like Newmont Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ivz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ivz/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Invesco Ltd. continues to demonstrate its commitment to providing a better investment experience for its clients by implementing changes to its ETFs. The company is set to release its fourth quarter 2023 results, signaling transparency and accountability to its investors. Invesco&amp;rsquo;s position in the market may improve as the company explores the potential for launching exchange traded funds tied to the spot price of bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: The merger between DISH Network and EchoStar has the potential to create a stronger satellite empire. Expanding wireless plans for Samsung Galaxy devices could attract new customers and drive revenue growth for Boost Infinite. Inclusion in the S&amp;amp;P SmallCap 600 index could bolster EchoStar&amp;rsquo;s visibility and attract more investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: Pet care stocks are incredibly effective in diversifying investment portfolios, leveraging the robust growth of the pet care industry. Chewy stock (NYSE:CHWY) has experienced an endless plunge over the past two years, which may make the stock a prime M&amp;amp;A target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fl/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Foot Locker, Inc. is leveraging its omni-channel capabilities to bridge the digital world with physical stores, providing a competitive edge in the retail sector Cost-optimization program implemented by Foot Locker is expected to improve its performance and financial results Strong start of the holiday season and revenue growth reported by Foot Locker indicates a favorable market position Risks: Nike&amp;rsquo;s weak sales outlook and cost cuts may indicate challenges in the athletic apparel and footwear industry, potentially impacting companies like Foot Locker Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s stock jump might be a short-term trend and not indicative of long-term performance Competition from industry peers like Nike, Lululemon Athletica, and adidas AG poses a risk to Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s market share Score:14 chances characters count - risks characters count = 14</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Plug Power is making significant strides in the hydrogen and fuel cell industry, with recent installations at Amazon fulfillment centers showcasing its potential for growth. The market for alternative energy technology is steadily expanding, providing Plug Power with opportunities for further commercialization and adoption of its fuel cell systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: The cybersecurity industry has been experiencing rapid growth, with increased demand for advanced technologies like AI for tackling next-generation threats. Risks: There have been significant insider sell transactions in SentinelOne Inc, which may raise concerns about the stock&amp;rsquo;s future performance. Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = 20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: VinFast is taking advantage of IRA funding and infrastructure bill opportunities to expand in the US and North America. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in CES 2024 indicates its commitment to showcasing new EV concepts and models, signaling potential growth in the electric vehicle market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hims/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Hims &amp;amp; Hers Health, Inc. unveiled Weight Loss by Hims &amp;amp; Hers, a comprehensive and customizable clinical approach specifically designed to help people achieve their individual weight-loss goals. The company has appointed Craig Primack, a pioneer in the field of clinical obesity medicine, as SVP of Weight Management, indicating a strong focus on addressing the growing issue of obesity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: U.S. equities made small gains, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 up 0.1%, fueled by optimism about possible Federal Reserve rate cuts in 2024 The market almost always rewards growth stocks through a higher valuation, and many high-flying names have been left behind after the initial pandemic rebound Risks: The market hasn’t been quite as enthusiastic about all growth stocks over the past three years Temporary growth slowdown as the post-COVID economic boom cools off and monetary Score:109 chances characters count - risks characters count = 109</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:351
Chances: VF Corp. (VFC) shares fell over 7% Monday after the owner of the Vans and North Face shoe and apparel brands warned that the company’s business operations were disrupted by a cyberattack. VF said in a regulatory filing Monday that the hacker encrypted some IT systems and stole data, including personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s strong focus on online entertainment content provides a unique and engaging platform for users. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to generate a word with shock value that was used 13.2 million times on their platform demonstrates strong user engagement. Risks: Bilibili missed on earnings expectations, reporting an EPS of $-2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:423
Chances: UiPath is well positioned to have a phenomenal decade. UiPath and CrowdStrike will continue their 2023 success into the new year. UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Market catalysts and internal growth make it likely that these stocks will continue to rally in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:83
Chances: Southwestern Energy Co. engages in the exploration, development, and production of natural gas, oil, and natural gas liquids (NGLs) Optimism prevails in the renewable energy industry despite recent downturns in renewable energy companies The United States is rich in natural gas resources found in multiple key basins and regions Risks: Recent downturns in renewable energy companies such as FirstSolar and Plug Power may impact the overall performance of the renewable energy sector Investors should be cautious about investing in &amp;lsquo;story stocks&amp;rsquo; that promise to be &amp;rsquo;the next big thing&amp;rsquo; Score:83 chances characters count - risks characters count = 83</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: ImmunityBio, Inc. is participating in the 35th Annual Piper Sandler Healthcare Conference, which is a positive sign for potential collaborations and investor interest. The new data showing the potential benefits of Memory Cytokine-Enriched Natural Killer cells (M-ceNK) for patients with small cell lung cancer and other types of neuroendocrine tumors indicates promising developments in the company’s immunotherapy platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: The merger between Warner Bros. Discovery and Paramount Global could result in a stronger position in the streaming world due to potential reshaping and reevaluation of portfolios Future mergers in the media and entertainment industry could lead to a lot of activity and potential bundling and deconsolidation of assets The opportunity for consumers to choose their own bundles in the future could be a positive development for the industry Risks: The disappointing box office performance of Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom raises concerns about the industry&amp;rsquo;s understanding of audience preferences Cord cutting, tough ad environment, and pressure to turn profits pose challenges for companies in the media and entertainment sector The unpredictability of box office performance and the potential impact on theater revenues may create uncertainty in the short term Score:27 chances characters count - risks characters count = 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:-51
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s real estate portfolio presents a significant opportunity for potential growth and value realization The company is constantly making moves to offer a seamless customer experience, showing a commitment to adapting to changing consumer preferences The potential buyout offer and the company&amp;rsquo;s high real estate value suggest a potential for significant returns for shareholders Risks: Smaller discounts and fewer marked down items at Macy&amp;rsquo;s during the holiday season may indicate a potential impact on sales and profitability The potential buyout and privatization of Macy&amp;rsquo;s may limit the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to undergo a transformative restructuring and adaptation to the evolving retail landscape The retail industry&amp;rsquo;s reliance on promotions and discounts could pose challenges for Macy&amp;rsquo;s in maintaining profitability Score:-51 chances characters count - risks characters count = -51</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: United Airlines is a founding member of Star Alliance, a global aviation partnership, which could provide the company with valuable market access and customer loyalty. The U.S. Transportation Department&amp;rsquo;s scrutiny of airline loyalty programs could lead to increased transparency and benefits for frequent fliers, potentially boosting customer satisfaction and retention for United Airlines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Immunovant, Inc. announced that results from the initial cohort of patients in the Phase 2 clinical trial of batoclimab in Graves’ disease exceeded 50% response rates, indicating promising potential for the drug Risks: Oral brepocitinib failed to meet its primary endpoint of Systemic Lupus Erythematosus Responder Index (SRI-4) change of 4 at Week 52, indicating a setback in the drug&amp;rsquo;s development for this specific indication Score:2 chances characters count - risks characters count = 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MANU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/manu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/manu/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: Manchester United stock has popped after the announcement of a new investor taking a 25% stake in the club and investing $300 million. The Santa Rally has gathered strength, contributing to the rise in Dow Jones and potentially impacting Manchester United stock as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: The Trade Desk Inc. has a strong position in the advertising technology sector, with a comprehensive platform that includes various advertising products and services. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent stock performance has shown resilience despite market fluctuations, indicating potential strength in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/onon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/onon/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: On Holding had another great quarter, and it has big plans for the next few years. The company is on a mission to double sales over the next three years. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. On Holding AG raised full-year sales guidance after posting another record quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YPF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</guid>
      <description>score:128
Chances: South America&amp;rsquo;s increased oil and gas production has huge implications for the global market Sweeping decree in Argentina opens the door for privatization of state-run companies Argentina&amp;rsquo;s U.S.-listed companies are enjoying a moment in the sun Risks: Argentina&amp;rsquo;s economy is broke and lacks funds Political instability in Argentina with the election of a far-right leader Score:128 chances characters count - risks characters count = -872</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:437
Chances: Solar power stocks received a boost from Jefferies, which initiated coverage on some of the biggest companies in the sector. Falling interest rates have fueled Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; stock this week. The projected fair value for Array Technologies is US$36.63 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity&amp;hellip; Jessica Lawrence-Vaca, Senior Vice President, Policy and External Affairs, Array Technologies ALBUQUERQUE, N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: India&amp;rsquo;s information technology firms are accepting tougher contract terms to win large deals from clients as they compete for fewer orders in an uncertain global economy. Generative AI technology can create more jobs than it is expected to eliminate, according to Tech Mahindra&amp;rsquo;s outgoing CEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gme/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: The investment landscape has been abuzz with the trend of meme stocks, a phenomenon ushered in by the remarkable and dramatic rise in GameStop’s stock in 2021. Investors know that the current expectations project rate cuts as early as March, which is a major positive for the economy overall and suggests that we have avoided a recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s expansion of the Shanghai Disney Resort with a Zootopia-themed attraction is expected to capitalize on the post-pandemic desire for travel and experiences in China. Risks: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s removal of the Disney+ app from its EVs amid ongoing feud between Elon Musk and Disney CEO Bob Iger may impact Disney&amp;rsquo;s revenue from in-car entertainment services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRIP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/trip/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Tripadvisor&amp;rsquo;s RS Rating has been upgraded from 78 to 81, indicating potential for a significant climb in share price. Kristen Dalton&amp;rsquo;s appointment as President of the Tripadvisor Core business suggests a strategic transformation within the company. Cruise Critic® has recognized Tripadvisor as a winner in its Editors&amp;rsquo; Picks Awards, highlighting the company&amp;rsquo;s strength in the cruise industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Organon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence shows a proactive approach to patient care and may lead to increased sales. The company&amp;rsquo;s exclusive distribution of Emgality and RAYVOW in Europe presents a significant opportunity for revenue growth in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: The acquisition by Clearlake Capital and Insight Partners could bring in new strategic direction and investment to help Alteryx regain market share. The premium of 29.1% from Alteryx’s last closing share price indicates investor confidence in the deal. Risks: Fierce competition from big rivals like Microsoft and Oracle could continue to impact Alteryx’s market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/azn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/azn/</guid>
      <description>score:-135
Chances: AstraZeneca (AZN) closed at $65.95, indicating a +1.77% shift from the previous trading day. AstraZeneca (AZN) announces that it is buying vaccine company, Icosavax. The additional supply of RSV shot for infants by AstraZeneca and Sanofi indicates a positive outlook for meeting winter demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</guid>
      <description>score:115
Chances: Netflix (NFLX) stock has continued its robust rally off its mid-2022 lows. With Squid Game: The Challenge reality series leaning on the strength of its impressive Squid Game franchise and new plans for its video game business, it’s hard not to feel better about the company’s growth story moving into 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Masonite&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PGT Innovations creates a leading door and window solutions company with over $4 billion in combined revenue, indicating potential for growth and expansion in the industry. Products from PGT&amp;rsquo;s brands were used in every home featured on a popular HGTV show, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s strong presence and market influence in the fenestration industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Recent revenue results and global market trends help solidify Roku as a strong investment opportunity. Several stocks soared in November on increasing signs that the Federal Reserve could be done raising interest rates as well as rising speculation that rates could even start coming down in the first half of 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Lucid Group has announced updates to the Air lineup, offering greater flexibility to customers and receiving recognition from Car and Driver for the Lucid Air Pure SiriusXM&amp;rsquo;s audio streaming entertainment experience is now available to all new and existing Canadian Lucid owners, potentially enhancing the overall customer experience Despite challenges and slowing sales growth in the electric vehicle market, there is potential for increased consumer adoption if the focus shifts from range to other factors Risks: The resignation of Lucid Group&amp;rsquo;s CFO, Sherry House, may raise concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial stability and leadership stability Downgrade by Needham analysts over weak demand for Lucid&amp;rsquo;s electric vehicles indicates potential challenges in the company&amp;rsquo;s market position and sales growth Waning U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: Nio management provided significant insights into the direction of the business. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. (NIO). NIO Inc. (NIO) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: The acquisition of Abcam by Danaher for $5.7 billion presents an opportunity for Danaher to expand its Life Sciences portfolio and accelerate the drug discovery process The completion of the acquisition despite initial opposition from Abcam&amp;rsquo;s founder demonstrates the determination of Danaher to enhance its product and service offerings Abcam shareholders&amp;rsquo; approval of the acquisition indicates confidence in the potential synergies and benefits of the deal Risks: There might be integration challenges and cultural differences between Danaher and Abcam, which could impact the success of the acquisition The valuation of $24 per share for Abcam could be considered high, and if the expected synergies do not materialize, it may result in financial losses for Danaher Unforeseen regulatory or market challenges could affect the planned expansion of Danaher&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences portfolio Score:41 chances characters count - risks characters count = -959</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s expansion into energy generation and storage systems presents a significant opportunity for growth and diversification. Despite declining vehicle insurance registrations in China, Tesla is still aiming for record-setting quarterly deliveries and a strong year overall. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to save lives and prevent injuries with its Autopilot technology provides a positive outlook for its automotive segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s shares jumped 7.3% in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s after an investor group made a $5.8 billion offer to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private Risks: The retail industry is facing challenges such as stiff competition from online rivals and high inflation Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -980</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:-89
Chances: XP stock has gained 53% and has outperformed the S&amp;amp;P 500&amp;rsquo;s 20% gain year to date. Cutting underperforming stocks out of your portfolio could help maximize your gains in the new year. Robinhood&amp;rsquo;s long-winning streak and recent gains suggest a positive momentum in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cere/</guid>
      <description>score:197
Chances: AbbVie&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Cerevel Therapeutics for $8.7 billion indicates a significant growth opportunity in the neuroscience sector Cerevel Therapeutics has a robust pipeline of multiple clinical-stage and preclinical candidates with potential across several diseases like schizophrenia, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease, and mood disorders Risks: The success of Cerevel Therapeutics&amp;rsquo; product candidates such as CVL-231, Darigabat, Tavapadon, CVL-871, and CVL-936 is not guaranteed Score:197 chances characters count - risks characters count = -803</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-89
Chances: One Nasdaq 100 component, with a slew of competitive advantages, is cheaper than it&amp;rsquo;s ever been as a publicly traded company Three historically inexpensive, brand-name companies owned by one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful investors are ripe for the picking in December Recent filings with the SEC have revealed that Gilchrist Malcolm Ian Grant, a director of Liberty SiriusXM Group (NASDAQ:LSXMA), sold 3,258 shares of the company on November 28, 2023 Risks: You probably had a good month in the markets, but a fifth of the stocks out there are trading lower through the rally The Oracle of Omaha&amp;rsquo;s company is requesting secrecy as it builds up its stake in one or more businesses This year has been a little dry when it comes to Warren Buffett stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Aurora Innovation, Inc. has reported strong progress towards commercial launch with an Autonomy Readiness Measure (ARM) of 84% in Q3 2023 The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in industry conferences and events indicates a commitment to showcasing its technology and engaging with potential investors The opening of the industry’s first lane for driverless trucks supported by commercial-ready terminals in Dallas and Houston demonstrates Aurora&amp;rsquo;s advancement in autonomous vehicle technology Risks: The company&amp;rsquo;s significant net loss of US$414.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/edr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/edr/</guid>
      <description>score:127
Chances: Endeavor Group Holdings operates as an intellectual property, content, events, and experiences company, with a focus on scarce sports properties and unique events The company has a strong portfolio of sports properties, including UFC, PBR, and Euroleague, which generate significant growth through innovative rights deals and exclusive live events Endeavor Content, the representation segment, provides services to talent and corporate clients Risks: The recent significant stock transaction by the CFO raises a potential red flag for investors Challenging market conditions and the need for continued innovative strategies to maintain growth Potential dependency on live events, which may be impacted by external factors such as global events and economic conditions Score:127 chances characters count - risks characters count = -873</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
