<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Us on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Us on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Ranking by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</guid>
      <description>DDOG (Datadog, Inc.) DIS (The Walt Disney Company) AFRM (Affirm Holdings, Inc.) ARRY (Array Technologies, Inc.) RLLCF (Rolls-Royce Holdings plc) DVN (Devon Energy Corporation) PR (Permian Resources Corporation) NVST (Envista Holdings Corporation) BTG (B2Gold Corp.) CLVT (Clarivate Plc) VTRS (Viatris Inc.) GEN (Gen Digital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:1202
Chances: B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call discussed operational and financial results, including total gold production and performance highlights. B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 revenues increased year-over-year due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. B2Gold delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating a potential positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:1294
Chances: Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; Q2 results may show increased megawatts shipment and strong margin performance from STI Norland acquisition. Array Technologies has an impressive earnings surprise history and a favorable combination for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The growth of solar energy and technological advancements create opportunities for solar stocks, including Array Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:946
Chances: KE Holdings Inc. (BEKE) stock had its Relative Strength (RS) Rating upgraded, indicating potential early-stage gains. BEKE is recognized as a Strong Buy growth stock, indicating positive growth prospects. KE Holdings Inc. joins the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;1t.org&amp;rsquo; China Action community to support tree planting and ecosystem restoration goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:963
Chances: Strong copper demand due to electrification trends and supply constraints is expected to support robust metal prices. Southern Copper Corp. is recognized as the best value copper stock, and Capstone Copper Corp. leads in growth and momentum. Freeport-McMoRan (FCX) stock has gained attention from investors, and understanding its prospects is important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:875
Chances: Tencent Music Entertainment Group (TME) announced the upcoming release of its unaudited Q2 2023 financial results. TME&amp;rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, Mr. Cheuk Tung Tony Yip, resigned for personal reasons, effective August 31, 2023. TME was listed among Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) value stocks on July 12, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Nordstrom plans to open a new Nordstrom Rack store in Queen Creek, Arizona, expanding its retail presence. Nordstrom announces the date for reporting its second quarter 2023 financial results and provides an outlook for the year. Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s Relative Strength (RS) Rating improves, indicating improving technical performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> STLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stla/</guid>
      <description>score:1101
Chances: Stellantis faces intense competition in the EV market but has opportunities in profitable niches like electric boats. General Motors plans to increase employment for EV production, despite concerns of reduced labor needs. The Jeep brand celebrates the 30th anniversary of the &amp;lsquo;Jurassic Park&amp;rsquo; film with an exclusive Jurassic Park Package for Wrangler and Gladiator vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UNVR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</guid>
      <description>score:1087
Chances: Univar Solutions has completed an acquisition by Apollo Funds, maintaining its global presence under the Univar Solutions name and brand. The company has expanded its distribution relationship with Kalsec Inc. for hop ingredients in the United States, enhancing its specialty ingredient offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ENPH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enph/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Enphase Energy is strategically expanding its presence in the renewable energy market, particularly in Europe where sales are growing. The global alternative energy market is showing strong growth, offering significant investment opportunities for Enphase Energy. Solar energy is projected to become the largest source of power globally by 2027, providing a favorable outlook for Enphase Energy&amp;rsquo;s solar-based solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CPB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</guid>
      <description>score:910
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao’s pasta sauce and noosa yogurt, aims for strategic growth and expansion. The acquisition of Sovos Brands for $2.7 billion demonstrates Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing its grocery business. Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s deal with Sovos Brands offers a premium to shareholders and has positively impacted its stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:823
Chances: The aerospace industry is recovering, and Chinese airlines&amp;rsquo; need to renew their fleets could present an opportunity for Boeing. The launch of electric vertical takeoff and landing aircraft by companies like Joby and Archer could offer potential upside for Boeing. Positive performance of blue chip stocks, including Boeing, contributed to higher market benchmarks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:787
Chances: BP&amp;rsquo;s earnings and profits have been impacted by falling oil and gas prices, but energy prices could rebound in the future. HSBC reported a profit jump in the second quarter, indicating positive economic trends that could benefit BP. The wind business, including offshore projects, is considered key for meeting climate targets, which could lead to opportunities for BP&amp;rsquo;s green energy initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:763
Chances: Renewed interest in meme stocks and retail trading may drive more attention to Peloton&amp;rsquo;s stock. Share price of Peloton saw a recent 23% increase, indicating short-term positive momentum. Social media and Reddit&amp;rsquo;s influence on meme stocks might create short-term opportunities for Peloton investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:771
Chances: Bilibili to report second quarter 2023 unaudited financial results, showcasing its growth and financial performance. Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s record high stock price in 2021 indicates strong investor interest and growth potential. Technical performance and Relative Strength Rating upgrade suggest improving trends for Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:716
Chances: Chevron completes acquisition of PDC Energy, bolstering its U.S. oil and gas operations. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment model, known for transparency and consistency, highlights Chevron as a potential long-term investment. Oil prices have quietly rallied, potentially benefiting Chevron&amp;rsquo;s earnings and cash flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:825
Chances: Infosys benefits from strong demand for cloud, data analytics, IoT, and security products amid the ongoing digital transformation wave. Optimism returns for India&amp;rsquo;s IT companies as easing odds of a US recession and the emergence of AI as a revenue source drive a rebound in stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:724
Chances: Gilead Sciences expects a third of sales to come from its cancer treatments by 2030, driving optimism and stock price movement. Gilead Sciences is focused on developing therapies for life-threatening infectious diseases and expanding its portfolio to include pulmonary, cardiovascular diseases, and cancer treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:1057
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reliable and stable performance makes it an attractive stock for long-term gains. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment model and Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s portfolio receive widespread attention for long-term performance. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s diverse product portfolio includes well-known brands like Coke, Sprite, Dasani water, Costa Coffee, and Minute Maid juices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:986
Chances: Major U.S. airlines request an extension of cuts to minimum flight requirements at congested airports due to air traffic control staffing issues. Flights to Europe have significantly increased, with a 600% rise in Americans traveling to Europe from 2021 to 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:966
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results show increases in sales and earnings, driven by brand strength and pricing. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter, and it raised its full-year 2023 net sales growth forecast. Keurig Dr Pepper appointed Monique Oxender as Interim Chief Corporate Affairs Officer, overseeing corporate responsibility and communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:1034
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s is set to report its second quarter 2023 sales and earnings results, with a call and webcast hosted by company executives. Retailers like Macy&amp;rsquo;s are expanding their use of &amp;lsquo;breathable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cooling&amp;rsquo; fabrics to boost sales amid high demand for heat-relief clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:1126
Chances: Under Armour announced the launch of its &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, aiming to strengthen customer connections and brand loyalty. The company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance customer connections, innovations, and a new loyalty program are expected to contribute to brand growth. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s senior executive leadership team changes are aligned with the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to drive consistent profitable growth and returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:1179
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs (NYSE: CLF) reported second-quarter results, showing improved automotive volumes, higher prices, and lower steelmaking unit costs. The company&amp;rsquo;s external sales volumes for steel products increased by around 15.4% year over year in Q2. Cleveland-Cliffs stock price rose by 2.3% over the past week, driven by long-term fundamentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JOBY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/joby/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/joby/</guid>
      <description>score:1050
Chances: Joby Aviation (NYSE: JOBY) issued its Q2 2023 Shareholder Letter with operational and financial results. The company is developing all-electric aircraft for commercial passenger service. Joby Aviation submitted Certification Plans to the FAA, progressing toward certifying its aircraft for commercial use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:1044
Chances: SentinelOne (NYSE: S) is helping counteract the increase in cybersecurity threats with its AI technologies. SentinelLabs announced a premier cybersecurity research conference, LABScon 2023. Cybersecurity investment opportunities are significant due to the rising instances of data breaches. Demand for high-performance cybersecurity services is expected to increase as work processes go digital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Pipeline giant Kinder Morgan (NYSE: KMI) is a high-yield dividend stock with a yield of 6.2%. Kinder Morgan has spent the last eight years reviving its image after dividend cut in 2015. Kinder Morgan&amp;rsquo;s ability to secure high-return expansion projects to grow cash flow is a positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:771
Chances: Charlie Ergen is nearing a deal to merge Dish Network and EchoStar for a nationwide wireless network. DISH Network partners with Amazon to sell Boost Infinite wireless plans to Prime members. Risks: Uncertainties related to the successful completion of the merger between Dish Network and EchoStar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:981
Chances: TAL Education Group share price has gained 56% in the last period. TAL Education Group announces unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. TAL Education Group to release unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. Chinese hedge funds add TAL Education Group to their portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:1129
Chances: Oracle leads stocks to watch with AI and cloud play, along with Amazon rival MercadoLibre. Oracle announces new Oracle Cloud for Australian Government and Defense to meet growing global demand. Wendy&amp;rsquo;s implements Oracle Fusion Cloud Applications Suite and moves to Oracle Cloud Infrastructure for improved business insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Ukraine reports significant results from U.S. Patriot and German IRIS-T defense systems against attacks by Russia. RTX faces quality and durability concerns with its single-aisle jetliner bet in the aerospace and defense sector. RTX beats Q2 earnings estimates with organic sales growth of 12% year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:1151
Chances: KeyCorp&amp;rsquo;s stock price bounced back strong in July, climbing 33%, outperforming major market indices. KeyBank introduces new products and services to enhance banking experience for consumers. KeyBank Foundation awards grant to Michigan Ability Partners for $175,000. KeyBank Community Development Lending and Investment (CDLI) supports construction of permanent supportive housing in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) expected to approve construction of a €10 billion facility in Dresden, Germany. TSMC&amp;rsquo;s leading position as the world&amp;rsquo;s top contract chip manufacturer makes it an intriguing investment. Growing trend of artificial intelligence (AI) and TSMC&amp;rsquo;s involvement in chip production for AI applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:1030
Chances: Kraft Heinz reports sales growth in North America and International regions due to solid pricing. Earnings season impact on Kraft Heinz&amp;rsquo;s sales and demand from cost-conscious consumers. Positive outlook for the economy and economic performance. Continued focus on pricing strategy and maintaining higher prices for products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s support for new iPhone models suggests improved chip volumes for the current quarter. Positive results from tech giants&amp;rsquo; quarterly reports despite some being muted. Formation of a new company by chipmakers, including Qualcomm, to develop RISC-V technology. Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s daily gain and EPS performance raise questions about its valuation and potential for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:993
Chances: Appointment of Marcy Hingst as General Counsel of Huntington National Bank. Huntington Bancshares announces an increase in its prime rate to 8.5%. Positive second-quarter profit for Huntington Bancshares due to rising interest rates and strong demand for commercial loans. Stabilizing deposits and positive economic data contributing to optimism for avoiding a full-blown recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Regions Bank introduces digital solutions for business clients to manage billing and communications. Appointment of Alison Rand to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Bank increases prime lending rate to 8.50%. Enhancement of Treasury Management suite of products and services to meet customer needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: The EV charging market is expected to reach $76.9 billion by 2027, creating growth opportunities for companies like ChargePoint. Global sales of electric vehicles (EVs) are expected to increase by 35% in 2023, driving demand for EV charging solutions. Demand for EVs and EV charging facilities is on the rise due to government support and climate change awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:1182
Chances: PDD Holdings (PDD) surged as much as 3.6% as China&amp;rsquo;s central bank signaled support for economic recovery. Ultra low-cost e-commerce platform Temu, owned by PDD Holdings, started selling to Japan, expanding its market reach. E-commerce stocks, including PDD, outpaced gains by the broader market as China&amp;rsquo;s central bank offered economic support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:1154
Chances: Merck reported stronger-than-expected Q2 earnings and raised its 2023 guidance. Keytruda cancer-drug sales drove better-than-expected Q2 revenue and a raised full-year sales forecast. Merck&amp;rsquo;s top-selling products, Keytruda and HPV vaccine Gardasil, experienced strong demand. Cleveland Clinic has started enrolling subjects in a treatment arm evaluating Anixa&amp;rsquo;s breast cancer vaccine with Keytruda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:1257
Chances: Permian Resources announces Q2 2023 financial and operational results. Board declares quarterly base and variable cash dividends for Class A common stock. Investors invited to participate in earnings conference call regarding Q2 results. Pickering Energy Partners co-manages secondary public offering for Permian Resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</guid>
      <description>score:1237
Chances: Envista announces successful pricing of $435 million Convertible Senior Notes offering. Consistent growth in Specialty Products &amp;amp; Technologies and Equipment &amp;amp; Consumables segments drive Q2 revenues. Envista delivers positive Q2 2023 earnings and revenue surprises. Envista Smile Project completes mission trip to the Dominican Republic, providing dental care to underserved patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:1055
Chances: Coterra Energy reports strong Q2 2023 financial and operating results, exceeding production expectations. Positive stock performance with an 11% increase in share market value. Announcement of a conference call to discuss Q2 2023 financial and operating results. Retirement of two Executive Officers of Coterra Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:1153
Chances: Cenovus Energy&amp;rsquo;s positive Q2 earnings aided by higher contributions and lower expenses. Earnings and revenue surprises for Cenovus Energy in the second quarter of 2023. Beat in profit estimates due to higher downstream throughput and better production margins. Strong cash generation and funds flow for Cenovus Energy in Q2 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:1000
Chances: Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s positive Q2 2023 earnings call transcript. Renewal of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s normal course issuer bid (NCIB) program. Earnings and revenue surprises for Kinross Gold in the second quarter of 2023. Declaration of dividend by Kinross Gold for Q2 2023. Expectations of higher earnings for Kinross Gold due to improved production and higher gold prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:1269
Chances: Formation of strategic partnership between WaterBridge NDB and Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary, yielding the largest private water infrastructure. Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend reduction due to weaker oil and gas prices. Discussion on investing in the energy sector for income stocks. Analysis of Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend cut and its impact on passive income investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:1182
Chances: Gen Digital experiences a gain with positive Earnings Per Share (EPS). Gen Digital offers cybersecurity solutions, identity protection, and privacy solutions. Gen Digital&amp;rsquo;s Q1 results show strong customer growth, global expansion benefits, and Avast acquisition impact. Gen Digital releases its fiscal year 2024 first-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:1176
Chances: Toast launches Toast Catering &amp;amp; Events, a fully integrated product for managing large catering orders and event planning. Toast Invoicing, a digital invoicing tool, complements Toast Catering &amp;amp; Events. Toast announces the release date of its second quarter 2023 financial results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:1400
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s Relative Strength (RS) Rating has been upgraded, indicating potential for significant gains. The projected fair value for Datadog is estimated at $129 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. Datadog continues to experience steady adoption of its cloud-based monitoring and introduces new capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1097
Chances: Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s CEO expresses confidence despite the second downgrade of the US credit rating, indicating potential resilience in the face of credit challenges. Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s support for nonprofit organization Concordance&amp;rsquo;s national expansion to promote financial health and stability reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to community development and positive social impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:1041
Chances: Cemex and Synhelion&amp;rsquo;s joint effort to develop fully solar-driven cement production represents a significant milestone, potentially revolutionizing the energy-intensive cement manufacturing process. Double-digit price hikes and a strong peso have contributed to Cemex&amp;rsquo;s rise in net profit and revenue in the second quarter, demonstrating positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:1026
Chances: JD.com&amp;rsquo;s strong stock performance and positive momentum over the last month indicate potential for higher returns and market outperformance. Analyst projections suggest a fair value for JD.com based on Free Cash Flow to Equity, potentially indicating undervaluation and room for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Lufax Holding&amp;rsquo;s strong financial results for the first quarter ended March 31, 2023, with earnings and revenue surprises, indicate positive performance and potential growth. Notable upgrades by analysts suggest positive sentiment and market response to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial results, potentially boosting investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mo/</guid>
      <description>score:942
Chances: Altria&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings beat expectations, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to maintain its cash cow business model and deliver positive financial results. Despite industrywide challenges, Altria has managed to hold up well, showcasing its resilience against headwinds in the tobacco industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Intel to create a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s technological capabilities and competitiveness. Cradlepoint&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Ericsson in modernizing network infrastructure for Los Angeles County showcases Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s involvement in innovative and impactful projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:990
Chances: Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s recent appointment of Tim Stone as Chief Financial Officer is a positive move that could contribute to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial management and strategic direction. Riding Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s love for innovative tech businesses, Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s stock had soared in the past, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for growth and investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:1029
Chances: NextEra Energy&amp;rsquo;s strong financial performance and dividend income potential from its stocks make it an attractive choice for retirees seeking to bridge the gap in their expenses. The global shift towards renewable energy sources, as highlighted by the International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s projection of solar becoming the largest power source, bodes well for NextEra Energy&amp;rsquo;s focus on clean energy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JPM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</guid>
      <description>score:818
Chances: JPMorgan Chase is expanding its presence and innovation efforts in India with the opening of two state-of-the-art facilities, enhancing service excellence and efficiency. JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s Advancing Black Wealth Tour aims to deliver financial education, workshops, and wealth-building seminars to Black communities, contributing to financial empowerment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Monster Beverage Corporation reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1% to $1.85 billion, driven by gains in brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions. Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to reflect gains from continued strength in the energy drinks category and robust product innovation plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:1027
Chances: Southwest Airlines is extending its flight schedule through April 8, 2024, offering more nonstop options for customers, particularly during peak travel times. The denial of a Southwest pilot strike request by the National Mediation Board reduces the likelihood of a strike, allowing negotiations to resume next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: Li Auto is expected to report strong earnings and revenue growth, with analysts predicting about 24 cents/share of earnings on revenue of $3.7 billion. Li Auto delivered 34,134 vehicles in July 2023, an increase of 227.5% year over year, surpassing the 30,000 mark for the second consecutive month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:991
Chances: Coupang&amp;rsquo;s stock increased significantly by 6.9% over the past period. Coupang is estimated to have a fair value of US$25.12 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. E-commerce players like Coupang are expected to grow by 9% or greater levels in both 2023 and 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:972
Chances: Bristol Myers Squibb has a history of consistently paying dividends for the last 90 years. Pharmaceutical company AbbVie reports better-than-expected Q2 sales for its arthritis medication Humira. Discounted blue-chip stocks with potential upside may offer investment opportunities in a market with some lagging stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</guid>
      <description>score:957
Chances: Boston Scientific&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings saw organic and operational revenue growth in core business segments and geographies. Continued strength in BD&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences segment&amp;rsquo;s base business is expected to benefit Q3 sales. Boston Scientific stock rose as hospital procedures stabilized after the Covid pandemic, contributing to a 20% rise in earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:903
Chances: Medical Properties Trust&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings may benefit from favorable healthcare industry trends and capital recycling efforts. Investors looking for super-high-yield dividend stocks may consider Medical Properties Trust with its dividend yield of about 11.6%. Medical Properties Trust will host a conference call to discuss its Q2 2023 financial results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: AGNC Investment (AGNC) may be worthy of consideration as the worst effects of interest rate hikes appear to be over. AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s commitment to repositioning its portfolio in the current interest rate scenario may optimize performance. Dividend-focused investors may find AGNC Investment appealing due to its high yield and potential income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:1095
Chances: Outlook for CSCO stock depends on trends for cloud computing and corporate/telecom networks amid remote work shift. Corporate clients&amp;rsquo; boost could benefit Zoom stock, but Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s presence poses competition. Synovus Trust Portfolio Manager pleased with tech companies&amp;rsquo; quarterly results, including CSCO&amp;rsquo;s upcoming report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:971
Chances: Comcast Corporation celebrates the beginning of FIFA Women&amp;rsquo;s World Cup Australia &amp;amp; New Zealand 2023™. NBCUniversal is moving into a new metro Atlanta film studio amid concurrent Hollywood strikes. &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; movie surpasses $1 billion at the global box office in just 17 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:960
Chances: U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s strategic alliance with Mitsubishi UFJ will boost capital and growth opportunities. Investors with cash may find buying opportunities in U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s stock. U.S. Bank increased its prime lending rate to 8.50 percent. U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s initiatives and alliances may contribute to potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Cybersecurity ETFs are discussed as potential investments in the growing cybersecurity market. Palo Alto Networks announced the release of its fiscal fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. Strong potential is identified in Internet software stocks like PANW for the rest of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:1031
Chances: Ambev&amp;rsquo;s stock performance is compared to other companies like Beyond Meat and Carlsberg in terms of value. Investors are looking into dividend penny stocks, including Ambev, as potential investment options. Despite high inflation, there are opportunities for affordable stocks like Ambev that offer potential returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:999
Chances: Occidental Petroleum reported a surprise profit in Q2 2023 despite the impact of soft commodity prices. Permian Basin production remains strong, contributing to Occidental&amp;rsquo;s production volumes for the year. Sunrise&amp;rsquo;s surprise profit, DXC&amp;rsquo;s guidance, and Wayfair&amp;rsquo;s performance could provide insights into Occidental&amp;rsquo;s industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:1112
Chances: Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) announces a transition plan for CFO Tarek Robbiati, who will assume an external CEO role. HPE expands its Bare Metal Cloud platform with cloud-native HPE ProLiant RL300 Gen11 servers, enhancing AI inferencing and cloud-native workloads. ZoomInfo delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, potentially impacting HPE&amp;rsquo;s stock and market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FLR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flr/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Fluor Corporation successfully priced $500 million aggregate principal amount of Convertible Senior Notes due 2029. Fluor reported outstanding financial results, leading to a significant rating upgrade and positive market sentiment. Fluor announced its intention to offer Convertible Senior Notes due 2029, potentially raising capital for future operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:1124
Chances: Barrick Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to benefit from higher gold and copper production along with cost reduction. Barrick Gold aims to restart operations at the Porgera gold mine in Papua New Guinea, potentially contributing to future production. Barrick Gold Corporation is actively engaging in transparency by disclosing site-level tailings storage facility (TSF) information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:1098
Chances: Sirius XM (SIRI) experienced improvement in average revenue per user in Q2 2023, despite declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM delivered earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, holding potential clues for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. The Liberty Media tracking stock, which includes Sirius XM, trades at a significant discount to the value of the company&amp;rsquo;s Live Nation Stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:1127
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock has reached a new 52-week low, with charts and indicators indicating a weak setup due to a downward trend. Despite market fluctuations, the value of Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock is being assessed, considering its potential amidst challenges. Moderna&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call revealed a miss on earnings expectations, which could impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:1350
Chances: Disney CEO Bob Iger returned after a short retirement and expressed surprise at the problems discovered at the company, including challenges in the traditional television business and box office disappointments. Investors are eager to assess Disney&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings, focusing on theme park performance, broadcast partnerships for ESPN, and Bob Iger&amp;rsquo;s strategic plans for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</guid>
      <description>score:1131
Chances: Tyson Foods CEO referred to the closures as an &amp;rsquo;efficiency play short term&amp;rsquo;, indicating potential cost-cutting measures. The closure of meat-processing plants is part of Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; efforts to address challenges in its chicken, beef, and pork operations. Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; assessment of beef price increases points to supply issues and herd liquidation, contributing to higher cattle costs and beef prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:960
Chances: Fisker Inc. announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, targeting a popular segment in the U.S. market. The Fisker Alaska pickup truck, priced at $45,400 before incentives, is expected to capitalize on demand for affordable electric trucks. The company&amp;rsquo;s decision to manufacture cars in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:992
Chances: Carvana has reached an agreement to reduce its outstanding debt, indicating a positive step towards improving its financial position. The introduction of same-day delivery in Arizona could enhance customer convenience and potentially drive sales growth. Carvana&amp;rsquo;s strong momentum and revenue growth have contributed to significant gains in its stock price this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:936
Chances: Nokia Corporation has been actively repurchasing its own shares, indicating potential confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Nokia partners with Sanmina Corporation for manufacturing broadband network electronics products, which could lead to job creation and growth. Risks: Market volatility and potential challenges in the telecommunications industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:929
Chances: Exxon Mobil is part of the Zacks top Analyst Blog, indicating positive sentiment. Oil prices experienced a winning streak aided by Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s production cuts. Insiders within Exxon Mobil have been actively buying company shares. Risks: Exxon Mobil&amp;rsquo;s shale assets in Argentina are under review, potentially impacting its future investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:1139
Chances: Shopify is considered to have growth potential alongside other stocks like Visa and Roku. Shopify President, Harley Finkelstein, discusses the company&amp;rsquo;s approach to potential U.S. recession. Shopify posted better-than-expected Q2 revenue and adjusted earnings per share. Despite recent decline, several analysts have raised their price targets for Shopify stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kos/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Kosmos Energy reports positive financial and operating results for Q2 2023, generating net income of $23 million. Successful start-up of Jubilee South East (JSE) project offshore Ghana in partnership with Tullow Oil and others. Adjusted net income and diluted earnings per share figures indicate a favorable financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ELAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/elan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/elan/</guid>
      <description>score:923
Chances: Elanco Animal Health reports strong financial results for Q2 2023 and raises guidance for the full year. Approval of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s Seresto flea and tick collar by the EPA and FDA contributes to stock surge. Elanco releases Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Report highlighting enhanced governance and transparency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Energy Transfer reports strong performance in operations with record volumes, including NGL exports. Ares Capital offers a high dividend yield of nearly 9.7%, attracting investors seeking income. Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s expanded operations in the Permian Basin and strong export volumes likely benefit Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:1083
Chances: Alibaba Cloud releases open-source large language models (LLMs) to expand its influence in generative artificial intelligence. Paytm founder Vijay Shekhar Sharma to acquire a 10.3% stake in Ant Group from Alibaba, becoming the company&amp;rsquo;s largest shareholder. Alibaba introduces licensing requirement for businesses with over 100 million monthly active users to access its large language models (LLMs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> APLS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/apls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/apls/</guid>
      <description>score:964
Chances: Apellis Pharmaceuticals grants equity awards to new employees as part of the company&amp;rsquo;s employment inducement plan. Apellis reports better-than-expected second-quarter 2023 results, with significant growth in net product revenues. SYFOVRE shows promise in reducing GA lesion growth and demonstrates consistent safety profile in clinical studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csx/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: CSX Corporation announces dividend payment of $0.11, indicating a commitment to shareholder returns. CSX partners with SMART-TD to extend conductor training program, focusing on hands-on experience and enhanced skills. Amid industry challenges, CSX remains on investors&amp;rsquo; radar alongside other transportation-rail stocks like CNI and USDP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:953
Chances: RLX Technology&amp;rsquo;s positive quarterly results and stock price increase indicate potential growth and market performance. British American Tobacco, Vector Group, and RLX Technology stand out among their peers for factors such as value, growth, and performance. Shares of RLX Technology rose on the back of encouraging quarterly figures and positive investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:1102
Chances: Grab Holdings&amp;rsquo; upcoming announcement of its unaudited second quarter 2023 results and conference call could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance and strategic outlook. Strategic reorganization and job cuts by Grab Holdings aim to manage costs, achieve affordability, and adapt to the evolving business environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:1298
Chances: Affirm&amp;rsquo;s upcoming publication of its Q4 and fiscal year 2023 shareholder letter, financial results, and conference call may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and strategic outlook. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Cathay Pacific to become its exclusive U.S. pay-over-time partner could open new growth opportunities in the airline industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:1193
Chances: Clarivate&amp;rsquo;s CEO and CFO are scheduled to present at Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo;s technology conference, which could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy and future plans. The release of German hospital prescribing insights within Clarivate Patient Data Intelligence (CPDI) could enhance understanding of market trends and patient characteristics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: Increased political instability contributes to cybersecurity market growth, potentially benefiting companies like Fortinet. Cloud security companies may be better positioned in the cybersecurity market as corporate budgets tighten. Collaboration across sectors and investment in AI-powered security services are important for disrupting cybercrime, potentially benefiting Fortinet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> XPEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</guid>
      <description>score:1055
Chances: The International Energy Agency anticipates a significant increase in electric vehicle (EV) sales, which could positively impact companies like XPeng. Earnings and sales boost for EV stocks driven by growing demand for electric vehicles and charging solutions. China&amp;rsquo;s EV manufacturers, including XPeng, gained ground as Tesla&amp;rsquo;s EV sales in China dropped more than 30%, potentially benefiting domestic competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Microsoft is seeking to patent a &amp;lsquo;high-sensitivity&amp;rsquo; facial recognition technology, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s focus on innovative advancements. Rising corporate spending on digital transformation projects has positively impacted CRM stock, with completed merger synergies from the Slack deal being a key driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:1092
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co announced an underwritten secondary offering of its Class A common stock, indicating potential investor interest and capital infusion. Strong demand for data center equipment, driven by cloud and colocation markets, has contributed to Vertiv&amp;rsquo;s stock rise, with positive full-year earnings guidance updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:1139
Chances: Upstart, a consumer lender using AI for creditworthiness, experienced a significant stock rally, driven by a short squeeze, improving macro environment, AI excitement, and positive earnings report. Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 performance likely benefited from new product additions amid a challenging macro environment and support from funding partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:1054
Chances: Nu Holdings, a Brazilian digital bank backed by Berkshire Hathaway, is focusing on high-yield savings accounts to drive growth in Latin America&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy. Nu Holdings has surpassed 80 million customers in Brazil and expanded operations to Mexico and Colombia, indicating rapid customer acquisition and potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VALE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vale/</guid>
      <description>score:1015
Chances: Vale&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the potential London lawsuit over Brazil&amp;rsquo;s environmental disaster could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s liability and reputation. Vale&amp;rsquo;s earnings call discussed its second-quarter results, providing insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance and outlook. Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s entry into the metal and mining investment landscape, including a stake in Vale&amp;rsquo;s base metals unit, may signal new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s shares are well-positioned for a potential bullish market wave. Uber&amp;rsquo;s solid results and improved profitability could have positive implications for Lyft&amp;rsquo;s performance. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s upcoming second-quarter earnings report could provide insights into its financial performance and competitive positioning. Risks: Lyft faces pressure from the market&amp;rsquo;s reaction to its peer Uber&amp;rsquo;s mixed second-quarter report and profit-taking after a recent strong run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:1071
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson is allowing shareholders to swap for shares of Kenvue, which has brands like Tylenol, at a discount. Dividend stocks like Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (JNJ) are considered a stable investment option, especially for risk-averse investors. Boasting brands like Band-Aid and Benadryl, Kenvue has become the largest pure-play consumer health company, offering potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:1000
Chances: AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results are expected to benefit from robust Admissions, and Food and Beverage revenues. The ongoing success of the movie &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; at the box office could potentially have a lasting financial impact on companies in fashion, entertainment, and home decor industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: Kenvue Inc., the consumer brand spinoff of Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (J&amp;amp;J), reported strong quarterly earnings and beat analyst estimates on both the top and bottom lines, indicating a positive start for the newly public company. Kenvue&amp;rsquo;s forecast for full-year profit above Wall Street estimates, driven by resilient demand for skincare and self-care products, such as Neutrogena and Tylenol, signals confidence in its business outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RLLCF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</guid>
      <description>score:1277
Chances: Rolls-Royce Holdings Plc has seen a notable shift in analyst sentiment, with no analysts recommending selling shares for the first time since 2006, potentially indicating positive sentiment and optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The company has shown signs of a turnaround and recovery from the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, with its new CEO&amp;rsquo;s turnaround plan contributing to improved profit and positive market expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sq/</guid>
      <description>score:991
Chances: Square&amp;rsquo;s Cash App and synergies from the Afterpay acquisition are driving optimism among investors, potentially contributing to the company&amp;rsquo;s growth and profitability. Block&amp;rsquo;s strong second-quarter earnings, particularly in its consumer Cash App business, reflect positive momentum and potential value creation for shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PDCE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</guid>
      <description>score:999
Chances: PDC Energy&amp;rsquo;s acquisition by Chevron is set to enhance Chevron&amp;rsquo;s U.S. oil and gas operations, potentially leading to increased growth and profitability for the combined entity. Shareholder approval of Chevron&amp;rsquo;s $7.6 billion deal to acquire PDC Energy signals positive investor sentiment and confidence in the strategic move, reflecting potential value creation in the merged company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Alphabet Inc.&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary Waymo and General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise are seeking approval to expand self-driving car services in San Francisco, presenting growth opportunities in the emerging autonomous vehicle industry. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s (GOOG) return-to-office tactic of offering employees discounts to hotels on the Google campus reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to transition back to in-person work and maintain a collaborative work environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:967
Chances: Gerdau (GGB) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, which could drive the stock higher in the near term. Gerdau (GGB) made it through our &amp;lsquo;Fast-Paced Momentum at a Bargain&amp;rsquo; screen, making it a potential choice for investors looking for stocks with strong recent momentum at reasonable prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:976
Chances: ImmunoGen, Inc. (IMGN) reports encouraging Q2 earnings with positive adoption of its sole-marketed drug Elahere, showing promising growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 financial results included significant positive surprises in both earnings and revenue, indicating a potential upward trend in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> C</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/c/</guid>
      <description>score:997
Chances: Citigroup Inc. (C) is experiencing growth in its Asia family office business, expecting a 25% increase in clients this year, driven by strong demand from wealthy individuals in Singapore and Hong Kong. The bank saw a significant increase in client numbers in 2022, indicating positive momentum in its family office advisory business in the Asian market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RIOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/riot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/riot/</guid>
      <description>score:1054
Chances: Riot Platforms, Inc. (RIOT) is an industry leader in Bitcoin mining and data center hosting, which positions the company to benefit from the continued growth and adoption of cryptocurrencies. Despite recent fluctuations in Bitcoin prices, Riot Platforms and other crypto-adjacent stocks like MicroStrategy and CleanSpark experienced strong performance, demonstrating investor interest and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:942
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s sale of Simon &amp;amp; Schuster to buyout firm KKR for $1.6 billion in an all-cash deal indicates strategic moves to optimize its portfolio and focus on core businesses. Paramount Global-B (PARA) reported second-quarter results that beat Wall Street estimates, showcasing positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:946
Chances: Intel Corporation&amp;rsquo;s decision to open an innovation hub in China to support local technology startups indicates a commitment to growth and innovation despite geopolitical tensions. Shares of Intel have experienced a 35% gain this year, recovering from previous losses and demonstrating positive momentum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:993
Chances: The transition to the green economy and the shift from fossil fuel to renewable energy sources, including hydrogen, presents significant growth opportunities for Plug Power (PLUG). Plug Power&amp;rsquo;s expanding customer base and increased sites with fuel contracts are expected to positively impact its Q2 earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SOVO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</guid>
      <description>score:877
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao&amp;rsquo;s pasta sauces and noosa yogurt, aligns with its strategy to strengthen its grocery business. The $2.7 billion deal for Sovos Brands presents a growth opportunity for Campbell Soup to expand its presence in frozen meals and premium pasta sauce markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:1021
Chances: Shares of AI software company C3.ai (NYSE: AI) experienced a 7% decline after analysts raised concerns about AI stocks being in a potential bubble. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s shift to a consumption-based business model for fiscal 2024 may help lower entry barriers for new customers and quickly strike deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:1188
Chances: Viatris shares advanced after posting better-than-expected Q2 2023 results and announcing planned divestitures, including a new multiple sclerosis treatment in collaboration with Mapi Pharma. Viatris CEO plans $9 billion in divestitures to optimize the company&amp;rsquo;s business lines and products, a third of which is already completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BKI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bki/</guid>
      <description>score:1173
Chances: Black Knight&amp;rsquo;s Data &amp;amp; Analytics division releases August 2023 Mortgage Monitor Report highlighting the heating housing market and rising home prices. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) dismisses federal court case against Intercontinental Exchange&amp;rsquo;s proposed acquisition of Black Knight, clearing the regulatory path for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PBR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Petrobras considers increasing investments in the next five-year plan, possibly by up to 10% over the previous one. The increase may include inflation adjustments and funding for new projects, supporting the company&amp;rsquo;s growth. President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva aims to use Petrobras to drive a green transition and increase investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:1032
Chances: Uber reports a positive operating profit based on accounting principles, signaling a positive performance. Uber&amp;rsquo;s shares are well-positioned to benefit from the market&amp;rsquo;s next bullish wave. Italy&amp;rsquo;s government approves a 20% increase in taxi licenses to address cab shortage and service problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Verizon offers exclusive bundle savings and special offer for NFL Sunday Ticket from YouTube and YouTubeTV. Verizon provides value through myPlan and +play, offering customers a limited-time offer for Netflix&amp;rsquo;s Premium Plan. Verizon and Nokia to showcase 5G innovations, highlighting the power of 5G through dynamic demonstrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:977
Chances: American Airlines explores new narrowbody jet order with Airbus and Boeing amid travel boom. American Airlines considering new jet order with Airbus and Boeing, indicating potential expansion. Over the last year, airlines have been exploring flight subscription models for travelers. American Airlines in talks with Boeing and Airbus for narrowbody aircraft needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:992
Chances: Southwestern Energy reports positive Q2 2023 earnings with lower operating costs and expenses. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show potential positive momentum for Southwestern Energy (SWN). Strong sector performance by Permian Resources, Civitas Resources, and Northern Oil &amp;amp; Gas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:1002
Chances: PayPal launches its own U.S. dollar-backed stablecoin, PYUSD, for payments and transfers. PYPL stock surges on the news of the stablecoin launch in the cryptocurrency market. Introduction of stablecoin by a major fintech firm like PayPal can drive further cryptocurrency adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:1049
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E encourages customers to enroll in an energy incentive program to lower energy costs and support clean energy goals. Sunrun customers share excess solar energy to increase grid resiliency during peak energy consumption. PG&amp;amp;E confirms deal to purchase its headquarters building, expected to close by 2025.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:1058
Chances: Itaú Unibanco releases revised projections for 2023, complying with regulatory requirements. Positive growth in commissions, fees, insurance operations, and acquisitions supporting financials. Approval of interest on capital payment to stockholders by Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors. Potential divestment of operations in Argentina through preliminary negotiations with Banco Macro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:883
Chances: Airlines adapting routes to cater to changing travel preferences between leisure and business travelers. JetBlue and Allegiant Travel&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strong air travel demand. JetBlue partners with Air Serbia for codeshare agreement to expand flight availability. Risks: Dependence on recovery of business travel demand, which has been slower to rebound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ginkgo Bioworks collaborates with Merck to enhance biologic manufacturing. Collaboration between Ginkgo Bioworks and the Government of Panama to develop new biosecurity capabilities in Latin America. Ginkgo Bioworks plans a presentation and Q&amp;amp;A session to review business performance for Q2 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery plans to add live sports to its streaming service Max, potentially launching with MLB playoffs in October. Paramount reported Q2 results beating estimates and announced a $1.62 billion deal with KKR for Simon &amp;amp; Schuster business. Barbie movie grossed $1 billion globally in just 17 days, marking a milestone for director Greta Gerwig and potential changes in film production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:978
Chances: Bank of America announced a corrected dividend amount on the Fixed-to-Floating Rate Non-Cumulative Preferred Stock, Series U, payable on September 1, 2023. Bank of America has raised the yield on a $500 million blue bond for Gabon to attract investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:953
Chances: AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results are expected to benefit from robust Admissions and Food and Beverage revenues. The strong performance of &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; at the box office could have a lasting financial impact on companies in fashion, entertainment, and home decor industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:953
Chances: BioNTech, Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s partner, is still on track with its &amp;lsquo;variant-adapted Covid-19 vaccine&amp;rsquo; despite a drop in sales during the second quarter. Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s CEO is focusing on new drug approvals and deals to drive growth after the pandemic-related boost from Covid-19 vaccine and drug sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Opendoor Technologies reported financial results for Q2 2023, delivering earnings and revenue surprises that exceeded expectations. Despite a challenging housing market, Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s Q2 performance indicated it exceeded the high end of its outlook, demonstrating potential resilience. Opendoor Technologies is a leading e-commerce platform for residential real estate transactions, showcasing its position in the real estate technology market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</guid>
      <description>score:1012
Chances: Carnival&amp;rsquo;s stock has rebounded significantly this year, with gains of 134%, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s recovery from the pandemic-induced downturn. Carnival Corporation announced redemption of senior secured notes, reflecting potential efforts to manage its debt and financial obligations. Cruise vacations have become popular among cost-conscious consumers, but cruise companies like Carnival are signaling price increases as demand rises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:1079
Chances: Marathon Digital Holdings reported mining a record 179 blocks in July 2023 and produced 1,176 BTC, showcasing strong operational performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s increased operational and installed hash rate contributed to its significant Bitcoin production and accumulation. Marathon&amp;rsquo;s strategic joint venture in Abu Dhabi began mining operations and produced 17 BTC in July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:1006
Chances: SoFi Technologies reported strong Q2 2023 results, with a 37% rise in adjusted quarterly revenue year over year, beating estimates. SoFi&amp;rsquo;s impressive performance and growth potential have led to a 37% increase in its stock price in July. The company&amp;rsquo;s positive Q2 report and raised full-year outlook indicate a promising trajectory for its business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:883
Chances: Banco Bradesco SA is partnering with Amazon.com to launch a credit card offering in Brazil, expanding the bank&amp;rsquo;s fintech offerings. The launch of the credit card is expected next week and will be managed by Banco Bradesco, powered by Mastercard. The collaboration with Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:744
Chances: Nvidia (NVDA) is set to report its quarterly results on August 23, and analysts are optimistic about the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The recent positive performance of other tech companies, such as Meta and Google, in terms of online ad spend rates, may indicate positive trends for Nvidia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:759
Chances: Rivian Automotive is experiencing favorable earnings estimate revisions and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season. The International Energy Agency predicts a significant increase in electric vehicle sales, which could benefit companies like Rivian. Risks: Shares of Rivian, along with other EV hopefuls, fell in response to caution sparked by price cuts and competition in the electric vehicle market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:992
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s stock has lagged behind the market over the past decade, but current prices suggest a potential bargain opportunity. AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s historically low churn rate and gains in postpaid mobile subscribers indicate positive growth. The Telecom sector is posting mixed results, presenting both opportunities and challenges for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:870
Chances: Lucid Group reaffirmed its production goals for the year, aiming to produce 10,000 vehicles. Lucid Air, the luxury electric vehicle by Lucid Group, won the 2023 World Luxury Car Award, highlighting its industry recognition. Several companies, including Lucid, are reporting quarterly results, providing insights into the automotive industry and economic conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:885
Chances: NIO achieved a new record-high monthly delivery of vehicles, indicating strong demand and growth in the EV market. The EV market saw a 65% increase in EV sales last year, presenting growth potential for companies like NIO. NIO&amp;rsquo;s strong deliveries and market interest have led to increased trading volume and investor interest in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:880
Chances: Advanced Micro Devices&amp;rsquo; (AMD) MI300 AI chip set is gaining attention and seen as a potential competitor to Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s AI hardware. AI-driven investment has positively impacted Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s stock and could have a similar effect on AMD&amp;rsquo;s stock. Long-term investing in strong businesses like AMD can be life-changing and rewarding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:977
Chances: Amazon reported strong quarterly results, indicating continued consumer spending and potential positive signals for competitors like Walmart and Target. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s physical store operations, including Amazon Fresh, Whole Foods, and Go convenience stores, saw a significant increase in sales. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s plans to launch prototype internet satellites for its Kuiper program could expand its global internet offering from space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AAPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</guid>
      <description>score:963
Chances: Growth in Apple&amp;rsquo;s Services segment is promising, helping to offset slowing Product segment sales. Apple&amp;rsquo;s stock buybacks are seen as good news for Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s Berkshire Hathaway. Despite smartphone demand concerns, Apple is about to unveil the iPhone 15, indicating new product potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s AI platform, launched in April, is gaining traction with over 100 organizations and talks with more than 300 additional companies. Palantir raised its annual revenue forecast and announced a $1 billion stock buyback plan, indicating confidence in its growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Model Y SUV became the world&amp;rsquo;s best-selling car with 267,200 vehicles sold in the first three months of the year. Tesla plans to begin production at its Debrecan, Hungary plant in 2025 and its Munich plant in 2026. EV sales increased by 65% last year, indicating a growing market for electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PBR-A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</guid>
      <description>score:1205
Chances: Petrobras&amp;rsquo; potential increase in investments and capital expenditures in its next five-year business plan reflects a commitment to growth and expansion, supported by President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva&amp;rsquo;s focus on driving a green transition. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to raise the average capacity use of its refineries and break production records for diesel showcases operational efficiency and the ability to adapt to market demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:962
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings report for Q2 2023 and its first profit since Covid are indications of the company&amp;rsquo;s recovery from the pandemic. Investors and traders may consider buying the dip in Norwegian Cruise Line shares following the earnings report, as the company&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown resilience and a robust recovery trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:1032
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s decision to raise $300 million through a public offering of shares could provide a significant influx of cash for the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth. Shares of QuantumScape have experienced a more than 50% increase in the past three months, indicating positive investor sentiment and potential demand for the company&amp;rsquo;s innovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Meta Platforms&amp;rsquo; potential involvement in a fight with Tesla&amp;rsquo;s CEO Elon Musk could attract attention and generate media coverage. The $1 billion stock buyback plan announced by Palantir might indicate a positive move for the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. The call to empower parents and require children to have explicit permission for social media accounts in certain states could benefit platforms like Meta, ensuring compliance and addressing privacy concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:1078
Chances: Transocean&amp;rsquo;s securing of a significant ultra-deepwater drillship contract worth $518 million reflects its ability to strengthen its market position. Total contract drilling revenues of $729 million, compared to $649 million in the first quarter of 2023, indicate a revenue increase and potentially positive business performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:1058
Chances: IonQ&amp;rsquo;s leadership in the quantum computing industry positions the company well to capitalize on the growing demand for advanced computing solutions. The partnership with South Korea&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Science and ICT reflects IonQ&amp;rsquo;s commitment to education and the development of a local quantum ecosystem, potentially expanding its market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Snap Inc. (SNAP) is witnessing a stock rally and positive sentiment driven by the AI craze and better-than-expected earnings reports from top tech companies. The recent rally in the stock market, along with improved sentiment, has contributed to Snap&amp;rsquo;s stock price surge by about 40%, indicating investor optimism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:1031
Chances: Alphabet Inc. is seeking regulatory approval to expand self-driving car services in San Francisco, indicating potential growth in this emerging market. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s strategic move to offer employee discounts to hotels on the Google campus as part of its return-to-office tactic could encourage employees to return to the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:919
Chances: DraftKings&amp;rsquo; stock has nearly tripled from its December lows, driven by better-than-hoped financials, including a surprising profit last quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s revenue outlook for the second quarter has been hoisted for the second time in a row, indicating strong growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:935
Chances: Ford is adjusting its EV production targets and positioning itself as a long-term winner in the industry. Ford&amp;rsquo;s higher dividend yield of over 4.6% could make it an appealing dividend stock for investors. Ford beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue and earnings, showing strong performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:1194
Chances: Aramark is introducing innovative ordering technologies and food concepts for college campuses, aiming to engage and ground students through dining programs tailored to industry and campus-specific data. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnership with BLK &amp;amp; Bold, the first Black-owned nationally distributed coffee brand, expands its coffee offerings to Aramark Refreshments clients, potentially boosting revenue and customer engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:1009
Chances: Under Armour is launching the &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, aiming to enhance customer connections and drive brand loyalty. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic focus on innovation and loyalty programs could contribute to improved customer engagement and growth. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s Protect This House 3 (PTH3) strategy aims to drive consistent profitable growth and elevate brand heat globally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TEVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teva/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teva/</guid>
      <description>score:969
Chances: Teva has reached an agreement to settle claims with U.S. hospitals, agreeing to pay up to $126 million over 18 years and provide anti-overdose drug naloxone. TEVA&amp;rsquo;s strong second-quarter results beat estimates for both earnings and sales, indicating positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:1093
Chances: Aurora Innovation announced positive First Half 2023 results with a narrowed net loss of US$414.0 million. The company is scheduled to present at the Canaccord Genuity 43rd Annual Growth Conference, indicating efforts to engage with investors. Aurora&amp;rsquo;s second quarter 2023 results have been released, and its shareholder letter and financial results are available for review on its investor relations website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1114
Chances: Unity Software reported strong Q2 2023 results with an 11% year-over-year revenue increase to $533 million, exceeding analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations by $16 million. The company&amp;rsquo;s Unity Wētā Tools division aims to reshape the digital entertainment landscape and provide solutions for artists to collaborate and create 2D and 3D content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:1066
Chances: Marathon Oil reported positive earnings surprises in the second quarter, with net income of $287 million and adjusted net income of $295 million. The company&amp;rsquo;s solid production profile could have contributed to somewhat favorable Q2 results despite lower commodity realizations and higher costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1014
Chances: Truist Financial Corporation is set to pay a dividend of $0.52 per share, indicating a potential income opportunity for investors. Truist Ventures led an $18 million Series A funding round for GoTab, showcasing potential strategic investments and partnerships. Truist Foundation&amp;rsquo;s grant of $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Luminar&amp;rsquo;s announcement of new key executives joining the company suggests a potential positive impact on its leadership and strategic direction. Autonomous driving stocks are expected to experience significant growth over the next decade, indicating a potential market opportunity for Luminar. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading global automotive technology company may position it well to benefit from the growth in autonomous driving and AI advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:940
Chances: Robinhood posted a net profit of $25 million in the second quarter, a significant improvement from a net loss of $511 million a year earlier, indicating potential for improved financial performance. Despite challenges, Robinhood&amp;rsquo;s financial results suggest it may have passed its cyclical trough and is moving towards profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Micron Technology is expanding its CXL ecosystem by offering sample availability of the Micron CZ120 memory expansion modules, which could contribute to revenue growth. The CZ120 modules&amp;rsquo; high capacities and memory read/write bandwidth could position Micron to meet the increasing demand for advanced memory solutions in data-intensive applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
