<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Us on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Us on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Ranking by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</guid>
      <description>I use ChatGPT to analyze and rank most active us stocks:
NCLH (Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings Ltd.) WFC (Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company) FCX (Freeport-McMoRan Inc.) CLVT (Clarivate Plc) NYCB (New York Community Bancorp, Inc.) SQ (Block, Inc.) U (Unity Software Inc.) PDD (PDD Holdings Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Outstanding operational execution and production beat. Positive stock performance with a significant 11% increase. Increase in production guidance for 2023. Projected fair value analysis indicating potential. Retirement of two Executive Officers in the company. Risks: Uncertainty due to conflicting market indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BKR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Rallying energy stocks providing opportunities. Exploring intrinsic value through proprietary analysis. Collaboration for development of microgrid solutions. Positive impact of increased quarterly cash dividend. Rising activity levels contributing to earnings growth. Risks: Market volatility affecting energy stocks. Complex energy market and macro environment challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: Recent major moves indicate company activity. Appeal against the unusual court order shows determination. Interest from public due to pricing changes. In-depth analysis of financial health available. Strategic decisions affecting pricing changes. Risks: Legal challenges and controversy affecting reputation. Negative impact of court orders on company operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Quality dividend stock with potential for growth when down. Positive earnings surprise and beats earnings expectations. Interest from insiders buying the stock. Diverse offerings catering to dividends or explosive growth. Strong performance in the reliable healthcare sector. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: Solid earnings estimate revisions indicate potential for share price growth. Stock included in Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) growth stocks list. Positive momentum for stocks with recent bullish run. Strategic acquisitions expanding the business and contributing to revenues. Management&amp;rsquo;s positive guidance and strong year for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Aramark recognized as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Companies for Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion&amp;rsquo; Positive movement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating. Strong performance in Q3 2023 results. Upcoming spin-off of Aramark Uniform Services (AUS) as an independent public company. Dividend payment announcement for August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: NextEra Energy owns the largest renewables business in the U.S. Positive opportunity presented by the stock&amp;rsquo;s selloff. Expected gains from ongoing capital investments and acquisitions. Dividend income potential from utility stocks for retirees. Strategic plans for strengthening transmission and distribution network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: U.S. Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s removal of obstacles for completing the Mountain Valley Pipeline project. Expected completion of the Mountain Valley Pipeline project by the end of 2023. Positive Q2 2023 financial results with earnings and revenue surprises. Ratification of federal approvals for the pipeline project by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Approval of Jemperli for new frontline treatment in endometrial cancer. Initiation of separation of consumer healthcare business as part of restructuring plan. Positive Q2 2023 financial results with revenue increase. Growth potential from successful drugs in the pharmaceutical sector. Innovation focus through the use of AI and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Announcement of Oracle Compute Cloud@Customer for flexible cloud infrastructure. Oracle selected by Salam for driving 5G innovation in the Middle East. Positive outlook for technology and Oracle&amp;rsquo;s role in it. Expansion of Oracle Cloud services for Australian Government and Defense. Consistent growth and innovation focus highlighted in news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: Appointment of Monique Oxender as Interim Chief Corporate Affairs Officer. Positive Q2 2023 results with increases in sales and earnings. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Rising average price of Keurig Dr Pepper&amp;rsquo;s soda in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: Encouragement for homeowners and contractors to call 811 for utility line marking. Dividend payment of $0.6675 scheduled for September 20. Second-quarter earnings per share better than guidance due to lower operating expenses. Coastal Virginia Offshore Wind project on budget and track for completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:-94
Chances: Revenues and earnings beat in first-quarter fiscal 2024. Direct-to-consumer revenues rose 4% in the quarter. Exploration of potential wholesale partnerships in various retail channels. Positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Launch of &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program to engage loyal consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iq/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Strong box office performance of films released on iQIYI&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Cinema. Expansion of offline parent-child theme park for IP commercialization. Partnership with PubMatic to maximize revenue through programmatic advertising. Recognition and awards received from industry events, showcasing content quality. Continuous commitment to empowering the Chinese anime industry&amp;rsquo;s growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Crypto lobbying organizations and senators call for the dismissal of SEC lawsuit against Coinbase. Operational turnaround and impressive quarterly results reported by Coinbase. Investment in Rocket Pool&amp;rsquo;s native token RPL, indicating strategic moves. Positive shifts in crypto trading volumes and market dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teva/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Positive impact of new product launches on the Zacks Medical - Generic Drugs industry. Strong second-quarter results with beating estimates for earnings and sales. Prospects for brand name drugs, including migraine drug Ajovy, boosting revenue. Re-taking of the 200-day moving average by Teva stock after beating second-quarter estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AQN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Announcement of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s CEO Arun Banskota&amp;rsquo;s resignation and the appointment of interim CEO Christopher Huskilson. Consideration of the potential sale of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy unit as a strategic move to reduce debt. Discussion of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s dividend declarations and its financial decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:331
Chances: Discussion of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s potential as an e-commerce business compared to Amazon&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory. Upgrading of CPNG shares by TheStreet&amp;rsquo;s Quant Ratings service. Coverage of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and its financial performance. Explanation of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s quarterly profit streak and factors contributing to improved margins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Analysis of eBay&amp;rsquo;s intrinsic value using GuruFocus&amp;rsquo; valuation method. Discovery of alarms failing to detect deadly gas, raising safety concerns. Exploration of the thrift store experience and its impact on consumer sentiment. Examination of self-made female billionaires under 50, including their business success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Announcement of significant milestone in developing solar-driven cement production technology. Double-digit price hikes and strong peso contributing to a slight rise in second-quarter net profit. Positive growth in revenue, up by 13% in the second quarter. Cemex&amp;rsquo;s focus on scaling technology for solar-driven cement production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/smci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/smci/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Consistent profitability reflected in the company&amp;rsquo;s Profitability Rank of 9 out of 10. Impressive growth in terms of revenue and profitability with a Growth Rank of 10 out of 10. Benefiting from the demand for AI servers, contributing to growth. Delivery of high-throughput, low latency E3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:-44
Chances: Reported growth in monthly active user (MAU) base, up 8% YoY in Q2. Rebound potential with a return to user growth and focus on building better ad tools. Rise in revenue due to increasing user base, strength in emerging verticals, and AI integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOBY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/joby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/joby/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Release of operational and financial results for the second quarter, showcasing progress. Company&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing all-electric aircraft for commercial passenger service. Submission of Certification Plans to the FAA, marking progress towards aircraft certification. Annual release of Environmental, Social, Governance (ESG) report, highlighting responsible practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Truist Financial announces commitments to support affordable housing and economic mobility programs. Participation in industry conferences to present company&amp;rsquo;s strategies and outlook. Collaborative efforts with MIT Solve for social impact initiatives. Investment in hospitality commerce platform GoTab signals innovation and expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:101
Chances: RLX Technology to report unaudited financial results for the second quarter, indicating transparency and accountability. Positive market sentiment towards Chinese stocks&amp;rsquo; recovery and potential stimulus. Shares of RLX Technology showing upward movement. Notable performance metrics, such as best value and best performance in comparison to peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: Stronger-than-expected second-quarter earnings indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s financial strength. Positive results from clinical trials and collaborations in the healthcare sector. Rise in revenue and better full-year sales forecast driven by strong Keytruda cancer-drug sales. Expansion of ongoing Phase 1 dose escalation trial for breast cancer vaccine in collaboration with Cleveland Clinic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Strong quarterly results indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to perform well in the healthcare sector. Doximity&amp;rsquo;s leading digital platform for medical professionals positions it well in the telemedicine and healthcare technology industry. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show positive performance and potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: Expansion of EV charging network through joint venture indicates growth potential for BP&amp;rsquo;s Indian operations. BP&amp;rsquo;s consideration of offshore wind farm construction without government assistance shows commitment to renewable energy. Positive outlook for BP&amp;rsquo;s dividend and earnings potential, with a focus on improving profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ubs/</guid>
      <description>score:155
Chances: UBS Group&amp;rsquo;s positive news from the March Credit Suisse bailout led to a breakout and new high in stock price. Voluntary termination of Loss Protection Agreement and Public Liquidity Backstop indicates confidence in the takeover of Credit Suisse. UBS no longer relying on Swiss government assistance shows progress in the absorption of Credit Suisse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:144
Chances: Continued recovery in leisure demand and business transient demand may benefit Q2 earnings. Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is the largest lodging real estate investment trust (REIT) and an S&amp;amp;P 500 company. Investor presentation provides insights into Q2 2023 results. Moderating rates at resorts impacting comparable hotel Revenue Per Available Room (RevPAR) growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Schlumberger has been closely watched by Zacks.com users, indicating interest in the stock. Revenue for Q2 2023 increased by 20% despite a downturn in North America rig counts. Positive signs of breakout as U.S. oil prices rise. Rapidly changing climate creating opportunities in clean energy and related sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Luminar reported Q2 2023 results in line with expectations and maintains full-year financial guidance. Luminar delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with automakers like Polestar and Nissan indicate growth prospects. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s focus on advanced semiconductor capabilities and AI technologies is positioning it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: KE Holdings has shown improved Relative Strength (RS) Rating, indicating positive momentum. The company&amp;rsquo;s membership in the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;1t.org&amp;rsquo; China Action community highlights its commitment to environmental goals. BEKE made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) growth stocks list, showcasing its growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: Charles Schwab announced a scholarship program, demonstrating commitment to talent development. Positive outlook for brokerage stocks like Charles Schwab and Interactive Brokers. Diversified financial services offered by Charles Schwab, including advisory, banking, and brokerage services. Steady performance and returns for portfolio management firms like Broyhill Asset Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:102
Chances: ChargePoint announced it will release its Q2 fiscal year 2024 financial results on September 6, 2023. Significant investment in technology to deliver nearly 100% charging station reliability. Positive outlook for the EV charging landscape in the second half of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:77
Chances: Gap&amp;rsquo;s stock has gained 24% in the past three months. Back-to-school season shopping projected to reach $135 billion, potentially benefiting GPS. Collaboration with LoveShackFancy to create a multi-category capsule collection. Value-priced, everyday clothing brand with recognizable American identity. Risks: Sales from Gap&amp;rsquo;s clothing line are underwhelming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vips/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Vipshop is a leading online discount retailer for brands in China. Strong position in China&amp;rsquo;s competitive e-commerce market. Anticipated release of second quarter 2023 financial results. Risks: Volatility in the stock price due to market movements. Competitive nature of China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: TME&amp;rsquo;s leading position in online music and audio entertainment in China. Announcement of unaudited financial results for the second quarter of 2023. Inclusion in Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) value stocks list. Positive trends in earnings estimates and estimate revisions. Risks: Resignation of Chief Strategy Officer and relevant roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mo/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Altria&amp;rsquo;s consistent cash flow to support dividend payments. Positive Q2 earnings results beating expectations. Steady performance against industry headwinds. Juul Labs seeking fundraising efforts. Risks: Longevity concerns over Altria&amp;rsquo;s cash cow business. Market competition and regulatory challenges for tobacco industry. Potential risks associated with Juul Labs&amp;rsquo; fundraising and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Range of perks and offers from Lloyds&amp;rsquo; student bank accounts. Lloyds&amp;rsquo; reputation and customer trust in banking services. Positive Q2 earnings results beating expectations. Optimistic economic outlook and interest rate predictions. Monitoring of banks&amp;rsquo; performance and loan books by regulators. Risks: Potential impact of rising interest rates on borrowers&amp;rsquo; ability to repay debts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: KeyBank Foundation&amp;rsquo;s charitable donations to support community programs. Positive impact of empowerment programs for youth and young adults. Recognition as a Community Champion by Mile High United Way. Stock price rebound and outperformance in July. Commitment to enhancing banking experience and services for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATVI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/atvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/atvi/</guid>
      <description>score:55
Chances: New release Overwatch 2: Invasion with exciting features and gameplay. Strong performance of ATVI compared to its sector. Positive growth potential from Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s takeover deal. Expansion of Hearthstone® with the latest TITANS expansion. Licensing deals and commitments to improve cloud gaming competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:119
Chances: Higher downstream throughput and better production margins contribute to profit. Positive adjusted funds flow and free funds flow in the second quarter. Planned turnaround and production impacts in May and June due to maintenance. Strong cash generation from operating activities. Improvement in sustainability performance and methane reduction milestone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Earnings ESP. Positive stock price performance, up 17% in the last quarter. Key appointment of Chief Financial Officer, Tim Stone. Leading global platform for the luxury fashion industry. Risks: Vulnerability of stock price to institutions due to large stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: Improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. Cooperating with an investigation into &amp;lsquo;brokerage execution quality&amp;rsquo;. Retail crypto trading volumes potentially shifting to Robinhood. Defeating an appeal by investors over restricting purchases of &amp;lsquo;meme stocks&amp;rsquo;. Risks: Regulatory and legal proceedings faced by the online brokerage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Merging with EchoStar creates a new kind of satellite and wireless data services company. Merger aims to give financial flexibility to build a nationwide wireless network. Share price saw a 10% increase after the merger announcement. Creation of a larger wireless network to compete with AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Increase in revenues due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Operational and financial results in-line with expectations for Q2 2023. Positive outlook for penny stocks, including BTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Investments in low-carbon pilot projects to promote sustainability. Acquisition benefits and commercial discovery in the Sunspear exploitation prospect. Confirmation of investments in low-carbon pilot projects. Positive market outlook with mixed midday trading. Risks: Potential disruptions due to worker strikes at LNG facilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Collaboration with Google Cloud to drive efficiencies and improve employee experiences. Engagement in generative artificial intelligence (gen AI) to enhance innovation. Integration of artificial intelligence, robotics, and automation in operations. Positive outlook on infrastructure projects and auto production to raise demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/umc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/umc/</guid>
      <description>score:77
Chances: Tech stocks in the growth portion of the market are gaining momentum, including UMC. Emerging companies in the semiconductor industry, like UMC, hold growth potential. Focus on meeting customer demand for artificial intelligence (AI) in the semiconductor sector. Resilience of the equities market and potential opportunities for tech stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Fortinet is expanding cybersecurity knowledge and skill sets to address the cybersecurity talent shortage. Discussion of best cybersecurity ETFs and potential opportunities in the cloud security sector. Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s top analyst calls, including upgrades and cybersecurity market trends. Focus on improving cybersecurity strategies to address vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:101
Chances: Infosys unveils its sonic brand identity to reinforce its core identity and brand purpose. Strong demand for cloud, data analytics, IoT, and security products reflected in first-quarter results. Easing odds of a recession in the US and emerging AI revenue potential driving rebound in IT stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:144
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s kicks off the back-to-school season with a wide range of fashion and accessories. The consumer cyclical sector is gaining steam this year. Macy&amp;rsquo;s to report second quarter 2023 sales and earnings results on August 22, 2023. Retailers like Macy&amp;rsquo;s expanding use of &amp;lsquo;breathable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cooling&amp;rsquo; fabrics to boost sales during heat waves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:353
Chances: First Horizon Corp. recognized as one of America&amp;rsquo;s Best Large Employers by Forbes Magazine. Broyhill Asset Management&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 investor letter discussing portfolio performance. Five-year employment agreement announced with CEO Bryan Jordan following a failed acquisition effort by TD Bank. Recognition of First Horizon Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:636
Chances: Increase in Kinross&amp;rsquo; production in Q2 due to higher grades and recoveries at specific locations. Announcement of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and transcript. Renewal of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s normal course issuer bid (NCIB) program. Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s delivery of positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:684
Chances: Announcement of Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; second quarter 2023 financial and operational results. Declaration of a quarterly base and variable cash dividend by Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; Board of Directors. Notice of Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; second quarter 2023 financial and operating results reporting date. Discussion on Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; potential earnings beat based on options market movements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sq/</guid>
      <description>score:1062
Chances: Discussion on Square&amp;rsquo;s Cash App and Afterpay synergies, and potential concerns over Bitcoin and a possible recession. Advice to focus on the longer-term performance of Square stock despite recent performance. Highlighting Block&amp;rsquo;s 2023 second-quarter financials, including its gross profit growth and customer-centric approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:1029
Chances: Discussion about the labor contract negotiations of Ford and General Motors, and their impact on related stocks. Coverage of shopping app Temu&amp;rsquo;s popularity and its implications for Amazon. Highlighting Chinese stocks worth watching or potentially buying, including PDD Holdings. Coverage of online sellers&amp;rsquo; legal battles and competition in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:892
Chances: Share price movement and percentage change in the latest trading sessions. Discussion about volatility as a risk and focusing on avoiding it. Overview of stock market corrections, bear markets, and the performance of major U.S. stock indexes. Observation on Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s stock performance and its recent run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:792
Chances: Announcement of Credo Technology Group Holding&amp;rsquo;s conference call to discuss financial results for the fiscal first quarter. Credo&amp;rsquo;s participation in OCP China Day to showcase its HiWire AEC technology. Discussion about share price drop and potential concerns among shareholders. Earnings and revenue surprises reported for the quarter ended April 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:782
Chances: Affirm Holdings&amp;rsquo; recent stock price movement, closing at $15.52, with a -1.77% change from the previous session. Announcement of Affirm&amp;rsquo;s plan to publish its Q4 and fiscal year 2023 shareholder letter, financial results, and conference call details. Positive improvement in Affirm Holdings&amp;rsquo; Relative Strength (RS) Rating, upgrading from 85 to 92.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Announcement of QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s successful closing of an underwritten public offering, raising $300 million. Discussing the decline in QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s stock price despite gains in Chinese stocks and reasons behind the drop. Reviewing QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s financial position and assessing the risk of running out of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1416
Chances: Discussing Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company&amp;rsquo;s potential as a value investor&amp;rsquo;s pick. Highlighting the company&amp;rsquo;s introduction of a special-purpose credit program to address barriers to homeownership. Advising to focus on Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s long-term future despite past challenges. Noting insider stock sales by Wells Fargo &amp;amp; Company insiders over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:1601
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line (NCL) welcomes the first guests aboard the all-new Norwegian Viva, marking an important milestone. Discussing the inclusion of Carnival, Norwegian Cruise Line, and Gentherm in the Zacks Screen of the Week article. Exploring the strong performance of travel stocks due to consumers&amp;rsquo; confidence in travel despite economic concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:1219
Chances: Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) is investigating a cybersecurity incident affecting its information systems. Reviewing the industry outlook and highlighting Freeport-McMoRan, along with other companies, in the sector. Analyzing the near-term prospects for the Zacks Mining - Non Ferrous industry, considering low metal prices and strong demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:939
Chances: Discussing the impact of higher interest rates on Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s business valuation and the changing outlook. Reviewing Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and the missed earnings expectations. Analyzing the performance of renewable energy stocks, including the impact of interest rates and EV market strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1061
Chances: Discussing the top stock picks of ARK Invest and Unity&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the portfolio. Reviewing Unity&amp;rsquo;s latest quarterly update and evaluating its potential as an AI stock investment. Highlighting the year-over-year improvement in Unity&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results in terms of revenue and earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:1024
Chances: Highlighting the use of Zacks Earnings ESP to find stocks expected to beat quarterly earnings estimates. Discussing Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report and the key expectations. Announcing the scheduled earnings call and unaudited financial results reporting for Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:1065
Chances: Highlighting high-yield dividend stocks with rapid growth, where UWM Holdings ranks as a leading mortgage lender. Announcing the hiring of Michele Celestino as EVP and Head of Commercial and Private Banking, Southeast at Flagstar Bank, N.A., a subsidiary of NYCB. Announcing the successful completion of Flagstar Bank&amp;rsquo;s MortgageTech Accelerator program by fintech graduates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR-A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</guid>
      <description>score:870
Chances: Highlighting insights on Petrobras alongside other companies like Wayfair, UPS, and Six Flags. Clarifying that Petrobras does not intend to turn petrochemical producer Braskem into a government-controlled firm. Noting Petrobras&amp;rsquo; major shareholder status in Braskem and its contractual rights in case of a potential sale by Novonor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:935
Chances: Highlighting AGNC Investment Corp. as one of the best monthly dividend stocks to buy according to analysts. Exploring high-yield dividend stocks with an average yield of almost 11.1% and their potential for consistent income. Announcing AGNC&amp;rsquo;s declaration of a cash dividend of $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:1065
Chances: Highlighting the launch of Clarivate&amp;rsquo;s enhanced search platform using generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) and its potential impact on the Life Sciences &amp;amp; Healthcare sector. Announcing Clarivate&amp;rsquo;s participation in Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo;s Technology, Internet &amp;amp; Communications Conference and presenting opportunities for insights and networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:618
Chances: Discussing the top 11 stock picks of ARK Invest and mentioning Shopify as one of the key holdings. Highlighting the movement in the options market for Shopify and its significance for investors. Providing insights into Shopify&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value and its potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:274
Chances: Comparisons of Ambev with other stocks like DEO and CABGY in terms of value could highlight its investment potential. Tracking Ambev&amp;rsquo;s performance compared to Beyond Meat and other stocks within the sector provides insights into its relative strength. Exploring dividend penny stocks and identifying Ambev as a potential candidate for investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sirius XM&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results reflect improvement in average revenue per user amid declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which could provide insights into the stock&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend payment announcement and trading at a specific price level could attract investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:72
Chances: AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s revised stockholder settlement was approved, clearing the way for the company to sell more shares and pay down some of its debt. AMC reported second-quarter results that beat analyst estimates on both the top and bottom lines, with the third quarter off to an &amp;rsquo;explosive start&amp;rsquo; due to strong movie performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:178
Chances: Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, which could drive the stock higher in the near term. Stocks like GGB are attracting investor attention due to their higher dividend yields compared to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown a significant 39% increase in the last quarter, which could attract investor attention. Some S&amp;amp;P 500 constituents, including U.S. Bancorp, have experienced double-digit gains, indicating potential positive sentiment. Eli Lilly&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings and guidance, along with Moody&amp;rsquo;s consideration of credit ratings, might impact U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:-115
Chances: Huntington Bancshares Incorporated&amp;rsquo;s investors are due to receive a dividend payment per share, which could attract investors looking for income. Huntington Bancshares beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit, earning more from rising interest rates and experiencing strong demand for commercial loans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-191
Chances: V.F. Corporation (VFC) reported a daily gain of 3.78% with positive Earnings Per Share (EPS) results, indicating potential growth. VF Corporation beats earnings expectations, with reported EPS exceeding expectations in the first quarter of fiscal year 2024. Although V.F. (VFC) delivered lower-than-expected earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, the company&amp;rsquo;s performance might be worth considering compared to the year-ago numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Nvidia is reportedly receiving a significant number of orders for its AI chips from top Chinese tech giants, indicating potential growth in demand for TSM&amp;rsquo;s semiconductor manufacturing services. Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM) is making investments in the U.S., showing its commitment to expanding its operations and potentially gaining from the growth of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Barrick Gold beat earnings estimates in Q2 due to higher average realized price of gold, indicating positive financial performance. The company maintained its full-year production outlook for gold and copper, indicating stable operational performance and growth potential. Risks: Barrick Gold CEO Mark Bristow stated the company won&amp;rsquo;t be pressured into major acquisitions, potentially affecting its competitive position and growth strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csx/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: CSX Corp. is addressing the Deutsche Bank 2023 Transportation Conference, indicating active participation in industry events and potential positive financial outlook. CSX is partnering with the International Association of Sheet Metal, Air, Rail and Transportation Workers to extend its conductor training program, which could enhance employee skills and operational efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Marvell Technology is outlining its strategy for optimizing storage and memory technologies for AI and data-intensive cloud workloads, indicating a focus on innovation and technology advancement. Investors looking for relatively cheap AI stocks may consider Marvell Technology, suggesting potential value and growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:-60
Chances: The company is moving into a new brick-and-beam office building, which could signify expansion and growth. Toast is launching new products like Toast Catering &amp;amp; Events, indicating innovation and potential revenue growth. Risks: Toast reported lower-than-expected earnings and revenue for the second quarter, which might affect investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stla/</guid>
      <description>score:-61
Chances: Stellantis&amp;rsquo; collaboration with Boeing and Wisk on autonomous technology could indicate innovation and growth potential. The release of a special edition Jeep Gladiator Rubicon FarOut edition could attract consumer interest and drive sales. Risks: Growing tensions between Stellantis and the United Auto Workers (UAW) could lead to disruptions, such as strikes, affecting the company&amp;rsquo;s operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:-83
Chances: Marathon Oil&amp;rsquo;s positive adjusted free cash flow and strong net operating cash flow could signal financial stability. Beating earnings and revenue surprises for the second quarter might boost investor confidence. The declaration of a dividend and consistent net income performance could attract dividend-focused investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Li Auto&amp;rsquo;s strong delivery outlook and aim to outsell premium car brands in China by 2024 could boost investor confidence. Significant revenue growth in the second quarter and positive earnings performance could contribute to stock growth. Launch of Li Auto&amp;rsquo;s first pure battery electric model &amp;lsquo;MEGA&amp;rsquo; and its expected popularity could drive sales and market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Nu Holdings&amp;rsquo; expected increase in second-quarter 2023 revenues could positively impact the stock. Partnership with Hopper to power Nubank&amp;rsquo;s travel portal could lead to growth in customer engagement. Surpassing 80 million customers in Brazil and Latin America indicates strong customer base expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: HPE&amp;rsquo;s expanding services with cloud-native infrastructure and improved performance could lead to positive growth. Strong financial results and exceeding Wall Street estimates could boost investor confidence. Transition plan for CFO Tarek Robbiati stepping down could bring new leadership and opportunities. Risks: Departure of CFO Tarek Robbiati could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial management and stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:118
Chances: Comcast&amp;rsquo;s broadband network&amp;rsquo;s importance to future technology could positively impact its stock. Growing demand for high-speed Internet and increased media consumption benefiting CMCSA. Comcast offering fast, reliable, and affordable internet for back-to-school needs could attract more customers. Partnerships and expansions in the entertainment industry, such as new film studios, could enhance Comcast&amp;rsquo;s market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: Barclays&amp;rsquo; appointment of James Edmonds as Global Head of Sustainable Project Finance demonstrates commitment to sustainability. Europe&amp;rsquo;s biggest banks announcing new share buybacks worth $5 billion could benefit Barclays&amp;rsquo; market position. Barclays&amp;rsquo; dividend payment announcement reflects its commitment to shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: PayPal&amp;rsquo;s launch of its own stablecoin PYUSD could drive mass consumer adoption of cryptocurrencies. PayPal&amp;rsquo;s strong track record and market presence position it as a leader in digital payments. Positive sentiment towards PayPal&amp;rsquo;s success despite challenges in the financial services sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: JetBlue launched its annual fall promotion offering attractive deals on flights from New York. Upbeat air travel demand scenario and Q2 results benefit JetBlue and the industry. Growing leisure-oriented flights strategy in response to changing travel trends. Cheap flight deals and promotions could attract more travelers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mq/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Marqeta renewed its contract with Block to power its Cash App debit card for another four years. Shares of Marqeta soared after announcing the contract renewal with Block. Positive Q2 earnings report and extension of key contract could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery announced successful completion of cash tender offers. Warner Bros. Discovery is adding live sports to its streaming service, which could attract more subscribers. Blockbuster film &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; achieved impressive box office earnings within a short period. Paramount&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings results might indicate potential growth for Warner Bros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enb/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Enbridge has a history of paying dividends and steady growth. Enbridge generated positive distributable cash flow in the second quarter. Enbridge&amp;rsquo;s natural gas distribution business serves millions of customers. Enbridge reported higher profit in the second quarter due to increased oil volumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:129
Chances: Carvana&amp;rsquo;s impressive revival from near bankruptcy has captured attention. Carvana raised its profit outlook, indicating momentum from an early-year turnaround. Positive update on future profits, with expected gross profit per unit and adjusted EBITDA above expectations. An analyst hiked the price target for Carvana&amp;rsquo;s shares due to the optimistic profit outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Cisco&amp;rsquo;s stock has been moving higher and On-Balance-Volume (OBV) line suggests aggressive buying. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s earnings report next week is expected to beat peers Arista and Juniper, according to Citi. Juniper Networks CEO highlights growth driven by AI innovation and differentiation in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Roblox&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results reflect top-line growth and increased daily active users. Analysts upgraded Roblox stock on improved risk-reward prospects. Despite disappointing Q2 earnings, some analysts see buying opportunities. Risks: Roblox delivered weaker-than-expected quarterly bookings growth. Roblox stock crashed after the Q2 earnings miss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:106
Chances: Exxon Mobil received a $77 million award from the World Bank arbitration court. Energy sector insider buying signals positive sentiment for energy stocks. Exxon Mobil&amp;rsquo;s success against Engine No. 1 in a proxy battle gained attention. Engine No. 1 is eyeing more deals in critical minerals, potentially impacting Exxon Mobil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Peloton will release its fourth quarter and full-year fiscal 2023 results. Peloton stock rose 26.3% last month, driven by bullish sentiment and favorable macroeconomic data. Retail investors&amp;rsquo; renewed interest in meme stocks is bringing attention to Peloton. Risks: Peloton remains far from being profitable and has severe fundamental weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:50
Chances: Verizon is contributing $100,000 to the Hawai`i Community Foundation in support of the Maui Strong Fund. Verizon Business forms a global strategic partnership with HCLTech for managed network services. High-dividend stocks under $10 are discussed, with Verizon being mentioned as a high-dividend stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: Meta Platforms, formerly known as Facebook, is a prominent tech company in the social media industry. Meta&amp;rsquo;s new microblogging platform, Threads, gained more than 100 million sign-ups. Highlighted as a top-rated AI stock to watch in the technology sector. Risks: Public conflict and ongoing feud between Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg and Tesla CEO Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Lufax Holding is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China. Lufax reported unaudited financial results for Q1 2023 with positive earnings and revenue surprises. Change in non-executive director and appointments within the company&amp;rsquo;s board. Risks: Lufax reported an 86% YoY decline in profit for Q1 2023 due to China&amp;rsquo;s lackluster economic recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary Waymo and GM&amp;rsquo;s Cruise received regulatory approval for expanding driverless robotaxi services. GOOG&amp;rsquo;s positive cash flow generation and potential spending opportunities. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s stock still within a buy zone after a recent breakout. Risks: Tech companies cutting spending on the future may impact GOOG&amp;rsquo;s long-term growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Positive economic data bullish for housing sector, potentially benefiting Opendoor. Projected fair value suggests potential positive outlook for Opendoor. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Risks: Opendoor misses earnings expectations and provides disappointing financial guidance. Decline in Apple sales and lower financial performance guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XPEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</guid>
      <description>score:78
Chances: Chinese EV market maturing, investors evaluating earnings for shares. Demand for electric vehicles and charging solutions contributing to earnings and sales boost. Domestic EV manufacturers in China like BYD, Nio, and Xpeng gaining ground. Increasing interest in electric vehicles, battery technology, and autonomous driving ETFs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-24
Chances: JD.com&amp;rsquo;s stock has had a significant 19% run-up over the last month. Projected fair value for JD.com is $63.64 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. Global AI market growth potentially benefiting AI-driven companies like JD.com. JD.com is a leading supply chain-based technology and service provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Strong earnings and revenue beat ratios for the healthcare sector. Attractive dividend yield of 4.7%, making it appealing for income-seeking investors. Global presence and strong fundamentals of Pfizer as a pharmaceutical heavyweight. Risks: Challenges related to declining sales of Covid products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</guid>
      <description>score:-55
Chances: Tapestry&amp;rsquo;s strong portfolio consisting of Coach, Kate Spade, and Stuart Weitzman brands. Positive earnings surprise history and favorable ingredients for potential quarterly beat. Risks: Integration challenges and execution risks associated with the acquisition of Capri Holdings. Mixed response from Wall Street and the industry to the acquisition deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Higher rates and expectations of reduced delinquency rates in Brazil&amp;rsquo;s banking industry could benefit Itaú Unibanco (ITUB). Growth in commissions, fees, insurance operations, and strategic acquisitions support Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s financials. Revised projections for 2023 and dividend payments indicate management&amp;rsquo;s commitment to shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Snap&amp;rsquo;s evolution into an augmented reality company indicates a strategic shift that could attract content creators and advertisers. The availability of dark mode for all users without requiring a subscription could enhance user engagement and satisfaction. Snap&amp;rsquo;s focus on revenue acceleration through evolving strategies and addressing key areas could lead to positive outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Nokia&amp;rsquo;s recent repurchase of its own shares indicates the company&amp;rsquo;s confidence in its financial position and potential future growth. The transfer of Nokia shares to participants of equity-based incentive plans aligns with the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to rewarding employees and aligning their interests with shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-57
Chances: Despite the recent stock price decline, Upstart&amp;rsquo;s long-term growth potential remains promising due to its AI-powered lending marketplace. Upstart generated revenue growth, reaching $136 million in the last quarter, indicating its ability to generate strong sales in its niche. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance in the second quarter was better than feared, with better-than-expected Q2 results and revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APLS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/apls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/apls/</guid>
      <description>score:-69
Chances: Apellis Pharmaceuticals reported better-than-expected second-quarter 2023 results, indicating strong performance in its financials. Positive data on SYFOVRE&amp;rsquo;s reduction of nonsubfoveal GA lesion growth could reflect the potential effectiveness of Apellis&amp;rsquo; products. Equity awards granted to new employees could attract and incentivize talented individuals to join the company, contributing to its growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:124
Chances: Uber&amp;rsquo;s partnership with grocery chain Hy-Vee to offer on-demand and scheduled grocery delivery could enhance the convenience and attractiveness of Uber Eats&amp;rsquo; services, potentially increasing customer engagement and revenue. The Indian government&amp;rsquo;s plan to roll out welfare measures for gig workers employed through platforms like Uber could improve the social and financial well-being of workers, potentially leading to positive sentiment and improved relationships with the government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDCE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Chevron&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PDC Energy and the approval from shareholders could bolster Chevron&amp;rsquo;s U.S. oil and gas operations, potentially leading to increased operational efficiency and growth opportunities. Despite the all-stock transaction and expected transitional leadership changes, the successful closure of the deal between Chevron and PDC Energy may result in a strengthened combined entity with enhanced market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:102
Chances: American Airlines&amp;rsquo; efforts to reduce aviation&amp;rsquo;s environmental impact through contrail avoidance, as verified by satellite imagery, could enhance its environmental reputation and sustainability practices. The improvement in American Airlines&amp;rsquo; stock price performance and its IBD Relative Strength Rating upgrade suggest positive market sentiment and potential for further growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Grab&amp;rsquo;s strategic reorganization involving job cuts and cost management aims to sustainably offer more affordable services and penetrate the masses, reflecting its focus on long-term growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s unaudited financial results and its annual report filings suggest transparency and accountability in its operations, which could enhance investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Waymo and General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise receiving regulatory approval to expand their robotaxi services for driverless ride-hailing services 24/7 across San Francisco suggests growth potential in autonomous transportation. Google parent Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s robust cash generation of nearly $29 billion in the second quarter could provide opportunities for strategic investments and innovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:87
Chances: Occidental Petroleum receiving hundreds of millions of dollars in grants for a carbon capture project from the U.S. Department of Energy indicates potential growth opportunities in the energy transition sector. Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s significant ownership of Occidental Petroleum&amp;rsquo;s shares, approximately 25%, showcases confidence from a prominent investor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PENN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/penn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/penn/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Penn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s partnership with ESPN for the launch of ESPN Bet indicates a significant investment and potential growth in the sports betting market. The $2 billion deal with Penn Entertainment to launch ESPN Bet showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to diversify and capitalize on the growing sports betting industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/riot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/riot/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Riot reported a new all-time record hash rate capacity of 10.7 EH/s, strong revenue of $76.7 million, and an expanded execution of power strategy, which suggests positive growth potential. Bitcoin production and operations updates for July 2023 show Riot&amp;rsquo;s continued commitment to expanding its Bitcoin mining capabilities and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:127
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings beating estimates and the positive earnings and revenue surprises suggest favorable operational performance. Strong sector performance by Permian Resources, Civitas Resources, and Northern Oil &amp;amp; Gas could indicate a positive industry trend for Southwestern Energy. Top stocks in August for best value, fastest growth, and most momentum include Theravance Biopharma, Sun Country Airlines Holdings, and Cabaletta Bio, which could reflect potential opportunities for Southwestern Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: Petrobras&amp;rsquo; management indicating that it&amp;rsquo;s not interested in government ownership of Braskem suggests strategic decisions for the petrochemicals producer. Petrobras&amp;rsquo; decision not to sell its stake in Braskem could imply confidence in the long-term prospects of the petrochemical firm. Analysts&amp;rsquo; reports of potential benefits from Airbnb&amp;rsquo;s shift towards alternative accommodations could highlight Petrobras&amp;rsquo; diversification opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E&amp;rsquo;s initiatives for National 811 Day and energy incentive programs highlight its commitment to safety and clean energy goals. Partnerships like the one with Sunrun to share excess solar energy demonstrate efforts to enhance grid resiliency. Beat in adjusted earnings and revenue growth in recent quarters indicate some positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s solid position in the tech industry and consistent performance make it a key blue chip stock to consider. Positive analyst calls and expectations of gains in the Nasdaq index suggest potential growth for Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s stock. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s involvement in cloud computing and artificial intelligence efforts positions it well to capitalize on growing trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: Ginkgo Bioworks&amp;rsquo; collaborations with industry leaders like Merck and Sumitomo Chemical highlight its potential for expanding its biomanufacturing capabilities and advancing synthetic biology. Participation in conferences and panels, such as the UBS MedTech, Tools and Genomics Summit, showcases Ginkgo&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading player in the field of cell programming and biosecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s plans to introduce in-app ads and in-car services could enhance its revenue potential by creating new streams of income and a more personalized experience for users. Partnerships with technology companies like Rokt to offer personalized and relevant offers to riders might attract more engagement and improve user satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-29
Chances: Wayfair&amp;rsquo;s potential gains in sales and profits could indicate a positive trend that might indirectly benefit companies like General Motors. Driverless robotaxi services, including General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise, being granted permission to expand their business could open up new growth opportunities for GM in the autonomous vehicle sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:-172
Chances: Transocean expects adjusted contract drilling revenues of $720 million in Q3 2023, indicating potential revenue growth. Total adjusted contract drilling revenues showed an increase in Q2 2023 compared to the first quarter, which might suggest improving business performance. The global demand for energy presents an opportunity for energy stocks, including Transocean, to capitalize on the need for various energy sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: The popularity of &amp;lsquo;parlays&amp;rsquo; is leading to fatter profits for DraftKings and similar sites, potentially indicating increased revenue. The partnership between DraftKings and ESPN&amp;rsquo;s rebranded sportsbook, ESPN Bet, could provide a new platform for growth and user acquisition. Penn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s $2 billion investment in ESPN Bet and the partnership between ESPN and PENN could have positive implications for DraftKings as the sports betting market evolves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s fiscal third-quarter results were well-received, initially sending shares higher, indicating positive investor sentiment. Efforts to reduce account sharing, following the model of Netflix, could potentially increase Disney&amp;rsquo;s revenue and strengthen its position in the streaming market. The return of the writers union to the bargaining table could lead to positive developments for Disney and other major studios affected by the Hollywood strikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Marathon Digital Holdings reported mining a record number of blocks and producing significant amounts of BTC, indicating strong operational performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s unrestricted cash and Bitcoin holdings have increased, which could potentially provide financial stability and investment opportunities. Undervalued blockchain stocks, including Marathon Digital, have rebounded in line with the resurgence of the cryptocurrency sector, presenting investment potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: Intel is doubling down on R&amp;amp;D for new chip manufacturing facilities, indicating a commitment to innovation and technological advancement. Intel executives participating in webcast events for the investment community suggest a willingness to engage with investors and share insights. The U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: AMC successfully secured court approval for a stock conversion plan, allowing the company to raise capital. The company&amp;rsquo;s marketing efforts are being led by experienced professionals, potentially driving positive brand awareness. AMC reported second-quarter results that beat analyst estimates on both revenue and earnings, with an explosive start to the third quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Alibaba reported solid quarterly results that exceeded top and bottom line expectations, with strong revenue expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance is being compared to Amazon, Meta Platforms, and Microsoft, indicating positive competitive positioning. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s return to growth across all main divisions is a positive sign of a potential comeback after a period of malaise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</guid>
      <description>score:-13
Chances: Carnival has experienced a stunning comeback from cancelled cruises, surpassing previous sales records and achieving growth. Record quarterly bookings and increasing demand have contributed to Carnival&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory. Exclusive partnerships with renowned chefs and new gourmet dining experiences could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s appeal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Lucid Group raised its production guidance for the year after a better-than-expected second quarter. Despite an earnings miss and falling short of EV deliveries, Lucid Group&amp;rsquo;s stock is still seeing positive movement. The unveiling of final production specs for the Lucid Air Sapphire model showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s innovation in electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Plug Power reported record revenue in its second-quarter results, reaffirming its full-year sales estimate. Despite recent losses and challenges, Plug Power remains one of the most hyped hydrogen stocks with potential. The hydrogen technology company has hydrogen production plants in various states, contributing to its revenue drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:252
Chances: SoFi&amp;rsquo;s differentiation in the fintech space through low fees and an extensive suite of digital financial services is resonating with customers. SoFi&amp;rsquo;s strong revenue growth and significant increase in its member base showcase the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for expansion. The positive earnings report and revenue growth have contributed to a more than 100% increase in SOFI stock in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VALE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vale/</guid>
      <description>score:153
Chances: Investment fund Engine No. 1&amp;rsquo;s interest in Vale SA&amp;rsquo;s base metals business suggests potential for strategic deals in critical minerals. Vale&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the mining industry, especially in base metals, positions it for potential growth and partnerships. Vale&amp;rsquo;s earnings call provides insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance during the second quarter, offering investors valuable information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: Rivian reported a narrower-than-anticipated loss in the second quarter and raised its production guidance, indicating positive operational performance. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s production guidance increase to 52,000 vehicles from 50,000 showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet demand and grow. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s stock has experienced a significant rally over the past 90 days, driven by growing demand for its electric pickup and SUV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Medical Properties Trust is a real estate investment trust (REIT) that specializes in hospital properties. Favorable healthcare industry trends and capital recycling efforts could positively impact Medical Properties Trust&amp;rsquo;s earnings. Quarterly dividend payments of $0.29 per share demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to rewarding shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s stock price is currently at its lowest level since the mid-1990s, which may present a buying opportunity. AT&amp;amp;T is a leading wireless carrier in the U.S., with positive developments in its core wireless business. Automatic bill payment and discounts could positively impact customer retention and revenue for AT&amp;amp;T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Bank of America&amp;rsquo;s stock has garnered significant attention, indicating investor interest. Strong influence of institutions due to substantial holdings could impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s direction. Bank of America is considered an attractive dividend stock in the current market. Risks: Moody&amp;rsquo;s downgrade and credit rating reviews for multiple banks, including Bank of America, may affect the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Impressive second-quarter earnings and revenue beat ratios in the healthcare sector highlight positive performance. Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dividend stock could attract investors looking for consistent income. FDA approval for antibody-based therapy Talvey indicates potential for innovation in difficult-to-treat blood cancer treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:68
Chances: Amazon&amp;rsquo;s potential to become a central ID system for various aspects of people&amp;rsquo;s lives could lead to increased customer engagement and loyalty. Strong interest from prominent investors like Baupost Group and Fidelity indicates positive market sentiment and potential growth. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s focus on executing big solutions in large markets and the continued resilience of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Kenvue&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the S&amp;amp;P 500 index could boost its visibility and potentially attract more investors. Strong quarterly earnings and positive outlook signal potential growth and market confidence in Kenvue&amp;rsquo;s business. Spin-off from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and successful IPO indicate a level of independence and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Apple&amp;rsquo;s potential role in central ID systems and expansion into various sectors could drive long-term growth and innovation. Analyst expectations of undervalued blue chip and technology stocks could indicate positive sentiment towards Apple&amp;rsquo;s market performance. Continued focus on Dow Jones and stock market trends may present opportunities for Apple stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: Banco Bradesco&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Amazon.com for launching a credit card offering in Brazil could enhance its fintech and expansion efforts. Positive response from the chief executives of Brazil&amp;rsquo;s largest private lenders, defending the government&amp;rsquo;s planned tax reform, could indicate potential economic opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: IonQ&amp;rsquo;s increased bookings expectations and the expansion of its quantum computer availability indicate potential growth in demand and revenue. Partnerships with entities like South Korea’s Ministry of Science and ICT and QuantumBasel suggest IonQ&amp;rsquo;s efforts to collaborate and promote quantum science and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:91
Chances: NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown remarkable growth, with shares up roughly 180% year to date and the company reaching $1 trillion in market capitalization. Advancements in artificial intelligence have contributed to NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s excitement and growth, positioning the company at the heart of the AI frenzy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s track record of success in AI and data mining positions it well in the current artificial intelligence boom. Despite recent stock price fluctuations, Palantir has achieved adjusted net profitability and GAAP profitability, indicating positive financial performance. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Investment Management&amp;rsquo;s estimation of significant economic gains from AI software could indirectly benefit Palantir&amp;rsquo;s AI-focused activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:112
Chances: NIO&amp;rsquo;s stock hitting an all-time high in the past indicates its potential for significant growth during periods of strong deliveries and investor enthusiasm. NIO&amp;rsquo;s achievement of new record-high monthly deliveries showcases its ability to increase vehicle sales, which could positively impact its stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Booming demand for AI chips could drive AMD&amp;rsquo;s growth in the second half of the year. AMD&amp;rsquo;s technology in the AI space, while not on par with Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s, still holds a strong position and is considered by many clients. AMD&amp;rsquo;s focus on AI technology aligns well with the growing popularity of the AI revolution in the business world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:180
Chances: Ford&amp;rsquo;s Brazilian unit reaching a transfer agreement with the government of Bahia state to transfer ownership of a closed factory complex could lead to potential asset monetization. Interest from Chinese EV manufacturer BYD in the factory complex suggests potential for acquisition, which might bring in revenue for Ford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:-39
Chances: Tesla (TSLA) CEO Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s planned cage fight with Mark Zuckerberg could potentially attract significant attention and media coverage. Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s announcement of an &amp;rsquo;epic location&amp;rsquo; with an ancient Roman theme and potential charity involvement could create a positive image for Tesla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:1294
Chances: Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; Q2 results may show increased megawatts shipment and strong margin performance from STI Norland acquisition. Array Technologies has an impressive earnings surprise history and a favorable combination for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The growth of solar energy and technological advancements create opportunities for solar stocks, including Array Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Nordstrom plans to open a new Nordstrom Rack store in Queen Creek, Arizona, expanding its retail presence. Nordstrom announces the date for reporting its second quarter 2023 financial results and provides an outlook for the year. Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s Relative Strength (RS) Rating improves, indicating improving technical performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UNVR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</guid>
      <description>score:1087
Chances: Univar Solutions has completed an acquisition by Apollo Funds, maintaining its global presence under the Univar Solutions name and brand. The company has expanded its distribution relationship with Kalsec Inc. for hop ingredients in the United States, enhancing its specialty ingredient offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ENPH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enph/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Enphase Energy is strategically expanding its presence in the renewable energy market, particularly in Europe where sales are growing. The global alternative energy market is showing strong growth, offering significant investment opportunities for Enphase Energy. Solar energy is projected to become the largest source of power globally by 2027, providing a favorable outlook for Enphase Energy&amp;rsquo;s solar-based solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CPB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</guid>
      <description>score:910
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao’s pasta sauce and noosa yogurt, aims for strategic growth and expansion. The acquisition of Sovos Brands for $2.7 billion demonstrates Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing its grocery business. Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s deal with Sovos Brands offers a premium to shareholders and has positively impacted its stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:823
Chances: The aerospace industry is recovering, and Chinese airlines&amp;rsquo; need to renew their fleets could present an opportunity for Boeing. The launch of electric vertical takeoff and landing aircraft by companies like Joby and Archer could offer potential upside for Boeing. Positive performance of blue chip stocks, including Boeing, contributed to higher market benchmarks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:724
Chances: Gilead Sciences expects a third of sales to come from its cancer treatments by 2030, driving optimism and stock price movement. Gilead Sciences is focused on developing therapies for life-threatening infectious diseases and expanding its portfolio to include pulmonary, cardiovascular diseases, and cancer treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:1057
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reliable and stable performance makes it an attractive stock for long-term gains. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment model and Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s portfolio receive widespread attention for long-term performance. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s diverse product portfolio includes well-known brands like Coke, Sprite, Dasani water, Costa Coffee, and Minute Maid juices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:986
Chances: Major U.S. airlines request an extension of cuts to minimum flight requirements at congested airports due to air traffic control staffing issues. Flights to Europe have significantly increased, with a 600% rise in Americans traveling to Europe from 2021 to 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:1126
Chances: Under Armour announced the launch of its &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, aiming to strengthen customer connections and brand loyalty. The company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance customer connections, innovations, and a new loyalty program are expected to contribute to brand growth. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s senior executive leadership team changes are aligned with the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to drive consistent profitable growth and returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:1179
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs (NYSE: CLF) reported second-quarter results, showing improved automotive volumes, higher prices, and lower steelmaking unit costs. The company&amp;rsquo;s external sales volumes for steel products increased by around 15.4% year over year in Q2. Cleveland-Cliffs stock price rose by 2.3% over the past week, driven by long-term fundamentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:1044
Chances: SentinelOne (NYSE: S) is helping counteract the increase in cybersecurity threats with its AI technologies. SentinelLabs announced a premier cybersecurity research conference, LABScon 2023. Cybersecurity investment opportunities are significant due to the rising instances of data breaches. Demand for high-performance cybersecurity services is expected to increase as work processes go digital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Pipeline giant Kinder Morgan (NYSE: KMI) is a high-yield dividend stock with a yield of 6.2%. Kinder Morgan has spent the last eight years reviving its image after dividend cut in 2015. Kinder Morgan&amp;rsquo;s ability to secure high-return expansion projects to grow cash flow is a positive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:981
Chances: TAL Education Group share price has gained 56% in the last period. TAL Education Group announces unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. TAL Education Group to release unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. Chinese hedge funds add TAL Education Group to their portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Ukraine reports significant results from U.S. Patriot and German IRIS-T defense systems against attacks by Russia. RTX faces quality and durability concerns with its single-aisle jetliner bet in the aerospace and defense sector. RTX beats Q2 earnings estimates with organic sales growth of 12% year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:1030
Chances: Kraft Heinz reports sales growth in North America and International regions due to solid pricing. Earnings season impact on Kraft Heinz&amp;rsquo;s sales and demand from cost-conscious consumers. Positive outlook for the economy and economic performance. Continued focus on pricing strategy and maintaining higher prices for products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s support for new iPhone models suggests improved chip volumes for the current quarter. Positive results from tech giants&amp;rsquo; quarterly reports despite some being muted. Formation of a new company by chipmakers, including Qualcomm, to develop RISC-V technology. Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s daily gain and EPS performance raise questions about its valuation and potential for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Regions Bank introduces digital solutions for business clients to manage billing and communications. Appointment of Alison Rand to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Bank increases prime lending rate to 8.50%. Enhancement of Treasury Management suite of products and services to meet customer needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</guid>
      <description>score:1237
Chances: Envista announces successful pricing of $435 million Convertible Senior Notes offering. Consistent growth in Specialty Products &amp;amp; Technologies and Equipment &amp;amp; Consumables segments drive Q2 revenues. Envista delivers positive Q2 2023 earnings and revenue surprises. Envista Smile Project completes mission trip to the Dominican Republic, providing dental care to underserved patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:1269
Chances: Formation of strategic partnership between WaterBridge NDB and Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary, yielding the largest private water infrastructure. Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend reduction due to weaker oil and gas prices. Discussion on investing in the energy sector for income stocks. Analysis of Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend cut and its impact on passive income investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:1182
Chances: Gen Digital experiences a gain with positive Earnings Per Share (EPS). Gen Digital offers cybersecurity solutions, identity protection, and privacy solutions. Gen Digital&amp;rsquo;s Q1 results show strong customer growth, global expansion benefits, and Avast acquisition impact. Gen Digital releases its fiscal year 2024 first-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:1400
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s Relative Strength (RS) Rating has been upgraded, indicating potential for significant gains. The projected fair value for Datadog is estimated at $129 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. Datadog continues to experience steady adoption of its cloud-based monitoring and introduces new capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Intel to create a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s technological capabilities and competitiveness. Cradlepoint&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Ericsson in modernizing network infrastructure for Los Angeles County showcases Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s involvement in innovative and impactful projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JPM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</guid>
      <description>score:818
Chances: JPMorgan Chase is expanding its presence and innovation efforts in India with the opening of two state-of-the-art facilities, enhancing service excellence and efficiency. JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s Advancing Black Wealth Tour aims to deliver financial education, workshops, and wealth-building seminars to Black communities, contributing to financial empowerment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Monster Beverage Corporation reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1% to $1.85 billion, driven by gains in brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions. Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to reflect gains from continued strength in the energy drinks category and robust product innovation plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:972
Chances: Bristol Myers Squibb has a history of consistently paying dividends for the last 90 years. Pharmaceutical company AbbVie reports better-than-expected Q2 sales for its arthritis medication Humira. Discounted blue-chip stocks with potential upside may offer investment opportunities in a market with some lagging stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</guid>
      <description>score:957
Chances: Boston Scientific&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings saw organic and operational revenue growth in core business segments and geographies. Continued strength in BD&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences segment&amp;rsquo;s base business is expected to benefit Q3 sales. Boston Scientific stock rose as hospital procedures stabilized after the Covid pandemic, contributing to a 20% rise in earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Cybersecurity ETFs are discussed as potential investments in the growing cybersecurity market. Palo Alto Networks announced the release of its fiscal fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. Strong potential is identified in Internet software stocks like PANW for the rest of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FLR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flr/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Fluor Corporation successfully priced $500 million aggregate principal amount of Convertible Senior Notes due 2029. Fluor reported outstanding financial results, leading to a significant rating upgrade and positive market sentiment. Fluor announced its intention to offer Convertible Senior Notes due 2029, potentially raising capital for future operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:1127
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock has reached a new 52-week low, with charts and indicators indicating a weak setup due to a downward trend. Despite market fluctuations, the value of Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock is being assessed, considering its potential amidst challenges. Moderna&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call revealed a miss on earnings expectations, which could impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</guid>
      <description>score:1131
Chances: Tyson Foods CEO referred to the closures as an &amp;rsquo;efficiency play short term&amp;rsquo;, indicating potential cost-cutting measures. The closure of meat-processing plants is part of Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; efforts to address challenges in its chicken, beef, and pork operations. Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; assessment of beef price increases points to supply issues and herd liquidation, contributing to higher cattle costs and beef prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:960
Chances: Fisker Inc. announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, targeting a popular segment in the U.S. market. The Fisker Alaska pickup truck, priced at $45,400 before incentives, is expected to capitalize on demand for affordable electric trucks. The company&amp;rsquo;s decision to manufacture cars in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kos/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Kosmos Energy reports positive financial and operating results for Q2 2023, generating net income of $23 million. Successful start-up of Jubilee South East (JSE) project offshore Ghana in partnership with Tullow Oil and others. Adjusted net income and diluted earnings per share figures indicate a favorable financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ELAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/elan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/elan/</guid>
      <description>score:923
Chances: Elanco Animal Health reports strong financial results for Q2 2023 and raises guidance for the full year. Approval of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s Seresto flea and tick collar by the EPA and FDA contributes to stock surge. Elanco releases Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Report highlighting enhanced governance and transparency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Energy Transfer reports strong performance in operations with record volumes, including NGL exports. Ares Capital offers a high dividend yield of nearly 9.7%, attracting investors seeking income. Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s expanded operations in the Permian Basin and strong export volumes likely benefit Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RLLCF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</guid>
      <description>score:1277
Chances: Rolls-Royce Holdings Plc has seen a notable shift in analyst sentiment, with no analysts recommending selling shares for the first time since 2006, potentially indicating positive sentiment and optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The company has shown signs of a turnaround and recovery from the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, with its new CEO&amp;rsquo;s turnaround plan contributing to improved profit and positive market expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:976
Chances: ImmunoGen, Inc. (IMGN) reports encouraging Q2 earnings with positive adoption of its sole-marketed drug Elahere, showing promising growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 financial results included significant positive surprises in both earnings and revenue, indicating a potential upward trend in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> C</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/c/</guid>
      <description>score:997
Chances: Citigroup Inc. (C) is experiencing growth in its Asia family office business, expecting a 25% increase in clients this year, driven by strong demand from wealthy individuals in Singapore and Hong Kong. The bank saw a significant increase in client numbers in 2022, indicating positive momentum in its family office advisory business in the Asian market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:942
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s sale of Simon &amp;amp; Schuster to buyout firm KKR for $1.6 billion in an all-cash deal indicates strategic moves to optimize its portfolio and focus on core businesses. Paramount Global-B (PARA) reported second-quarter results that beat Wall Street estimates, showcasing positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SOVO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</guid>
      <description>score:877
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao&amp;rsquo;s pasta sauces and noosa yogurt, aligns with its strategy to strengthen its grocery business. The $2.7 billion deal for Sovos Brands presents a growth opportunity for Campbell Soup to expand its presence in frozen meals and premium pasta sauce markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:1021
Chances: Shares of AI software company C3.ai (NYSE: AI) experienced a 7% decline after analysts raised concerns about AI stocks being in a potential bubble. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s shift to a consumption-based business model for fiscal 2024 may help lower entry barriers for new customers and quickly strike deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:1188
Chances: Viatris shares advanced after posting better-than-expected Q2 2023 results and announcing planned divestitures, including a new multiple sclerosis treatment in collaboration with Mapi Pharma. Viatris CEO plans $9 billion in divestitures to optimize the company&amp;rsquo;s business lines and products, a third of which is already completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BKI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bki/</guid>
      <description>score:1173
Chances: Black Knight&amp;rsquo;s Data &amp;amp; Analytics division releases August 2023 Mortgage Monitor Report highlighting the heating housing market and rising home prices. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) dismisses federal court case against Intercontinental Exchange&amp;rsquo;s proposed acquisition of Black Knight, clearing the regulatory path for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:1093
Chances: Aurora Innovation announced positive First Half 2023 results with a narrowed net loss of US$414.0 million. The company is scheduled to present at the Canaccord Genuity 43rd Annual Growth Conference, indicating efforts to engage with investors. Aurora&amp;rsquo;s second quarter 2023 results have been released, and its shareholder letter and financial results are available for review on its investor relations website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Micron Technology is expanding its CXL ecosystem by offering sample availability of the Micron CZ120 memory expansion modules, which could contribute to revenue growth. The CZ120 modules&amp;rsquo; high capacities and memory read/write bandwidth could position Micron to meet the increasing demand for advanced memory solutions in data-intensive applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
