<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Us on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Us on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:37:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Stock Ranking by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</guid>
      <description>I use ChatGPT to analyze and rank most active us stocks:
INFY (Infosys Limited) FTI (TechnipFMC plc) FTNT (Fortinet, Inc.) NKE (NIKE, Inc.) AMCR (Amcor plc) LUV (Southwest Airlines Co.) CVNA (Carvana Co.) TSM (Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited) MRK (Merck &amp;amp; Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: BlackBerry has unveiled its agenda for BlackBerry Summit, indicating its focus on innovation. Participation in the Mobility in Harmony (MIH) Consortium for electric vehicle development could open new growth opportunities. The company&amp;rsquo;s quarterly Threat Intelligence Report highlights the increasing cybersecurity challenges, which could drive demand for its solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnq/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Canadian Natural Resources expects the Trans Mountain expansion project to proceed, which could benefit the company. Institutional investors control a significant portion of CNQ&amp;rsquo;s shares, indicating confidence in the stock. The company reported strong Q2 2023 earnings with sales beating estimates, suggesting a positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Devon Energy is attracting investor attention, and it could be a buy for its upcoming dividend. Some oil stocks, including Devon Energy, have recently received a boost and may have potential for further growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong financial prospects suggest that weakness in its stock may not reflect its true value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sbra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sbra/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Sabra Health Care REIT has announced its participation in several healthcare and real estate conferences, indicating an active presence in the industry. The company has published its third annual sustainability report, reflecting a commitment to sustainability and responsible business practices. Despite recent stock price declines, there&amp;rsquo;s potential for a 20% rise in dividend yields, as suggested by Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Valero Energy Corp has experienced a surprising 27% stock rally, indicating a positive momentum in the stock. Valero Energy is considered a fairly valued powerhouse in the oil &amp;amp; gas industry with strong financial prospects. The company recently reported Q2 earnings that beat estimates, showcasing its resilience in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: ZoomInfo Technologies Inc. has announced partnerships and events to expand its digital media capabilities, indicating growth potential. Despite recent weakness in ZI stock, its financial prospects are considered decent by some analysts, suggesting a possible turnaround. ZoomInfo earned numerous #1 Grid rankings and leader ratings in G2&amp;rsquo;s Summer 2023 report, reflecting its strong industry position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: V.F. Corporation (VFC) has seen positive gains despite market dips, suggesting resilience in its performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2024 earnings report indicates that it topped revenue estimates, showing potential for growth. VFC has made strategic changes and appointed new leadership, which could contribute to its future success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nov/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: NOV Inc. has reported strong momentum in its stock price, indicating positive market sentiment. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent earnings reports, including Q2 2023, have been promising, which may attract investors. Wall Street analysts believe that NOV Inc. has the potential to surge by 51.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: PPL Corporation is recognized as a leader in diversity and inclusion, which can contribute to its positive corporate image and potential growth opportunities. The company is focused on clean power generation, aligning with the increasing demand for sustainable energy sources. PPL Electric Utilities has implemented innovative technologies to improve reliability and reduce costs, which could enhance its operational efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: Wall Street analysts see a 27.77% upside potential in KE Holdings Inc., indicating optimism about its future growth prospects. KE Holdings Inc. recently announced an upsizing and extension of its share repurchase program and a special cash dividend, which may attract investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: Sea Limited reported strong Q2 2023 earnings with revenue growth, which may attract investors looking for growth opportunities. Despite recent setbacks, some analysts believe Sea Limited has significant long-term potential and could rebound in the future. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s focus on growth over profits signals its commitment to expanding its market presence and capturing opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Chewy, Inc. announced strong Q2 2023 financial results, beating earnings and revenue estimates, which may attract investors. Chewy&amp;rsquo;s CEO mentioned that helping customers with ease drives loyalty to the brand, which could lead to sustained growth. Some Wall Street analysts believe that Chewy has significant growth potential, with projections of over 50% gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NWL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nwl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nwl/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: Newell Brands reported Q2 earnings that surpassed estimates, which could be a positive sign for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Blackstone and Airbnb are set to join the S&amp;amp;P 500, potentially indicating a positive sentiment in the market, which might benefit Newell Brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATVI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/atvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/atvi/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: Microsoft is revising its deal with Activision in a bid to obtain UK regulatory approval, which could be a positive development for the company. Activision Blizzard has various popular gaming franchises, and its partnership with Microsoft is a strategic move that may boost its long-term prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSNY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/psny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/psny/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Polestar reported record deliveries in the second quarter, growing 36% year-on-year, indicating strong momentum. Polestar is collaborating with Mobileye to build an integrated driver assist solution for its electric SUV coupé, Polestar 4. Polestar plans to adopt the North American Charging Standard to enable access to Tesla Supercharger network in the USA and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: Toast announces the launch of a Catering &amp;amp; Events platform to help restaurants streamline event management and improve guest experience. Toast is transforming the restaurant industry with its restaurant technology platform, which could drive future growth. Toast is approved for use in Marriott Select Service Hotels in the United States and Canada, expanding its market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:-3
Chances: Tencent Music Entertainment reports rising quarterly revenue, although it warns of a potential decline ahead. Tencent Music&amp;rsquo;s implied volatility is surging for its stock options, indicating increased market interest. Tencent Music Entertainment sees increased revenue from paying users, which could drive future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper (KDP) reports strong Q2 earnings that top estimates and provide an optimistic sales view. Keurig Dr Pepper makes a strategic move by partnering with La Colombe to expand its reach. Solid market gains are expected to aid Keurig Dr Pepper amid cost woes, potentially driving growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COTY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coty/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Coty successfully completes refinancing of its revolving credit facility, signaling financial stability. Coty focuses on boosting its global presence and ups its FY23 view, indicating growth prospects. Marc Jacobs and Coty expand their license partnership to beauty, potentially driving brand sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: JD.com reports earnings beat in the second quarter, outperforming estimates despite economic challenges in China. Gucci and JD.com announce a digital partnership and the launch of an official Gucci flagship store, indicating growth in the luxury e-commerce segment. Analysts suggest JD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bk/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: BNY Mellon launches an open banking payments solution, Bankify, indicating a move towards modern banking technology. BNY Mellon appoints Sinead Colton-Grant as Chief Investment Officer, showcasing strategic leadership changes. BNY Mellon joins the FedNow® Service, advancing the U.S. payment system, which could lead to new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: CVS Health announces additional responsibilities for executive leadership team members, indicating strategic expansion. CVS Health survey finds that more than two-thirds of Americans plan to get a flu shot this season, which can boost revenue. CVS Health launches Cordavis to target the biosimilar market, tapping into a potentially lucrative sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stla/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: Stellantis is offering a 14.5% wage hike to UAW, which may help mitigate the risk of a potential strike. The company plans to expand its battery capacity, positioning itself for growth in the EV market. Stellantis is exploring the use of e-fuels, demonstrating its commitment to sustainable and alternative technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DELL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dell/</guid>
      <description>score:15
Chances: Dell&amp;rsquo;s stock is surging on optimism related to its AI initiatives, which could drive future growth. The company reported strong second-quarter results and raised its forecast, citing AI strength and demand recovery. Dell&amp;rsquo;s focus on generative AI is positioning it as a winner in the evolving AI market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Fisker plans to significantly increase EV production in the fourth quarter, which could lead to higher revenues. Fisker is expanding its presence in Europe, opening up new markets and increasing its global reach. Fisker&amp;rsquo;s innovative and affordable electric vehicle, the Fisker Pear, is generating interest with its competitive pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Coterra Energy reports positive second-quarter 2023 results and announces a quarterly dividend. Goldman Sachs likes Coterra Energy as a top dividend stock yielding as high as 10%. Coterra Energy investors have seen a respectable 75% return over the last three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Coinbase is outpacing stock market gains, indicating strong performance in the crypto industry. The company is expanding its services and targeting regulatory clarity for international expansion. Coinbase-backed insurance alternative OpenCover debuts on Layer 2 blockchain Base, showing innovation. Coinbase announces interim results and extension and upsizing of cash tender offer for its outstanding senior notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BROS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bros/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Dutch Bros raises guidance as profit doubles, indicating strong financial performance. The company is focused on new markets and expansion, which may lead to growth opportunities. Dutch Bros reports second-quarter 2023 financial results, reflecting positive performance. The company has caught the attention of institutional investors with a sizeable 35% stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Boeing wins a contract to enhance Japan&amp;rsquo;s F-15 Fighter Jets, showcasing potential growth opportunities. Boeing will meet its 737 delivery goal despite new production problems, providing confidence in meeting targets. Boeing clinches a $173 million contract to aid F/A-18 E/F Aircraft, indicating continued business contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:208
Chances: Infosys welcomes tennis world No.1 Iga Świątek and tennis icon Rafael Nadal as brand ambassadors, enhancing global brand presence. Infosys Foundation USA invests $200,000 to boost tech careers through collaboration, reflecting corporate social responsibility. Infosys expands strategic collaboration with Liberty Global to bring AI-powered digital entertainment to customers worldwide, indicating growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMCR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</guid>
      <description>score:151
Chances: Amcor launches high-barrier performance paper packaging in North America, indicating growth opportunities. The company reported fiscal 2023 results and provided an outlook for fiscal 2024, which may attract investors. Amcor announces intent to acquire Moda Systems, showcasing expansion strategies. Amcor becomes the first flexible packaging company to offer certified-circular plastics in Australia and New Zealand, demonstrating sustainability efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:159
Chances: Fortinet has caught the eye of investors, indicating potential investment opportunities. The company won Google Cloud Technology Partner of the Year Award for Security, showcasing its capabilities. Fortinet expands its SASE solution to provide cloud-delivered enterprise-grade protection, positioning itself for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:115
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM) is a leading player in the AI revolution, positioning it for growth. TSMC&amp;rsquo;s August sales indicate a promising start, boosting market confidence. TSMC may decide to invest in Arm IPO, signaling strategic opportunities for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FNMA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fnma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fnma/</guid>
      <description>score:57
Chances: Fannie Mae reports net income of $5.0 billion for the second quarter of 2023, indicating financial strength. Fannie Mae is actively providing disaster relief options for those affected by natural disasters, enhancing its reputation. Consumer confidence in housing may have plateaued, potentially stabilizing the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wrk/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: WestRock engages in merger talks with Smurfit Kappa, indicating potential for growth and expansion. The proposed merger with Smurfit Kappa could create a $20 billion packaging giant, offering strategic advantages. WestRock beats profit estimates in its fiscal third quarter, showing resilience in a dynamic environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs signs a tentative labor agreement with USW, potentially stabilizing labor relations. U.S. Steel explores strategic alternatives amid acquisition proposals, indicating potential growth opportunities. Steelworkers&amp;rsquo; support for Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;rsquo; bid for U.S. Steel could tip the scales in favor of the acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: HP CEO discusses the potential impact of the AI boom on computers, hinting at future innovations. Miro and HP collaborate to accelerate collaboration and innovation, which may drive business growth. HP matches Q3 earnings estimates, indicating a degree of stability and meeting investor expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:122
Chances: Carvana completes a debt restructuring, slashing $1.3 billion of debt, which could improve financial stability. The company launches same-day vehicle delivery services, enhancing speed and convenience for local shoppers. Carvana is named among America&amp;rsquo;s Best Employers for Women, signaling a positive reputation as an employer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kim/</guid>
      <description>score:-34
Chances: Kimco Realty to acquire RPT Realty in a $2 billion all-stock transaction, which can bolster growth prospects. Kimco expands its portfolio with the acquisition of Stonebridge at Potomac Town Center, further strengthening its assets. Strong leasing demand from grocers and positive Q2 results demonstrate Kimco Realty&amp;rsquo;s potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: RTX secured a $277 million contract for Excalibur 155 mm projectiles, indicating potential growth opportunities. The company is attracting institutional investors, with 81% ownership among them, which could signal investor confidence. RTX is involved in the development of advanced technology solutions for the aerospace and defense sector, a growing industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aes/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: AES is focusing on renewable energy investments, which could provide growth opportunities in the future. The company has announced positive momentum in its first-quarter results, reaffirming its 2023 guidance. AES recently acquired the largest permitted solar-plus-storage project in the United States, positioning itself in the renewable energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FITB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fitb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fitb/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: Fifth Third Bancorp reported strong second-quarter 2023 earnings, beating estimates, and showcasing potential for growth. Organic growth is supporting Fifth Third (FITB) despite high costs, indicating resilience in a challenging environment. The bank is opening eight new branches in strategic locations, which could expand its customer base and revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmb/</guid>
      <description>score:68
Chances: Williams Companies, Inc. (WMB) reported strong second-quarter results, indicating potential growth opportunities and positive performance. The company recently executed an agreement with Chattanooga Gas for the delivery of certified low-emission NextGen Gas, aligning with sustainability trends. Williams CEO is scheduled to present at the 2023 Barclays CEO Energy-Power Conference, which could attract investor attention and provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ms/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Morgan Stanley plans to launch an AI chatbot to enhance its services for wealthy clients, which could lead to improved customer engagement and satisfaction. The global wealth management industry is experiencing growth, and Morgan Stanley aims to capitalize on this trend by attracting investor attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: CNH Industrial achieved zero waste to landfill at all its production sites in Brazil, showcasing its commitment to sustainability. The company&amp;rsquo;s innovative products, such as the all-electric utility tractor and precision farming technology, are receiving positive attention. CNH Industrial reported record second-quarter net income of $710 million, indicating strong performance in equipment demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: B2Gold declared a dividend of $0.04 per share for the third quarter of 2023, which may attract income-oriented investors. Strong Q2 2023 operating results and lower costs position B2Gold well to achieve its 2023 annual guidance. B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s updated mineral resource estimate for the Anaconda Area in Mali indicates growth potential for the company&amp;rsquo;s operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Unity Software announced the launch of Unity Wētā Tools Division, which could drive future growth in film and real-time 3D applications. The company reported Q2 2023 earnings that beat estimates, with rising revenues year-over-year. Unity Software launched several initiatives and partnerships, such as Safe Voice and visionOS integration, to expand its reach and product offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts provided an update on recent weather events, showing concern for potential impacts on the tourism industry. The company reported strong Q1 2023 results, with FFO and revenues beating estimates, and it raised its 2023 view. Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts announced an increased second-quarter dividend, which may attract dividend-focused investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: First Horizon has been recognized as one of the best-in-state employers and banks by Forbes, reflecting a positive company image. The company has received awards and designations, such as the Savings Excellence Award and Best Employers for Women, highlighting its commitment to excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rol/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Rollins, Inc. reported 11% year-over-year revenue growth, indicating a strong demand environment. The company is launching a secondary public offering of common stock, which could signal growth opportunities. Rollins stock has shown resilience, gaining 13% in the past 6 months. Risks: Rollins stock has experienced recent weakness, which may raise concerns among prospective shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Freeport-McMoRan has shown attractive financial prospects, which could make it an appealing investment opportunity. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price increased, rewarding institutional investors with strong returns. Freeport-McMoRan&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat estimates, indicating strong performance despite challenges. Risks: The international obstacles, such as production issues and challenges in Indonesia, pose a risk to the company&amp;rsquo;s profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Barclays is making new senior appointments and hiring key personnel, indicating a commitment to strengthening its teams and services. The bank has announced plans for share buybacks and dividend payments, which can attract income-focused investors. Barclays is exploring opportunities in private credit and technology investment banking, showing a strategic focus on growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: An intrinsic calculation suggests that Occidental Petroleum Corporation (OXY) is potentially undervalued by 32%, which could present a buying opportunity for investors. Occidental Petroleum offers dividends, making it an attractive option for income-focused investors. The company is making acquisitions and investments, such as the acquisition of Carbon Engineering, indicating a strategic focus on growth and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wu/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: Western Union is paying a dividend of $0.235, which can be attractive to income-focused investors. The company has opened its first-ever concept store in Jordan, which could potentially enhance its presence in the region and attract new customers. Western Union reported strong Q2 earnings, beating estimates and raising its annual profit outlook, indicating positive growth in its core business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iq/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: iQIYI has launched the drama &amp;lsquo;My Journey To You,&amp;rsquo; showcasing Chinese aesthetics, which could attract a broader audience and boost viewership. The company is leveraging AI and technology to improve content production and marketing efficiency, which may lead to cost savings and increased revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:158
Chances: Nike has entered the sustainable shoe market with its recyclable ISPA Axis sneaker, which could appeal to environmentally-conscious consumers and boost sales. Despite recent challenges, the Jordan brand, part of Nike, is considered to have substantial growth potential, which may positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EQT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: EQT Corporation recently completed the acquisition of Tug Hill and XcL Midstream, which could potentially enhance its operational capabilities and revenue streams. The company&amp;rsquo;s acquisition received approval from the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC), allowing it to proceed without regulatory hurdles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Newmont Corporation is proceeding with its acquisition of Newcrest, having received regulatory clearances from Australia and Korea, which could open up new growth opportunities. The company is operating in the gold mining industry, which tends to perform well during economic uncertainties, making it an attractive investment option for investors seeking a safe haven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>score:100
Chances: Dominion Energy is set to sell its gas distribution companies to Enbridge in a $14 billion deal, which could fuel its high-yielding payout and create new growth opportunities. The company is advancing its business with strategic agreements and initiatives, such as building a solar farm in Dulles Airport and investing in renewable energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teva/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Teva Pharmaceutical Industries is set to present data for various products, indicating ongoing research and potential for growth. Teva&amp;rsquo;s CEO sees &amp;lsquo;significant&amp;rsquo; potential for a trio of branded drugs, which could drive future revenue and profits. Teva&amp;rsquo;s strategic evaluation, including the potential sale of its active ingredients unit, might create opportunities for restructuring and focus on core operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Gilead&amp;rsquo;s Phase 2 EVOKE-02 Study of Trodelvy in Combination with KEYTRUDA demonstrates promising clinical activity in first-line metastatic non-small cell lung cancer, indicating potential growth opportunities. Gilead Sciences has a high institutional ownership of 86%, suggesting confidence from major investors. The FDA approval for Veklury to treat COVID-19 in people with hepatic impairment is a positive development for Gilead&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) has reported $7 billion in revenue for Q3, indicating strong financial performance. The company has shown fast-paced momentum, making it a potentially attractive choice for investors. HPE has bumped its full-year profit outlook, suggesting renewed corporate spending and positive prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jci/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Johnson Controls has reported strong revenue and EPS growth in Q3, which could indicate a positive outlook for the company. The acquisition of FM:Systems for $455 million shows the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its digital buildings capabilities. Johnson Controls is the winner of the 2023 Microsoft Global Independent Software Vendor Partner of the Year, highlighting its industry recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XPEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: XPeng Inc. plans to expand into more European markets next year, potentially increasing its global market presence. Chinese electric vehicle (EV) manufacturers like XPeng are gaining market share and competing with established players, such as Tesla. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic acquisitions and partnerships, like the deal with Didi&amp;rsquo;s smart EV development business, can drive future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:107
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. (MRK) is a favorite among institutional investors, with 78% institutional ownership, indicating institutional confidence. Merck received approval to expand the indication of its ERVEBO® Ebola Zaire Vaccine to include children aged 1 year and older, potentially expanding its market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mo/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: Altria Group, Inc. (MO) has the favor of institutional owners who hold 60% of the company, indicating institutional confidence. MO recently raised its dividend, making it an attractive option for passive income investors seeking reliable dividend stocks. The stock has outpaced stock market gains, reflecting its strong performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDLZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mdlz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mdlz/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Mondelez International (MDLZ) reported better-than-expected Q2 earnings and raised its full-year sales guidance, leading to a rise in its stock price. MDLZ is favored by institutional investors who own 79% of the company, indicating strong institutional confidence. The company thrives on strategic buyouts and demonstrates strength in the snacking category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) reported Q2 earnings that beat estimates, leading to a 5.1% rise in its stock price. The company has a history of offering high yields to its investors, making it attractive for income-seeking investors. NYCB has shown steady growth in high margins despite facing cost-related challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson recently completed the separation of Kenvue, which could lead to better focus and growth opportunities in the pharmaceutical and medical tech sectors. The company forecasts double-digit earnings growth after the Kenvue spin-off, indicating a positive outlook. J&amp;amp;J continues to generate strong free cash flow, supporting its dividend decisions and financial stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: Kinross Gold announced positive earnings and revenue beats in the last quarter, leading to a 7.6% increase in stock price. The company was granted the right to earn a 70% interest in Launi East, potentially unlocking new growth opportunities. Kinross Gold declared a quarterly dividend, offering returns to its shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Permian Resources announced a $500.0 million private placement of senior notes due in 2032, indicating its ability to raise capital. The company is set to acquire Earthstone Energy in an all-stock transaction, creating a $14 billion premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P, which may lead to growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JPM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. is favored by institutional owners who hold 72% of the company, indicating strong investor confidence. The company could launch a blockchain-based deposit token &amp;lsquo;relatively quickly&amp;rsquo; after regulatory approval, showcasing its innovative potential. JPMorgan&amp;rsquo;s CEO Jamie Dimon recently delivered a stern warning to remote workers, suggesting adaptability to changing work trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: Cenovus Energy has delivered a solid 57% CAGR over the past 3 years, indicating positive performance for shareholders. The company beat quarterly profit estimates, with shares climbing as a result, suggesting strong financial performance. Cenovus Energy&amp;rsquo;s fundamentals appear strong, indicating potential growth opportunities in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Clarivate&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the data and analytics sector positions it well to capitalize on growing demand for research and information services. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships and acquisitions, such as the integration of ProQuest Dissertations and Theses Global, enhance its offerings and market reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BRFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/brfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/brfs/</guid>
      <description>score:-62
Chances: BRF S.A. (BRFS) is benefiting from rising chicken prices and lower grain costs, which could improve its profitability. The company is forming a halal meat joint venture with Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s PIF, which could open up new markets and revenue streams. BRF&amp;rsquo;s operational overhaul and cost-saving measures are expected to lift margins, providing growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CARR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/carr/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Carrier Global Corp (CARR) has been expanding its offerings and recently added new heat pumps to its HVAC products, indicating growth potential. The company reported strong Q2 2023 earnings, with revenues and earnings beating estimates, suggesting robust financial performance. Carrier Global is set to present at Morgan Stanley&amp;rsquo;s 11th Annual Laguna Conference, which may provide insights into its future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bte/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Baytex Energy Corp. (BTE) is gaining attention as one of the undervalued stocks in the market. The company recently announced its second-quarter 2023 results, indicating its financial performance. Baytex Energy is set to present at the EnerCom Denver - The Energy Investment Conference, suggesting a focus on growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: Viatris Inc. (VTRS) has been gaining attention as a pharmaceutical stock that may be undervalued. The company recently received tentative approval from the FDA for a pediatric HIV regimen, which could open new revenue streams. Viatris reported strong Q2 2023 earnings with growth in its generics business, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vst/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Vistra Corp. (VST) is receiving positive attention from analysts and investors, making it a potentially favorable investment. The company has reported strong earnings and results in the second quarter of 2023, which could attract investors seeking growth. Vistra Corp. is expanding its energy storage system, positioning itself for the growing demand for clean energy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Chevron appeals to an Australian workplace arbiter to resolve a labor impasse, indicating efforts to address labor-related issues. Chevron is taking steps to halt Australia LNG strike action, which could help mitigate potential supply disruptions. Despite labor strikes, Chevron&amp;rsquo;s LNG prices are rising, which may positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s revenues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pten/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pten/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Industry analysts have upgraded Patterson-UTI Energy&amp;rsquo;s revenue forecasts by 36%, indicating positive growth prospects. The completion of the merger between Patterson-UTI Energy and NexTier Oilfield Solutions suggests potential synergies and expansion opportunities. Patterson-UTI Energy expects rig counts and completions activity to rise later this year, aligning with potential industry recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: NextEra Energy has a strong institutional ownership of 80%, which may indicate confidence among large investors. Wall Street analysts seem bullish on NextEra Energy, suggesting a positive outlook for the company&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s involvement in renewable energy projects positions it well in the growing green energy sector, offering long-term growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:56
Chances: Regions Financial has been aided by growth in Net Interest Income (NII) and loan growth, which could contribute positively to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming dividend is expected to be larger than the previous year&amp;rsquo;s, which can attract income-focused investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enb/</guid>
      <description>score:103
Chances: Enbridge recently closed a significant common equity offering, raising CDN$4.6 billion, which could provide additional financial resources for the company&amp;rsquo;s growth plans. The acquisition of natural gas utilities from Dominion Energy for $14 billion is expected to bolster Enbridge&amp;rsquo;s position in the energy sector and contribute to its high-yielding payout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Companhia Energética de Minas Gerais (CIG) reported its Q2 2023 earnings, and the details can be found in the earnings call transcript. CEMIG Geração e Transmissão S.A. announced early tender date results for its cash tender offer for senior notes due 2024, which could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters (AEO) reported strong Q2 earnings and sales, exceeding Wall Street estimates, and raised its revenue forecast. The company has been upgraded to &amp;lsquo;Strong Buy&amp;rsquo;, indicating positive sentiment among analysts. AEO is showing signs of being a fast-paced momentum stock and may be considered a bargain investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Gerdau introduced recyclable steel into Formula 1 São Paulo Grand Prix, indicating its innovative approach and market presence. The company has been upgraded to a &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; rating, suggesting potential positive momentum for investors. Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock recently crossed above the 50-day moving average and the 200-day moving average, which can be a bullish indicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Sunrun has been upgraded and is well-positioned to navigate a potentially volatile solar market. The company reported better-than-expected Q2 2023 earnings with an earnings per share (EPS) beat, which is a positive sign for investors. Sunrun has expanded its collaboration with PG&amp;amp;E to share critical solar energy with California&amp;rsquo;s grid, which can enhance its market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNOW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snow/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: Snowflake is transforming into an AI software platform, positioning itself for growth in the AI industry. Analysts believe that Snowflake is a top AI stock to buy, considering its potential in the growing cloud computing market. The company reported strong Q2 2024 earnings with revenue growth, which is a positive sign for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:-94
Chances: AGNC Investment Corp. has outperformed the stock market, indicating positive investor sentiment. Wall Street analysts view AGNC Investment as a good investment opportunity, suggesting potential growth. The company offers a high dividend yield, making it attractive for income-seeking investors. Risks: AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s stock performance has seen fluctuations, and it has dipped since the last earnings report, which may raise concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs has ratified a new labor contract with the United Steelworkers for its Northshore Mining Operations, ensuring labor stability. The company is actively involved in bid attempts and negotiations, indicating an interest in strategic expansion. Cleveland-Cliffs has the exclusive rights to bid for U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Kraft Heinz is innovating and expanding its product lines, such as Oscar Mayer&amp;rsquo;s On-The-Go Refrigerated Breakfast and FUNdamental Textbooks. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment in Kraft Heinz suggests long-term stability and dividend potential. The company is participating in conferences like the 2023 Barclays Global Consumer Staples Conference, indicating an interest in investor engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Delta Air Lines employees participating in training to de-ice planes could improve safety measures and operational efficiency. Delta Air Lines&amp;rsquo; strategic partnership with Tom Brady as a strategic adviser might lead to innovative business strategies. The airline is expanding in Asia through the Honolulu-Tokyo route, potentially tapping into new markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BKR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</guid>
      <description>score:57
Chances: Baker Hughes secured a deal to supply equipment for the Driftwood LNG project, potentially contributing to revenue growth. The company signed agreements and expanded equipment supply partnerships with Venture Global, supporting its long-term expansion plans. Despite market fluctuations, Baker Hughes shareholders have earned a 38% CAGR over the last three years, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Transocean secured a $222 million drilling contract from ONGC, indicating a potential revenue boost. Transocean announced a $518 million ultra-deepwater drillship contract, which could contribute to future earnings. Transocean&amp;rsquo;s stock has gained 3.3% over the past week, showing positive market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: Barrick Gold beat quarterly profit estimates on the back of higher gold prices, indicating potential for strong financial performance. Barrick Gold is progressing with the extension of its long-term value delivery runway, suggesting a positive outlook. Gulf nations are poised to invest billions in Pakistan, which could benefit Barrick Gold as it explores opportunities in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bur/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Burford Capital Limited&amp;rsquo;s strong revenue growth and favorable return of 86% over the last three years indicate potential for growth. The company won a landmark case against Argentina, which could have a positive impact on its financial performance. Insiders acquired a significant amount of stock, signaling confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: U.S. Bancorp is experiencing revenue growth despite high costs, which could be seen as a positive sign for investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s business banking segment, Elavon, has launched a new product called Talech Terminal, indicating innovation and potential market expansion. U.S. Bancorp has strong institutional backing, with 76% ownership, which may instill confidence in investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Roku has made steady financial progress, and management has raised its guidance, which could be seen as a positive sign for long-term investors. Roku expects third-quarter revenue to be substantially higher than its previous forecast, indicating potential growth in its business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: VinFast Auto gained significant attention and experienced a massive rally in August, indicating investor interest in the company&amp;rsquo;s potential. The Vietnamese EV maker, VinFast, has made its U.S. debut, signaling its expansion into international markets, which could offer growth opportunities. VinFast&amp;rsquo;s successful business combination with Black Spade Acquisition Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: Southwest Airlines is working on initiatives to offer quicker ways for customers to earn the coveted Companion Pass, which could boost customer loyalty and revenue. The airline industry is showing resilience despite challenges, and Southwest Airlines has the potential to benefit from the rebound in travel demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fti/</guid>
      <description>score:160
Chances: TechnipFMC has clinched a significant contract for the Girassol Life Extension Project, indicating growth potential in the oil and gas sector. The company announced the initiation of a quarterly dividend and an additional $400 million share repurchase authorization, which may attract income and value investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</guid>
      <description>score:55
Chances: Avantor has partnered with Tobin Scientific to provide comprehensive solutions for research lab services, showing commitment to innovation. The Avantor Foundation supports high school students pursuing STEM careers, which may contribute to future talent development. Avantor earned a Bronze Medal from EcoVadis for sustainability performance, indicating a commitment to responsible business practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings has shown resilience despite market challenges. Consumer demand for travel experiences remains robust, which is positive for the company. The company reported strong second-quarter 2023 financial results and improved its full-year guidance. Risks: Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings faced a 25% drop in stock price in August, indicating market volatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:-66
Chances: Halliburton has shown strength in the market, outperforming during market dips. Analysts are optimistic about Halliburton&amp;rsquo;s future growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance has been positively impacted by the energy sector&amp;rsquo;s recovery. Risks: Halliburton faces potential risks related to its exposure to international markets and geopolitical events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Shopify&amp;rsquo;s landmark deal with Amazon to integrate &amp;lsquo;Buy with Prime&amp;rsquo; is expected to boost its sales and market presence. The company has been consistently growing, and its stock has outperformed the broader market in recent times. Investors are showing strong interest in Shopify as it continues to innovate and expand its partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s has announced a quarterly dividend, which could attract income-focused investors. Collaborations with brands like Gap on a sleepwear collection suggest potential for increased sales and brand partnerships. Despite challenges, consumers are spending, and there is optimism for a potential rebound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Bilibili Inc. has seen stronger profits and growth potential, as it benefits from generative AI and the Chinese tech sector&amp;rsquo;s growth. Despite recent losses, there is still an opportunity in Bilibili Inc. as it aims to rebound and overcome challenges. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings reports and revenue estimates suggest the potential for positive developments in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABNB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abnb/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Airbnb&amp;rsquo;s hot growth has led to its inclusion in the S&amp;amp;P 500, attracting investor attention and potentially indicating more room for growth. The platform&amp;rsquo;s unique business model and strong fundamentals make it a top momentum stock for the long-term. Despite regulatory challenges in cities like New York, Airbnb continues to operate and adapt to changing regulations, showing resilience in its business model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Las Vegas Sands has announced various charitable contributions and initiatives, showcasing its commitment to social responsibility. The company&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat Wall Street estimates, indicating a positive performance in key markets like Macao and Singapore. Macao reclaimed its position as the world&amp;rsquo;s top gambling hub, which could benefit Las Vegas Sands&amp;rsquo; operations in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Marvell&amp;rsquo;s AI revenue is showing promising growth, which could be a positive sign for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. Despite a recent pullback, institutional shareholders have seen a 7.2% return over the past year, indicating some level of confidence in Marvell. The company beat Q2 earnings and revenue estimates, which may suggest its resilience in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Ambev S.A. continues to see growth potential, with its net profit rising 36% in Q4, and its efforts to tap into the international beverage market. The demand for energy drinks could boost Ambev&amp;rsquo;s sales, as it navigates through inflationary pressures and explores growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:93
Chances: Bristol-Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s investigational LPA1 antagonist shows promise in reducing lung function decline in a Phase 2 study, which could lead to a potential breakthrough in pulmonary fibrosis treatment. Bristol-Myers Squibb celebrates a decade of its Coast 2 Coast 4 Cancer cross-country bike ride in support of the V Foundation for Cancer Research, showcasing its commitment to corporate social responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Charles Schwab experienced a successful weekend, converting TD Ameritrade clients and advisors, potentially leading to increased assets under management. Bond investors are showing confidence in Schwab after its cost-cutting measures, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health. Schwab&amp;rsquo;s trader survey indicates that recession fears are receding, suggesting positive sentiment among traders and investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Marathon Oil&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings beat expectations, driven by higher domestic output, indicating positive performance. Billionaires are showing confidence in Marathon Oil, with notable investments, which might attract other investors. Marathon Oil has gained 287% over the past three years, showcasing strong long-term growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Lyft has seen a 5.5% increase in its stock price since its last earnings report, indicating positive investor sentiment. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s new CEO is focusing on making the company more &amp;lsquo;customer-focused,&amp;rsquo; which could enhance its market position. Lyft is making efforts to expand its ad business and introduce in-car services on its app, potentially boosting its revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMAR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/smar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/smar/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Smartsheet Inc. reported Q2 2024 earnings that exceeded guidance with 26% YoY revenue growth, which is a positive sign for the company. Smartsheet was recognized as a 2023 Gartner® Peer Insights™ Customers’ Choice for Collaborative Work Management, indicating strong market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: Lloyds Banking Group (LYG) has reported an increase in profits, beating forecasts, as lenders anticipate a Bank of England rate hike. UK business confidence is at an 18-month high despite inflation and a cost of living crisis, which could positively impact Lloyds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Micron Technology (MU) has been considered one of the best stocks to invest in according to AI algorithms. The company has shown rising performance and an RS rating of 84, indicating its strength in the market. Micron launched a Memory Expansion Module Portfolio to accelerate CXL 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Qualcomm (QCOM) has partnerships with BMW and Mercedes to supply chips for displays and voice features, driving innovation. The company is considered a market leader in the semiconductor industry and has reported positive returns on capital. Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s involvement in 5G technology positions it as one of the top 5G stocks to consider for investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: PDD Holdings Inc. (PDD) has reported strong revenue growth, with sales soaring and beating expectations. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock jumped 15% after an earnings beat, reflecting positive investor sentiment. Pinduoduo-owner PDD&amp;rsquo;s growth has been defying Chinese economic challenges, making it a notable player in e-commerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Opendoor Technologies Inc. has shown significant growth potential, making it an attractive stock for investors. The company could be one of the market&amp;rsquo;s biggest winners over the next decade, indicating long-term growth prospects. Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s stock performance has been impressive, with a more than 200% increase in value this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xp/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: XP Inc. reports positive earnings growth, indicating its potential for profitability and growth. The company announces the termination of a shareholders agreement, which might lead to strategic changes. Despite recent market cap fluctuations, institutional investors have benefited from long-term gains in XP Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: Roivant Sciences ranks No. 25 on Fast Company’s list of the 100 Best Workplaces for Innovators, indicating a positive work environment. Roivant reports positive topline results from various clinical trials, demonstrating the potential for successful drug development. Lokavant, a Roivant spin-off, emerges with multiple industry partnerships to accelerate clinical research, which could drive future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stx/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Seagate Technology reported an award for the Most Innovative Sustainability Technology in Data Center Storage, showcasing its commitment to innovation. The company announced the pricing of $1.3 billion of Exchangeable Senior Unsecured Notes, which could provide additional capital for growth. Seagate has affirmed its dividend of $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vsh/</guid>
      <description>score:91
Chances: Vishay Intertechnology reported Q2 earnings that beat estimates, and revenues showed a year-over-year increase. Vishay is expanding its product offerings and capabilities, such as adding new devices and enhancing its opto capabilities. The company has opened a new state-of-the-art resistors manufacturing facility and signed agreements to bundle haptic technology licenses with its products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:-47
Chances: Energy Transfer LP has shown market leadership with a jump to an 82 RS (Relative Strength) rating. The acquisition of Crestwood Equity Partners in a $7.1 billion deal could potentially boost ET&amp;rsquo;s payout. Investors are attracted to Energy Transfer LP, which offers a 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Alibaba has unveiled new B2B products for small businesses, indicating efforts to expand its offerings. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s move to expand its B2B business in the US suggests growth potential in the American e-commerce market. Individual and institutional investors have profited from Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s recent surge, indicating investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:-50
Chances: Oracle is considered a heavily in-demand stock, indicating strong investor interest. Analysts have predicted &amp;lsquo;solid&amp;rsquo; multiyear growth for Oracle, driven by AI potential. Oracle&amp;rsquo;s AI cloud outlook has prompted upgrades, indicating optimism about its future prospects. Risks: Oracle stock may face a downside correction, which could impact its short-term performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Medical Properties Trust is actively working to pay down debt, which could strengthen its financial position in the long term. Investors looking for high-yield dividend stocks might find value in Medical Properties Trust, especially if it recovers. The company has updated its capital allocation strategy to enhance long-term value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: Roblox is planning its PlayStation debut and introducing new world-building AI tools, indicating growth potential. Roblox is becoming an artificial intelligence (AI) powerhouse, which could lead to market-crushing returns. Despite recent setbacks, some analysts believe Roblox stock is a prospective investment with significant growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: DraftKings is poised to benefit from the NFL season kick-off, as millions of Americans are expected to bet on games. Analysts look optimistic about DraftKings&amp;rsquo; future prospects, suggesting it may be a good buy. DraftKings&amp;rsquo; expansion efforts, like the opening of Golden Nugget&amp;rsquo;s casino in Pennsylvania, indicate growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E reached a milestone with 100,000 participants in its Smart Thermostat Demand Response Program. PG&amp;amp;E&amp;rsquo;s initiatives to combat food insecurity and promote STEM scholarships reflect positive corporate responsibility. PG&amp;amp;E&amp;rsquo;s upgraded rating to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; indicates a positive outlook by analysts. Risks: PG&amp;amp;E faces wildfire risks and power outage-related challenges in Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bx/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Blackstone&amp;rsquo;s private credit fund secured $2.4 billion, indicating strong demand for their offerings. Blackstone is set to join the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index, potentially leading to further upside for the stock. Blackstone&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Vornado Realty Trust to create Manhattan&amp;rsquo;s first film-and-TV studio is a notable development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: KeyBank provided a $5 million line of credit to advance small businesses, indicating support for growth. KeyBank celebrated the opening of a new, full-service branch, demonstrating expansion efforts. KeyCorp is paying a dividend of $0.205, offering a 7.1% dividend yield, which may attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Lufax Holding reported Q2 2023 earnings that topped estimates, indicating potential growth. Despite recent earnings declines, Lufax Holding could bounce back, as public companies are its largest shareholders. Lufax Holding Ltd successfully listed on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong, which could open up new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: C3.ai is off to a strong start with significant traction across its business in Q1 2024. Ark Invest predicts that the AI industry will add $200 trillion to the economy by 2030, making AI stocks promising. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s Q1 loss was narrower than expected, and revenues rose year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: GSK&amp;rsquo;s value is being questioned, but it may be undervalued, making it an attractive investment option. GSK announces availability of AREXVY, its Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) vaccine, at all major US retail pharmacies. Settling the first Zantac cancer lawsuit could soothe investors and impact GSK&amp;rsquo;s stock positively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Huntington Bancshares is paying out a dividend of $0.155, which may attract income-focused investors. The bank&amp;rsquo;s focus on transforming medical billing with software could lead to revenue growth in the healthcare industry. Huntington National Bank ranks No. 1 among regional banks in the J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Meta is developing a new, more powerful AI system, indicating potential for technological advancement. Meta Platforms is poised for a trillion-dollar valuation next year, which suggests growth potential. Meta&amp;rsquo;s push into artificial intelligence could be a driving force behind its turnaround story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Alphabet is a leader in the tech industry with strong growth potential. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Invest has shown interest in unique AI growth stocks, which could benefit Alphabet. Google&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sundar Pichai, believes that AI could be a significant market, suggesting potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Ginkgo Bioworks has announced several collaborations and partnerships, indicating growth opportunities. The company was awarded a DARPA contract to reimagine the manufacturing of complex therapeutic proteins. Ginkgo Bioworks focuses on synthetic biology and biosecurity, which are promising fields for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: UiPath stock has joined an elite rank with a Composite Rating of over 95, indicating strong performance. UiPath shares surged as revenue increased significantly due to soaring demand for AI products. UiPath Automation Cloud™ achieved HITRUST Risk-based, 2-year Certification, demonstrating a high level of information protection assurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:33
Chances: Swiss Bank doubled down on EV stock Rivian and achieved significant gains, indicating investor interest. Battery material price easing expected in the next year could benefit Rivian&amp;rsquo;s EV production. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia + Technology Conference suggests market engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Pfizer Inc. (PFE) is a trending stock, indicating strong market interest. Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s COVID-era growth may influence investment decisions. Pfizer and BioNTech receive positive CHMP opinion for Omicron XBB.1.5-adapted COVID-19 vaccine in the European Union, indicating potential market expansion. Risks: Big Pharma&amp;rsquo;s battle with the Biden administration could have long-lasting consequences, posing regulatory risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s AI software business is expected to be its fastest to reach $10 billion in revenue, indicating growth potential. Microsoft pledges copyright protection for Copilot users, which could boost its appeal to developers and software creators. Bill Gates&amp;rsquo; investment in Anheuser-Busch InBev could pay off, potentially benefiting Microsoft indirectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Comcast moves up the date for the Hulu deal with Disney, potentially unlocking new opportunities. Xfinity&amp;rsquo;s HBCU Fall Tour may contribute to the company&amp;rsquo;s growth and innovation in the future. Comcast NBCUniversal is named one of the top companies on PEOPLE&amp;rsquo;s annual &amp;lsquo;100 Companies That Care&amp;rsquo; list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sq/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Goldman Sachs predicts that innovation and growth will drive success for companies like Block, Inc. Cash App and Square are steadily recovering after recent outages, indicating resilience in payment services. Positive mentions by Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Invest may attract investor interest and support SQ stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Petrobras&amp;rsquo; strategic expansion cooperation deal with CNOOC could lead to increased business opportunities and growth. The purchase of carbon credits by Petrobras showcases its commitment to sustainability, which can attract socially responsible investors. Expectations of another 40 years of oil production by Petrobras indicate long-term stability and potential revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:93
Chances: Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s addition of new AI features like &amp;lsquo;Dreams&amp;rsquo; showcases its commitment to innovation, which could drive user engagement and stock growth. Safety measures to comply with EU regulations may help Snap Inc. maintain a positive reputation and user trust. Snap&amp;rsquo;s expansion into generative AI and the appointment of a former Google exec for India growth hint at potential growth strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: ChargePoint&amp;rsquo;s role in expanding EV charging infrastructure suggests growth potential due to the increasing demand for electric vehicles. Partnerships like the one with Tesla and Hilton could contribute to ChargePoint&amp;rsquo;s success and market presence. The need for more EV charging stations in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Nokia&amp;rsquo;s involvement in rural broadband PON deployment presents growth potential in expanding connectivity. Launch of 5G private wireless services in Thailand indicates Nokia&amp;rsquo;s commitment to advancing technology. Introduction of 25G PON kit and improved home connectivity software demonstrates Nokia&amp;rsquo;s innovation in high-speed connectivity solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s expansion into artificial intelligence (AI) is seen as a growth opportunity, with AI software potential to be a $14 trillion market. Google CEO Sundar Pichai&amp;rsquo;s belief in the significance of AI technology presents potential for long-term growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: Verizon increases dividend for the 17th consecutive year, indicating a strong commitment to dividend payments. Verizon launches new technologies and connectivity solutions, potentially expanding its customer base. The company extends partnerships with the NFL and MetLife Stadium, showcasing a focus on sports and entertainment sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Lucid CEO mentions that Air EV price cuts were well received, indicating positive market response. Lucid announces final production specifications for the Lucid Air Sapphire, enhancing its product portfolio. Rivian, another EV maker, raises production targets, signaling potential growth in the EV market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Nio is pioneering the EV revolution, suggesting growth potential in the electric vehicle industry. Analysis on NIO Inc. from BestGrowthStocks.com may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. There are catalysts expected for Nio stock investors in 2023, indicating potential opportunities. Goldman Sachs includes NIO Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: CEOs of major Brazil lenders see a &amp;lsquo;unique opportunity&amp;rsquo; for the local economy, suggesting potential growth. Amazon is set to launch a credit card in Brazil with Bradesco, which could open up new revenue streams. Banco Bradesco&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call transcript may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:-29
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery expects success with the &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; movie, predicting a rise in gross billings. Warner Bros. Discovery to offer free live sports on Max, potentially attracting a larger audience. Mark Thompson appointed as Chairman and CEO of CNN Worldwide, signaling a potential growth phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T is issuing dividends, attracting income-focused investors looking for high-yield dividend stocks. T-Mobile is issuing its first dividend, potentially making it a more attractive investment option. AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s CEO sees potential in the drone business, indicating diversification and growth opportunities. Some cable sites show no public health risk, potentially reducing concerns and liabilities for AT&amp;amp;T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csx/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: CSX is expanding its intermodal service in partnership with Georgia Ports Authority, potentially increasing revenue streams. CSX has affirmed its dividend of $0.11, which may be attractive to income-focused investors. CSX is committed to improving conductor training and safety after recent incidents, which could enhance its reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Palantir is partnering with Policlinico Gemelli to use AI for healthcare data science, potentially opening new revenue streams. Palantir customers are showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s AI platform at AIPCon, indicating strong adoption and potential growth. Cathie Wood recently purchased Palantir stock, suggesting confidence in its long-term prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Bank of America is favored by institutional owners, with 58% ownership, indicating investor confidence. Higher interest rates have historically benefited Bank of America, which could lead to improved profitability. Bank of America is expanding its credit card cashback rewards, which may attract more customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:-69
Chances: Amazon is leading the market and showing strength in its stock. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s AWS (Amazon Web Services) is gaining new clients like BMW Group, which could boost its revenue. The company&amp;rsquo;s competitive advantage appears to be unstoppable, indicating long-term growth potential. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Shopify could have positive implications for its business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TLRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tlry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tlry/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: The DEA&amp;rsquo;s recommendation for the rescheduling of marijuana suggests potential progress towards legalization. Tilray&amp;rsquo;s expansion of its cannabis portfolio with new Redecan products in Canada may drive growth. Acquiring 8 big beer brands from Anheuser-Busch could have a positive impact on Tilray&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Intel stock has experienced a significant surge in 2023, suggesting potential growth opportunities. Intel is betting on artificial intelligence (AI) beyond the cloud, which could drive future innovation and demand. Partnerships and agreements with companies like Tower Semiconductor and Synopsys may strengthen Intel&amp;rsquo;s position in the semiconductor market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: AMD is expanding its client base and powering next-gen technologies, such as Hitachi Astemo&amp;rsquo;s AI-based camera system. AMD&amp;rsquo;s graphics card market share has bounced back, indicating strength in its core business. The CEO of AMD states that the AI market is &amp;lsquo;skyrocketing,&amp;rsquo; suggesting potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the AI and semiconductor sectors positions it for potential growth. Partnerships with companies like Reliance and Tata in India could open up new markets and opportunities for NVIDIA. The AI and semiconductor industries are expected to continue growing, benefiting NVIDIA as a major player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:57
Chances: Ford reveals a new electric vehicle challenge to compete with top Tesla models, indicating innovation in the EV market. Rising investments and job plans in the US battery cell venture suggest potential growth in the electric vehicle (EV) sector. Ford raises pay for 8,000 UAW workers in line with the 2019 contract, which may improve labor relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:-17
Chances: Kenvue becomes a fully independent company following the separation from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, which could lead to growth opportunities. Kenvue is set to join the S&amp;amp;P 500, indicating positive recognition in the market. Strong second-quarter 2023 results and a positive annual profit forecast may boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: Apple&amp;rsquo;s upcoming iPhone 15 launch is highly anticipated and could drive stock growth. Despite recent market cap losses, some analysts view Apple as a buying opportunity. Apple&amp;rsquo;s resilience in the face of market challenges is noteworthy. Strong performance in certain product segments like iPhones may support future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Tesla stock receives a huge price target hike, indicating potential for significant growth. Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s involvement in geopolitics could benefit Tesla&amp;rsquo;s global positioning. Tesla&amp;rsquo;s dominance in the Chinese EV market is a strong competitive advantage. Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Supercharger network expansion through deals with Hilton and Honda will enhance user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUTU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/futu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/futu/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: S&amp;amp;P Expects A Steady Increase in Futu&amp;rsquo;s Overseas Client Base, Reaffirms Its BBB- Rating Futu Holdings Stock Shows Improved Relative Price Strength Futu Announces Plan for App Removal in Mainland China App Stores Moomoo Expands Into Malaysia Following Success In Singapore Futu Ranks #2 on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s 100 Fastest-Growing Companies List For 2022 Risks: Futu Announces Proposed Dual Primary Listing on The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong Limited Futu Provides Regulatory Update in China Futu Holdings Records Solid Growth in Q3 with US$247.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LULU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lulu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lulu/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Lululemon Continues Its Quarterly Report Winning Streak and Shows It Is Worthy of Challenging Nike Lululemon Stock Pops On High Chinese Demand and Positive Earnings Report Lululemon says third quarter off to &amp;lsquo;solid start&amp;rsquo; as N.America improves Risks: Lululemon Shares Just Can&amp;rsquo;t Stretch Very Far Anymore Lululemon Heads Toward Earnings In Weak Shape As IBD Sector Leaders Pull Back Retailers Raise Red Flags; Analysts Turn Cautious Amid Divergent Results Score:40 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: ConocoPhillips Proves Why A Gap Down In Price Is Not Always Bad ConocoPhillips expands full year production guidance with company-wide records ConocoPhillips (NYSE:COP) Looks Like A Good Stock, And It&amp;rsquo;s Going Ex-Dividend Soon Risks: ConocoPhillips Misses Earnings Expectations Despite Record Production ConocoPhillips misses on profit, hikes full-year output forecast ConocoPhillips (COP) Lags on Q2 Earnings, Ups &amp;lsquo;23 Output View Score:29 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: Li Auto Inc. August 2023 Delivery Update China&amp;rsquo;s Li Auto aims to outsell BMW, Mercedes, Audi in its home market in 2024 EVgo Charging Network Sees Revenue Soar, Uplifted By Project Tied To Warren Buffett Risks: Why Did Li Auto Stock Crash Today?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/estc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/estc/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Elastic Wins Google Cloud Global Technology Partner of the Year Award Elastic Awarded 2023 U.S. AWS Partner Award Total Economic Impact™ Study Reveals 293% Three-Year ROI for Organizations Using Elasticsearch for Search Applications Risks: Elastic (NYSE:ESTC) shareholders have endured a 18% loss from investing in the stock three years ago Here’s Why Elastic N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gh/</guid>
      <description>score:298
Chances: Guardant Health to Participate in the Morgan Stanley 21st Annual Global Healthcare Conference Guardant Health Stock Sees Renewed Technical Strength Guardant Health (GH) Reports Solid Q2 Results Guardant Health Receives Regulatory Approval from Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Health Sciences Authority for Guardant360® CDx blood test Guardant Health Secures Coverage From Major US Commercial Health Insurers for Guardant360® Blood Test for Comprehensive Genomic Profiling Risks: Further weakness as Guardant Health (NASDAQ:GH) drops 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALIT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alit/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Alight Announces Closing of Secondary Offering Alight Reports Second Quarter Results Analysts Say These 3 Stocks Are Their Top Picks for the Rest of 2023 Alight ranked as a top U.S. defined contribution record keeper by Pensions &amp;amp; Investments Risks: ‘S&amp;amp;P 500 to hit 3,500’: J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIDIY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/didiy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/didiy/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: XPeng inks $744M deal with ride-share giant Didi, linking two of China&amp;rsquo;s biggest tech names XPeng Shares Rise after Announcing Strategic Partnership with DiDi Risks: Disney defends Bob Iger, Didi gets approval to register users, FAA investigates near-crash at JFK&amp;hellip; Score:61 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: Are You Looking for a Top Momentum Pick? Why Cemex (CX) is a Great Choice Cemex and Synhelion make further progress toward the world’s first fully solar-powered cement plant Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Cemex profit climbs modestly on price hikes, strong peso Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Cemex beats profit estimates on price hikes, easing inflation Volvo Trucks and CEMEX Unveil First Fully Electric Heavy Concrete Mixer Truck Risks: Cemex Explores Sale of Dominican Republic Business Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Cemex posts surprise quarterly loss; shares drop Statement on the Illegal Occupation of Vulcan&amp;rsquo;s Property in Mexico US firm says Mexican authorities illegally seized its port terminal CEMEX Contributes to Circular Economy With Launch of Its Regenera Waste Management Score:62 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Boston Scientific&amp;rsquo;s (BSX) FARAPULSE System Study Data Positive Boston Scientific Surges As It Looks To Enter A Market Worth Nearly $8 Billion Boston Scientific Leads the S&amp;amp;P 500 Boston Scientific Reports Positive Results from Atrial Fibrillation Device ADVENT Study of the FARAPULSE™ Pulsed Field Ablation System Meets Primary Efficacy and Safety Endpoints Risks: Boston Scientific Stock Gets 81 RS Rating After Profit Pops 56% In Year EVP &amp;amp; Grp Pres, MedSurg &amp;amp; APAC Arthur Butcher Sells 6,600 Shares of Boston Scientific &amp;hellip; Ozempic Is All the Rage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Danaher (DHR) to Acquire Abcam, Boost Life Sciences Unit Danaher Buys Abcam for $5.7 Billion to Expand Its Product Offerings Here’s Why Abcam plc (ABCM) Outperformed in Q2 Abcam Highlights Successful Execution of Strategic Priorities to Drive Shareholder Value NanoString and Abcam Expand Collaboration to Advance Spatial Multiomics Research Risks: Abcam shares fall after $5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:-297
Chances: Peloton Interactive, Inc. Announces Participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference Peloton&amp;rsquo;s return to positive cash flow hit by bike recall, shares slide Peloton Interactive, Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year Fiscal 2023 Financial Results Peloton and the University of Michigan Announce Partnership Reaching Students, Athletes and Alumni Risks: Is Peloton in Trouble?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: IonQ and BearingPoint Bring Quantum Consulting to the European Market IonQ Signs Agreement With South Korea’s Ministry of Science and ICT to Cultivate Regional Quantum Computing Ecosystem IonQ Raises 2023 Bookings Expectations to $50M at Midpoint, Anticipates Doubling Bookings from Prior Year IonQ Forte Launched For Commercial Use, Making #AQ 29 Available for Customers Worldwide IonQ Demonstrates World-First Quantum Cognition Models Risks: While shareholders of IonQ (NYSE:IONQ) are in the black over 1 year, those who bought a week ago aren&amp;rsquo;t so fortunate IonQ Poised for Aggressive Commercial Growth in 2023, Sets Date to Report on Momentum and Fourth Quarter 2022 Financial Results IonQ and Hyundai Motor Company Expand Quantum Computing Partnership, Continuing Pursuit of Automotive Innovation IonQ Announces Third Quarter 2022 Financial Results IonQ Chief Scientist to Presen&amp;hellip; Score:-7 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oln/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oln/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Olin Corp. announces shakeup in C-suite Olin Announces CEO Transition Plan Olin (OLN) Acquires White Flyer Targets to Grow Winchester Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Julie Piggott Appointed to Olin&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors Risks: Why Olin Stock Is Down Today Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Olin (OLN) Misses Q1 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Olin (OLN) to Close Epoxy Facilities in Restructuring Program An Intrinsic Calculation For Olin Corporation (NYSE:OLN) Suggests It&amp;rsquo;s 49% Undervalued Score:-43 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: Why Full Truck Alliance Stock Is Jumping Today Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd. Just Recorded A 100% EPS Beat: Here&amp;rsquo;s What Analysts Are Forecasting Next Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s (NYSE:YMM) Fundamentals Look Pretty Strong: Could The Market Be Wrong About The Stock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iot/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Samsara Earnings Top Estimates On Big Spending Customers Samsara Inc. (IOT) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Samsara Announces Appointment of Todd Bluedorn to Board of Directors Samsara To Announce Second Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results On August 31, 2023 Samsara Officially Named As A 2023 UK’s Best Workplace for Women™ Risks: Samsara Reports First Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results Samsara Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Plug Power Announces Settlement with SEC 3 Best Green Hydrogen Stocks to Buy in August 2023 Plug Power Hosts Analyst Day, Showcasing the World’s First 15TPD Green Hydrogen Plant Plug Power Sales Beat Expectations, the Stock Is Tanking. Here’s Why. Why Shares of Plug Power Surged 26% in July Risks: Plug Power will pay $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Wells Fargo’s latest layoffs may signal bank is on the mend Wells Fargo-SEC settlement on advisory fees underscores M&amp;amp;A challenges Wells Fargo Is Cleared to Underwrite Texas Muni-Bond Deals by AG Wells Fargo to pay $35 million penalty over excessive fees, U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:-165
Chances: American Airlines Flight Attendants Vote to Authorize a Strike Busy Labor Day Weekend Awaits US Airlines: 3 Stocks to Watch U.S. airline passengers are finding low-cost business class fares American Airlines Pilots Ratify New Contract Risks: Pilot shortages, air traffic control are &amp;rsquo;lingering problems&amp;rsquo; for airlines: Expert American Airlines passenger lashes out at people reclining seats American Airlines may have a big problem on its hands (customers won&amp;rsquo;t like it) American Airlines fined $4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: SentinelOne raises full-year forecast, adds partnership with Wiz still on SentinelOne Announces Second Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results SentinelOne Leads the Way in XDR SentinelOne and Netskope Team to Secure Modern Workforce SentinelOne Stock: Bull vs. Bear Risks: SentinelOne scraps Wiz partnership nearly a week after bid interest SentinelOne Might Be Up for Sale &amp;ndash; What Should You Do if You Own the Stock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/riot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/riot/</guid>
      <description>score:77
Chances: Riot&amp;rsquo;s Exponential Growth in 2023: Unveiling Its Promising Trajectory 3 Crypto Stocks to Buy for 100% Gains as Bitcoin Stabilizes 3 Stocks Poised for a 100% Short Squeeze Rally Why Shares of Riot Platforms, TeraWulf, and Marathon Digital Are Surging This Week Riot Purchases 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: SoFi&amp;rsquo;s Earnings Report Was Rock Solid. Here&amp;rsquo;s Why the Stock Is a Screaming Buy. SoFi Snags Higher Price Target as Investors Show ‘More Sustained Interest’ A Bull Market Is Coming: 3 Exceptional Growth Stocks to Buy Now and Hold for a Decade SoFi Named to CNBC World’s Top Fintech Companies 2023 List SoFi Has More Than Doubled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Grab advances break-even timeline on boost from cost cuts, strong demand Grab Reports Second Quarter 2023 Results Grab Reports First Quarter 2023 Results Grab lifts revenue forecast, delivery business breaks even Grab targets Group Adjusted EBITDA breakeven by H2 2024 as it accelerates path to profitability Risks: Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Grab cuts 1,000 jobs to stay competitive Grab Holdings stock boosted despite falling delivery sales Indonesia’s GoTo Extends Stock Slump After Shaking Up Top Ranks Grab Sees Slower Growth While It Pursues 2024 Profitability HappyFresh Board Is Said to Hire Alvarez &amp;amp; Marsal for Review Score:12 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer Bob Bakish to Participate in the 2023 Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference PATH Launches Limited Edition Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem Bottles in Partnership with Paramount Consumer Products Paramount Global Drops Plan to Sell BET Media S&amp;amp;P 500 Gains and Losses Today: Index Falls as Tech Stocks Lose Ground Risks: Paramount global debt cut to just above junk by Moody’s Hollywood strikes, subscriber churn, sports rights: Big media woes Americans are canceling more streaming plans as prices balloon Traditional TV &amp;lsquo;past the point of no return&amp;rsquo; as viewership hits record low Trouble in Tinseltown: 3 Entertainment Stocks to Sell Before the Curtain Falls Score:36 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Implied Volatility Surging for Nu Holdings (NU) Stock Options This Unstoppable Fintech Keeps Crushing Analyst Estimates Nu Holdings Ltd. (NU) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Buffett-Backed Nubank Bets on Mexico for ‘Pivotal’ Growth Wall Street Bulls Look Optimistic About Nu Holdings Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/td/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/td/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Announcement of common share repurchase up to 90 million shares. Declaration of dividends and positive third quarter financial results. Positive customer satisfaction ranking for banking mobile app. Regulatory approval for normal course issuer bid. Expansion plans with new branch openings and appointments to board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Positive Q2 and Q1 earnings results announced. Announcement of unaudited financial results and transcripts. Stock upgraded to &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; by MSCI ESG Rating. CEO&amp;rsquo;s holdings reduced by 13%, but still a significant shareholder. Risks: Declining stock performance over the past year. Volatility and fluctuations in stock value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates, showing growth year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s valuation remains relatively cheap and attractive for passive income investors. Positive signs of tech-led business reimagination using AI. Better than expected Q2 2023 results reported by eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Selected by Farmers Insurance Federal Credit Union for personal lending. Potential for significant upside due to AI technology in the financial sector. Stock&amp;rsquo;s impressive rally of over 400% since May 2023. Strong performance among the best performing stocks in the last 3 and 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Under Armour reports Q1 earnings beat and maintains fiscal outlook. Under Armour launches new &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s growth strategies appear encouraging. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Positive impact from executive changes and growth strategies. Risks: Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s revenue slips amid challenging retail environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/envx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/envx/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: Enovix achieves quarterly milestone by producing 18,000 cells. Positive response to Enovix&amp;rsquo;s high-volume production facility location in Malaysia. Multiple leadership additions and appointments to the board of directors. Successful UL1642 safety certification for Enovix&amp;rsquo;s wearable cells. Participation in investor conferences to connect with potential investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Coupang sustains profit streak, sees logistics investments pay off. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat estimates. Coupang stock clears key benchmark, hitting 80-plus RS rating. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s sales beat estimates after big spending pays off. Positive momentum and growth trends in Coupang&amp;rsquo;s returns on capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Target expands key advantage over Walmart, Amazon. Target Sees Slowdown But Is Still a Strong Retail Buy. Dirt-Cheap Dividend King raises its payout to a record high. Positive analyst calls for Target. Strong consumer spending noted for retail sector. Risks: Retail theft affecting profits and outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XEL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xel/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Xcel Energy declared dividend on common stock. XEL surpasses 50% carbon-free electricity generation companywide. Intrinsic value potentially 49% above share price. Positive growth potential in utility sector. XEL is favored by institutional ownership. Risks: Q2 earnings and revenue lagged estimates. Impact of regulatory changes in the energy industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s beats profit estimates on cost cuts and leaner inventory. Earnings surpass estimates, maintains full-year guidance. Strategic efforts aiding growth in Kohl&amp;rsquo;s. Back-to-school shopping convenience and affordable prices. Positive takeaways from Q2 earnings call. Risks: Profits plunge more than 50% annually on weak sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Revenues rise in Q2 2023 despite stock slide. Positive impact of new partnership to research hypersonic travel. Boeing awarded military contract for Spirit-tied P-8 aircraft trainers. Expectation of ramping up 737 Max production by more than 20% by Boeing. Striking workers at a key Boeing supplier approve a new contract and will return to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s focus on teen safety features and user experience enhancements. Positive sentiment from analysts and investors for Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s growth potential. Strong performance in Q2 with revenue beating estimates and improved margins. Advertising benefits from &amp;lsquo;clean, wholesome content&amp;rsquo; on the platform. Anticipation for Pinterest Investor Day event in September 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docn/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Strong quarterly earnings results announced. Positive price performance and RS rating improvement. Expansion of AI footprint indicated after acquisition. Strategic bet on AI with a significant investment. Potential for growth as an AI-driven cloud services provider. Risks: Unexpected drop in stock price due to CEO transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/umc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/umc/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Positive Q2 2023 results reported. Announcement of 40nm RFSOI platform for 5G mmWave applications. Collaboration with Cadence on 3D-IC Hybrid Bonding Reference Flow. Leadership in semiconductor foundries as per Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. Partnership extension with Infineon for 40nm eNVM Microcontroller Production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Realty Income&amp;rsquo;s consistent dividend payments and yield. Positive outlook for long-term investment. Strong financial performance and revenue surpassing estimates. Investment in Bellagio Las Vegas at a significant valuation. Stable monthly dividend declarations for years. Risks: Potential impact of rising interest rates on dividend stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR-A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Expectation of another 40 years of oil production. Successful start of operations for the second FPSO at Campos Basin. Petrobras rebalancing with market through fuel price hikes. Positive investment plans in the new 5-year plan. Initiation of service contracts and radio links for offshore units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Expected to beat earnings estimates and move higher. Positive earnings call transcripts and potential value. Potential for strong rally and upside potential. Highlighted by analysts as a potential value stock. Positive financial results and profit beating forecasts. Risks: Stock price volatility and potential declines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Strong contender in the media industry with good outperformance potential. Positive Q2 earnings match and potential growth. Dividend declaration and positive financial results. Recent stock price surge and analyst upgrades. Participation in important industry conferences. Risks: Stock price volatility and short-squeeze focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Merger and consolidation efforts to enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s position. Strategic partnership with Amazon for wireless services. Expansion into the 5G network with coverage for a significant portion of the U.S. population. Positive market response to the merger deal with EchoStar. Billionaire Charlie Ergen&amp;rsquo;s influence and leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Steady dividend payouts with attractive yields. Positive stock performance and returns over the last three years. Strong institutional ownership indicating investor confidence. Q2 earnings beat and positive financial results. Potential growth opportunities with pipeline expansion plans. Risks: Shutdown of compressor station affecting operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Attracting investor attention and innovation recognition. Positive growth projections and strong financial metrics. Recognition as an undervalued stock with potential. Successful expansion into the fintech and crypto sectors. Strong user base and adoption among millennials. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Positive analyst recommendations and growth potential. Strong second quarter results and raised full-year outlook. Significant surge in stock price and momentum. Participation in secondary offerings and announcements. Recognition as a strong growth stock in various lists. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Aurora announces successful public offerings and fundraising. Expansion of commercial operations through partnerships. Introduction of new capabilities for commercial launch. Promotion of key executives and leadership changes. Participation in industry conferences and presentations. Risks: Continued losses in earnings, but improvements from previous year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wba/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Walgreens Boots Alliance named Disability:IN&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Employer of the Year. Expansion of partnership with VillageMD in Chicago. Announcement of new vaccination and testing offerings. Recognition for commitment to diversity and clinical trials. Positive dividend affirmation and high dividend yield. Risks: Bankruptcy filing and store closures by Rite Aid affecting the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/extr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/extr/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Extreme Networks surpasses Q4 earnings and revenue estimates. Extreme Networks recognized as a Gartner Peer Insights™ Customers&amp;rsquo; Choice. Favorable industry outlook highlighting networking stocks. High institutional ownership indicates investor confidence. Positive response to innovative products and solutions. Risks: Uncertain future affecting the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for outperformance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: TAL Education Group beats earnings expectations for full year 2023. Institutional investors show interest with a significant ownership stake. TAL Education Group files its annual report on Form 20-F. TAL Education Group&amp;rsquo;s strong week for shareholders doesn&amp;rsquo;t alleviate long-term losses. Top-line decline in Q3 attributed to seasonality and forex fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:-58
Chances: ExxonMobil plans to develop sixth oil project in Guyana. ExxonMobil receives award worth $77M against Venezuela. Exxon Mobil Corporation&amp;rsquo;s stock is going strong. Exxon awarded $77 million in claim against Venezuela. ExxonMobil stock sloshed higher today. Risks: Insiders sell $2.4M of Exxon Mobil stock, signaling caution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/asx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/asx/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: ASE Technology Holding achieves the best overall performance on the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. ASE&amp;rsquo;s Bumping Factory in Kaohsiung, Taiwan inducted into the World Economic Forum’s Global Lighthouse Network. ASE announces advancements under the VIPack™ Platform. ASX reports positive Q2 2023 earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Positive performance outpacing stock market gains. Grants and investments in community support projects and programs. Dividend yield and attractive payouts to shareholders. Participation in conferences and presentations to enhance visibility. Focus on core businesses and cost-cutting strategies. Risks: Moody&amp;rsquo;s watch for potential credit downgrade affecting credit ratings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VALE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vale/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Strong growth potential in the EV boom with increased demand for minerals. Investor attention attracted due to the company&amp;rsquo;s activities and deals. Emerging markets growth opportunities and significant increase in iron ore output. Positive market reaction to the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Potential for dividend yield and income growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-24
Chances: Positive potential for rebound after recent earnings report decline. Collaboration with battery materials startup for EV battery technology. Partnership with Hyundai Motor to scale up Indian operations. Investment in EV battery startup to shift future focus to cheaper materials. Interest and investment in EV market amid potential value increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Strong performance with positive earnings and revenue growth. Investor confidence due to Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI potential and cheap valuation. Successful sustainability efforts and focus on AI technology. Trending stock with potential for growth and long-term investment. Positive industry outlook and potential for technology sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:-77
Chances: JetBlue&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 earnings beating estimates. Partnerships and collaborations to reinforce commitment to customers. Positive moves in response to customer needs such as fare changes. JetBlue Plus Card receiving awards and recognition. Expansions and programs targeting specific customer segments. Risks: Potential loss in Q3 due to ending a deal with American Airlines and flight disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings beat on lower operating costs. Positive investor sentiment with notable returns in the past three years. Expectations of beating earnings estimates for upcoming quarters. Several instances of beating revenue and earnings estimates. Potential undervaluation of Southwestern Energy Company (SWN) based on analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Discussion of potential streaming partnership and deals with Amazon and ESPN. Box office success of Barbie movie contributing to business performance. Investor attention towards The Walt Disney Company (DIS). Opportunity for potential growth due to undervalued stock according to some analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/c/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Citigroup enters Latin America FX space, invests in Rextie. Citigroup launches relationship tiers, simplifies banking. Positive impact of NII and streamlining efforts on Citigroup. Strategic investment in Rextie for FX services. Citi&amp;rsquo;s focus on simplifying retail banking for customer benefit. Risks: Challenges from accelerated settlements identified in Citi survey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:-46
Chances: Uber raises minimum age for most California drivers to 25. Collaboration with Oracle and White House CancerX Project. Bullish tech stocks for market rebound. Uber CEO&amp;rsquo;s participation in fireside chat hosted by Goldman Sachs. Positive outlook for growth and investment in tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TWNK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/twnk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/twnk/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Hostess Brands reports strong Q2 earnings, beating estimates. Positive performance and earnings beat in Q1 2023. Hostess Brands completes refinancing transaction, enhancing financial position. Launch of new products like Hostess &amp;lsquo;Mashup&amp;rsquo; and Zero Sugar Mini Wafers. Participation at investor conferences and corporate responsibility efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Gap surpasses Q2 earnings estimates despite a weak forecast. Positive focus on profit beat and strong Q2 earnings performance. Gap reports profit beat and slight revenue miss, comp. sales dip. Analysts highlight potential for Gap&amp;rsquo;s growth after positive Q2 performance. Gap&amp;rsquo;s strategic partnerships and limited-edition collections contribute to opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Cruise operators plan to hike prices as demand for cruises swells. New partnerships and themed cruise offerings contribute to customer attraction. Carnival announces successful bond offerings and secured term loan facilities for refinancing. Princess Cruises season sale for South America and Antarctica shows growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:87
Chances: Strategic buyouts and acquisitions contribute positively to Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s growth amid cost challenges. Increased earnings and revenues reported in recent quarters indicate a favorable trend. Recognition in sustainability indices demonstrates Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to corporate responsibility. Positive projections and inclusion in major indices highlight potential growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</guid>
      <description>score:-48
Chances: Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenue beat estimates, indicating positive performance. Resilient demand leads to Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s quarterly revenue estimates being surpassed. Strong performance of Nordstrom stock in the midst of challenging market conditions. Nordstrom reiterates annual guidance after Q2 results exceed expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:-34
Chances: AMC&amp;rsquo;s stock conversion process completes, potentially leading to more stable shares. Wedbush upgrades AMC&amp;rsquo;s rating amid stock conversion. AMC&amp;rsquo;s preferred shares conversion approved, allowing the sale of new shares. AMC receives go-ahead for APE stock conversion, despite stock plunge. Market anticipates stock conversion, causing AMC&amp;rsquo;s shares to tumble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: Affirm shares soar on higher-than-expected forecast as delinquencies decline. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s strong performance is attributed to growth in customer transaction volumes. Affirm is well-positioned to harness changes in consumer behavior, according to the CFO. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s stock pops following analyst note on Debit+ card, indicating market optimism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:50
Chances: AMC&amp;rsquo;s stock conversion is over, and analysts predict potential for more dilution. AMC&amp;rsquo;s stock conversion receives approval, allowing the company to sell nearly 400 million new shares. AMC CEO explains stock divide following court ruling. AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s revised stock conversion plan gets approved by a judge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kr/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Kroger&amp;rsquo;s potential acquisition of Albertsons to address pharmacy deserts and provide better access to medicines could improve its social impact and customer reach. Competing with dominant retailers like Walmart, Costco, and Amazon could drive Kroger&amp;rsquo;s motivation to merge with Albertsons for increased size and scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hmy/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Harmony Gold&amp;rsquo;s upgraded Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) suggests growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, potentially driving the stock higher. Presentations from virtual investor conferences and opportunities for online viewing may indicate efforts to engage with investors and provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: United Airlines&amp;rsquo; plans to resume daily flights between San Francisco and Beijing, as well as increase flights to Shanghai, could indicate a potential for increased revenue. Collaboration with TSA PreCheck enrollment provider IDEMIA Identity and Security for an enrollment initiative at Denver International Airport could enhance customer experience and convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: BP&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, Jio-bp, is expanding its EV charging network in India, which could contribute to future growth. BP&amp;rsquo;s consideration of constructing two offshore wind farms without government assistance shows its commitment to renewable energy. BP&amp;rsquo;s joint venture with Jio-bp indicates a focus on expanding its presence in the growing EV charging market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TECK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teck/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Teck Resources collaborates with NORDEN to reduce carbon emissions in its steelmaking coal supply chain. Teck Resources works on reducing carbon dioxide emissions in the steelmaking coal supply chain through a partnership with NORDEN. Teck Resources aims to reduce annual emissions from its shipments handled by NORDEN by 25%, contributing to environmental sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</guid>
      <description>score:-65
Chances: Netflix is expanding into the gaming sector with a game controller app, diversifying its offerings beyond movies and TV shows. Netflix&amp;rsquo;s strategic initiatives like gaming and expanding its offerings could position it for future growth. Netflix&amp;rsquo;s move into artificial intelligence and high-wage AI job postings indicate its focus on innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnpr/</guid>
      <description>score:156
Chances: Juniper Networks&amp;rsquo; successful quarterly performance that exceeded revenue and profit forecasts indicates a positive outlook for the company&amp;rsquo;s financials. The introduction of Juniper&amp;rsquo;s AI platform, the Juniper Mist AI Platform, showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach and potential for growth in the AI and networking sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cah/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: Cardinal Health&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings call indicated that the company beat earnings expectations, showcasing its ability to perform well financially. The positive response to weight loss drugs and its impact on revenue growth signals a potential market opportunity and positive outlook for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:24
Chances: Moderna (MRNA) has been actively working on updating its COVID-19 vaccine to address emerging variants, showcasing its commitment to combating the pandemic. Preliminary clinical trial data indicate that Moderna&amp;rsquo;s updated COVID-19 vaccine has shown a significant boost in neutralizing antibodies against specific variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) could benefit from a bullish trendline that might drive its stock price closer to record highs. The auto and industrial chip sector&amp;rsquo;s potential for accelerating growth and profit expansion in the coming year could positively impact ON Semiconductor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-160
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing next-generation solid-state lithium-metal batteries showcases its commitment to innovative technology, which could position it well in the evolving EV industry. Despite recent fluctuations in QS stock, the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to raise significant capital through underwritten public offerings demonstrates investor interest and support for its growth initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/onon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/onon/</guid>
      <description>score:-96
Chances: On Holding reported six consecutive record top-line quarters and raised its outlook for sales. Despite mixed second quarter results, On Holding reported very strong sales and growth in wholesale and direct-to-consumer channels. The company&amp;rsquo;s revenue beat estimates and it raised its outlook for net sales, indicating potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/su/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/su/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Suncor Energy&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results were strong, demonstrating resilience despite challenges in the industry. Continued talks with TotalEnergies about buying its stake in the Fort Hills oil sands mine could enhance Suncor&amp;rsquo;s portfolio. Approval of a quarterly dividend by Suncor&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors indicates commitment to shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dfs/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Discover Financial Services&amp;rsquo; CEO Roger Hochschild resigned, creating an opportunity for leadership transition. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on digital experiences and fraud management could enhance customer engagement. Discover plans to host a business update call, providing insights into its future strategies and initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gfi/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Gold Fields reported earnings decline for the first half of the year due to lower volumes sold and higher operating costs. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pursuing growth by building new mines and searching for new gold deposits indicates a strategic approach to expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TJX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: TJX Companies (TJX) reported earnings, indicating consumers&amp;rsquo; preferences for trade-down purchases in retail chains over department stores. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to adapt to changing consumer spending habits due to inflation and high rates might positively impact its performance. TJX&amp;rsquo;s strategic pricing, merchandise initiatives, and focus on memberships could contribute to its consistent sales growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chk/</guid>
      <description>score:-29
Chances: Chesapeake Energy&amp;rsquo;s strategic decision to exit the Eagle Ford assets could streamline its focus on gas-rich formations. The sale of Eagle Ford assets to SilverBow Resources for $700 million adds to Chesapeake Energy&amp;rsquo;s proceeds from its strategic divestments. SilverBow Resources&amp;rsquo; acquisition of Chesapeake Energy&amp;rsquo;s assets could enhance operational footprint and shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COHR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cohr/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: Coherent Corp. being a global leader in materials, networking, and lasers positions it well in innovative technology segments. Upgrades from analysts and positive performance by the U.S. oil &amp;amp; gas sector indicate some positive sentiment in the market. Investor interest in the company&amp;rsquo;s shareholder letter and updated presentation could imply a focus on transparency and strategic direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hl/</guid>
      <description>score:-171
Chances: Hecla Mining&amp;rsquo;s strong silver production and its target to produce 17 million ounces of silver in 2023 could indicate potential growth opportunities. The acquisition of ATAC Resources Ltd. and the investment in Cascadia Minerals Ltd. might enhance Hecla Mining&amp;rsquo;s exploration capabilities and diversify its portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dependable dividend payer makes it attractive to income-focused investors seeking stable income over time. Strong financial performance, including robust revenue growth and consecutive dividend increases, adds confidence to Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s investment potential. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s resilience and innovation are highlighted, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to thrive and adapt in changing market conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s first-quarter fiscal 2024 results beat revenue and earnings estimates, showcasing its ability to navigate challenges in the market. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on direct-to-consumer revenues and e-commerce demand indicates its adaptability to changing consumer preferences. The launch of the &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program demonstrates Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s efforts to engage and retain loyal customers, potentially driving brand loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADYEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/adyey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/adyey/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: Adyen being among the first to complete testing and receive certification to utilize the FedNow(R) Service reflects its commitment to investing in the North American region. Expansion of in-person payment offering with Tap to Pay on Android can improve convenience and potentially attract more business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FMCC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fmcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fmcc/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: US mortgage rates have surged, with the average 30-year fixed rate reaching its highest level in more than 21 years. The increase in mortgage rates is coinciding with a low inventory of homes, which could impact home ownership. Freddie Mac&amp;rsquo;s Chief Economist suggests that the improving economy and rising Treasury yields have contributed to the climb in mortgage rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hln/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hln/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Haleon has raised its annual organic revenue growth forecast, indicating a positive outlook for demand in essential healthcare products. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on essential, over-the-counter respiratory and oral health products has led to growing volumes and consumer spending. Haleon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Halodoc in Indonesia to provide mobile clinic services showcases its commitment to improving medical care access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STNE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stne/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: StoneCo&amp;rsquo;s strong top-line growth driven by expanding clientele indicates a positive growth trajectory. The consistently above-market projection results, with significant revenue and profit growth, demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s strong performance. The Financial Services segment&amp;rsquo;s revenue growth and the positive performance of the Software segment contribute to the overall success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WOLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wolf/</guid>
      <description>score:123
Chances: Wolfspeed&amp;rsquo;s leadership in silicon carbide technology positions the company to capitalize on the growing demand for power devices in electric vehicle (EV) applications. The shipment of a Purion H200™ SiC ion implant system to Wolfspeed from Axcelis Technologies indicates the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing its production capabilities for power devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-117
Chances: Walmart Inc. (WMT) is a well-established retail giant with a long track record of performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s brand is synonymous with quality products and services. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s willingness to pay increasing dividends to shareholders indicates a commitment to rewarding investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s dominance in the retail sector, especially in groceries, is seen as &amp;lsquo;unstoppable&amp;rsquo; and offers growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Marathon&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in Bitcoin mining, including record blocks and increased operational hash rate, indicates its leadership in the crypto mining sector. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic expansion, such as its mining operations in Abu Dhabi, demonstrates its commitment to diversifying and scaling its operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Aramark recognized as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Companies for Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion&amp;rsquo; Positive movement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating. Strong performance in Q3 2023 results. Upcoming spin-off of Aramark Uniform Services (AUS) as an independent public company. Dividend payment announcement for August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: U.S. Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s removal of obstacles for completing the Mountain Valley Pipeline project. Expected completion of the Mountain Valley Pipeline project by the end of 2023. Positive Q2 2023 financial results with earnings and revenue surprises. Ratification of federal approvals for the pipeline project by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AQN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Announcement of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s CEO Arun Banskota&amp;rsquo;s resignation and the appointment of interim CEO Christopher Huskilson. Consideration of the potential sale of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy unit as a strategic move to reduce debt. Discussion of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s dividend declarations and its financial decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/smci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/smci/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Consistent profitability reflected in the company&amp;rsquo;s Profitability Rank of 9 out of 10. Impressive growth in terms of revenue and profitability with a Growth Rank of 10 out of 10. Benefiting from the demand for AI servers, contributing to growth. Delivery of high-throughput, low latency E3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOBY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/joby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/joby/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Release of operational and financial results for the second quarter, showcasing progress. Company&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing all-electric aircraft for commercial passenger service. Submission of Certification Plans to the FAA, marking progress towards aircraft certification. Annual release of Environmental, Social, Governance (ESG) report, highlighting responsible practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Strong quarterly results indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to perform well in the healthcare sector. Doximity&amp;rsquo;s leading digital platform for medical professionals positions it well in the telemedicine and healthcare technology industry. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show positive performance and potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ubs/</guid>
      <description>score:155
Chances: UBS Group&amp;rsquo;s positive news from the March Credit Suisse bailout led to a breakout and new high in stock price. Voluntary termination of Loss Protection Agreement and Public Liquidity Backstop indicates confidence in the takeover of Credit Suisse. UBS no longer relying on Swiss government assistance shows progress in the absorption of Credit Suisse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Luminar reported Q2 2023 results in line with expectations and maintains full-year financial guidance. Luminar delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with automakers like Polestar and Nissan indicate growth prospects. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s focus on advanced semiconductor capabilities and AI technologies is positioning it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vips/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Vipshop is a leading online discount retailer for brands in China. Strong position in China&amp;rsquo;s competitive e-commerce market. Anticipated release of second quarter 2023 financial results. Risks: Volatility in the stock price due to market movements. Competitive nature of China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Earnings ESP. Positive stock price performance, up 17% in the last quarter. Key appointment of Chief Financial Officer, Tim Stone. Leading global platform for the luxury fashion industry. Risks: Vulnerability of stock price to institutions due to large stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: Improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. Cooperating with an investigation into &amp;lsquo;brokerage execution quality&amp;rsquo;. Retail crypto trading volumes potentially shifting to Robinhood. Defeating an appeal by investors over restricting purchases of &amp;lsquo;meme stocks&amp;rsquo;. Risks: Regulatory and legal proceedings faced by the online brokerage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:792
Chances: Announcement of Credo Technology Group Holding&amp;rsquo;s conference call to discuss financial results for the fiscal first quarter. Credo&amp;rsquo;s participation in OCP China Day to showcase its HiWire AEC technology. Discussion about share price drop and potential concerns among shareholders. Earnings and revenue surprises reported for the quarter ended April 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mq/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Marqeta renewed its contract with Block to power its Cash App debit card for another four years. Shares of Marqeta soared after announcing the contract renewal with Block. Positive Q2 earnings report and extension of key contract could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</guid>
      <description>score:-55
Chances: Tapestry&amp;rsquo;s strong portfolio consisting of Coach, Kate Spade, and Stuart Weitzman brands. Positive earnings surprise history and favorable ingredients for potential quarterly beat. Risks: Integration challenges and execution risks associated with the acquisition of Capri Holdings. Mixed response from Wall Street and the industry to the acquisition deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APLS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/apls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/apls/</guid>
      <description>score:-69
Chances: Apellis Pharmaceuticals reported better-than-expected second-quarter 2023 results, indicating strong performance in its financials. Positive data on SYFOVRE&amp;rsquo;s reduction of nonsubfoveal GA lesion growth could reflect the potential effectiveness of Apellis&amp;rsquo; products. Equity awards granted to new employees could attract and incentivize talented individuals to join the company, contributing to its growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDCE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Chevron&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PDC Energy and the approval from shareholders could bolster Chevron&amp;rsquo;s U.S. oil and gas operations, potentially leading to increased operational efficiency and growth opportunities. Despite the all-stock transaction and expected transitional leadership changes, the successful closure of the deal between Chevron and PDC Energy may result in a strengthened combined entity with enhanced market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PENN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/penn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/penn/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Penn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s partnership with ESPN for the launch of ESPN Bet indicates a significant investment and potential growth in the sports betting market. The $2 billion deal with Penn Entertainment to launch ESPN Bet showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to diversify and capitalize on the growing sports betting industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:1294
Chances: Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; Q2 results may show increased megawatts shipment and strong margin performance from STI Norland acquisition. Array Technologies has an impressive earnings surprise history and a favorable combination for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The growth of solar energy and technological advancements create opportunities for solar stocks, including Array Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UNVR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</guid>
      <description>score:1087
Chances: Univar Solutions has completed an acquisition by Apollo Funds, maintaining its global presence under the Univar Solutions name and brand. The company has expanded its distribution relationship with Kalsec Inc. for hop ingredients in the United States, enhancing its specialty ingredient offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ENPH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enph/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Enphase Energy is strategically expanding its presence in the renewable energy market, particularly in Europe where sales are growing. The global alternative energy market is showing strong growth, offering significant investment opportunities for Enphase Energy. Solar energy is projected to become the largest source of power globally by 2027, providing a favorable outlook for Enphase Energy&amp;rsquo;s solar-based solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CPB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</guid>
      <description>score:910
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao’s pasta sauce and noosa yogurt, aims for strategic growth and expansion. The acquisition of Sovos Brands for $2.7 billion demonstrates Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing its grocery business. Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s deal with Sovos Brands offers a premium to shareholders and has positively impacted its stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</guid>
      <description>score:1237
Chances: Envista announces successful pricing of $435 million Convertible Senior Notes offering. Consistent growth in Specialty Products &amp;amp; Technologies and Equipment &amp;amp; Consumables segments drive Q2 revenues. Envista delivers positive Q2 2023 earnings and revenue surprises. Envista Smile Project completes mission trip to the Dominican Republic, providing dental care to underserved patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:1182
Chances: Gen Digital experiences a gain with positive Earnings Per Share (EPS). Gen Digital offers cybersecurity solutions, identity protection, and privacy solutions. Gen Digital&amp;rsquo;s Q1 results show strong customer growth, global expansion benefits, and Avast acquisition impact. Gen Digital releases its fiscal year 2024 first-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:1400
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s Relative Strength (RS) Rating has been upgraded, indicating potential for significant gains. The projected fair value for Datadog is estimated at $129 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. Datadog continues to experience steady adoption of its cloud-based monitoring and introduces new capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Intel to create a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s technological capabilities and competitiveness. Cradlepoint&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Ericsson in modernizing network infrastructure for Los Angeles County showcases Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s involvement in innovative and impactful projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Monster Beverage Corporation reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1% to $1.85 billion, driven by gains in brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions. Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to reflect gains from continued strength in the energy drinks category and robust product innovation plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Cybersecurity ETFs are discussed as potential investments in the growing cybersecurity market. Palo Alto Networks announced the release of its fiscal fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. Strong potential is identified in Internet software stocks like PANW for the rest of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FLR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flr/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Fluor Corporation successfully priced $500 million aggregate principal amount of Convertible Senior Notes due 2029. Fluor reported outstanding financial results, leading to a significant rating upgrade and positive market sentiment. Fluor announced its intention to offer Convertible Senior Notes due 2029, potentially raising capital for future operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsn/</guid>
      <description>score:1131
Chances: Tyson Foods CEO referred to the closures as an &amp;rsquo;efficiency play short term&amp;rsquo;, indicating potential cost-cutting measures. The closure of meat-processing plants is part of Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; efforts to address challenges in its chicken, beef, and pork operations. Tyson Foods&amp;rsquo; assessment of beef price increases points to supply issues and herd liquidation, contributing to higher cattle costs and beef prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kos/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Kosmos Energy reports positive financial and operating results for Q2 2023, generating net income of $23 million. Successful start-up of Jubilee South East (JSE) project offshore Ghana in partnership with Tullow Oil and others. Adjusted net income and diluted earnings per share figures indicate a favorable financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ELAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/elan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/elan/</guid>
      <description>score:923
Chances: Elanco Animal Health reports strong financial results for Q2 2023 and raises guidance for the full year. Approval of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s Seresto flea and tick collar by the EPA and FDA contributes to stock surge. Elanco releases Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Report highlighting enhanced governance and transparency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RLLCF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</guid>
      <description>score:1277
Chances: Rolls-Royce Holdings Plc has seen a notable shift in analyst sentiment, with no analysts recommending selling shares for the first time since 2006, potentially indicating positive sentiment and optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The company has shown signs of a turnaround and recovery from the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, with its new CEO&amp;rsquo;s turnaround plan contributing to improved profit and positive market expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:976
Chances: ImmunoGen, Inc. (IMGN) reports encouraging Q2 earnings with positive adoption of its sole-marketed drug Elahere, showing promising growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 financial results included significant positive surprises in both earnings and revenue, indicating a potential upward trend in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SOVO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</guid>
      <description>score:877
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao&amp;rsquo;s pasta sauces and noosa yogurt, aligns with its strategy to strengthen its grocery business. The $2.7 billion deal for Sovos Brands presents a growth opportunity for Campbell Soup to expand its presence in frozen meals and premium pasta sauce markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BKI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bki/</guid>
      <description>score:1173
Chances: Black Knight&amp;rsquo;s Data &amp;amp; Analytics division releases August 2023 Mortgage Monitor Report highlighting the heating housing market and rising home prices. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) dismisses federal court case against Intercontinental Exchange&amp;rsquo;s proposed acquisition of Black Knight, clearing the regulatory path for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
