<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Market Share on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-share/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Market Share on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-share/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SNOW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snow/</guid>
      <description>score:100
Chances: Snowflake Inc. is the IBD Stock of the Day as software growth stocks start off 2024 in the black after big gains last year. The company gains market share from enterprise customers, coupled with deeper adoption, improving margins and a favorable macroeconomic environment, suggesting upside potential for the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Toast received an upgrade from &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; by Goldman Sachs analysts There is optimism about the restaurant software provider&amp;rsquo;s ability to gain market share in 2024 Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies Risks: Etsy stock declined after Goldman Sachs downgraded it from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Charles Schwab shares came under pressure after a downgrade from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Elena Gomez, CFO of Toast Inc, executed a sale of company shares Score:16 chances characters count - risks characters count = 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: The acquisition by Clearlake Capital and Insight Partners could bring in new strategic direction and investment to help Alteryx regain market share. The premium of 29.1% from Alteryx’s last closing share price indicates investor confidence in the deal. Risks: Fierce competition from big rivals like Microsoft and Oracle could continue to impact Alteryx’s market position.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
