<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economy on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economy on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Food Prices Are Still Up 8.2% Online Even as Inflation Cools</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-food-prices-are-still-up-8.2-online-even-as-inflation-cools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-food-prices-are-still-up-8.2-online-even-as-inflation-cools/</guid>
      <description>Food Prices Still Rising Food prices online are still up 8.2% in May 2023, even as overall inflation has cooled. This is due to a number of factors, including higher transportation costs, rising labor costs, and supply chain disruptions.
The rising cost of food is putting a strain on household budgets, particularly for low-income families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</guid>
      <description>China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals China lost more of its share of US imports in 2022, falling to 50.7% from 53.5% in 2021. This trend has been ongoing since 2013, and is likely due to a number of factors, including rising labor costs in China, the US-China trade war, and the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Layoffs 2023: Cut Workers Now Called &#39;Among Those Impacted&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-layoffs-2023-cut-workers-now-called-among-those-impacted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-layoffs-2023-cut-workers-now-called-among-those-impacted/</guid>
      <description>Tech Layoffs 2023 Tech companies have been laying off workers in 2023, with more than 147,000 jobs lost so far. The layoffs have been driven by a number of factors, including the economic slowdown, rising inflation, and the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigerian Naira Devaluation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nigerian-naira-devaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:56:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nigerian-naira-devaluation/</guid>
      <description>The Nigerian naira has been devalued against the US dollar in recent months. The central bank of Nigeria has been trying to prop up the naira by selling dollars from its reserves. However, the naira has continued to weaken, and the central bank has been forced to raise interest rates in an effort to curb inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Spilling Into Russian Regions Adds to Risks Haunting Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</guid>
      <description>The war in Ukraine is having a devastating impact on the Russian economy. The conflict has disrupted supply chains, led to shortages of goods and services, and caused inflation to soar. The Russian government has taken steps to try to mitigate the damage, but these measures have so far been largely unsuccessful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungary&#39;s Economy Chief Floats Idea of Raising Inflation Target</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hungarys-economy-chief-floats-idea-of-raising-inflation-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 06:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hungarys-economy-chief-floats-idea-of-raising-inflation-target/</guid>
      <description>Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Economy Chief Floats Idea of Raising Inflation Target
Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Economy Minister, Marton Nagy, has suggested that the country&amp;rsquo;s inflation target should be raised from 3% to 4%.
Nagy said that the current target is no longer realistic, given the current high inflation levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Economy Remains &#39;Very, Very Hot,&#39; Larry Summers Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-economy-remains-very-very-hot-larry-summers-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-economy-remains-very-very-hot-larry-summers-says/</guid>
      <description>US Economy: Is a Recession Coming? Former US Treasury Secretary Larry Summers has warned that the US economy is &amp;ldquo;very, very hot&amp;rdquo; and that there is a risk of a recession. Summers said that the Federal Reserve needs to take aggressive action to cool the economy, including raising interest rates by more than 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBOC in Focus: Will it Cut Policy Rate This Week? (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pboc-in-focus-will-it-cut-policy-rate-this-week-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pboc-in-focus-will-it-cut-policy-rate-this-week-video/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s PBOC May Cut Interest Rates The People&amp;rsquo;s Bank of China (PBOC) is in focus this week as investors wait to see if the central bank will cut its one-year policy rate. Bloomberg Economics believes that the PBOC is likely to cut the rate by 25 basis points to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Korea Warns of Financial Risk as Real Estate Loans Fail</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bank-of-korea-warns-of-financial-risk-as-real-estate-loans-fail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bank-of-korea-warns-of-financial-risk-as-real-estate-loans-fail/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Korea Warns of Financial Risk Bank of Korea Governor Rhee Chang-yong has warned of growing financial sector risks amid a rise in real estate loan delinquencies. The share of non-bank financial institutions has increased, making it more difficult for the BOK to address financial risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLIV Pulse: Have Firms Raised Prices More Than Needed? (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mliv-pulse-have-firms-raised-prices-more-than-needed-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:31:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mliv-pulse-have-firms-raised-prices-more-than-needed-video/</guid>
      <description>Have Firms Raised Prices More Than Needed? A recent survey of investors by Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s Markets Live Pulse found that 90% believe companies have raised prices in excess of their own costs since the pandemic began in 2020. Almost four out of five investors said that tight monetary policy is the right way to tackle profit-led inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Economy to Grow Faster, Singapore to Slow, Survey Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hong-kong-economy-to-grow-faster-singapore-to-slow-survey-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hong-kong-economy-to-grow-faster-singapore-to-slow-survey-says/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Economy to Grow Faster Than Singapore in 2023 A recent survey of economists by Bloomberg predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy will grow by 4.6% in 2023, up from a previous estimate of 3.4%. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy is expected to grow by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brexit Hurts UK Investment Appeal, Hasn&#39;t Reduced Tax or Regulation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brexit-hurts-uk-investment-appeal-hasnt-reduced-tax-or-regulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:01:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brexit-hurts-uk-investment-appeal-hasnt-reduced-tax-or-regulation/</guid>
      <description>Brexit Hurts UK Investment Appeal, Hasn&amp;rsquo;t Reduced Tax or Regulation A new study by the Centre for European Reform (CER) found that Brexit has hurt the UK&amp;rsquo;s investment appeal, with foreign direct investment (FDI) falling by 25% in the two years since the UK left the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Sunday UK Briefing: Tories Risk &#39;Civil War&#39;; CBI Funding Fears</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-sunday-uk-briefing-tories-risk-civil-war-cbi-funding-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:31:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-sunday-uk-briefing-tories-risk-civil-war-cbi-funding-fears/</guid>
      <description>UK Politics in Turmoil: Tories Face &amp;lsquo;Civil War&amp;rsquo;, CBI Fears for Economy
The Conservative Party is facing a leadership crisis, with a group of Conservative MPs planning to submit letters of no confidence in Boris Johnson if he does not resign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Coming &#39;Balance-Sheet Recession&#39;: New Economy Saturday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:45:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Coming Balance-Sheet Recession China&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing a number of challenges, including a slowdown in growth, rising debt, and a property market crisis. These challenges are likely to lead to a &amp;ldquo;balance-sheet recession&amp;rdquo; in China, which is a recession caused by a decline in corporate and household balance sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Africa: Practice What You Preach Is Lesson for Zimbabwe</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/next-africa-practice-what-you-preach-is-lesson-for-zimbabwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:40:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/next-africa-practice-what-you-preach-is-lesson-for-zimbabwe/</guid>
      <description>Zimbabwe&amp;rsquo;s New President Faces Tough Challenges Zimbabwe&amp;rsquo;s new president, Emmerson Mnangagwa, has a lot of work to do. He has promised to revive the country&amp;rsquo;s economy and restore its reputation, but he will need to walk the talk if he wants to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&#39;s Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:10:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</guid>
      <description>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Economy
Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has appointed a new finance minister and central bank governor, signaling a shift in economic policy. The new finance minister, Mehmet Simsek, is a former investment banker who has pledged to restore confidence in the Turkish economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia Names Abdul Rasheed Ghaffour as Central Bank Governor</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/malaysia-names-abdul-rasheed-ghaffour-as-central-bank-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 10:36:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/malaysia-names-abdul-rasheed-ghaffour-as-central-bank-governor/</guid>
      <description>Malaysia Names Abdul Rasheed Ghaffour as Central Bank Governor Malaysia has appointed Abdul Rasheed Ghaffour as the new governor of the central bank, Bank Negara Malaysia. Ghaffour is a career banker who has served in various senior positions at Bank Negara Malaysia, including as deputy governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey State Lenders Return to Lira&#39;s Defense After Sharp Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:06:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</guid>
      <description>The Turkish lira recovered some ground on Thursday after the government intervened in the market to sell dollars. The lira had fallen to a record low against the US dollar on Wednesday, after the government suspended a program that allowed state lenders to sell dollars to support the currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippines Cuts Banks&#39; Reserve Ratio, May Extend Rate Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/philippines-cuts-banks-reserve-ratio-may-extend-rate-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/philippines-cuts-banks-reserve-ratio-may-extend-rate-pause/</guid>
      <description>The Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP) has cut the reserve requirement ratio (RRR) of banks by 250 basis points to 9.5%, effective June 30. The RRR cut is expected to free up about PHP100 billion in liquidity for banks, which they can use to lend to businesses and consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Latest: Germany Is Running Out of Workers</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest-germany-is-running-out-of-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest-germany-is-running-out-of-workers/</guid>
      <description>Germany is facing a serious labor shortage. The number of unemployed people in Germany has fallen to its lowest level in 25 years, and businesses are struggling to find workers to fill open positions. This is having a negative impact on the German economy, as businesses are forced to turn down orders or hire temporary workers at higher wages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&#39;s Win</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:56:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</guid>
      <description>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s Win Turkish banks are divided over the size of rate hikes that the central bank will need to implement after President Recep Tayyip Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s re-election victory.
Some banks believe that the central bank will need to raise rates by 500 basis points or more in order to curb inflation, which is currently running at 70%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Latest:</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:09:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest/</guid>
      <description>World Economy Facing Synchronized Slowdown The World Bank has downgraded its global growth forecast for 2023 to 2.9%, down from 3.6% in 2022. The downgrade is due to a number of factors, including the war in Ukraine, rising inflation, and tighter monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the Economy Is So Bad, Why Is the Labor Market So Good?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/if-the-economy-is-so-bad-why-is-the-labor-market-so-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/if-the-economy-is-so-bad-why-is-the-labor-market-so-good/</guid>
      <description>The Strong Labor Market in a Weak Economy The US economy is facing a number of challenges, including high inflation, a weak stock market, and rising interest rates. However, the labor market remains strong. The unemployment rate is at a 50-year low, and job openings are at a record high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico&#39;s Business Class Is Doing Fine Under AMLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mexicos-business-class-is-doing-fine-under-amlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mexicos-business-class-is-doing-fine-under-amlo/</guid>
      <description>Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Business Class Thrives Under AMLO
The Mexican business class has largely thrived under President Andrés Manuel López Obrador (AMLO). The stock market has reached record highs, and foreign investment has increased. AMLO has also implemented a number of policies that have been beneficial to businesses, such as reducing taxes and regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Markets Believe in American Exceptionalism</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-markets-believe-in-american-exceptionalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-markets-believe-in-american-exceptionalism/</guid>
      <description>Markets Believe in American Exceptionalism
The markets believe in American exceptionalism. This is evident in the fact that the U.S. stock market has outperformed other major markets in recent years. Investors are willing to pay a premium for U.S. assets, such as stocks and bonds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam&#39;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:18:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control Vietnamese Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh has urged the government to focus on economic growth while keeping inflation under control.
Chinh made the remarks at a government meeting on Tuesday, as the country faces rising inflation and a slowdown in economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mauritius Expects Debt to Fall to 60% of GDP Before 2030</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mauritius-expects-debt-to-fall-to-60-of-gdp-before-2030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 08:57:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mauritius-expects-debt-to-fall-to-60-of-gdp-before-2030/</guid>
      <description>Mauritius&amp;rsquo; public sector debt is expected to fall to 60% of gross domestic product (GDP) by 2030. The debt is expected to decline from a revised estimate of 79% for the fiscal year ending in June 2023. Lower debt will provide the government with sufficient financial firepower to face future shocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &#39;Economic Collapse&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:05:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &amp;lsquo;Economic Collapse&amp;rsquo; President Biden on Tuesday defended the recent debt deal, saying it was necessary to avoid an &amp;ldquo;economic collapse.&amp;rdquo;
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, which will allow the government to continue borrowing money to pay its bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France Dodges a Second Downgrade as Macron Plans to Slash Debt</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/france-dodges-a-second-downgrade-as-macron-plans-to-slash-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:42:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/france-dodges-a-second-downgrade-as-macron-plans-to-slash-debt/</guid>
      <description>France Dodges a Second Downgrade as Macron Plans to Slash Debt France avoided a second downgrade of its credit rating by Standard &amp;amp; Poor&amp;rsquo;s, after President Emmanuel Macron announced plans to slash the country&amp;rsquo;s debt.
S&amp;amp;P said it would keep France&amp;rsquo;s credit rating at &amp;ldquo;AA&amp;rdquo; with a &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; outlook, but warned that the country&amp;rsquo;s debt burden was still too high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India: Vedanta Chip Setback Shows Cracks in Modi&#39;s Economic Push</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</guid>
      <description>Modi&amp;rsquo;s Economic Push Hits a Major Setback
The Indian government&amp;rsquo;s $24 billion plan to boost manufacturing in the country has hit a major setback, with Vedanta Resources Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s $10 billion chip unit being delayed.
The delay is a blow to Prime Minister Narendra Modi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to make India a global manufacturing hub and comes at a time when the country&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing headwinds from rising inflation and a slowdown in growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawkish Australian Economists See RBA Raising Key Rate to 4.6%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</guid>
      <description>RBA to Raise Cash Rate to 4.6%?
A group of Australian economists are predicting that the Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA) will raise the cash rate to 4.6% by the end of 2023. This would be the highest level for the cash rate since 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Inquiry, Inheritance Tax, House Prices: The Readout</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:09:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</guid>
      <description>Key Issues in the UK News The UK news is dominated by a number of key issues in the coming weeks and months. These include:
The long-awaited public inquiry into the UK government&amp;rsquo;s handling of the Covid-19 pandemic. The government&amp;rsquo;s plans to raise the threshold at which people start to pay inheritance tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Clear Evidence: The Bloomberg Close, Europe Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</guid>
      <description>Will the War in Ukraine Lead to a Global Recession? The war in Ukraine has had a significant impact on the global economy. The International Monetary Fund has downgraded its growth forecast for the global economy in 2022, but it still expects growth of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria Central Bank Denies Devaluing Naira as Calls Grow Louder</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nigeria-central-bank-denies-devaluing-naira-as-calls-grow-louder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:45:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nigeria-central-bank-denies-devaluing-naira-as-calls-grow-louder/</guid>
      <description>Nigeria Central Bank Denies Devaluing Naira as Calls Grow Louder The Nigerian Central Bank (CBN) has denied reports that it is planning to devalue the naira. The CBN Governor, Godwin Emefiele, said that the naira is &amp;ldquo;fundamentally strong&amp;rdquo; and that there is no need to devalue it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazil&#39;s Economy Bounces Back Under Lula</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brazils-economy-bounces-back-under-lula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:08:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brazils-economy-bounces-back-under-lula/</guid>
      <description>Brazil&amp;rsquo;s economy bounced back in the first quarter of 2023, growing at an annualized rate of 1.2%. This defied expectations that the economy would contract, and was driven by a rebound in consumer spending and investment. The unemployment rate fell to 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Respite Period For UK Housing Is Over</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:06:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</guid>
      <description>The UK housing market is showing signs of slowing down, with house prices stabilizing in May after a sharp rise in the fourth quarter of 2022. However, transaction volumes are falling, suggesting that further price falls are only a matter of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats, Don&#39;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</guid>
      <description>Democrats, Don&amp;rsquo;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle In 2011, Republicans held the debt ceiling hostage in an attempt to extract concessions from Democrats. The crisis caused significant economic damage, and it could have been avoided if Democrats had not caved to Republican demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eskom Latest: Spar Retailers&#39; Diesel Bill at $35 Million</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</guid>
      <description>Spar Retailers Spend $35 Million on Diesel to Run Generators South African food and liquor retailer Spar Group estimates that its outlets spent more than 700 million rand ($35 million) on diesel to run generators in the six months through March. This is more than triple the amount spent on diesel in the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Municipal Debt Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Municipal Debt Crisis China&amp;rsquo;s municipal debt has been growing rapidly in recent years, reaching a total of 50 trillion yuan ($7.9 trillion) in 2022. This debt is largely used to finance infrastructure projects, which have helped to boost China&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan Moves to Ease Pressure on Rupee in Retail Market</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:16:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan has taken a number of steps to stabilize the rupee in the retail market. These measures include increasing the State Bank of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s (SBP) foreign exchange reserves by $1 billion, selling dollars to commercial banks at a discounted rate, and increasing the amount of foreign currency that Pakistanis can carry when they travel abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:08:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</guid>
      <description>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause European stocks rose on Tuesday after the US Congress reached a deal to avert a debt default and the Federal Reserve signaled that it may pause its interest rate hikes.
The pan-European Stoxx 600 index rose 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germany&#39;s Sneeze May Give European Stocks a Cold</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</guid>
      <description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s Recession Could Hurt the Eurozone Germany, the eurozone&amp;rsquo;s largest economy, is in recession. The country&amp;rsquo;s GDP shrank by 0.3% in the first quarter of 2023, following a 0.5% decline in the fourth quarter of 2022.
The recession is being driven by a number of factors, including the global slowdown, the trade war between the United States and China, and the Brexit uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Rupee Trap Is Adding to $147 Billion Hoard Stuck Abroad</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Rupee Trap Russia has been selling oil to India in exchange for rupees, but it has been difficult for Russia to use these rupees to buy goods and services from India. This is because India has strict foreign exchange controls that make it difficult for foreigners to repatriate rupees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</guid>
      <description>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets The European Central Bank (ECB) has warned that a change in policy by the Bank of Japan (BOJ) could test global bond markets.
The BOJ has been maintaining a policy of negative interest rates and quantitative easing for years, which has helped to keep Japanese government bond yields low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</guid>
      <description>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies The Japanese government plans to set up an official security clearance system for accessing classified information related to economic security. The system is intended to help Japanese companies win contracts abroad, particularly in areas such as cutting-edge chip technology and cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
