<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economy on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economy on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:18:32 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam&#39;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:18:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control Vietnamese Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh has urged the government to focus on economic growth while keeping inflation under control.
Chinh made the remarks at a government meeting on Tuesday, as the country faces rising inflation and a slowdown in economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mauritius Expects Debt to Fall to 60% of GDP Before 2030</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mauritius-expects-debt-to-fall-to-60-of-gdp-before-2030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 08:57:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mauritius-expects-debt-to-fall-to-60-of-gdp-before-2030/</guid>
      <description>Mauritius&amp;rsquo; public sector debt is expected to fall to 60% of gross domestic product (GDP) by 2030. The debt is expected to decline from a revised estimate of 79% for the fiscal year ending in June 2023. Lower debt will provide the government with sufficient financial firepower to face future shocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &#39;Economic Collapse&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:05:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &amp;lsquo;Economic Collapse&amp;rsquo; President Biden on Tuesday defended the recent debt deal, saying it was necessary to avoid an &amp;ldquo;economic collapse.&amp;rdquo;
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, which will allow the government to continue borrowing money to pay its bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France Dodges a Second Downgrade as Macron Plans to Slash Debt</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/france-dodges-a-second-downgrade-as-macron-plans-to-slash-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:42:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/france-dodges-a-second-downgrade-as-macron-plans-to-slash-debt/</guid>
      <description>France Dodges a Second Downgrade as Macron Plans to Slash Debt France avoided a second downgrade of its credit rating by Standard &amp;amp; Poor&amp;rsquo;s, after President Emmanuel Macron announced plans to slash the country&amp;rsquo;s debt.
S&amp;amp;P said it would keep France&amp;rsquo;s credit rating at &amp;ldquo;AA&amp;rdquo; with a &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; outlook, but warned that the country&amp;rsquo;s debt burden was still too high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India: Vedanta Chip Setback Shows Cracks in Modi&#39;s Economic Push</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</guid>
      <description>Modi&amp;rsquo;s Economic Push Hits a Major Setback
The Indian government&amp;rsquo;s $24 billion plan to boost manufacturing in the country has hit a major setback, with Vedanta Resources Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s $10 billion chip unit being delayed.
The delay is a blow to Prime Minister Narendra Modi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to make India a global manufacturing hub and comes at a time when the country&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing headwinds from rising inflation and a slowdown in growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawkish Australian Economists See RBA Raising Key Rate to 4.6%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</guid>
      <description>RBA to Raise Cash Rate to 4.6%?
A group of Australian economists are predicting that the Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA) will raise the cash rate to 4.6% by the end of 2023. This would be the highest level for the cash rate since 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Inquiry, Inheritance Tax, House Prices: The Readout</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:09:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</guid>
      <description>Key Issues in the UK News The UK news is dominated by a number of key issues in the coming weeks and months. These include:
The long-awaited public inquiry into the UK government&amp;rsquo;s handling of the Covid-19 pandemic. The government&amp;rsquo;s plans to raise the threshold at which people start to pay inheritance tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Clear Evidence: The Bloomberg Close, Europe Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</guid>
      <description>Will the War in Ukraine Lead to a Global Recession? The war in Ukraine has had a significant impact on the global economy. The International Monetary Fund has downgraded its growth forecast for the global economy in 2022, but it still expects growth of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria Central Bank Denies Devaluing Naira as Calls Grow Louder</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nigeria-central-bank-denies-devaluing-naira-as-calls-grow-louder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:45:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nigeria-central-bank-denies-devaluing-naira-as-calls-grow-louder/</guid>
      <description>Nigeria Central Bank Denies Devaluing Naira as Calls Grow Louder The Nigerian Central Bank (CBN) has denied reports that it is planning to devalue the naira. The CBN Governor, Godwin Emefiele, said that the naira is &amp;ldquo;fundamentally strong&amp;rdquo; and that there is no need to devalue it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazil&#39;s Economy Bounces Back Under Lula</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brazils-economy-bounces-back-under-lula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:08:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brazils-economy-bounces-back-under-lula/</guid>
      <description>Brazil&amp;rsquo;s economy bounced back in the first quarter of 2023, growing at an annualized rate of 1.2%. This defied expectations that the economy would contract, and was driven by a rebound in consumer spending and investment. The unemployment rate fell to 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Respite Period For UK Housing Is Over</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:06:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</guid>
      <description>The UK housing market is showing signs of slowing down, with house prices stabilizing in May after a sharp rise in the fourth quarter of 2022. However, transaction volumes are falling, suggesting that further price falls are only a matter of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats, Don&#39;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</guid>
      <description>Democrats, Don&amp;rsquo;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle In 2011, Republicans held the debt ceiling hostage in an attempt to extract concessions from Democrats. The crisis caused significant economic damage, and it could have been avoided if Democrats had not caved to Republican demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Things You Need to Know to Start Your Day</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/five-things-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:30:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/five-things-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-day/</guid>
      <description>Five Things to Know to Start Your Day The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates by 0.50% today. The stock market is expected to open lower today. Oil prices are rising today. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note is rising today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eskom Latest: Spar Retailers&#39; Diesel Bill at $35 Million</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</guid>
      <description>Spar Retailers Spend $35 Million on Diesel to Run Generators South African food and liquor retailer Spar Group estimates that its outlets spent more than 700 million rand ($35 million) on diesel to run generators in the six months through March. This is more than triple the amount spent on diesel in the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Municipal Debt Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Municipal Debt Crisis China&amp;rsquo;s municipal debt has been growing rapidly in recent years, reaching a total of 50 trillion yuan ($7.9 trillion) in 2022. This debt is largely used to finance infrastructure projects, which have helped to boost China&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan Moves to Ease Pressure on Rupee in Retail Market</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:16:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan has taken a number of steps to stabilize the rupee in the retail market. These measures include increasing the State Bank of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s (SBP) foreign exchange reserves by $1 billion, selling dollars to commercial banks at a discounted rate, and increasing the amount of foreign currency that Pakistanis can carry when they travel abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:08:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</guid>
      <description>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause European stocks rose on Tuesday after the US Congress reached a deal to avert a debt default and the Federal Reserve signaled that it may pause its interest rate hikes.
The pan-European Stoxx 600 index rose 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germany&#39;s Sneeze May Give European Stocks a Cold</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</guid>
      <description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s Recession Could Hurt the Eurozone Germany, the eurozone&amp;rsquo;s largest economy, is in recession. The country&amp;rsquo;s GDP shrank by 0.3% in the first quarter of 2023, following a 0.5% decline in the fourth quarter of 2022.
The recession is being driven by a number of factors, including the global slowdown, the trade war between the United States and China, and the Brexit uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Rupee Trap Is Adding to $147 Billion Hoard Stuck Abroad</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Rupee Trap Russia has been selling oil to India in exchange for rupees, but it has been difficult for Russia to use these rupees to buy goods and services from India. This is because India has strict foreign exchange controls that make it difficult for foreigners to repatriate rupees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</guid>
      <description>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets The European Central Bank (ECB) has warned that a change in policy by the Bank of Japan (BOJ) could test global bond markets.
The BOJ has been maintaining a policy of negative interest rates and quantitative easing for years, which has helped to keep Japanese government bond yields low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</guid>
      <description>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies The Japanese government plans to set up an official security clearance system for accessing classified information related to economic security. The system is intended to help Japanese companies win contracts abroad, particularly in areas such as cutting-edge chip technology and cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
