<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bonds on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/bonds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bonds on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:01 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/bonds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bond Bulls Bet Fed Is Right in Anticipating Low Rates to Return</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</guid>
      <description>Bond Investors Bet on Lower Interest Rates Bond investors are betting that the Federal Reserve will be unable to sustain its current rate-hike cycle and that interest rates will eventually return to low levels. This is a reversal of the trend that has been in place for the past decade, during which the Fed has steadily raised rates in an effort to combat inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOE Considers Ending Corporate Bond Sales Program</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/boe-considers-ending-corporate-bond-sales-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:55:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/boe-considers-ending-corporate-bond-sales-program/</guid>
      <description>BOE Considers Ending Corporate Bond Sales Program The Bank of England (BOE) is considering ending its active corporate bond sales program as soon as next month. The program was launched in 2020 to help businesses finance their operations during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Misses Out on Unexpected Rally in Local EM Bonds</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/wall-street-misses-out-on-unexpected-rally-in-local-em-bonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/wall-street-misses-out-on-unexpected-rally-in-local-em-bonds/</guid>
      <description>Local EM Bonds Rally in First Quarter of 2023 Local emerging market (EM) bonds rallied unexpectedly in the first quarter of 2023, while global EM bonds and US Treasuries underperformed.
The rally was driven by a number of factors, including:
Increased risk appetite among investors A decline in US Treasury yields A weaker US dollar The rally in local EM bonds has benefited EM economies by reducing their borrowing costs and providing them with more room to maneuver in terms of fiscal and monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Happening in EM: Local Debt&#39;s Surprising Rally (Podcast)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/whats-happening-in-em-local-debts-surprising-rally-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/whats-happening-in-em-local-debts-surprising-rally-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Local EM Debt Rally in First Quarter of 2023 Local emerging market (EM) debt rallied unexpectedly in the first quarter of 2023, while global EM debt and US Treasuries underperformed.
The rally was driven by a number of factors, including:
Increased risk appetite among investors A decline in US Treasury yields A weaker US dollar The rally in local EM debt has benefited EM economies by reducing their borrowing costs and providing them with more room to maneuver in terms of fiscal and monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</guid>
      <description>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets The European Central Bank (ECB) has warned that a change in policy by the Bank of Japan (BOJ) could test global bond markets.
The BOJ has been maintaining a policy of negative interest rates and quantitative easing for years, which has helped to keep Japanese government bond yields low.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
