<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analyst sentiment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/analyst-sentiment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analyst sentiment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:30:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/analyst-sentiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:24
Chances: NYCB reports Q2 earnings beat, stock rises by 5.1%. Expansion of private banking business with hires and acquisitions. Positive response to the company&amp;rsquo;s quarterly cash dividend on preferred stock. Analysts bullish on bank growth and share potential. Successful implementation of AFSVision® at Flagstar Bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s focus on teen safety features and user experience enhancements. Positive sentiment from analysts and investors for Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s growth potential. Strong performance in Q2 with revenue beating estimates and improved margins. Advertising benefits from &amp;lsquo;clean, wholesome content&amp;rsquo; on the platform. Anticipation for Pinterest Investor Day event in September 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: JD.com beats earnings estimates despite China&amp;rsquo;s economic challenges. Strong net profit growth in the second quarter. Partnership with Gucci and digital flagship store launch. Positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts. Investment potential in high-growth tech stocks. Risks: JD.com stock impacted by China&amp;rsquo;s economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RLLCF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rllcf/</guid>
      <description>score:1277
Chances: Rolls-Royce Holdings Plc has seen a notable shift in analyst sentiment, with no analysts recommending selling shares for the first time since 2006, potentially indicating positive sentiment and optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The company has shown signs of a turnaround and recovery from the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, with its new CEO&amp;rsquo;s turnaround plan contributing to improved profit and positive market expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
