<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:25:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: The solar energy industry is experiencing a surge in demand and interest, driven by increased government support and consumer incentives. Array Technologies, Inc. has recently appointed Jessica Lawrence-Vaca as senior vice president, indicating a focus on policy and external affairs to drive growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-97
Chances: Rivian has a clear path forward; it just comes down to execution. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s success as a company is masked by its meme-stock past. Stifel analysts initiated coverage of electric vehicle maker Rivian (RIVN) with a &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; rating and a $23 price target this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:49
Chances: Organon &amp;amp; Co. is set to participate in the Piper Sandler Annual Healthcare Conference, indicating potential positive exposure and opportunities for the company&amp;rsquo;s future growth. The partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence and refill rates demonstrates a proactive approach to patient care and potential for increased sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:-35
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s receiving a $5.8 billion acquisition offer could unlock more value for the company. Shareholders could stand to benefit from a potential leveraged buyout offer for Macy&amp;rsquo;s. Market watchers believe the Federal Reserve may potentially cut interest rates in the first half of next year, which could positively impact Macy&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
