<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Misses Out on Unexpected Rally in Local EM Bonds</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/wall-street-misses-out-on-unexpected-rally-in-local-em-bonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/wall-street-misses-out-on-unexpected-rally-in-local-em-bonds/</guid>
      <description>Local EM Bonds Rally in First Quarter of 2023 Local emerging market (EM) bonds rallied unexpectedly in the first quarter of 2023, while global EM bonds and US Treasuries underperformed.
The rally was driven by a number of factors, including:
Increased risk appetite among investors A decline in US Treasury yields A weaker US dollar The rally in local EM bonds has benefited EM economies by reducing their borrowing costs and providing them with more room to maneuver in terms of fiscal and monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Happening in EM: Local Debt&#39;s Surprising Rally (Podcast)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/whats-happening-in-em-local-debts-surprising-rally-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/whats-happening-in-em-local-debts-surprising-rally-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Local EM Debt Rally in First Quarter of 2023 Local emerging market (EM) debt rallied unexpectedly in the first quarter of 2023, while global EM debt and US Treasuries underperformed.
The rally was driven by a number of factors, including:
Increased risk appetite among investors A decline in US Treasury yields A weaker US dollar The rally in local EM debt has benefited EM economies by reducing their borrowing costs and providing them with more room to maneuver in terms of fiscal and monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Pitches Automakers GM, Toyota on Developing Southern States</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mexico-pitches-automakers-gm-toyota-on-developing-southern-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mexico-pitches-automakers-gm-toyota-on-developing-southern-states/</guid>
      <description>Mexico Pitches Automakers GM, Toyota on Developing Southern States Mexico is in talks with General Motors (GM) and Toyota Motor Corporation (TMC) about investing in a narrow strip of land in southern Mexico. The government is hoping to attract investment to the region, which has been lagging behind the rest of the country in terms of economic development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
