<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Q2 Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/q2-earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Q2 Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/q2-earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: Expansion of EV charging network through joint venture indicates growth potential for BP&amp;rsquo;s Indian operations. BP&amp;rsquo;s consideration of offshore wind farm construction without government assistance shows commitment to renewable energy. Positive outlook for BP&amp;rsquo;s dividend and earnings potential, with a focus on improving profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mq/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Marqeta renewed its contract with Block to power its Cash App debit card for another four years. Shares of Marqeta soared after announcing the contract renewal with Block. Positive Q2 earnings report and extension of key contract could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:1294
Chances: Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; Q2 results may show increased megawatts shipment and strong margin performance from STI Norland acquisition. Array Technologies has an impressive earnings surprise history and a favorable combination for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The growth of solar energy and technological advancements create opportunities for solar stocks, including Array Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:1179
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs (NYSE: CLF) reported second-quarter results, showing improved automotive volumes, higher prices, and lower steelmaking unit costs. The company&amp;rsquo;s external sales volumes for steel products increased by around 15.4% year over year in Q2. Cleveland-Cliffs stock price rose by 2.3% over the past week, driven by long-term fundamentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</guid>
      <description>score:1237
Chances: Envista announces successful pricing of $435 million Convertible Senior Notes offering. Consistent growth in Specialty Products &amp;amp; Technologies and Equipment &amp;amp; Consumables segments drive Q2 revenues. Envista delivers positive Q2 2023 earnings and revenue surprises. Envista Smile Project completes mission trip to the Dominican Republic, providing dental care to underserved patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:976
Chances: ImmunoGen, Inc. (IMGN) reports encouraging Q2 earnings with positive adoption of its sole-marketed drug Elahere, showing promising growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 financial results included significant positive surprises in both earnings and revenue, indicating a potential upward trend in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
