<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Q2 Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/q2-earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Q2 Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/q2-earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: Positive dividend payout of $0.155 per share. Strong Q2 profit estimates beating expectations. Ranking first in mobile app satisfaction study. Positive business loan growth. Expanding services with Fund Finance Banking Team. Risks: Interest income weakness affecting U.S. banks. Potential decline in Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Strong contender in the media industry with good outperformance potential. Positive Q2 earnings match and potential growth. Dividend declaration and positive financial results. Recent stock price surge and analyst upgrades. Participation in important industry conferences. Risks: Stock price volatility and short-squeeze focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XPEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: XPeng stock gains after Q2 earnings miss, indicating investor optimism. Positive upgrade and partnership news contribute to XPeng stock surge. Anticipated jump in Q3 deliveries and recovery hints for XPeng amid a wider loss. China&amp;rsquo;s EV market growth and increased deliveries potentially benefit XPeng.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</guid>
      <description>score:-48
Chances: Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenue beat estimates, indicating positive performance. Resilient demand leads to Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s quarterly revenue estimates being surpassed. Strong performance of Nordstrom stock in the midst of challenging market conditions. Nordstrom reiterates annual guidance after Q2 results exceed expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mq/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Marqeta renewed its contract with Block to power its Cash App debit card for another four years. Shares of Marqeta soared after announcing the contract renewal with Block. Positive Q2 earnings report and extension of key contract could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:1294
Chances: Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; Q2 results may show increased megawatts shipment and strong margin performance from STI Norland acquisition. Array Technologies has an impressive earnings surprise history and a favorable combination for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The growth of solar energy and technological advancements create opportunities for solar stocks, including Array Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</guid>
      <description>score:1237
Chances: Envista announces successful pricing of $435 million Convertible Senior Notes offering. Consistent growth in Specialty Products &amp;amp; Technologies and Equipment &amp;amp; Consumables segments drive Q2 revenues. Envista delivers positive Q2 2023 earnings and revenue surprises. Envista Smile Project completes mission trip to the Dominican Republic, providing dental care to underserved patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:976
Chances: ImmunoGen, Inc. (IMGN) reports encouraging Q2 earnings with positive adoption of its sole-marketed drug Elahere, showing promising growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 financial results included significant positive surprises in both earnings and revenue, indicating a potential upward trend in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
