<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Q2 Earnings on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/q2-earnings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Q2 Earnings on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:13:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/q2-earnings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1273 BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:1273
Chances: Institutions&amp;rsquo; substantial holdings in Bristol-Myers Squibb imply significant influence on the stock. Merck&amp;rsquo;s stronger-than-expected second-quarter earnings may signal positive prospects for the pharmaceutical sector. Bristol-Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023 could provide insights into the stock&amp;rsquo;s future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0955 EXR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/exr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/exr/</guid>
      <description>score:955
Chances: Extra Space Storage Inc. reported operating results for the three and six months ended June 30, 2023. MetTel&amp;rsquo;s POTS Transformation solution selection by Extra Space Storage could improve network intelligence and avoid significant capital investment. Extra Space Storage&amp;rsquo;s solid presence in key cities and high brand value may have contributed to gains in Q2 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1036 W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:1036
Chances: Shares of Wayfair (W) beat the market this week, gaining 9% through Thursday trading compared to a 2% decline in the wider market. Wayfair made important progress in the second quarter, particularly on the cost-cutting front, boosting its gross margin and reducing operating costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1147 MGM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mgm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mgm/</guid>
      <description>score:1147
Chances: MGM Resorts&amp;rsquo; second-quarter 2023 results gain from increased business volume and travel activity, indicating positive performance in the travel and hospitality sector. MGM (MGM) delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 11.32% and 4.80%, respectively, for the quarter ended June 2023, suggesting strong financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0934 COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:934
Chances: ConocoPhillips expands full-year production guidance with Q2 records in the Permian Basin and company-wide, indicating positive performance and growth potential. ConocoPhillips has signed 20-year deals to receive a collective 2.2 million tons of liquefied natural gas (LNG) a year from Mexico Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Saguaro export facility, providing the company with access to LNG from Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Pacific coast, opening new opportunities for revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0979 DOCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docn/</guid>
      <description>score:979
Chances: The growth in cloud computing and the demand for cloud services from startups and SMBs could positively impact DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s revenue. DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s strategic acquisitions and strong customer growth may contribute to positive financial performance in the second quarter. Enhanced offerings from DigitalOcean could drive customer adoption and revenue growth in the cloud computing market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0946 RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:946
Chances: Transocean secured a $518 million ultra-deepwater drillship contract, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s market position and revenue. The global population&amp;rsquo;s increasing energy demand could benefit offshore drilling companies like Transocean, potentially leading to improved financial performance. Positive surprises in revenue and better-than-expected revenue efficiency in the quarter ended June 2023 may be seen as favorable signs for the company&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1132 HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:1132
Chances: Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts provided an updated investor presentation for second-quarter 2023 results, which could attract potential investors and improve market perception. The reopening of The Ritz-Carlton, Naples and completion of the Marriott Transformational Capital Program may have a positive impact on Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts&amp;rsquo; financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1076 VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:1076
Chances: Viatris has the potential to be a great dividend holding due to its decently high dividend yield, stable line of business, and disruption-resistant business model. The launch of Breyna™, the first generic version of AstraZeneca&amp;rsquo;s Symbicort®, could potentially contribute to Viatris&amp;rsquo; revenue and growth in the healthcare sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery is working on bringing news and live sports to U.S. streaming platforms, which could help increase its subscriber base. The CEO, David Zaslav, is hopeful about resolving negotiations with striking Hollywood writers and actors&amp;rsquo; unions, which could potentially benefit the company&amp;rsquo;s content offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s total returns over the past decade have lagged behind the overall market, but at current prices, the stock is considered a bargain that may be too good to pass up. AT&amp;amp;T pays a high dividend that yields 7.6%, making it attractive to investors seeking passive income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0400 FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:400
Chances: Fortinet beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, reporting an EPS of $0.38, surpassing the estimated $0.34. This positive performance may attract investors interested in companies with potential for reversing their fortunes. Risks: A warning about slowing sales from Fortinet spooked investors, which could create uncertainty and potential downward pressure on the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1235 SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:1235
Chances: Southwestern Energy reported Q2 earnings with declining total operating costs and expenses, which positively impacted its results. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023, beating Wall Street estimates by 28.57% and 11.76%, respectively. Key metrics for Southwestern Energy in Q2 2023 could indicate a positive performance compared to the previous year and Wall Street estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
