<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ukraine on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/ukraine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ukraine on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>China Lobbies EU Over Proposal to Punish Firms Supplying Russia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</guid>
      <description>China Lobbies EU Over Proposed Trade Restrictions China is lobbying the European Union to scrap proposed trade restrictions on Chinese companies that the bloc says are enabling Russia&amp;rsquo;s war machine in Ukraine.
The EU is considering sanctions on Chinese companies that provide Russia with semiconductors, telecommunications equipment, and other technologies that could be used for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday
The stock market was down on Tuesday as investors continued to worry about the war in Ukraine and the impact of rising inflation.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.5%, while the Nasdaq Composite was down 1.2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Counterattack Faces Flooded Front Line</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-counterattack-faces-flooded-front-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:18:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-counterattack-faces-flooded-front-line/</guid>
      <description>Flooding Hampers Ukrainian Counterattack in the South
Ukrainian forces are planning a counterattack in the south of the country, but their efforts are being hampered by flooding. Heavy rains have caused rivers to overflow, creating a quagmire that is making it difficult for Ukrainian troops to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Default Averted, NATO Mulls Ukraine&#39;s Future: Weekend Reads</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-default-averted-nato-mulls-ukraines-future-weekend-reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 12:00:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-default-averted-nato-mulls-ukraines-future-weekend-reads/</guid>
      <description>Debt Averted, NATO Mulls Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Future Ukraine avoided a default on its debt after the U.S. Treasury Department granted a waiver on a key payment deadline. The waiver allowed Ukraine to make a payment on its debt in U.S. dollars, even though the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank is currently frozen out of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Clear Evidence: The Bloomberg Close, Europe Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</guid>
      <description>Will the War in Ukraine Lead to a Global Recession? The war in Ukraine has had a significant impact on the global economy. The International Monetary Fund has downgraded its growth forecast for the global economy in 2022, but it still expects growth of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine NATO allies are divided over whether to deepen ties with Ukraine. Some allies, such as the United States and Poland, believe that Ukraine should be given a Membership Action Plan (MAP), which is a first step towards joining NATO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine&#39;s Attacks on Russia Are a Calculated Gamble</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Attacks on Russian Territory Ukraine has recently carried out a series of attacks on Russian territory. The attacks have targeted Russian military bases, supply lines, and infrastructure. Russia has accused Ukraine of carrying out the attacks with the help of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets
Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces launched airstrikes on 11 Russian clusters of personnel and equipment on May 27, 2023. The strikes were carried out by Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s air force over the past day.
The strikes come as anticipation grows that Kyiv is on the brink of beginning a long-awaited offensive to regain lost territory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
