<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ukraine on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/ukraine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ukraine on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 07:09:24 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Ukraine Latest News: June 18, 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russia-ukraine-latest-news-june-18-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 07:09:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russia-ukraine-latest-news-june-18-2023/</guid>
      <description>Russia-Ukraine War: Latest News The war in Ukraine has entered its 120th day. Russian forces have continued to bombard Ukrainian cities, including Severodonetsk, Lysychansk, and Mariupol. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has said that the war is &amp;ldquo;entering a new, long phase.&amp;rdquo; The United States and its allies have imposed new sanctions on Russia in an effort to cripple the country&amp;rsquo;s economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Can&#39;t Depend on Ukraine Coalition to Stop China: Niall Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-cant-depend-on-ukraine-coalition-to-stop-china-niall-ferguson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-cant-depend-on-ukraine-coalition-to-stop-china-niall-ferguson/</guid>
      <description>US Can&amp;rsquo;t Depend on Ukraine Coalition to Stop China In a recent article for Bloomberg, Niall Ferguson argues that the US cannot depend on the coalition that has been formed to stop Russia in Ukraine to also stop China. Ferguson says that the coalition is too weak and divided to effectively confront China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Ukraine Latest News: June 17, 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russia-ukraine-latest-news-june-17-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 07:40:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russia-ukraine-latest-news-june-17-2023/</guid>
      <description>Russia-Ukraine War Update: June 17, 2023 Russian forces make gains in Donbas, but Ukrainian forces resist
Russian forces have made gains in the eastern Donbas region, but Ukrainian forces are still putting up a strong resistance. The Russian military has captured the city of Severodonetsk and surrounding towns, but Ukrainian forces have held on to the city of Lysychansk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s War in Ukraine Latest News Updates on June 14, 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-war-in-ukraine-latest-news-updates-on-june-14-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-war-in-ukraine-latest-news-updates-on-june-14-2023/</guid>
      <description>Russia-Ukraine War: Latest Updates On June 14, 2023, the war in Ukraine entered its fifth month. Here are the latest updates:
At least three people were killed and 13 were wounded in a Russian missile attack on the Ukrainian port city of Odesa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unipec and TotalEnergies Face Off in Battle for Russian Oil</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/unipec-and-totalenergies-face-off-in-battle-for-russian-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:13:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/unipec-and-totalenergies-face-off-in-battle-for-russian-oil/</guid>
      <description>Unipec and TotalEnergies Face Off in Battle for Russian Oil Unipec, the trading arm of China&amp;rsquo;s Sinopec, and TotalEnergies, the French oil major, are locked in a battle for Russian oil cargoes. Unipec is offering to pay a premium of $10 per barrel above the market price for Russian Urals crude oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s War in Ukraine Latest News Updates on June 13, 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-war-in-ukraine-latest-news-updates-on-june-13-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:03:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-war-in-ukraine-latest-news-updates-on-june-13-2023/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s War in Ukraine Update: June 13, 2023
The war in Ukraine continues, with heavy fighting reported in the eastern Donbas region. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has called for more weapons from the West, saying that his country is facing a &amp;ldquo;critical moment&amp;rdquo; in the war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War in Ukraine So Far Favors the Defense</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/war-in-ukraine-so-far-favors-the-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/war-in-ukraine-so-far-favors-the-defense/</guid>
      <description>War in Ukraine So Far Favors the Defense The war in Ukraine has been raging for over two months now, and it is clear that the defense has been favored so far. The Russian military has failed to achieve its initial objectives, and has suffered heavy losses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Spilling Into Russian Regions Adds to Risks Haunting Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</guid>
      <description>The war in Ukraine is having a devastating impact on the Russian economy. The conflict has disrupted supply chains, led to shortages of goods and services, and caused inflation to soar. The Russian government has taken steps to try to mitigate the damage, but these measures have so far been largely unsuccessful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe&#39;s Risky Plan to Avert a Winter Energy Crisis: Stash Gas in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/europes-risky-plan-to-avert-a-winter-energy-crisis-stash-gas-in-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/europes-risky-plan-to-avert-a-winter-energy-crisis-stash-gas-in-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>Europe&amp;rsquo;s Risky Plan to Avert a Winter Energy Crisis: Stash Gas in Ukraine Europe is facing a potential winter energy crisis due to the war in Ukraine and the uncertainty of Russian gas supplies. One way to avert the crisis is to store gas in Ukraine, which has the largest underground gas storage system in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Dam Collapse Could Lead to Global Food Shortage</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-dam-collapse-could-lead-to-global-food-shortage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:00:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-dam-collapse-could-lead-to-global-food-shortage/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Dam Collapse Could Lead to Global Food Shortage A dam in Ukraine collapsed due to Russian shelling, causing a major disruption to food production in the country. The dam collapse is expected to reduce Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s wheat production by 20%, and could lead to a global wheat shortage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Lobbies EU Over Proposal to Punish Firms Supplying Russia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</guid>
      <description>China Lobbies EU Over Proposed Trade Restrictions China is lobbying the European Union to scrap proposed trade restrictions on Chinese companies that the bloc says are enabling Russia&amp;rsquo;s war machine in Ukraine.
The EU is considering sanctions on Chinese companies that provide Russia with semiconductors, telecommunications equipment, and other technologies that could be used for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday
The stock market was down on Tuesday as investors continued to worry about the war in Ukraine and the impact of rising inflation.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.5%, while the Nasdaq Composite was down 1.2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Counterattack Faces Flooded Front Line</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-counterattack-faces-flooded-front-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:18:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-counterattack-faces-flooded-front-line/</guid>
      <description>Flooding Hampers Ukrainian Counterattack in the South
Ukrainian forces are planning a counterattack in the south of the country, but their efforts are being hampered by flooding. Heavy rains have caused rivers to overflow, creating a quagmire that is making it difficult for Ukrainian troops to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Default Averted, NATO Mulls Ukraine&#39;s Future: Weekend Reads</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-default-averted-nato-mulls-ukraines-future-weekend-reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 12:00:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-default-averted-nato-mulls-ukraines-future-weekend-reads/</guid>
      <description>Debt Averted, NATO Mulls Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Future Ukraine avoided a default on its debt after the U.S. Treasury Department granted a waiver on a key payment deadline. The waiver allowed Ukraine to make a payment on its debt in U.S. dollars, even though the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank is currently frozen out of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Clear Evidence: The Bloomberg Close, Europe Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</guid>
      <description>Will the War in Ukraine Lead to a Global Recession? The war in Ukraine has had a significant impact on the global economy. The International Monetary Fund has downgraded its growth forecast for the global economy in 2022, but it still expects growth of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine NATO allies are divided over whether to deepen ties with Ukraine. Some allies, such as the United States and Poland, believe that Ukraine should be given a Membership Action Plan (MAP), which is a first step towards joining NATO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine&#39;s Attacks on Russia Are a Calculated Gamble</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Attacks on Russian Territory Ukraine has recently carried out a series of attacks on Russian territory. The attacks have targeted Russian military bases, supply lines, and infrastructure. Russia has accused Ukraine of carrying out the attacks with the help of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets
Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces launched airstrikes on 11 Russian clusters of personnel and equipment on May 27, 2023. The strikes were carried out by Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s air force over the past day.
The strikes come as anticipation grows that Kyiv is on the brink of beginning a long-awaited offensive to regain lost territory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
