<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>credit rating on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/credit-rating/</link>
    <description>Recent content in credit rating on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/credit-rating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Truist Financial announces commitments to support affordable housing and economic mobility programs. Participation in industry conferences to present company&amp;rsquo;s strategies and outlook. Collaborative efforts with MIT Solve for social impact initiatives. Investment in hospitality commerce platform GoTab signals innovation and expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown a significant 39% increase in the last quarter, which could attract investor attention. Some S&amp;amp;P 500 constituents, including U.S. Bancorp, have experienced double-digit gains, indicating potential positive sentiment. Eli Lilly&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings and guidance, along with Moody&amp;rsquo;s consideration of credit ratings, might impact U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Bank of America&amp;rsquo;s stock has garnered significant attention, indicating investor interest. Strong influence of institutions due to substantial holdings could impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s direction. Bank of America is considered an attractive dividend stock in the current market. Risks: Moody&amp;rsquo;s downgrade and credit rating reviews for multiple banks, including Bank of America, may affect the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
