<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sales Growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/sales-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sales Growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:55:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/sales-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: PagSeguro Digital is expected to have the right combination of key factors for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Increasing sales figures and vertical market growth could positively impact PagSeguro Digital&amp;rsquo;s business in 2023. The positive trend in earnings estimate revisions suggests a potential upside in PagSeguro Digital&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TJX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: TJX Companies (TJX) reported earnings, indicating consumers&amp;rsquo; preferences for trade-down purchases in retail chains over department stores. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to adapt to changing consumer spending habits due to inflation and high rates might positively impact its performance. TJX&amp;rsquo;s strategic pricing, merchandise initiatives, and focus on memberships could contribute to its consistent sales growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: JNJ&amp;rsquo;s Pharma and MedTech units are expected to drive sales growth in 2023. Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson is set to split off its consumer health unit, potentially unlocking value. JNJ&amp;rsquo;s key drugs and new products like Darzalex could positively impact Pharma sales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
