<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>china on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in china on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur Scholar Is Missing in Hong Kong, Rights Group Says, Raising Fear of Detention</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</guid>
      <description>Uyghur Scholar Missing in Hong Kong A Uyghur scholar, Abuduwaili Abudureheman, has been missing in Hong Kong since May 10, 2023. Abudureheman was last heard from saying he was being interrogated by police. Amnesty International has raised concerns that Abudureheman may have been detained by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Rules for Business Travel to China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</guid>
      <description>The New Rules for Business Travel to China Business travel to China can be a challenge, but it can also be a rewarding experience. By following these tips, you can increase your chances of success:
Be prepared for heightened security measures. Chinese border agents are increasingly scrutinizing travelers, especially those from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Alternative to Bloomberg Terminals Quietly Limits Information Overseas</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Data Provider Wind Limits Information for Foreign Users
Wind Information, a Chinese data provider, has quietly limited the information that foreign users can access. This includes data on e-commerce shopping trends and satellite images. The move has clouded the view of the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy for foreign investors and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
