<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>china on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in china on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</guid>
      <description>China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals China lost more of its share of US imports in 2022, falling to 50.7% from 53.5% in 2021. This trend has been ongoing since 2013, and is likely due to a number of factors, including rising labor costs in China, the US-China trade war, and the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to Allow South Korean, Taiwan Chip Makers to Keep Operations in China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</guid>
      <description>The United States has announced that it will allow South Korean and Taiwanese chip makers to keep their operations in China without reprisals. This is a reversal of previous U.S. policy, which had sought to discourage chipmakers from doing business in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Samsung Exec Accused of Building Copycat Chip Plant in China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ex-samsung-exec-accused-of-building-copycat-chip-plant-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 06:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ex-samsung-exec-accused-of-building-copycat-chip-plant-in-china/</guid>
      <description>Former Samsung Executive Accused of Stealing Trade Secrets A former Samsung executive has been accused of stealing trade secrets and building a copycat chip plant in China.
The executive, who has not been named, is alleged to have stolen blueprints and designs for Samsung&amp;rsquo;s semiconductor plant in Xi&amp;rsquo;an, China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBOC in Focus: Will it Cut Policy Rate This Week? (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pboc-in-focus-will-it-cut-policy-rate-this-week-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pboc-in-focus-will-it-cut-policy-rate-this-week-video/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s PBOC May Cut Interest Rates The People&amp;rsquo;s Bank of China (PBOC) is in focus this week as investors wait to see if the central bank will cut its one-year policy rate. Bloomberg Economics believes that the PBOC is likely to cut the rate by 25 basis points to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Coming &#39;Balance-Sheet Recession&#39;: New Economy Saturday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:45:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Coming Balance-Sheet Recession China&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing a number of challenges, including a slowdown in growth, rising debt, and a property market crisis. These challenges are likely to lead to a &amp;ldquo;balance-sheet recession&amp;rdquo; in China, which is a recession caused by a decline in corporate and household balance sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI CEO Calls for Collaboration With China to Counter AI Risks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/openai-ceo-calls-for-collaboration-with-china-to-counter-ai-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/openai-ceo-calls-for-collaboration-with-china-to-counter-ai-risks/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI CEO Calls for Collaboration With China to Counter AI Risks OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has called for collaboration between the United States and China on artificial intelligence (AI). Altman believes that AI is a &amp;ldquo;global problem&amp;rdquo; that requires a &amp;ldquo;global solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Offshore Oil Drilling Expands for Energy Security</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-offshore-oil-drilling-expands-for-energy-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-offshore-oil-drilling-expands-for-energy-security/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Offshore Oil Drilling Expands for Energy Security China is expanding its offshore oil drilling in order to secure its energy supply. The expansion is being driven by a number of factors, including the country&amp;rsquo;s growing population and economy, and the need to reduce its reliance on imported oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Supports South Africa in Hosting BRICS Activities, Xi Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-supports-south-africa-in-hosting-brics-activities-xi-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:42:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-supports-south-africa-in-hosting-brics-activities-xi-says/</guid>
      <description>China Supports South Africa in Hosting BRICS Activities China has expressed its support for South Africa in hosting various BRICS activities this year. The announcement was made by Chinese President Xi Jinping during a phone call with his South African counterpart Cyril Ramaphosa on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: India Decoupling From China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-india-decoupling-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-india-decoupling-from-china/</guid>
      <description>India Decouples From China India is increasingly decoupling from China in terms of its supply chains. This is due to a number of factors, including the ongoing trade war between the United States and China, as well as India&amp;rsquo;s own economic growth and ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Lobbies EU Over Proposal to Punish Firms Supplying Russia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</guid>
      <description>China Lobbies EU Over Proposed Trade Restrictions China is lobbying the European Union to scrap proposed trade restrictions on Chinese companies that the bloc says are enabling Russia&amp;rsquo;s war machine in Ukraine.
The EU is considering sanctions on Chinese companies that provide Russia with semiconductors, telecommunications equipment, and other technologies that could be used for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Gold Binge Extends to Seventh Month as Holdings Climb</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-gold-binge-extends-to-seventh-month-as-holdings-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:21:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-gold-binge-extends-to-seventh-month-as-holdings-climb/</guid>
      <description>China continues to buy gold, adding 9.6 tons in May to bring its total holdings to 1,953.6 tons. This is the seventh consecutive month that China has added to its gold reserves.
The People&amp;rsquo;s Bank of China (PBOC) has been buying gold since 2015, and its holdings have more than doubled in that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downbeat Data: The Bloomberg Close, Asia Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/downbeat-data-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:17:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/downbeat-data-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</guid>
      <description>Asian stocks fell on Wednesday after data showed that China&amp;rsquo;s manufacturing activity slowed in June. The Caixin/Markit Manufacturing Purchasing Managers&amp;rsquo; Index (PMI) fell to 50.4 in June from 51.1 in May. A reading below 50 indicates contraction, while a reading above 50 indicates expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Traders Are Leveraging Up The Most on Record on Flush Cash</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-traders-are-leveraging-up-the-most-on-record-on-flush-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:53:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-traders-are-leveraging-up-the-most-on-record-on-flush-cash/</guid>
      <description>Chinese traders are borrowing more money to invest in the stock market, reaching a record high in June. The surge in leverage is a sign that traders are confident in the market and are willing to take on more risk. However, the high level of leverage could be a risk to the market if the economy were to slow down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday
The stock market was down on Tuesday as investors continued to worry about the war in Ukraine and the impact of rising inflation.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.5%, while the Nasdaq Composite was down 1.2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citigroup CEO Visits China as Wall Street Seeks Closer Ties</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/citigroup-ceo-visits-china-as-wall-street-seeks-closer-ties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/citigroup-ceo-visits-china-as-wall-street-seeks-closer-ties/</guid>
      <description>Citigroup CEO Jane Fraser visited China this week, meeting with Chinese officials and executives to discuss potential areas of cooperation.
Fraser&amp;rsquo;s visit comes as China&amp;rsquo;s economy is showing signs of recovery, and as the country&amp;rsquo;s government is looking to open up its financial markets to foreign investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: US-China Relations Stay Distant Despite Talks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</guid>
      <description>US-China Relations Remain Distant Despite Talks on Supply Chains The United States and China held high-level talks on supply chain issues on June 3, but the two sides remain divided on a number of issues, including technology transfer and intellectual property rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Says US Allies Can Have Productive Ties With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Minister Richard Marles has said that US allies can have productive ties with China, even as they maintain a longstanding defense alliance with the US.
Marles said that navigating the two relationships is complex and requires discussion, but he believes it is possible to have both a productive relationship with China and a strong defense alliance with the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top US Treasury Official Meets China Ambassador as Contacts Grow</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:24:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</guid>
      <description>US Treasury Official Meets with China&amp;rsquo;s Ambassador Top US Treasury official Janet Yellen met with China&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to the United States Qin Gang on Tuesday. The meeting comes as the two countries have been engaged in a number of disputes, including over trade, Taiwan, and human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Municipal Debt Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Municipal Debt Crisis China&amp;rsquo;s municipal debt has been growing rapidly in recent years, reaching a total of 50 trillion yuan ($7.9 trillion) in 2022. This debt is largely used to finance infrastructure projects, which have helped to boost China&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Buys Up Cheap Coal as Prices Fall, Set to Drive Record Imports</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-buys-up-cheap-coal-as-prices-fall-set-to-drive-record-imports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-buys-up-cheap-coal-as-prices-fall-set-to-drive-record-imports/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Increased Coal Imports China is buying up cheap coal as prices fall, and this is set to drive record imports. The country&amp;rsquo;s purchases may hit 360 million to 380 million tons in 2023, according to its top industry association. This would be a significant increase from the 293 million tons that China imported last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur Scholar Is Missing in Hong Kong, Rights Group Says, Raising Fear of Detention</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</guid>
      <description>Uyghur Scholar Missing in Hong Kong A Uyghur scholar, Abuduwaili Abudureheman, has been missing in Hong Kong since May 10, 2023. Abudureheman was last heard from saying he was being interrogated by police. Amnesty International has raised concerns that Abudureheman may have been detained by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Rules for Business Travel to China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</guid>
      <description>The New Rules for Business Travel to China Business travel to China can be a challenge, but it can also be a rewarding experience. By following these tips, you can increase your chances of success:
Be prepared for heightened security measures. Chinese border agents are increasingly scrutinizing travelers, especially those from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Alternative to Bloomberg Terminals Quietly Limits Information Overseas</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Data Provider Wind Limits Information for Foreign Users
Wind Information, a Chinese data provider, has quietly limited the information that foreign users can access. This includes data on e-commerce shopping trends and satellite images. The move has clouded the view of the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy for foreign investors and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
