<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>china on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in china on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: US-China Relations Stay Distant Despite Talks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</guid>
      <description>US-China Relations Remain Distant Despite Talks on Supply Chains The United States and China held high-level talks on supply chain issues on June 3, but the two sides remain divided on a number of issues, including technology transfer and intellectual property rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Says US Allies Can Have Productive Ties With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Minister Richard Marles has said that US allies can have productive ties with China, even as they maintain a longstanding defense alliance with the US.
Marles said that navigating the two relationships is complex and requires discussion, but he believes it is possible to have both a productive relationship with China and a strong defense alliance with the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top US Treasury Official Meets China Ambassador as Contacts Grow</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:24:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</guid>
      <description>US Treasury Official Meets with China&amp;rsquo;s Ambassador Top US Treasury official Janet Yellen met with China&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to the United States Qin Gang on Tuesday. The meeting comes as the two countries have been engaged in a number of disputes, including over trade, Taiwan, and human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Municipal Debt Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Municipal Debt Crisis China&amp;rsquo;s municipal debt has been growing rapidly in recent years, reaching a total of 50 trillion yuan ($7.9 trillion) in 2022. This debt is largely used to finance infrastructure projects, which have helped to boost China&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Buys Up Cheap Coal as Prices Fall, Set to Drive Record Imports</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-buys-up-cheap-coal-as-prices-fall-set-to-drive-record-imports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-buys-up-cheap-coal-as-prices-fall-set-to-drive-record-imports/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Increased Coal Imports China is buying up cheap coal as prices fall, and this is set to drive record imports. The country&amp;rsquo;s purchases may hit 360 million to 380 million tons in 2023, according to its top industry association. This would be a significant increase from the 293 million tons that China imported last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur Scholar Is Missing in Hong Kong, Rights Group Says, Raising Fear of Detention</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</guid>
      <description>Uyghur Scholar Missing in Hong Kong A Uyghur scholar, Abuduwaili Abudureheman, has been missing in Hong Kong since May 10, 2023. Abudureheman was last heard from saying he was being interrogated by police. Amnesty International has raised concerns that Abudureheman may have been detained by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Rules for Business Travel to China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</guid>
      <description>The New Rules for Business Travel to China Business travel to China can be a challenge, but it can also be a rewarding experience. By following these tips, you can increase your chances of success:
Be prepared for heightened security measures. Chinese border agents are increasingly scrutinizing travelers, especially those from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Alternative to Bloomberg Terminals Quietly Limits Information Overseas</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Data Provider Wind Limits Information for Foreign Users
Wind Information, a Chinese data provider, has quietly limited the information that foreign users can access. This includes data on e-commerce shopping trends and satellite images. The move has clouded the view of the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy for foreign investors and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
