<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logistics on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/logistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logistics on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/logistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ups/</guid>
      <description>score:164
Chances: UPS customers in Taiwan can now leverage the power of the global logistics service provider&amp;rsquo;s network to export 30% more volume and get their shipments delivered within two business days to over 56 countries in Europe. Risks: High costs pose a significant threat to UPS investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHRW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chrw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chrw/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: C.H. Robinson Worldwide, Inc. operates in multiple segments, including North American Surface Transportation and Global Forwarding, which indicates diversified revenue streams. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion and automation initiatives, such as touchless appointments for truckload scheduling, demonstrate a commitment to efficiency and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:237
Chances: DoorDash stock received an upgrade to Overweight from Equal-Weight at Morgan Stanley, signaling positive sentiment from analysts The company continues to deliver peer-leading and better-than-expected consumer spend and gross order value results, indicating strong performance across its expanding platform DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Community Impact Report demonstrates positive impact on merchants, consumers, and Dashers, showing the company&amp;rsquo;s positive influence in the community Risks: DoorDash struggles to return to pre-pandemic levels of growth, trailing behind leading competitor Uber in key metrics The company missed on earnings expectations for Q4 2023, reporting an EPS of $-0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
