<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Institutional Investors on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/institutional-investors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Institutional Investors on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:36:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/institutional-investors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnq/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Canadian Natural Resources expects the Trans Mountain expansion project to proceed, which could benefit the company. Institutional investors control a significant portion of CNQ&amp;rsquo;s shares, indicating confidence in the stock. The company reported strong Q2 2023 earnings with sales beating estimates, suggesting a positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BROS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bros/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Dutch Bros raises guidance as profit doubles, indicating strong financial performance. The company is focused on new markets and expansion, which may lead to growth opportunities. Dutch Bros reports second-quarter 2023 financial results, reflecting positive performance. The company has caught the attention of institutional investors with a sizeable 35% stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: RTX secured a $277 million contract for Excalibur 155 mm projectiles, indicating potential growth opportunities. The company is attracting institutional investors, with 81% ownership among them, which could signal investor confidence. RTX is involved in the development of advanced technology solutions for the aerospace and defense sector, a growing industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:107
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. (MRK) is a favorite among institutional investors, with 78% institutional ownership, indicating institutional confidence. Merck received approval to expand the indication of its ERVEBO® Ebola Zaire Vaccine to include children aged 1 year and older, potentially expanding its market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mo/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: Altria Group, Inc. (MO) has the favor of institutional owners who hold 60% of the company, indicating institutional confidence. MO recently raised its dividend, making it an attractive option for passive income investors seeking reliable dividend stocks. The stock has outpaced stock market gains, reflecting its strong performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDLZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mdlz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mdlz/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Mondelez International (MDLZ) reported better-than-expected Q2 earnings and raised its full-year sales guidance, leading to a rise in its stock price. MDLZ is favored by institutional investors who own 79% of the company, indicating strong institutional confidence. The company thrives on strategic buyouts and demonstrates strength in the snacking category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Coupang sustains profit streak, sees logistics investments pay off. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat estimates. Coupang stock clears key benchmark, hitting 80-plus RS rating. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s sales beat estimates after big spending pays off. Positive momentum and growth trends in Coupang&amp;rsquo;s returns on capital.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
