<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dividend yield on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-yield/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dividend yield on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:33:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-yield/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mo/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Altria Group&amp;rsquo;s dividend yield is now at 8.8%, potentially attractive for investors. Altria reports narrow earnings beat and maintains profit forecast for the future. Altria&amp;rsquo;s demand for nicotine pouches contributes to beating revenue and profit expectations. Altria reaffirms 2023 full-year earnings guidance after second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Steady dividend payouts with attractive yields. Positive stock performance and returns over the last three years. Strong institutional ownership indicating investor confidence. Q2 earnings beat and positive financial results. Potential growth opportunities with pipeline expansion plans. Risks: Shutdown of compressor station affecting operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wba/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Walgreens Boots Alliance named Disability:IN&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Employer of the Year. Expansion of partnership with VillageMD in Chicago. Announcement of new vaccination and testing offerings. Recognition for commitment to diversity and clinical trials. Positive dividend affirmation and high dividend yield. Risks: Bankruptcy filing and store closures by Rite Aid affecting the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Positive performance outpacing stock market gains. Grants and investments in community support projects and programs. Dividend yield and attractive payouts to shareholders. Participation in conferences and presentations to enhance visibility. Focus on core businesses and cost-cutting strategies. Risks: Moody&amp;rsquo;s watch for potential credit downgrade affecting credit ratings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VALE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vale/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Strong growth potential in the EV boom with increased demand for minerals. Investor attention attracted due to the company&amp;rsquo;s activities and deals. Emerging markets growth opportunities and significant increase in iron ore output. Positive market reaction to the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Potential for dividend yield and income growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: Strong dividend yield of over 8% and potential growth opportunities. Insider buying activity by EVP and significant share purchases by Kelcy Warren. Attracting investor attention due to potential growth and income prospects. Potential M&amp;amp;A opportunities and expansion in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T generates growth in a stagnant industry, offering potential opportunities. Launch of 5G wireless home internet and catching up to rivals is a positive sign. High dividend yield, potential passive income, and undervalued stock are favorable factors. Positive moves like expanding Xfinity 10G Network and 5G wireless home internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:178
Chances: Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, which could drive the stock higher in the near term. Stocks like GGB are attracting investor attention due to their higher dividend yields compared to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
