<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cloud-based technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/cloud-based-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cloud-based technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:06:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/cloud-based-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ALIT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alit/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Alight Inc has signed a significant agreement to sell its Professional Services segment and its Payroll &amp;amp; HCM Outsourcing businesses, which could result in a positive financial impact. The company has been making strategic moves to strengthen its technology and enhance competitiveness, as stated by CEO Stephan Scholl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docu/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: DocuSign has seen significant share price rise in the past couple of months Direct lenders and Wall Street banks are in talks to provide financing for a potential buyout of DocuSign The firm provides cloud-based electronic signature solutions, which are in high demand as businesses and individuals look for secure and efficient ways to collect information and automate workflows Risks: The potential buyout and financing could introduce some uncertainty in the stock price Competition in the e-signature industry could pose a risk to DocuSign’s market share and growth prospects Market volatility and economic conditions may impact the demand for electronic signature solutions Score:88 chances characters count - risks characters count = 88</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
