<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stock valuation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-valuation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stock valuation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-valuation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:567
Chances: The digital payment giant&amp;rsquo;s transaction take rates are still declining. A single quarter could be worth more than $200 &amp;ndash; and it has nothing to do with inflation. Companies are cutting staff and focusing on efficiency amid a commitment to do more with less following a year of widespread layoffs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNOW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snow/</guid>
      <description>score:-363
Chances: Long-term AI tailwinds could turn $2,000 and some patience into big-time returns. Certain Wall Street analysts see substantial upside for Snowflake and Sea Limited shareholders. The trend toward cloud optimization is beginning to wane. Snowflake&amp;rsquo;s growth potential comes from an ever increasing need to store and analyze larger amounts of data securely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Shares of ZoomInfo jumped 6.9% after a notable analyst upgrade, indicating positive market sentiment towards the stock. The stock trades at a 50% discount valuation to its software peers, leaving lots of runway for multiple expansion. Risks: The company is considered controversial, which could lead to increased volatility in the stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-89
Chances: One Nasdaq 100 component, with a slew of competitive advantages, is cheaper than it&amp;rsquo;s ever been as a publicly traded company Three historically inexpensive, brand-name companies owned by one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful investors are ripe for the picking in December Recent filings with the SEC have revealed that Gilchrist Malcolm Ian Grant, a director of Liberty SiriusXM Group (NASDAQ:LSXMA), sold 3,258 shares of the company on November 28, 2023 Risks: You probably had a good month in the markets, but a fifth of the stocks out there are trading lower through the rally The Oracle of Omaha&amp;rsquo;s company is requesting secrecy as it builds up its stake in one or more businesses This year has been a little dry when it comes to Warren Buffett stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
