<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Valuation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-valuation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Valuation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-valuation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:251
Chances: Oracle Corp. has recently been recognized by Gartner for its cloud database solutions and autonomous database for transaction processing, demonstrating the company&amp;rsquo;s strong position in the cloud database management market. The introduction of new capabilities to Oracle Fusion Cloud Enterprise Performance Management (EPM) in conjunction with Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s implementation services shows Oracle&amp;rsquo;s commitment to meeting the complex tax requirements of multinational organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:83
Chances: Southwestern Energy Co. engages in the exploration, development, and production of natural gas, oil, and natural gas liquids (NGLs) Optimism prevails in the renewable energy industry despite recent downturns in renewable energy companies The United States is rich in natural gas resources found in multiple key basins and regions Risks: Recent downturns in renewable energy companies such as FirstSolar and Plug Power may impact the overall performance of the renewable energy sector Investors should be cautious about investing in &amp;lsquo;story stocks&amp;rsquo; that promise to be &amp;rsquo;the next big thing&amp;rsquo; Score:83 chances characters count - risks characters count = 83</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-89
Chances: One Nasdaq 100 component, with a slew of competitive advantages, is cheaper than it&amp;rsquo;s ever been as a publicly traded company Three historically inexpensive, brand-name companies owned by one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful investors are ripe for the picking in December Recent filings with the SEC have revealed that Gilchrist Malcolm Ian Grant, a director of Liberty SiriusXM Group (NASDAQ:LSXMA), sold 3,258 shares of the company on November 28, 2023 Risks: You probably had a good month in the markets, but a fifth of the stocks out there are trading lower through the rally The Oracle of Omaha&amp;rsquo;s company is requesting secrecy as it builds up its stake in one or more businesses This year has been a little dry when it comes to Warren Buffett stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
