<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:37:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1003 MWA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mwa/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Mueller Water Products achieved net sales of $326.6 million in the third quarter, which may indicate positive revenue performance. Mueller Water Products announced a quarterly dividend of 6.10 cents per share, which could attract income-focused investors. The stock increased significantly by 22% over a specific period, suggesting potential positive momentum in MWA&amp;rsquo;s stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1178 EOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eog/</guid>
      <description>score:1178
Chances: EOG Resources&amp;rsquo; Q2 earnings benefited from higher oil equivalent production volumes, which may indicate positive performance and growth potential. Year to date, EOG Resources has generated free cash flow of $2.1 billion, which is a positive indicator of the company&amp;rsquo;s financial strength and cash generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1003 FE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fe/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: FirstEnergy&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings were better than expected, benefiting from utility investment programs and lower operating expenses. American Transmission Systems, Inc., a subsidiary of FirstEnergy Corp., is making efforts to ensure the regional electric grid remains reliable and resilient, which may positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0736 DXC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dxc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dxc/</guid>
      <description>score:736
Chances: DXC Technology&amp;rsquo;s Q1 earnings decline is partially offset by a lower share count, which may positively impact its bottom line in future quarters. DXC Technology has announced a new multi-year agreement with AT&amp;amp;T to provide end-to-end support for a portion of its IT infrastructure operations, which may lead to potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0871 HL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hl/</guid>
      <description>score:871
Chances: Hecla Mining&amp;rsquo;s silver production for the second quarter of 2023 is on track to reach 3.8 million ounces, contributing to a total target of 17 million ounces for the year. The acquisition of ATAC Resources Ltd. and the investment in Cascadia Minerals Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1022 CTSH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctsh/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cognizant Technology Solutions Corp has been making waves in the stock market, with a high GF Score of 93 out of 100, indicating the highest outperformance potential. On August 3, 2023, Cognizant Technology Solutions Corp saw a 5.49% gain, reaching a stock price of $68.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0681 EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:681
Chances: Expedia Group, Inc. beat earnings expectations in the second quarter of 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89, higher than the expected $2.32. Earnings reports from online travel companies, including Expedia, show that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer trips, indicating strengthening travel demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: PPL Corporation reported second-quarter 2023 earnings, indicating ongoing capital investments and operation cost savings. PPL has been recognized for cultivating a collaborative, inclusive, and equitable culture, ranking No. 4 on DiversityInc&amp;rsquo;s Top Utilities list. PPL Electric Utilities is enhancing the reliability of its power delivery to customers through innovative technology, Dynamic Line Rating (DLR).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0922 TXN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/txn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/txn/</guid>
      <description>score:922
Chances: Texas Instruments has typically been seen as a safe-haven blue-chip stock, with the largest scale and lowest-cost manufacturing in analog and embedded chips. The company&amp;rsquo;s disciplined expansion and focus on &amp;lsquo;mature&amp;rsquo; chip manufacturing have led to sustained free-cash-flow-per-share growth. Semiconductors are increasingly crucial as economies become more digitized, which bodes well for top semiconductor stocks like Texas Instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0848 SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:848
Chances: Spirit AeroSystems&amp;rsquo; Q2 revenues of $1,365 million surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 7.4%, indicating strong performance in the quarter. The top line of Spirit AeroSystems rose 8% on a year-over-year basis, which may signal growth in the company&amp;rsquo;s business. Although the stock reported disappointing Q2 results, there may be a chance for a turnaround if the supply chain issues and labor costs are effectively addressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1025 JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: The projected fair value for JD.com is US$63.64 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity, suggesting potential upside in the stock. JD.com plans to release its unaudited financial results for the three months and six months ended June 30, 2023, which could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1222 MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1222
Chances: Manulife Investment Management has announced new leadership appointments on its real estate investment team, which could lead to a stronger global real estate investment strategy and portfolio growth. Investing in dividend-paying stocks like Manulife Financial may provide steady returns amid market volatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1084 KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper appointed Monique Oxender as Interim Chief Corporate Affairs Officer, which could bring positive changes and strengthen corporate responsibility. The company&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results showed increases in sales and earnings, driven by continued brand strength and significant pricing, indicating positive business performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0929 VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:929
Chances: V.F. Corp reported a daily gain of 3.78% with an EPS of $0.3, which could indicate positive market sentiment and earnings performance. VF Corp&amp;rsquo;s First Quarter 2024 Earnings Call indicated that the company beat earnings expectations, which could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1140 WBA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wba/</guid>
      <description>score:1140
Chances: Walgreens Boots Alliance sold some AmerisourceBergen Corp&amp;rsquo;s shares for about $1.85 billion, further cutting its ownership in the drug distributor, and plans to use the proceeds to pay down debt and for general corporate purposes. Walgreens is offering flu and respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccination appointments nationwide, which could attract customers and contribute to its revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0800 PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:800
Chances: PDD Holdings, an online seller founded in China, has started selling to Japan, marking its first foray into the Asian market and potentially expanding its customer base. China is the world&amp;rsquo;s No. 2 economy and home to several companies that trade in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1220 FSLY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsly/</guid>
      <description>score:1220
Chances: Fastly delivered significantly stronger-than-expected second-quarter results, with revenue climbing 20% year over year to $122.8 million, well above guidance and analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic initiatives to simplify its go-to-market, increase innovation velocity, and drive operational rigor and cost control are expected to contribute to its growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1058 TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:1058
Chances: Toast announced the launch of Toast Catering &amp;amp; Events, a new product integrated with the Toast point-of-sale to help restaurants manage large catering orders and event planning. Toast&amp;rsquo;s customizable banquet event orders (BEO), fulfillment tools, and lead management functionality in Toast Catering &amp;amp; Events could provide growth opportunities for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1025 DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: DoorDash reported record delivery orders and revenue in the second quarter, showing consumers&amp;rsquo; commitment to takeout despite rising prices. Strong demand for food and household essentials led to higher spending on the delivery of these items, prompting DoorDash to raise its full-year guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1103 ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:1103
Chances: ON Semiconductor exceeded expectations in its second-quarter 2023 results, driven by strong sales of chips for automotive and industrial applications. The company&amp;rsquo;s business transformation efforts led to profitable growth, with $100 million in business closeouts in Q2 2023 and $400 million since 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1016 VOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vod/</guid>
      <description>score:1016
Chances: Vodafone Group&amp;rsquo;s biggest shareholder is pushing ahead with an ambitious global expansion strategy. Vodafone secured a deal with 1&amp;amp;1 AG to provide 5G coverage in Germany, potentially boosting its market presence. Warburg Pincus is among potential suitors for Vodafone Group&amp;rsquo;s Spanish business, indicating potential business opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1071 JCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jci/</guid>
      <description>score:1071
Chances: Johnson Controls&amp;rsquo; fiscal Q3 results show strength in the HVAC &amp;amp; Controls and Fire &amp;amp; Security businesses. The company reported solid quarterly numbers, including a record backlog, which indicates positive performance. Cost-control measures and improving supply chains are likely to have aided Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1169 GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:1169
Chances: Gen Digital Inc experienced a 6.44% gain recently, with a positive Earnings Per Share (EPS) of 2.12. Q1 results reflect strong customer growth and benefits from global business expansion and the Avast acquisition, leading to year-over-year growth in revenues and bookings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1243 ABC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abc/</guid>
      <description>score:1243
Chances: AmerisourceBergen raised its full-year profit forecast, indicating positive performance driven by strong demand for specialty medicines. The drug distributor has been benefiting from specialty drugs, which are high-cost medications treating diseases like cancer and rheumatoid arthritis. The fiscal third-quarter 2023 results showed segmental growth, suggesting potential for increased revenue and earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1185 AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:1185
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters now expects revenue for the quarter to be flat to a year earlier, indicating potential positive results. The company expects operating income to exceed previous guidance, suggesting better financial performance. The focus on American Eagle&amp;rsquo;s iconic jeans through a back-to-school campaign could drive sales and brand engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1121 GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:1121
Chances: The back-to-school season shopping is projected to hit $135 billion, which could benefit Gap, Inc. (GPS). Gap, Inc. will report its second quarter fiscal 2023 financial results, presenting potential opportunities. Gap and LoveShackFancy announce a limited-edition capsule collection, merging Gap&amp;rsquo;s iconic styles with LoveShackFancy&amp;rsquo;s vintage-inspired florals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1116 IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings show an encouraging adoption of the sole-marketed drug Elahere. ImmunoGen delivered better-than-expected earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company announced a multi-target license and option agreement to develop next-generation antibody-drug conjugates. ImmunoGen made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) momentum stocks list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1120 CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:1120
Chances: Demand for EV charging is set to rise due to the increasing adoption of electric vehicles. International Energy Agency data indicates significant growth in electric vehicle sales, promising potential for EV charging companies. ChargePoint announced a new credit agreement, which may boost its financial position and growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1151 CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:1151
Chances: Coupang&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$25.12 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. E-commerce industry indicators, such as predictions of growth for Amazon and other players, suggest a potential bounce back for Coupang. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s stock saw a double-digit share price rise in the recent past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1273 BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:1273
Chances: Institutions&amp;rsquo; substantial holdings in Bristol-Myers Squibb imply significant influence on the stock. Merck&amp;rsquo;s stronger-than-expected second-quarter earnings may signal positive prospects for the pharmaceutical sector. Bristol-Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023 could provide insights into the stock&amp;rsquo;s future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0955 EXR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/exr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/exr/</guid>
      <description>score:955
Chances: Extra Space Storage Inc. reported operating results for the three and six months ended June 30, 2023. MetTel&amp;rsquo;s POTS Transformation solution selection by Extra Space Storage could improve network intelligence and avoid significant capital investment. Extra Space Storage&amp;rsquo;s solid presence in key cities and high brand value may have contributed to gains in Q2 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1036 W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:1036
Chances: Shares of Wayfair (W) beat the market this week, gaining 9% through Thursday trading compared to a 2% decline in the wider market. Wayfair made important progress in the second quarter, particularly on the cost-cutting front, boosting its gross margin and reducing operating costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1139 AMCR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</guid>
      <description>score:1139
Chances: Amcor plc (AMCR) will announce its Full Year 2023 results after the US market closes on August 16, 2023. Amcor announced its latest Amcor Lift-Off winner, Greyparrot, a growth-stage start-up that will receive a $500,000 investment and access to Amcor&amp;rsquo;s world-class capabilities in sustainability and packaging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1383 DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:1383
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s (DDOG) second-quarter results are likely to reflect the steady adoption of its cloud-based monitoring and introduction of new capabilities. Pinecone&amp;rsquo;s integration with Datadog, Inc. (DDOG) means developers now have access to enterprise-grade observability and monitoring capabilities that allow them to build and maintain high-performance GenAI applications more quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1038 MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:1038
Chances: Medical Properties Trust (MPW) is a real estate investment trust (REIT) that invests in hospitals, which could benefit from the potential recovery in the healthcare sector post-pandemic. Investors seeking high dividend yields may consider Medical Properties Trust (MPW), as it currently offers a dividend yield of about 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1097 SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:1097
Chances: Charles Schwab Corporation is about to trade ex-dividend, which could attract income-seeking investors looking for dividends. The decline in active users reported by Robinhood in the last quarter may present an opportunity for Charles Schwab&amp;rsquo;s retirement business to attract young investors seeking better retirement savings options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 KOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kos/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Kosmos Energy announced the successful start-up of the Jubilee South East (JSE) project offshore Ghana, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The financial results for the first quarter of 2023 indicate that Kosmos Energy generated a net income of $83 million and an adjusted net income of $78 million, reflecting potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1116 TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor is the leading contract chip manufacturer in the world, making it an intriguing investment with its crucial position in the market. The demand for artificial intelligence (AI) and the potential for large language models (LLMs) to improve search capabilities could positively impact Taiwan Semiconductor&amp;rsquo;s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1032 INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:1032
Chances: Infosys&amp;rsquo; first-quarter results reflect the benefits of strong demand for cloud, data analytics, IoT, and security products amid the ongoing digital transformation wave. Easing odds of a recession in the US and the emergence of artificial intelligence as a potential new source of revenue drive a rebound in Indian IT companies&amp;rsquo; stocks, including Infosys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1118 S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:1118
Chances: SentinelOne is a company helping to counteract the increase in cybersecurity threats by employing its own AI technologies to identify and stamp out threats. SentinelLabs announced a stellar lineup of speakers for LABScon 2023, the premier cybersecurity research conference, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s expertise in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1108 LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:1108
Chances: Li Auto deliveries surpassed 30,000 for the second straight month, with Li keeping the top spot among startups. Chinese electric-vehicle makers Li Auto, XPeng, and NIO deliver a combined 65,604 vehicles in July, a record and up more than 100% from last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0791 GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:791
Chances: Goodyear India reported a higher quarterly profit as a drop in raw material prices helped make up for its first revenue fall in 12 quarters. The Goodyear Tire &amp;amp; Rubber Company reported results for the second quarter 2023 in an Investor Letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1035 RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: Alison Rand has been appointed to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Financial Corporation announced an increase in its dividend from last year&amp;rsquo;s. Higher NII on the back of decent loan demand and rising rates supported Regions Financial&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 AES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aes/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: AES&amp;rsquo; Q2 revenues of $3,027 million beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 5.2%. The AES Corporation reported financial results for Q2 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s GF Value suggests that it&amp;rsquo;s modestly undervalued. AES declared a quarterly common stock dividend of $0.1659 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0923 BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:923
Chances: BP stock raised its dividend by 10% and announced a new $1 billion buyback program. HSBC&amp;rsquo;s profit jump in the second quarter may have positive implications for BP as well. BP reported a surplus of $2.3 billion, and its stock is near an early entry point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0947 BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:947
Chances: KE Holdings stock had its Relative Strength (RS) Rating upgraded from 70 to 83, indicating potential for bigger gains. The company joins the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;1t.org&amp;rdquo; China Action community, supporting tree planting and ecosystem restoration goals. BEKE, along with other stocks, made it to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) growth stocks list, suggesting positive sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 AVTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avtr/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Avantor achieved a Bronze Medal from EcoVadis, placing it in the top 50% of assessed companies, which reflects positively on its sustainability efforts. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion plans and focus on creating customized workflow solutions may provide growth opportunities for Avantor. Avantor&amp;rsquo;s culture of development and commitment to aligning associates&amp;rsquo; growth could contribute to a positive work environment and potential business growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1006 MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:1006
Chances: Investors are looking to buy Marvell Technology stock as it is considered a relatively cheap AI stock, which could attract more investment. Marvell Technology is a top AI chip stock and a key player in the AI industry, which is experiencing a surge in stock values due to AI advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1140 GFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gfi/</guid>
      <description>score:1140
Chances: Gold Fields plans to pursue growth by building new mines and exploring new gold deposits, which may contribute to future revenue and expansion. The company is investing in new operations, focusing on regions like Canada and Latin America with lucrative gold deposits, potentially increasing profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1049 X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:1049
Chances: United States Steel Corp. is exploring the use of artificial intelligence, robotics, and automation in its operations, showing its commitment to technological advancements and efficiency. US Steel Corp.&amp;rsquo;s Big River expansions proceeding on track and on time may contribute to business growth and increased demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1147 MGM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mgm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mgm/</guid>
      <description>score:1147
Chances: MGM Resorts&amp;rsquo; second-quarter 2023 results gain from increased business volume and travel activity, indicating positive performance in the travel and hospitality sector. MGM (MGM) delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 11.32% and 4.80%, respectively, for the quarter ended June 2023, suggesting strong financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0934 COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:934
Chances: ConocoPhillips expands full-year production guidance with Q2 records in the Permian Basin and company-wide, indicating positive performance and growth potential. ConocoPhillips has signed 20-year deals to receive a collective 2.2 million tons of liquefied natural gas (LNG) a year from Mexico Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Saguaro export facility, providing the company with access to LNG from Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Pacific coast, opening new opportunities for revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1346 BTE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bte/</guid>
      <description>score:1346
Chances: Baytex Energy Corp. released its 2022 Environment, Social and Governance (ESG) Report, demonstrating a commitment to transparency and accountability, and managing the environmental and social impacts of its business. Baytex Energy Corp. reports its operating and financial results for the three and six months ended June 30, 2023, following the Ranger transaction, positioning the company as a well-capitalized and diversified North American exploration and production company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1177 GSAT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gsat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gsat/</guid>
      <description>score:1177
Chances: Globalstar delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 100% and 6.75%, respectively, for the quarter ended June 2023, indicating positive financial performance. Globalstar announced its engagement with Jason Bernstein to provide strategic advice on investor relations and outreach, showing efforts to strengthen investor relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1058 SNOW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snow/</guid>
      <description>score:1058
Chances: Snowflake Inc. will present at two upcoming investor conferences, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to engage with investors. Snowflake Inc. announced it will release its financial results for the second quarter of fiscal year 2024, indicating transparency and regular financial reporting. The FAANG stocks, including Snowflake, have recently come roaring back, gaining 42% on average over the past year, suggesting potential for growth in the technology sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0954 CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:954
Chances: Coterra Energy Inc. announced that it will host a conference call on August 8, 2023, to discuss second-quarter 2023 financial and operating results, indicating transparency and communication with investors. The projected fair value for Coterra Energy is estimated to be US$29.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0898 CFLT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cflt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cflt/</guid>
      <description>score:898
Chances: Confluent reported a strong set of beats on second-quarter numbers and provided strong guidance, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to navigate the tough economic climate. Rohan Sivaram has been named Confluent&amp;rsquo;s Chief Financial Officer, which could bring positive changes to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial management and strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1057 CFG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cfg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cfg/</guid>
      <description>score:1057
Chances: Citizens Financial Group announced a partnership with Wyndham Destinations, offering a more predictable and affordable way for consumers to explore resort destinations, which could enhance customer engagement and potentially drive revenue. The raising of the prime lending rate by Citizens Bank could lead to increased interest income, positively impacting the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 IPG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: The Interpublic Group of Companies Inc (IPG) gained 4.25% daily, indicating investor interest in the stock. The company&amp;rsquo;s Earnings Per Share (EPS) of $2.41 adds to the positive sentiment among investors. As one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest advertising holding companies, IPG generates revenue from various advertising services, including traditional and digital services, which could potentially lead to future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0993 ENB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enb/</guid>
      <description>score:993
Chances: Enbridge reported higher second-quarter profit due to increased oil volumes, which could positively impact the stock. Enbridge&amp;rsquo;s favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season suggest a potential opportunity for the stock. The company reaffirming its 2023 financial outlook indicates confidence in its future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1073 KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:1073
Chances: Coca-Cola is known for its reliable long-term gains, making it a potential positive return investment. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment in Coca-Cola indicates it could be a good long-term investment based on his successful track record. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s decision to discontinue underperforming brands in its portfolio demonstrates the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to strategic optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1010 NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Flagstar Bank, a subsidiary of New York Community Bancorp, successfully completed its MortgageTech Accelerator program, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to fostering innovation in the mortgage technology sector. New York Community Bancorp delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which could signal positive prospects for the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1037 APA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/apa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/apa/</guid>
      <description>score:1037
Chances: APA Corporation announced its second-quarter 2023 results, which can be found on the company&amp;rsquo;s website, indicating transparency and accountability to investors. APA Corporation achieved key Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) goals in 2022, highlighting the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability and responsible practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1037 NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:1037
Chances: Newmont Corporation receives PNG Competition Commission clearance for the acquisition of Newcrest, indicating positive progress in their growth strategy. Investing in Newmont Corporation along with other industry-leading stocks can result in a dividend yield of 3.5%, providing potential returns for income investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0881 LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:881
Chances: The National Mediation Board&amp;rsquo;s denial of the Southwest pilot strike request reduces the likelihood of a strike, creating a positive outlook for the company. Southwest Airlines encourages customers to book spring break vacations with an extended flight schedule, indicating the airline&amp;rsquo;s efforts to boost travel demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0974 CVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</guid>
      <description>score:974
Chances: CVS Health Corporation beats earnings expectations, reporting EPS of $2.4 compared to the expected $2.12. Health insurers like CVS Health are outperforming expectations, signaling a potential rebound in the managed-care sector. CVS Health&amp;rsquo;s focus on healthcare services could be a chance for growth and potential upside in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1018 DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:1018
Chances: Investors should closely monitor DISH Network stock based on recent movements in the options market. DISH Network&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Amazon to offer Boost Infinite wireless plans to Prime members may fuel momentum for the telecom provider&amp;rsquo;s shares. The addition of Boost Infinite&amp;rsquo;s wireless plan to Amazon Prime could potentially pressure telecom prices in the United States and impact competitors like AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0940 DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:940
Chances: Delta Air Lines could benefit from the rise in international travel demand as more Americans are opting for longer journeys overseas. Strong leisure travel demand is positive for U.S. airlines, including Delta Air Lines, as the market begins to recover from notable losses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1074 RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:1074
Chances: Roblox is joining the Roblox Partner Program, which could amplify the company&amp;rsquo;s position in delivering impactful programs for brands on the global immersive platform. The metaverse is a growing trend, and Roblox is at the forefront of delivering immersive experiences across virtual platforms, which could open avenues for substantial gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1027 CNK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnk/</guid>
      <description>score:1027
Chances: Cinemark beat analysts&amp;rsquo; earnings and revenue expectations in Q2 2023, indicating strong financial performance. The movie theater chain achieved the highest domestic box office month of all time in July 2023, which could positively impact its future performance. Cinemark is seeing favorable earnings estimate revision activity and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season, suggesting potential upside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0871 MP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mp/</guid>
      <description>score:871
Chances: MP Materials beat analysts&amp;rsquo; top- and bottom-line expectations in Q2 2023, indicating strong financial performance. The company reported refining small amounts of rare earths in California, a milestone that bodes well for its future. Shares of MP Materials rose by 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1116 APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: AMC Theatres achieved its highest single-week admissions revenue in the Company&amp;rsquo;s entire 103-year history, signaling a positive performance and potential for increased revenue. AMC Entertainment posted its best-ever week of admissions revenue, fueled by a surge in cinema-goers eager to catch back-to-back screenings of &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Oppenheimer,&amp;rsquo; indicating strong demand for its films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1299 MTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mtch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mtch/</guid>
      <description>score:1299
Chances: This stock has been hammered by economic headwinds but could rebound big-time if analysts are right, indicating potential for a recovery in the stock. Match Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in Tinder and Hinge, suggesting positive performance in its key products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1459 FLR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flr/</guid>
      <description>score:1459
Chances: Shares of Fluor gained more than 15% after the company easily surpassed Wall Street expectations for the quarter and upped its full-year guidance, indicating positive performance. Fluor&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefited from a higher contribution from Energy Solutions and Urban Solutions segments, suggesting potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1005 NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Evergy&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings are better than expected, which could indicate positive performance for utility companies like NextEra Energy. IDACORP&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings benefited from customer additions and plans to add more hydropower generation to its portfolio, which might also be favorable for NextEra Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1022 PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: The share price of Peloton Interactive, Inc. (PTON) has increased by 23% in the last week, indicating recent positive performance. The hype surrounding meme stocks and renewed interest in retail trading could bring more investors back to Peloton&amp;rsquo;s stock. Analyst ratings can influence investors&amp;rsquo; decisions, and positive ratings could indicate potential outperformance for Peloton&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1033 ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1033
Chances: Roku&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results exceeded Wall Street estimates by a huge margin, indicating strong performance. The current price-to-sales (P/S) multiple of 4.2 is much lower than Roku&amp;rsquo;s historical average of 10.7, suggesting potential growth. The ad market could be showing signs of recovery, which could benefit Roku&amp;rsquo;s revenue growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0968 GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:968
Chances: Gilead Sciences expects a third of sales to come from its cancer treatments by 2030, which could drive future growth. Gilead Sciences has a rich portfolio of therapies for life-threatening infectious diseases, including pulmonary and cardiovascular diseases and cancer. The company&amp;rsquo;s CEO mentioned that Gilead is overperforming significantly, excluding one-time items, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1043 CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s top stocks often make for good long-term investments, and Chevron is one of his holdings. Oil prices have quietly rallied over the past month, which could benefit Chevron and the energy sector. Chevron and Chevron U.S.A. Inc. announced an exchange offer for Senior Notes, indicating potential financial opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1057 HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1057
Chances: Haliburton and Baker Hughes show strength, and SLB stock fuels signs of a breakout, indicating positive sentiment towards the company. Chevron&amp;rsquo;s dividend payment and share buyback indicate potential growth opportunities for oil and gas services companies like Halliburton. The energy sector is going through a dramatic shift, and investors may benefit from valuation mismatches in the market, considering both fossil fuel and clean energy stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1118 RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:1118
Chances: RLX Technology saw significant share gains despite not being widely known, indicating potential growth opportunities. Shares of RLX Technology rose nearly 15% as China&amp;rsquo;s central bank trimmed one of its short-term interest rates and rumors of stimulus circulated, which may signal positive sentiment towards the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1349 VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:1349
Chances: Vertiv Holdings reported strong second-quarter net sales of $1,734 million, showing a 24% increase compared to the same quarter last year, and a 25% organic net sales increase, indicating positive financial performance. Shares of Vertiv rose significantly, driven by ongoing demand for data center equipment in both the cloud/hyperscale and colocation markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1040 ABNB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abnb/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Airbnb, Inc. beat earnings expectations in the second quarter, reporting an EPS of $0.98 compared to the expected $0.77, indicating positive financial performance. The U.S. economy has shown resilience, and companies like Airbnb that stand to grow rapidly in such an environment might have a chance for further expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1033 BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:1033
Chances: B2Gold reported positive second-quarter 2023 earnings and revenue surprises, indicating potential growth and financial strength. Revenues rose year-over-year in the second quarter due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1104 MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1104
Chances: Monster Beverage reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1 percent to $1.85 billion, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Gains from strong brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions may contribute to Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s future growth. The completion of the acquisition of Bang Energy and its beverages could open new opportunities and expand Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1188 HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:1188
Chances: Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) announced a partnership with phoenixNAP to expand its Bare Metal Cloud platform, which could potentially boost the company&amp;rsquo;s cloud services revenue. The adoption of HPE ProLiant RL300 Gen11 servers with energy-efficient processors from Ampere Computing may enhance HPE&amp;rsquo;s cloud-native workloads performance and energy efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1226 KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:1226
Chances: KeyBank Foundation awarded a $175,000 grant to Michigan Ability Partners, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to community development. KeyBank provided $46.4 million for the construction of new permanent supportive housing in Los Angeles, which may have a positive impact on the company&amp;rsquo;s reputation and social responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1073 CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:1073
Chances: Cemex and Synhelion&amp;rsquo;s joint effort to develop fully solar-driven cement production is a significant milestone and could lead to more sustainable practices in the cement manufacturing industry. Cemex posted a slight rise in second-quarter net profit, with revenue up 13%, indicating positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1055 WFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1055
Chances: Wells Fargo is supporting a national expansion of Concordance, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to social responsibility. The commercial real estate industry coming into focus following the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s interest rate hikes could create potential opportunities for Wells Fargo. The talk about bringing manufacturing back to the US could lead to increased business activities for financial institutions like Wells Fargo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1053 OUT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/out/</guid>
      <description>score:1053
Chances: A rise in billboard revenues and transit and other revenues could indicate growth potential for OUTFRONT Media. OUTFRONT Media&amp;rsquo;s diverse portfolio of advertising sites and strategic investments for digital-billboard conversions augur well for the company. OUTFRONT XLabs winning awards at the Cannes Lions Festival of Creativity may boost its reputation and potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1020 MCW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mcw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mcw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Mister Car Wash delivering positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023 may boost investor confidence. The surge in artificial intelligence names and the tech industry could potentially benefit companies like Mister Car Wash, Inc. Mister Car Wash being the nations largest car wash brand could indicate a strong market position and growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1025 HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: The appointment of Marcy Hingst as General Counsel could bring valuable expertise to the Executive Leadership Team and enhance legal activities for the company. Huntington Bancshares beating Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit and strong demand for commercial loans may boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0950 ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:950
Chances: ZoomInfo executives participating in investor events could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s future plans and growth prospects. TRUSTe GDPR and CCPA Practices Validations, as well as ISO 27001 and 27701 certifications, could enhance ZoomInfo&amp;rsquo;s credibility and attract investor interest. Tech stocks, including ZoomInfo, could present better buying opportunities after the recent selloff following their quarterly reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Permian Resources Corporation announced its second quarter 2023 financial and operational results, which may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The declaration of a quarterly base and variable cash dividend by Permian Resources may attract income-seeking investors. Investors may find interest in participating in the earnings conference call to gain more insights into Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; performance and future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1168 FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Tim Stone joining Farfetch as Chief Financial Officer may bring new insights and strategies to enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s upcoming second quarter 2023 financial results release may provide valuable information for investors to assess the company&amp;rsquo;s current performance and growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1068 GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:1068
Chances: Grab plans to announce its unaudited second quarter 2023 results, indicating potential updates on the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Grab&amp;rsquo;s strategic reorganization to manage costs and offer more affordable services could signal efforts to adapt to the business environment and enhance long-term sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1146 CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:1146
Chances: Oliver Tuszik&amp;rsquo;s appointment as the next President of Cisco Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) could bring stability and growth opportunities to the region. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s scheduled conference call to announce its fourth quarter and fiscal year 2023 financial results indicates upcoming updates on the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1143 CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:1143
Chances: Comcast partnered with NBCUniversal Telemundo Enterprises and Women in Sports Tech to celebrate the FIFA Women&amp;rsquo;s World Cup, which could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s brand image and engagement with sports fans. Go Addressable and Advertiser Perceptions released findings on the growth and adoption of addressable advertising, which could indicate potential opportunities for Comcast in the advertising market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0764 LYG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</guid>
      <description>score:764
Chances: Lloyds Banking Group beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, reporting higher EPS than analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. Lloyds Banking Group offered hope to homeowners and predicted the UK economy will grow slightly this year, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s business. The bank has millions of customers and is a significant player in the UK banking industry, which provides stability and potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0860 MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:860
Chances: Micron Technology saw a positive improvement to its Relative Strength (RS) Rating, indicating potential growth. The memory industry is expected to benefit from the growing proliferation of artificial intelligence (AI), creating huge demand for storage and compute solutions, which may positively impact Micron Technology&amp;rsquo;s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1045 U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1045
Chances: Unity Software&amp;rsquo;s revenue rose 11% YoY on a pro forma basis, exceeding analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations, indicating potential growth opportunities. Unity Software Inc. delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, suggesting positive financial performance. Steady demand for Unity Software&amp;rsquo;s software solutions, expanding client base, and the launch of AI services may have contributed to its Q2 performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0873 PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:873
Chances: Pinterest reported a monthly active user (MAU) base of 465 million, up 8% year over year, indicating potential growth opportunities. Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s increasing user base, strength in emerging verticals, AI integration, and enhanced monetization may drive revenue growth in the second quarter of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0953 MCHP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mchp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mchp/</guid>
      <description>score:953
Chances: Microchip&amp;rsquo;s first-quarter fiscal 2024 results reflect continued momentum in the mixed signal microcontroller business, indicating growth opportunities. Record net sales and strong financial performance in the quarter ended June 2023 may positively impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s initiation of quarterly cash dividend payments may attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1090 IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:1090
Chances: IonQ is an industry leader in quantum computing, and its recent MOU with South Korea&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Science and ICT may boost its presence in the Asian quantum computing industry. The company has increased its 2023 bookings expectations by 25% and is expecting more than 100% growth in bookings compared to last year&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1009 DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:1009
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s operating income increased by 23% in one of its segments, indicating positive growth opportunities. The upcoming report on Disney&amp;rsquo;s fiscal third-quarter results may provide insights into its plans for ESPN, Disney+, and other segments. Liberty Media delivered impressive earnings and revenue surprises, which might indicate positive momentum for Disney as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1025 BCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: Barclays PLC is set to pay its dividend of 0.027 on the 15th of the month, which may attract income-focused investors. The appointment of Gautam Chawla and Amrit David as investment banking co-heads in the Americas could signal growth opportunities for Barclays in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0979 DOCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docn/</guid>
      <description>score:979
Chances: The growth in cloud computing and the demand for cloud services from startups and SMBs could positively impact DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s revenue. DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s strategic acquisitions and strong customer growth may contribute to positive financial performance in the second quarter. Enhanced offerings from DigitalOcean could drive customer adoption and revenue growth in the cloud computing market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: General Motors plans to boost employment next year despite concerns over the shift to electric vehicles, which could signal positive growth for the company. The expectation of offering unionized workers higher wages might indicate a positive outlook for General Motors&amp;rsquo; financial performance and workforce morale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0946 RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:946
Chances: Transocean secured a $518 million ultra-deepwater drillship contract, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s market position and revenue. The global population&amp;rsquo;s increasing energy demand could benefit offshore drilling companies like Transocean, potentially leading to improved financial performance. Positive surprises in revenue and better-than-expected revenue efficiency in the quarter ended June 2023 may be seen as favorable signs for the company&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1132 HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:1132
Chances: Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts provided an updated investor presentation for second-quarter 2023 results, which could attract potential investors and improve market perception. The reopening of The Ritz-Carlton, Naples and completion of the Marriott Transformational Capital Program may have a positive impact on Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts&amp;rsquo; financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1072 ELAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/elan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/elan/</guid>
      <description>score:1072
Chances: Elanco Animal Health&amp;rsquo;s shares surged after the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency confirmed the continued approval of the Seresto flea and tick collar for dogs and cats. EPA&amp;rsquo;s confirmation of the safety profile of Seresto flea and tick collar may positively impact Elanco Animal Health&amp;rsquo;s reputation and sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0998 DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:998
Chances: Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend is being reduced, but the company may have reasons for this decision that could benefit its financials. Potential buying opportunity for income investors as Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s stock price is 35% below its 52-week high. Strong production volumes from the Gulf of Mexico and Tupper Montney assets may positively impact Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1124 QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:1124
Chances: Formation of a new company by Qualcomm, NXP Semiconductors, and other chipmakers to develop RISC-V could lead to technological advancements. Qualcomm beating earnings expectations in Q3 2023 may attract investor interest and confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Investment management firm Aristotle Atlantic Partners&amp;rsquo; positive performance in Q2 2023 could reflect positively on Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0956 IEP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iep/</guid>
      <description>score:956
Chances: Icahn Enterprises&amp;rsquo; second-quarter financial results announcement may attract investor interest. The company&amp;rsquo;s decision to wind down bets on the stock market&amp;rsquo;s collapse might mitigate potential losses. Icahn Enterprises&amp;rsquo; victory in court against allegations related to Google&amp;rsquo;s antitrust case could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1006 AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:1006
Chances: Affirm&amp;rsquo;s positive improvement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating may indicate potential for a bullish trend. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Cathay Pacific to become its exclusive U.S. pay-over-time partner could drive growth and revenue. The company&amp;rsquo;s plan to publish its fourth quarter and fiscal year 2023 shareholder letter, including financial results, may attract investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0961 KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:961
Chances: Kinder Morgan being one of the largest energy transportation and storage companies in North America may indicate its potential for growth and profitability. Kinder Morgan&amp;rsquo;s high-yield dividend stock with a yield of 6.2% could attract investors looking for higher returns through dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0939 PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:939
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E encourages customers to enroll in an energy incentive program to help lower energy costs and support the state&amp;rsquo;s clean energy goals, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s reputation and customer loyalty. Sunrun customers in California sharing excess solar energy with their neighbors through an exclusive partnership with PG&amp;amp;E could increase grid resiliency and improve the company&amp;rsquo;s standing in the renewable energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1122 ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:1122
Chances: Ericsson has won the 2023 CRN Tech Innovator Awards for its NetCloud Private Networks solution, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s reputation and market presence. Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Intel to develop a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s 5G offerings and competitiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1100 HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:1100
Chances: Robinhood reported its first profitable quarter as a publicly traded company, which is a positive sign for investors. The company beat expectations on profit and revenue, indicating strong financial performance. Robinhood shares have filled a big chunk of the early downside price gap, showing signs of improvement in share prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1005 MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Marathon Oil reported second quarter 2023 net income of $287 million or $0.47 per diluted share, and adjusted net income was $295 million or $0.48 per diluted share. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, indicating positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1002 PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:1002
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s stock demonstrated a recent gain of 4.14%, indicating positive investor sentiment. Steady growth in viewership driven by strength in Paramount+ is expected to aid Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter performance. Potential acquisition talks with KKR &amp;amp; Co Inc to sell book publisher Simon &amp;amp; Schuster for $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1142 BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:1142
Chances: The outlook for e-commerce players like Alibaba is strengthening, making it a viable space to invest in for 2023 and beyond. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s cloud computing unit releasing open-source AI models could expand the company&amp;rsquo;s influence in the field of generative AI and drive innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0925 USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:925
Chances: U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s strategic alliance with Mitsubishi UFJ (MUFG) will boost capital and unlock growth opportunities. The stake purchase by Mitsubishi UFJ Financial Group Inc. in U.S. Bancorp is expected to deepen their alliance and create potential synergies. U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s stock price is sensitive to institutional ownership, which could indicate investor sentiment and influence the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1076 VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:1076
Chances: Viatris has the potential to be a great dividend holding due to its decently high dividend yield, stable line of business, and disruption-resistant business model. The launch of Breyna, the first generic version of AstraZeneca&amp;rsquo;s Symbicort, could potentially contribute to Viatris&amp;rsquo; revenue and growth in the healthcare sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1044 COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:1044
Chances: Coinbase Global reported improved losses in the second quarter, and its stock price target was raised, indicating potential positive developments for the company. Coinbase is creating diverse revenue streams, which may contribute to its future growth if the crypto industry experiences positive developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1043 XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Oil prices are experiencing a winning streak, aided by Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s decision to continue curtailing its production, which could positively impact Exxon Mobil&amp;rsquo;s revenue. Exxon Mobil&amp;rsquo;s insider activity has been observed, with a significant insider purchase of nearly $50 million in shares, indicating potential confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0984 ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:984
Chances: Ambev&amp;rsquo;s stock has been compared to other stocks like Diageo (DEO) and Carlsberg A/S (CABGY) in terms of value options, suggesting potential opportunities for investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance has been discussed in comparison to other stocks like Beyond Meat (BYND), indicating its relative position in the sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1100 UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:1100
Chances: Upstart has experienced an impressive rally, with its stock up more than 450% since May 1, driven by excitement over artificial intelligence, signs of an economic recovery, and a short squeeze. Upstart is a leader in alternative loan approval methods, utilizing AI to assess borrowers&amp;rsquo; creditworthiness and make unbiased opinions on loan default risks, making it a hot commodity associated with artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1026 NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:1026
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line posted its first profit since Covid, indicating a potential recovery in the cruise industry amid a boom in summer travel demand. Cruise stocks like Norwegian Cruise Line, Royal Caribbean Cruises, and Carnival are likely to benefit from rising personal income and personal spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1020 HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Hayward Holdings delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, indicating potential growth in the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Hayward Holdings has had a great run on the share market with its stock up significantly over a certain period, suggesting positive market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0848 OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:848
Chances: Occidental Petroleum recorded a daily gain, pushing its share price higher, indicating positive market sentiment. Permian Basin production remains strong, maintaining OXY&amp;rsquo;s production volumes for 2023, which may be viewed positively by investors. Occidental Petroleum Corp. demonstrated willingness to buy back Berkshire Hathaway Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1034 AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:1034
Chances: The worst appears to be over for AGNC Investment as the Federal Reserve hiked interest rates, which may make it a worthy buy. AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s commitment to repositioning its portfolio in the current volatile interest rate scenario may optimize its performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1056 NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Cloudflare reported second-quarter results that topped estimates, and the company raised its full-year 2023 outlook, which may attract investor interest. The company&amp;rsquo;s solid demand across its security portfolio amid work-from-home policies and escalating cyberattacks could benefit Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s financial situation is getting better, which may be seen as a positive signal by investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0883 PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:883
Chances: Plug Power Inc. will announce its 2023 second quarter results, which could attract investor interest and provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The wider adoption of hydrogen as a clean energy source and the potential growth of the hydrogen economy may create opportunities for Plug Power&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive hydrogen solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1157 PBR-A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</guid>
      <description>score:1157
Chances: Petrobras is closely following negotiations for a majority stake in petrochemicals producer Braskem SA and will be ready to act if any of the proposals go forward, potentially indicating a strategic move to expand the company&amp;rsquo;s business. Petrobras may further increase the average capacity use of its refineries in the third quarter, after raising usage to 93% between April and June, the highest level since the third quarter of 2015, which could boost the company&amp;rsquo;s operational performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1321 PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1321
Chances: Palo Alto Networks is a global cybersecurity leader, which positions the company to benefit from the increasing demand for cybersecurity solutions amid growing cybersecurity threats and attacks. The announcement of Palo Alto Networks&amp;rsquo; financial results for its fiscal fourth quarter and full year 2023 on August 18, 2023, could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance and growth prospects, potentially impacting the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0932 NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Nokia Corporation has been actively repurchasing its own shares, which indicates a positive signal from the company about its financial health and confidence in its future prospects. Nokia&amp;rsquo;s announcement of manufacturing broadband network electronics products for the BEAD program in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1052 CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Carvana&amp;rsquo;s stock (CVNA) has experienced significant gains of approximately 900% this year, showing positive momentum and strong performance. Carvana launched same-day delivery in Arizona, introducing a new level of speed and convenience for customers, which could enhance customer satisfaction and boost sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1036 C</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/c/</guid>
      <description>score:1036
Chances: Citigroup&amp;rsquo;s Asia family office business expects a 25% increase in clients this year, indicating growth opportunities in the wealth management sector in Asia. The bank&amp;rsquo;s family office business experienced a strong 50% year-on-year client increase in Asia in the past year, showing positive momentum in the region&amp;rsquo;s demand for private investment vehicles and business succession planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1014 RIOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/riot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/riot/</guid>
      <description>score:1014
Chances: Riot Platforms, Inc. is an industry leader in Bitcoin mining and data center hosting, indicating potential for growth in the cryptocurrency sector. The production and operations update for July 2023 shows that Riot produced 410 Bitcoins, and the company is expanding its execution of the power strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0876 PDCE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</guid>
      <description>score:876
Chances: Chevron expects to receive shareholder approval for the $7.6 billion deal to acquire PDC Energy, which could potentially boost PDC Energy&amp;rsquo;s stock performance. The acquisition of PDC Energy by Chevron is considered strategic and accretive, providing potential growth opportunities for both companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0771 LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:771
Chances: Lyft will report its second-quarter earnings, and investors will be closely watching the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance and response to rival Uber&amp;rsquo;s first operating profit. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results may benefit from improved profitability and increased revenues, considering the positive results posted by its peer, Uber Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0969 KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:969
Chances: Kinross Gold delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which may boost investor confidence. The Toronto Stock Exchange accepting the notice filed by Kinross Gold to renew its normal course issuer bid program could indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s confidence in its stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1045 TEVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teva/</guid>
      <description>score:1045
Chances: Teva Pharmaceutical Industries has agreed to pay up to $126 million to U.S. hospitals over 18 years to settle claims, which could resolve legal issues and potential liabilities. TEVA&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results were strong, beating estimates for both earnings and sales, which may lead to increased investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1049 GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:1049
Chances: Barrick Gold aims to restart operations at the Porgera gold mine in Papua New Guinea later this year, potentially increasing gold production. The signing of the New Reko Diq agreement in Pakistan and the progress on the Reko Diq copper-gold project could lead to future production and revenue growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0887 RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:887
Chances: Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023 suggest potential positive performance in the future. Sales activities outside of California have been robust, growing 25% year-over-year, indicating potential growth in other markets. Sunrun customers in California sharing excess solar energy with their neighbors may increase grid resiliency and enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0802 META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:802
Chances: Over three billion people a day use a Meta product, indicating a large user base and potential for growth. Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta has delivered impressive results, garnering positive reactions from investors. Meta&amp;rsquo;s investment in building chatbots with different personalities for its social media sites may indicate its commitment to innovation and user engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0889 SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:889
Chances: Despite Shopify posting better-than-expected second-quarter revenue and adjusted earnings per share, analysts upgraded their 12-month price targets for the stock after digesting the solid results. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results benefited from growth in merchant solutions revenues and an expanding merchant base. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s President, Harley Finkelstein, discussed how the e-commerce company is approaching a potential U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0899 GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:899
Chances: Gerdau has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, which may drive the stock higher in the near term. Gerdau made it through the &amp;lsquo;Fast-Paced Momentum at a Bargain&amp;rsquo; screen and could be a great choice for investors looking for stocks that have gained strong momentum recently but are still trading at reasonable prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0795 FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:795
Chances: Fisker announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, which could tap into the growing demand for electric trucks in the U.S. market. Fisker&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Henrik Fisker, expressed optimism about the demand for the Fisker Alaska pickup truck, especially if it is priced competitively and offers a &amp;lsquo;cool&amp;rsquo; product in the sub-$30,000 EV category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0965 SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:965
Chances: Snap&amp;rsquo;s stock has rallied about 40%, indicating a potential recovery from its lowest price in nearly four years last October. Meta&amp;rsquo;s report of double-digit revenue growth and better-than-expected third-quarter guidance suggests a positive outlook for social media companies, which may have a spillover effect on Snap&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1114 GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:1114
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s cloud segment grew 28% annually and posted its first profitable quarter, indicating potential growth opportunities in the cloud services business. The mixed results from Q1, with the advertising segment declining marginally but the cloud segment showing growth, suggest that investors are betting on Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s AI hype, which has contributed to the stock&amp;rsquo;s gain of 44% this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1209 AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:1209
Chances: C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s guidance for fiscal 2024 suggests that the shift in its business model from a subscription-based one to a consumption-based one is likely to work, which may attract investors looking for growth potential. The company made a strategic change to a pay-as-you-go model to reduce the entry barrier for new customers, leading to quicker deal closures and potential business growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1095 NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:1095
Chances: Nu Holdings is betting big that its high-yield savings accounts will stoke growth in Latin Americas second-largest economy, which could attract investors looking for growth opportunities. The company surpassed 80 million customers in Brazil and reached 85 million customers across Latin America, indicating rapid growth in its operations and potential for expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0977 ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:977
Chances: Energy Transfer had strong performance from its operations, delivering record volumes across its segments, which may be positively received by investors. The company offers a prodigious income stream, and its monster distribution significantly exceeded reported net income, which could attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1274 CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:1274
Chances: Clarivate Plc&amp;rsquo;s CEO and CFO are scheduled to present at Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo;s 26th Annual Technology, Internet &amp;amp; Communications Conference, which could generate positive interest from investors. The company reported results for the second quarter, and positive financial performance may attract positive sentiment from investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1245 SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:1245
Chances: SiriusXM&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results reflect improvement in average revenue per user, indicating positive performance in the company&amp;rsquo;s subscription-based business. Sirius XM Holdings Inc has a GF Score of 83 out of 100, indicating good outperformance potential, which may attract positive sentiment from investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1069 VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:1069
Chances: Verizon&amp;rsquo;s core wireless service revenue continues to grow, up 3.8% in the second quarter, which indicates positive performance in its wireless business. Verizon and Nokia&amp;rsquo;s showcase of the latest 5G innovations may attract attention and demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to investing in 5G wireless technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0907 AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:907
Chances: AMC achieved its highest single-week admissions revenue in the Company&amp;rsquo;s entire history, which may indicate positive performance. The surge in cinema-goers eager to catch back-to-back screenings of popular films &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo; contributed to AMC&amp;rsquo;s best-ever week of admissions revenue. AMC&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown significant year-to-date gains, outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1047 JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:1047
Chances: JetBlue and Allegiant Travel&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from upbeat air travel demand scenario, which may indicate positive performance for JBLU. JetBlue announced a new partnership with Air Serbia, which could potentially open up new opportunities for the company. U.S. airlines are enjoying strong leisure travel demand, which may contribute to JetBlue&amp;rsquo;s revenue growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0956 JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:956
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson is part of the Zacks top Analyst Blog, which could attract investor attention. JNJ is a longtime dividend payer and has earned the title of Dividend King, making it attractive to income-focused investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s involvement in appealing court appeals regarding talc-related claims may provide positive outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1153 KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:1153
Chances: Kenvue reported strong quarterly earnings, beating analyst estimates on both the top and bottom lines. The surge in heart procedures and higher demand for cold and flu medicines contributed to Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s solid gains in revenue and profit, which could also benefit Kenvue as its former consumer health unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0995 MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:995
Chances: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s strong cloud business is expected to support its growth and revenue generation. Cybersecurity shares often outperform other tech stocks during economic downturns, which could benefit Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity offerings. The overall stock market has staged an extraordinary recovery in 2023, and this positive sentiment could have a favorable impact on Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1209 MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:1209
Chances: Marathon Digital Holdings mined a record 179 blocks and produced 1,176 BTC in July 2023, indicating increased mining activities and potential revenue growth. The company reported unrestricted cash and cash equivalents of $115 million and increased its unrestricted Bitcoin holdings to 12,964 BTC, which may enhance its financial stability and investment potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1433 DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:1433
Chances: Ginkgo Bioworks has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding with the Government of Panama to develop new biosecurity capabilities in Latin America, indicating potential growth opportunities in the region. The company has been awarded a 4-year contract worth up to $18 million by DARPA to reimagine how to manufacture complex therapeutic proteins, suggesting advancements in protein manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1130 GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:1130
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s cloud segment grew 28% annually and posted its first profitable quarter, indicating positive growth in the cloud business. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s stock has gained 44% this year, partly driven by the hype around AI, which may signal positive sentiment towards the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0974 XPEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</guid>
      <description>score:974
Chances: Demand for electric vehicles and charging solutions is boosting earnings and sales for EV stocks, including XPeng Inc. XPeng is a leading Chinese smart electric vehicle company, which indicates its potential for growth in the expanding EV market. The company&amp;rsquo;s Senior Director of XPeng&amp;rsquo;s autonomous driving team, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1035 AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: American Airlines is in talks with planemakers Airbus and Boeing for a new narrowbody jet order, indicating potential growth opportunities. The airline is discussing its narrowbody aircraft needs for the latter half of this decade and beyond, suggesting potential fleet expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0969 INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:969
Chances: Intel still sees China as a great market for its chips, especially in emerging sectors such as 5G and electric vehicles, indicating growth potential. Semiconductor stocks, including Intel, have been performing well in 2023, despite the slowdown in chip demand in some markets, implying investor interest in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1182 UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:1182
Chances: Uber reported a positive operating profit based on generally accepted accounting principles, indicating improved financial performance. The U.S. economy has evolved over time, and the technology sector, where Uber operates, is leading the way today, implying growth potential. Delivery orders were a key driver for Uber&amp;rsquo;s business during the pandemic, indicating resilience and adaptation to changing market conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0996 PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Digital payment platforms like Venmo, PayPal, and CashApp have changed the way we use and keep physical cash on hand. Potential opportunity for patient investors who believe in the company&amp;rsquo;s comeback. PayPal reported another quarter of revenue and profit growth, with a non-GAAP operating margin improvement compared to the year-ago quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0832 ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:832
Chances: Growth in commissions and fees, results from insurance operations, and strategic acquisitions support Ita Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s financials. Approval of interest on capital payment to stockholders may attract investors looking for dividend-paying stocks. First-quarter recurring net profit up 14.6% year-on-year indicates positive performance and growth in the bank&amp;rsquo;s loan portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0842 VALE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vale/</guid>
      <description>score:842
Chances: The $2.6 billion deal with Saudi Arabia marks a potential landmark shift in the metal and mining investment landscape, indicating Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s entry as a pivotal player. Vale&amp;rsquo;s agreement to sell a 13% stake in its base metals business for $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0702 PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:702
Chances: The worldwide biotechnology market is projected to reach significant value, which could potentially benefit Pfizer as a major player in the biotech industry. Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s decision to make some products available only through its emergency ordering process to manage inventory after the tornado strike may indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s proactive approach to handling disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0760 CCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</guid>
      <description>score:760
Chances: Cruise vacations have emerged as a popular option among consumers in search of cheaper ways to travel, which could potentially boost demand for cruise operators like Carnival Corporation. Carnival Corporation&amp;rsquo;s stock has rebounded significantly since the beginning of the pandemic, with investors sitting on enviable gains, which may attract further interest in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0524 BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:524
Chances: Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment model and top stocks often make for good long-term investments, which could potentially attract investors to consider Bank of America as a stable and reliable stock. Investors continued to buy stock and bond funds, with stock funds seeing $4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery is working on bringing news and live sports to U.S. streaming platforms, which could help increase its subscriber base. The CEO, David Zaslav, is hopeful about resolving negotiations with striking Hollywood writers and actors&amp;rsquo; unions, which could potentially benefit the company&amp;rsquo;s content offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s total returns over the past decade have lagged behind the overall market, but at current prices, the stock is considered a bargain that may be too good to pass up. AT&amp;amp;T pays a high dividend that yields 7.6%, making it attractive to investors seeking passive income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0400 FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:400
Chances: Fortinet beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, reporting an EPS of $0.38, surpassing the estimated $0.34. This positive performance may attract investors interested in companies with potential for reversing their fortunes. Risks: A warning about slowing sales from Fortinet spooked investors, which could create uncertainty and potential downward pressure on the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1500 CSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csx/</guid>
      <description>score:1500
Chances: CSX announced that Jamie Boychuk, executive vice president of Operations, is leaving the company. While his departure might introduce uncertainty, CSX&amp;rsquo;s depth of operational experience is expected to ensure continuity during the search for a successor. Rail shippers are urging President Joe Biden to renominate Surface Transportation Board Chairman Marty Oberman and board member Patrick Fuchs to the board, which could have a positive impact on CSX&amp;rsquo;s operations and regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1235 SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:1235
Chances: Southwestern Energy reported Q2 earnings with declining total operating costs and expenses, which positively impacted its results. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023, beating Wall Street estimates by 28.57% and 11.76%, respectively. Key metrics for Southwestern Energy in Q2 2023 could indicate a positive performance compared to the previous year and Wall Street estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1153 SQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sq/</guid>
      <description>score:1153
Chances: Block reported second-quarter earnings that topped estimates, signaling a strong quarter for its consumer Cash App business. Square stock bulls focus on the potential synergies between Square&amp;rsquo;s Cash App and Afterpay, which could drive growth. The addition of Neha Narula, Director of the Digital Currency Initiative at the MIT Media Lab, to Block&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors might bring valuable insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1133 LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:1133
Chances: Lucid Group is reporting quarterly results next week, which may bring insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Former Dow CEO and current Lucid board member, Andrew Liveris, weighing in on the EV maker&amp;rsquo;s plans could provide valuable perspectives. Lucid Group&amp;rsquo;s move into China&amp;rsquo;s EV market and expansion in the Middle East region might offer growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0974 RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:974
Chances: Rivian&amp;rsquo;s rally has been driving higher over the past month, indicating positive market momentum. John Krafcik, a seasoned automotive executive, joining Rivian&amp;rsquo;s board of directors may bring valuable expertise and insights. One analyst believes Rivian could hit $40 per share, indicating potential for stock price growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1052 NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Artificial intelligence (AI) driving strong gains for the stock market is benefiting NVIDIA, leading to a whopping 209% gain for the year. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI leadership and strong earnings performance have contributed to the stock&amp;rsquo;s skyrocketing success. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI chip demand and potential for new growth phases thanks to AI technology indicate positive future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1072 PBR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</guid>
      <description>score:1072
Chances: Petrobras is closely following negotiations for a majority stake in Braskem SA and may act on proposals, indicating potential expansion opportunities. The company may further increase the average capacity use of its refineries, setting production records, and hitting targets, showing positive operational performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1109 SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:1109
Chances: SoFi Technologies reported another blowout quarter, showcasing rocket-like growth, which could potentially keep the company growing in the future. Mizuho analysts see a significant total addressable market opportunity in student loan refinancing for SoFi, indicating potential growth prospects in the fintech industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1130 QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:1130
Chances: QuantumScape announced the pricing of an underwritten public offering of its Class A common stock, which may indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to raise capital and develop its innovative EV charging technology. Shares of QuantumScape have soared more than 50% in the past three months, and the company&amp;rsquo;s plan to sell $300 million in additional shares could be seen as a positive move by investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1162 F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:1162
Chances: Ford reported second-quarter revenue and adjusted diluted earnings per share that beat Wall Street estimates, which could be positive for the stock. General Motors&amp;rsquo; plans to boost employment for electric vehicle production may have a positive impact on the automotive industry, including Ford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: DraftKings stock soared after blowing away Q2 estimates and raising its revenue outlook for the second quarter in a row. Shares of DraftKings surged as the company reported second-quarter sales that beat estimates and raised its full-year forecast. The sports betting company posted strong Q2 revenue, beating expectations, indicating potential gains for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0784 OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:784
Chances: Opendoor Technologies reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, with positive clues for the stock&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s shareholder letter indicated that Opendoor exceeded the high end of its financial expectations, showing potential growth prospects. Risks: Opendoor Technologies missed earnings expectations for Q2 2023, which may impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1179 PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:1179
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s strong prospects in the field of artificial intelligence could boost its stock in the commercial market. Palantir&amp;rsquo;s multi-year enterprise expansion with WesTrac Pty Ltd to deploy Foundry across core operations indicates potential growth opportunities. Analyst Stephen Guilfoyle&amp;rsquo;s positive view on Palantir&amp;rsquo;s stock and its surging AI spending could be favorable for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1174 BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:1174
Chances: Amazon.com will launch a credit card offering in Brazil in partnership with Banco Bradesco SA, expanding the bank&amp;rsquo;s fintech offering. Banco Bradesco expects bankrupt retailer Americanas SA and its lenders to reach a reasonable deal on debts, potentially resolving a financial issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1184 AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:1184
Chances: AMD&amp;rsquo;s new MI300 AI chip set appears capable of competing with Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s hardware, signaling potential growth opportunities. AMD&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown a daily gain of 3.79% and has an Earnings Per Share (EPS) of 0.23, indicating the potential for higher returns in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1183 NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:1183
Chances: NIO achieved a new record-high monthly deliveries, with deliveries of ES6 exceeding 10,000 in July 2023, indicating strong demand for its vehicles. The trading volume and On-Balance-Volume (OBV) line suggest increased investor interest in NIO&amp;rsquo;s stock, which could have positive implications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1186 TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:1186
Chances: Electric vehicle maker Lucid cut prices of its Air luxury sedans, sparking a price war with Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Model S and Model S Plaid. Tesla&amp;rsquo;s plans to monetize AI could potentially boost its growth in the long term. Upcoming plans for an upgraded Model 3 and leaks about the Model 3 refresh called Project Highland could have positive implications for Tesla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1193 AAPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</guid>
      <description>score:1193
Chances: Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s Berkshire Hathaway reported net income of $35.91 billion for the second quarter, boosted by stock holdings such as Apple. Tech giant is working on compressing language models to run efficiently on iPhones and iPads, which could benefit Apple&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1244 AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:1244
Chances: Amazon.com, Inc. beats earnings expectations with an EPS of $0.65 compared to the expected $0.34. The e-commerce and cloud-computing leader, Amazon.com, showed strong growth and gained over 8% in stock value after reporting quarterly earnings. The outlook for e-commerce players, including Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
