<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US Stocks Picked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ranking/</guid>
      <description>FIS (Fidelity National Information Services, Inc.) Middle Fidelity National Information Services, Inc. (FIS) shows promise due to positive stock performance, new partnerships, and integration of leading data networks, but faces potential risks from lower North American revenues and broader market trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fis/</guid>
      <description>score:299
Chances: Fidelity National Information Services, Inc. (FIS) shareholders should be happy to see the share price up 17%. The latest trading day saw Fidelity National Information Services (FIS) settling at $62.96, representing a -1.08% change from its previous close. FIS and Banked have formed a partnership to create new pay-by-bank solutions by leveraging the power of open banking, APIs and real-time payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: The U.S. Global Jets ETF provides investors access to the global airline industry. Rising economic situation, moderation in the rate of inflation, and the prospect of lower interest rates have a positive effect on consumer discretionary spending, which bodes well for airline carriers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:-83
Chances: This high-growth Chinese e-commerce company still has plenty of room to grow. Shares of e-commerce site Etsy, Inc. (ETSY) are slipping Thursday morning after reporting mixed fourth-quarter results. Risks: Etsy&amp;rsquo;s earnings fell short of estimates with adjusted gains of $0.62 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:155
Chances: Semiconductors are at the core of the development of artificial intelligence capabilities. The growing fear that there is not enough semiconductor supply to meet the AI demand is adding new urgency to the effort to bring chipmaking back on US soil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:-48
Chances: Wayfair Inc. beat earnings expectations in the fourth quarter of 2023, with reported EPS of $-0.11 compared to expectations of $-0.22. The company&amp;rsquo;s free cash flow of $62 million beat analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates, indicating improved cash generation. Wayfair reported an increase in active customers, showing positive growth in its customer base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:-72
Chances: The recent partnership between Delta Air Lines and Aeromexico could potentially boost revenue and expand market presence. The resumption of direct U.S. flights to Israel by United Airlines may lead to increased traffic and stronger market position for the company. Risks: The refusal of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vst/</guid>
      <description>score:104
Chances: Vistra Corp. (VST) has announced a 9% increase in its quarterly common stock dividend per share compared to the previous year. Vistra Corp. (VST) is well positioned to outperform the market, exhibiting above-average growth in financials. The company has received approval from the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC) to acquire Energy Harbor, adding significant assets to its portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:120
Chances: The longer-term bullish case for natural gas rests on expanding U.S. exports, which could benefit Southwestern Energy (SWN). SWN delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended December 2023, indicating positive performance. Risks: Front-month gas futures for March delivery rose, but supply and demand fluctuated, which could impact the business of SWN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gh/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: GH anticipates continued expansion with 2024 revenue outlook set between $655 to $670 million. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 109.9% in Guardant Health (GH). Guardant Health (GH) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:90
Chances: Coca-Cola continues to make sizable dividend increases and reward faithful shareholders. Genuine Parts, Coca-Cola, 3M, Hershey, and Home Depot have been highlighted in this Investment Ideas article. Several companies, including these five, have been delivering positive news of higher dividend payouts to shareholders lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: TSM has recently received a substantial subsidy from Japan to build a second chip fabrication plant, signaling a potential for expansion and increased production capacity. Risks: There is a risk of geopolitical tensions impacting TSM&amp;rsquo;s operations, particularly in the context of growing tensions between China and Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cm/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: CIBC has provided growth financing to InsightRX, a software company leveraging quantitative pharmacology and AI to improve therapeutic decision-making, indicating the bank&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and investment in emerging technologies. The smaller-than-expected increase in US crude stockpiles has added to signs of a tightening physical market, which could positively impact the bank&amp;rsquo;s capital markets and direct financial services segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:-82
Chances: The company plans to release its third quarter fiscal 2024 financial results soon, which could provide valuable insights into its performance. Fans will soon be able to purchase the Australia women&amp;rsquo;s goalkeeper kit, which may boost sales and brand visibility for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:-41
Chances: ConocoPhillips (COP) has been adding to its free cash flow, indicating potential for growth and profitability. The recent retirement of Dominic Macklon, executive vice president, may signal internal changes as the company looks to the future. Risks: The sale of shares by Christopher Delk, Vice President, Controller, may raise concerns about insider confidence in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Energy Transfer LP has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.com users lately, indicating high market interest. Energy Transfer is ready to make another acquisition if the right opportunity arises, showcasing a proactive and growth-oriented approach. Energy Transfer LP shares have started gaining and might continue moving higher in the near term, as indicated by solid earnings estimate revisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RKLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Rocket Lab has successfully completed the first space manufacturing mission outside of the International Space Station, indicating their capability in in-space manufacturing and hypersonic reentry logistics. Risks: The heavy reliance on government contracts for their launch services could pose a risk, particularly if there are changes in government priorities or budget allocations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:-51
Chances: Medical Properties Trust is making progress on its plan to get back on solid ground. MPW delivered FFO and revenue surprises of 33.33% and 142.04%, respectively, for the quarter ended December 2023. The healthcare REIT sub sector has emerged as the new leader among REITs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:94
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter results are likely to reflect the impacts of strong momentum across Promoted Listings and Managed payments. eBay is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s top destinations for trading cards and collectibles, and is hosting an epic one-day event featuring ultra-rare cards and collectibles with accessible price points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Certain Wall Street analysts selected Alphabet and Uber Technologies as top picks in 2024. Both management teams are disproving previous assumptions. The S&amp;amp;P 500 Index reached another record high in the wake of Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s blockbuster earnings. Risks: Uber (UBER) has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: JD.com, Inc. (JD) stood at $23.96, denoting a +0.71% change from the preceding trading day. JD.com&amp;rsquo;s management will hold a conference call to discuss its unaudited fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results. Risks: JD.com is considering an offer for British electronics retailer Currys, which may involve a bidding war and potential financial risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARDX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: Ardelyx (ARDX) exceeded revenue expectations and fared well with a strong commercial performance of IBSRELA and XPHOZAH, indicating potential for growth and market strength Positive trend in earnings estimate revisions and recent price strength screen suggest a favorable outlook for Ardelyx (ARDX) Risks: Earnings and revenue surprises of -33.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</guid>
      <description>score:217
Chances: ImmunityBio has completed enrollment and initial follow-up for a safety trial of its investigational cancer vaccine, showing progress in its clinical development. The company&amp;rsquo;s findings from Patient-Reported Outcomes (PROs) support positive interim results from its study of N-803 plus BCG in BCG-unresponsive non-muscle invasive bladder cancer, indicating potential efficacy of its therapies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: SoFi turned a profit in the fourth quarter for the first time ever, showing solid business momentum Optimism in the air with expectations of the stock market to continue hitting new highs Fintech industry, particularly SoFi, is reshaping traditional practices and disrupting the financial sector Risks: Stock is down 18% this year despite solid performance, indicating potential uncertainty in market perception Possible downbeat outlook for SOFI stock following a widely publicized post-earnings downgrade by a sell-side analyst Uncertainty surrounding interest rate fluctuations and their impact on consumer behavior Score:-20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wes/</guid>
      <description>score:119
Chances: WES announced multiple divestment agreements that could lead to improved financial performance The strong earnings results for Q4 2023 indicate positive momentum for WES The upcoming UBS Global Energy &amp;amp; Utilities Conference could provide WES with an opportunity to showcase its potential Risks: The potential divestment of assets could impact WES&amp;rsquo;s future growth potential Any fluctuations in the energy market could affect WES&amp;rsquo;s operations and financial performance Score:119 chances characters count - risks characters count = 119</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agl/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: Agilon Health, Inc. is participating in the 44th Annual Cowen Health Care Conference, indicating its commitment to engaging with investors and stakeholders. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing healthcare for seniors through a Total Care Model presents a significant opportunity in the growing Medicare market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:237
Chances: DoorDash stock received an upgrade to Overweight from Equal-Weight at Morgan Stanley, signaling positive sentiment from analysts The company continues to deliver peer-leading and better-than-expected consumer spend and gross order value results, indicating strong performance across its expanding platform DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Community Impact Report demonstrates positive impact on merchants, consumers, and Dashers, showing the company&amp;rsquo;s positive influence in the community Risks: DoorDash struggles to return to pre-pandemic levels of growth, trailing behind leading competitor Uber in key metrics The company missed on earnings expectations for Q4 2023, reporting an EPS of $-0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:256
Chances: Chevron (CVX) has received attention from Zacks.com users and Warren Buffett is increasing his stake in the company, indicating potential confidence in the stock Chevron voluntarily relinquished 23 permits for oil and gas development off Canada&amp;rsquo;s Pacific Coast, marking an important milestone in protecting the ecologically rich waters and potentially signaling a positive environmental stance Oil prices are near 3-week highs due to continued conflicts in the Middle East, indicating potential positive market conditions for energy stocks Risks: European majors like BP and Shell are facing pressure from ESG investors, which could impact the oil and gas industry in the medium term Chevron operates in the oil and gas industry, which is facing increasing scrutiny and challenges due to the ongoing transition away from fossil fuels Score:256 chances characters count - risks characters count = 256</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:-87
Chances: United Airlines plans to resume flights to Israel next month, potentially increasing revenue and market share The company reported a 1.36% positive shift in stock value in the most recent trading session Risks: The forced emergency landing of a United Airlines flight due to a bomb threat and other incidents may impact consumer confidence The ongoing investigation by the Federal Aviation Administration into an emergency landing of a United Airlines Boeing 757 flight could lead to regulatory issues Score:-87 chances characters count - risks characters count = -87</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chk/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Chesapeake Energy Corp is curtailing planned production for 2024, which could lead to a reduction in supply and a potential increase in natural gas prices. Shares of Chesapeake Energy and EQT took off as natural gas prices increased, indicating positive market sentiment towards the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: Lucid Group, Inc. has been setting new standards for luxury electric experience with the Lucid Air, America&amp;rsquo;s most awarded new luxury vehicle The company is making it easier than ever for people to buy and own the world&amp;rsquo;s best electric vehicle Electric vehicle market is advantageous for consumers looking to buy or lease an EV Lucid recently announced a 10% reduction in the starting price of its Air sedan, reflecting a strategic move to stimulate sales Risks: The company posted a loss of $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dfs/</guid>
      <description>score:123
Chances: With investors and bankers confident that interest rates won&amp;rsquo;t be heading higher in the coming years, merger activity has accelerated The acquisition aims to create a bigger competitor to Visa and Mastercard, potentially disrupting the close-knit U.S. credit card industry Risks: Antitrust concerns and questions about how the merger will affect customers Democrat Congresswoman Maxine Waters is deeply opposed to the acquisition Score:123 chances characters count - risks characters count = 123</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/exc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/exc/</guid>
      <description>score:97
Chances: Exelon&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings and revenues increased year over year, indicating a positive trend in the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s increased transmission spending reflects a strategic investment to address grid reliability concerns and capitalize on growing electricity demand from data centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: SolarEdge Technologies, Inc. has a strong track record in the energy technology sector, offering inverter solutions and a range of other products and services. The company&amp;rsquo;s Solar segment, which includes inverter solutions designed to maximize power generation, shows potential for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s has received an unsolicited $6 billion bid from an activist investor, indicating potential interest in the company&amp;rsquo;s value The nomination of nine independent, highly qualified candidates for election to Macy&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors suggests potential changes in the company&amp;rsquo;s governance and strategy Despite the rejection of the bid and the proxy battle, there may still be room for constructive dialogue and potential for a positive outcome Risks: The rejection of the bid and the ensuing proxy battle could lead to increased uncertainty and volatility in Macy&amp;rsquo;s stock price The lack of a clear financing plan from the activist investor and the potential for a prolonged proxy battle may create instability for Macy&amp;rsquo;s The ongoing struggle for control of the board could disrupt Macy&amp;rsquo;s operations and long-term strategic decisions Score:64 chances characters count - risks characters count = 64</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tcn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tcn/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: Tricon Residential, Inc. has delivered strong financial results in the past quarter, with both earnings and revenue surpassing expectations. The company has a strong business segment in Single-Family Rental, which owns and operates single family rental homes. The acquisition by Blackstone Real Estate Partners X is a significant opportunity for Tricon, valued at around $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: PPL&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings are better than estimates and the company continues to make substantial investment to further strengthen its existing operations. Robust Capital Investment Plan and Dividend Growth Announced PPL&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$20.44 based on Dividend Discount Model Risks: PPL Corporation misses on earnings expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kr/</guid>
      <description>score:-131
Chances: Kroger (KR) concluded the recent trading session at $48, signifying a +0.76% move from its prior day&amp;rsquo;s close. In honor of Black History Month, the Kroger Co. (NYSE: KR) today celebrates a variety of Black-owned and founded businesses. Risks: The United States Federal Trade Commission and a group of states could sue to block Kroger&amp;rsquo;s proposed $24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:-144
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;rsquo; stock is showing strong momentum and has been recommended as a buy by analysts at J.P. Morgan. Despite the recent challenges faced by the company, it has a history of resilience and strategic decision-making that may lead to recovery in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:-40
Chances: The Federal Reserve is slated to cut interest rates multiple times this year, which should cause a flood of liquidity in the markets as lending rates fall. Cheaper lending will lead to increased risk appetites overall. Risks: Certain streaming platforms are struggling remarkably in terms of their financials, with gross margins and revenue growth falling short of industry averages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:160
Chances: Plug Power Inc. announced a comprehensive initiative to significantly reduce its annual operational expenses by more than $75 million, which could enhance its financial performance and ensure long-term value creation in a competitive market. The company delivered first-of-its-kind portable refuelers to transit agencies and trucking fleet customers, removing a significant barrier to the consideration of fuel cell electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRIP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/trip/</guid>
      <description>score:79
Chances: Tripadvisor&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter results exceeded Wall Street estimates, showing significant growth in the Experience segment The company&amp;rsquo;s stock increased significantly by 45% over the past quarter, indicating strong market performance Tripadvisor&amp;rsquo;s platform provides contextually-relevant booking links to travel partners, which is a competitive advantage in the online travel industry Risks: The online travel industry is highly competitive and constantly evolving, posing potential challenges for Tripadvisor in maintaining its market position The company&amp;rsquo;s performance may be impacted by external factors such as economic downturns, changes in travel regulations, or disruptions in travel patterns Score:79 chances characters count - risks characters count = 79</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gtes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gtes/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: Gates Industrial Corp PLC&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Ivo Jurek, has increased the insider&amp;rsquo;s stake in the company by purchasing 20,492 shares, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s potential growth. The company has been recognized as one of America&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Workplaces for Diversity 2024, showcasing its commitment to diversity and inclusion, which can enhance its reputation and attract top talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rum/</guid>
      <description>score:98
Chances: Rumble Inc. is in a position of significant insider ownership, indicating inherent interests in company expansion Partnership with 1775 Coffee and launch of exclusive Rumble-branded product reflects diversification and ecosystem expansion Selection of small-cap stocks with potential for huge gains, in line with recent stock price rallies Upcoming oral argument on behalf of Rumble and Locals at the United States Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit could have implications for free speech on social media platforms Risks: Lawsuit against the state of New York could result in legal costs and potential regulatory challenges for Rumble Political uncertainty surrounding the upcoming election and its potential impact on stock market stability Cultural controversy and cancelation risks associated with video platform focus on avoiding cultural cancelation Unexpected gains in stocks may also come with increased volatility and potential downside Score:98 chances characters count - risks characters count = 98</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iova/</guid>
      <description>score:106
Chances: The U.S. health regulator has granted an accelerated approval for Iovance Biotherapeutics&amp;rsquo; cell therapy for advanced melanoma, making it the first such treatment for the deadliest form of skin cancer. The approval allows use in patients who have been previously treated with other therapies, but their cancer has spread to other parts of the body and cannot be removed with surgery, providing a significant market opportunity for Iovance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRSP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crsp/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: CRISPR Therapeutics has shown improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. The company is focused on creating transformative gene-based medicines for serious diseases, and has announced conditional marketing authorization for its gene edited therapy, CASGEVY. Risks: The company doesn&amp;rsquo;t possess the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALKS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alks/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Alkermes stock saw its Relative Strength Rating improve from 69 to 75, indicating a potential rebound in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenues outpaced estimates in the fourth quarter of 2023, driven by strong growth in proprietary products. Robust revenue growth and strategic focus are likely to propel Alkermes into 2024, indicating positive prospects for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOOR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/door/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/door/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: The acquisition by Owens Corning presents a new growth platform for Masonite, indicating potential for increased market share and expansion opportunities. The termination of the merger agreement with PGTI and the acceptance of a deal termination fee suggest that Masonite is focused on maximizing shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNOW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snow/</guid>
      <description>score:-363
Chances: Long-term AI tailwinds could turn $2,000 and some patience into big-time returns. Certain Wall Street analysts see substantial upside for Snowflake and Sea Limited shareholders. The trend toward cloud optimization is beginning to wane. Snowflake&amp;rsquo;s growth potential comes from an ever increasing need to store and analyze larger amounts of data securely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: The market continues to hit highs, fueled by AI stocks, but is looking extended. A number of artificial intelligence-related stocks posted strong gains this week with potential entry opportunities. The robotics sector stands at the forefront of transformative growth, with certain stocks displaying the utmost potential for surefire success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:165
Chances: CNH Industrial&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability and innovation is a positive sign for potential performance in the upcoming quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong showing in the S&amp;amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment indicates a solid foundation for future growth. Recent product innovations and awards from agricultural and construction industry forums reflect a forward-thinking approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: Oracle (ORCL) has been recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: U.S. Electronic Health Record (EHR) 2023-2024 Vendor Assessment, indicating potential for growth in the healthcare sector. Leading healthcare organizations are implementing Oracle Fusion Cloud Applications Suite, suggesting a potential increase in customer base and revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.4451, compared to expectations of $0.37. Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. and Plains GP Holdings LP combined Earnings Call indicates positive outlook for future growth in crude production in the Permian basin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wba/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Walgreens Boots Alliance has made strategic executive appointments and updates to its healthcare and retail pharmacy services, indicating a proactive approach to turning around its stock performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on its healthcare segment and cost structure alignment demonstrates a commitment to improving business performance and addressing waning demand for certain products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:821
Chances: Toyota Motor stock has hit all-time highs. Ford reported strong earnings and an upbeat 2024 profit outlook and said the company will keep spending more on its EV transformation. The $19 billion deal between General Motors (GM) and LG Chem represents a landmark moment in the evolution of the EV industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:122
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co. (VRT) closed at $61.67, indicating a +1.53% shift from the previous trading day. Services activity in the United States is expanding, which is helping stocks like Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT). The average brokerage recommendation (ABR) for Vertiv Holdings Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:121
Chances: Las Vegas Sands Corp. has been named one of Fortune&amp;rsquo;s World&amp;rsquo;s Most Admired Companies in 2024, indicating a strong reputation and respect within the global business community. The company&amp;rsquo;s full year 2023 results show a significant increase in revenue, up 152% from FY 2022, indicating strong financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:135
Chances: ImmunoGen has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months,ImmunoGen (IMGN) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects ImmunoGen Announces Inducement Grants Under Nasdaq Listing Rule 5635(c)(4) Risks: AbbVie Inc. announced its plans to acquire ImmunoGen in an all-cash transaction valued at roughly $10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:72
Chances: Emirates, a Boeing client, has expressed concerns about the planemaker&amp;rsquo;s performance, indicating potential pressure on Boeing&amp;rsquo;s commercial airplanes segment The announcement of a sports streaming service by major media companies may impact traditional television viewership, potentially affecting Boeing&amp;rsquo;s global services segment The investigation into the 737 MAX 9 blowout and the missing bolts raises quality and safety concerns for Boeing&amp;rsquo;s commercial airplanes segment Risks: Potential loss of confidence from clients like Emirates could impact future orders and revenue for Boeing Competition from new sports streaming services may lead to reduced demand for traditional commercial airline services, affecting Boeing&amp;rsquo;s global services segment Quality and safety issues with the 737 MAX 9 could lead to regulatory scrutiny, potential lawsuits, and damage to Boeing&amp;rsquo;s reputation Score:72 chances characters count - risks characters count = 72</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Shares of ZoomInfo jumped 6.9% after a notable analyst upgrade, indicating positive market sentiment towards the stock. The stock trades at a 50% discount valuation to its software peers, leaving lots of runway for multiple expansion. Risks: The company is considered controversial, which could lead to increased volatility in the stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Investors are jubilant after the Fed’s clear signal that it would begin cutting interest rates in 2024. US stock markets jumped recently as investors cheered the much-awaited Nvidia’s results which showed the chip company enjoying strong sales. Risks: America’s position as a globally dominant force is under threat due to divisive politics and potential US China war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: First Horizon (FHN) delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended December 2023, indicating potential positive performance. The price-to-sales ratio suggests that stocks like FHN hold promise, especially for early development cycle investments. Upgrades to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) reflect growing optimism about First Horizon (FHN) earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings report indicates a stable performance, with revenue climbing 15% and operating income surging 37% The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend history, yield, and growth rates show potential for sustainable returns for investors The Food and Support Services United States (FSS United States) segment continues to offer food, hospitality and facility services for various institutions and venues, indicating a steady revenue stream Risks: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2024 earnings call is approaching, and it&amp;rsquo;s essential to closely monitor key metrics and compare them with Wall Street estimates and year-ago numbers for any potential areas of concern While the company has seen decent share price growth, the economic environment can significantly impact its performance, posing a potential risk The company may face challenges related to specialized dietary and support services provided by the Food and Support Services International (FSS International) segment Score:-74 chances characters count - risks characters count = -74</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella has achieved significant growth for the company, with the stock rising over 1,200% during his tenure. The acquisition of Activision-Blizzard and major investments in AI show Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s Intelligent Cloud segment, including Azure and other cloud services, continues to drive growth and revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co. has demonstrated its commitment to expanding its animal health business through the recent acquisition of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s aqua business. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong earnings report and solid guidance indicate that it is well-positioned to thrive despite potential challenges such as the expiration of its patent on Keytruda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:78
Chances: Comcast&amp;rsquo;s expansion of its broadband network to seven cities shows a commitment to investing in future growth opportunities Partnership with Volkswagen of America to target consumers across NBCU&amp;rsquo;s portfolio indicates potential for increased advertising revenue Investment in Showmax&amp;rsquo;s video streaming platform in partnership with MultiChoice Group demonstrates potential for growth in the streaming market Risks: Competition in the pay-TV market has been intensifying, with Charter overtaking Comcast as the No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UEC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uec/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: Uranium Energy Corp has reported successful drill results from its Roughrider Project in Canada, indicating positive exploration and metallurgical sample drilling outcomes. The stock price of UEC witnessed a jump in the last session, accompanied by above-average trading volume, signaling potential market interest in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NXT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nxt/</guid>
      <description>score:306
Chances: Nextracker (NXT) has beaten earnings expectations and lifted guidance, showing robust performance and product differentiation in the solar market. Increasing installation activities and benefits from the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA) should benefit the U.S. solar industry amid declining module pricing. Apple, Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FLEX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flex/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Flex Ltd. beat earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.71 compared to expectations of $0.62. Increased demand for Flex&amp;rsquo;s solutions in the industrial and automotive segments is likely to have positively impacted the company&amp;rsquo;s third-quarter performance. The completion of the spin-off of Nextracker Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Z</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/z/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/z/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: Zillow Group, Inc. has launched Zillow Immerse, a new interactive way to explore home listings, which may attract more users to the platform. The company is introducing new features such as reporting renters&amp;rsquo; on-time payments to credit bureaus, potentially adding value to its rental marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: Nokia has made a return to the smartphone market in Germany after reaching a global 5G patent cross-licensing deal with Oppo, indicating potential growth opportunities in the 5G sector. Quarterly beats and misses don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story of a company&amp;rsquo;s performance, suggesting that Nokia&amp;rsquo;s recent performance may not fully reflect its potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docu/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: DocuSign has seen significant share price rise in the past couple of months Direct lenders and Wall Street banks are in talks to provide financing for a potential buyout of DocuSign The firm provides cloud-based electronic signature solutions, which are in high demand as businesses and individuals look for secure and efficient ways to collect information and automate workflows Risks: The potential buyout and financing could introduce some uncertainty in the stock price Competition in the e-signature industry could pose a risk to DocuSign’s market share and growth prospects Market volatility and economic conditions may impact the demand for electronic signature solutions Score:88 chances characters count - risks characters count = 88</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:49
Chances: Permian Resources Corp. is engaging in a series of portfolio optimization transactions, including bolt-on acquisitions, acreage swaps, divestiture of non-core assets, and grassroots acquisitions, indicating a focus on strategic growth and efficiency. The recent pricing of an underwritten public offering of Class A common stock resulting in gross proceeds of approximately $5 million suggests a strong financial position and access to capital for future initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abt/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Abbott Laboratories is launching new products in response to high demand for weight-loss drugs, indicating a potential growth opportunity in the healthcare space. The company&amp;rsquo;s Protality brand, including a high-protein shake, is a strategic move to capitalize on the surge in demand for weight-loss products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cl/</guid>
      <description>score:183
Chances: Colgate-Palmolive (CL) has started to reconfirm its growth expectations after strong quarterly results. The global growth outlook was given a boost, helping to ease concerns about crude demand. The company&amp;rsquo;s Pet Nutrition segment offers potential for growth in the consumer staples sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMAT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amat/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: The semiconductor industry is booming, and Applied Materials is well-positioned to benefit from this growth.The company is undervalued on a DCF basis and has a predictable business.State-of-the-art toolset will bridge academic innovations and industry pathways to scale for semiconductors, microelectronics and other critical technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: ICICI Bank Ltd. is well positioned for above-average growth in financials. Efforts to bolster fee income, domestic loan dependence, and digitization of banking services will support ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s financials. Risks: Concerns related to higher restructuring costs may pose a risk for ICICI Bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cah/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cah/</guid>
      <description>score:-141
Chances: Cardinal Health&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Specialty Networks for $1.2 billion shows its commitment to investing in the specialty pharmacy business, which is a positive sign for potential growth and expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in the Pharmaceutical segment in the second-quarter fiscal 2024 indicates stability and potential for continued growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Alteryx&amp;rsquo;s fair value estimate is US$56.24, indicating potential for upside. Appointment of Kevin Rubin as Interim CEO could bring positive changes to the company. Risks: Fierce competition from bigger rivals such as Microsoft and Oracle may pose a challenge. Setbacks in winning new business have suppressed Alteryx&amp;rsquo;s valuation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: The stock price of Liberty Energy Inc. (LBRT) is up by 14% this week, indicating positive momentum. The company announced full year and fourth quarter 2023 financial and operational results, suggesting potential growth and stability. The Board of Directors has increased its share repurchase authorization to $750 million, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:22
Chances: Cisco Systems (CSCO) settling at $52.24, representing a -0.1% change from its previous close. Cisco, Microsoft Corp. and Samsung Electronics announced new meeting room solutions for enhanced collaboration experiences. Cisco released its 2024 Data Privacy Benchmark Study, highlighting growing privacy concerns and trust challenges with AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpc/</guid>
      <description>score:131
Chances: Marathon Petroleum Corp. reported strong yearly net income of $9.7 billion amidst strong cash flow generation, indicating a robust financial performance The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on cost reduction and margin enhancement projects, as well as a 10% reduction in standalone capex for 2024, suggests potential for improved profitability Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and a positive Zacks Earnings ESP indicate potential for positive earnings results in the upcoming report Risks: Uncertainty in the global oil market and geopolitical events may impact the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and profitability Fluctuations in crude oil prices and refining margins could pose a risk to the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and financial stability Potential regulatory changes and environmental concerns may affect the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and profitability Score:131 chances characters count - risks characters count = 131</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:249
Chances: Gen Digital Inc. has a strong focus on consumer cyber safety through its business solutions, which could be highly beneficial in the current digital landscape The partnership with Dan Levy to raise awareness about cybersecurity through Norton Genie shows a commitment to public education and could positively impact the brand&amp;rsquo;s reputation The release of fiscal 2024 third quarter financial results and hosting a conference call could provide insight into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and future prospects Risks: The potential for lower interest rates creates a general risk for all companies, including Gen Digital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: SentinelOne (S) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Shares of SentinelOne (S) jumped 5.2% in the morning session after BTIG analyst Gray Powell upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Neutral to Buy and assigned a price target of $30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Salesforce (CRM) has been performing well in the market and has seen a significant increase in stock value in the past year. The company&amp;rsquo;s solutions in sales force automation, customer service, marketing automation, and digital commerce make it well-positioned for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Businesses&amp;rsquo; and consumers&amp;rsquo; access to AI — without having to go through the cloud — is about to change, says HP CEO Enrique Lores. The advent of AI-powered PCs has the focus of many on Wall Street as the AI race enters its second lap in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Investors seeking high dividend-yielding stocks may find New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) attractive The joint venture between Blackstone and CPPIB winning a stake in the commercial property loans portfolio is a positive development for NYCB Banco Santander&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a 20% stake in a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: Walmart&amp;rsquo;s initiative to better train front-line workers and reduce the use of third-party security services shows a commitment to improving operational efficiency and customer service. Walmart partner DroneUp being approved to fly drones beyond the visual line of sight opens up opportunities for the company to enhance its delivery services and logistics capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Baillie Gifford&amp;rsquo;s increased investment in Sea Ltd indicates confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects. Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock has seen positive movement in the recent trading sessions. The growth-fueled Nasdaq Composite presents potential opportunities for Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock. Risks: Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock price has fallen 16% in the last quarter, signaling potential challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Valero Energy Corp&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings beat Wall Street estimates, indicating operational strength amid market challenges. The company&amp;rsquo;s premium refining operations have shown resilience, even in a carbon-constrained business operating environment. Lower refinery maintenance and ethanol production have positively impacted the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings in Q4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:184
Chances: Tencent Music Entertainment Group (TME) has shown resilience in the face of changing media consumption trends, with a focus on online music entertainment platforms and strategic partnerships,Renewal of a multi-year strategic licensing agreement with Universal Music Group demonstrates TME&amp;rsquo;s commitment to creating value for artists and music lovers,Release of TME Chart 2023 Year-End Charts showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to attract top music talent and engage audiences Risks: Challenges in the media industry, such as declining traditional distribution channels and pressure on online advertising models, could impact TME&amp;rsquo;s revenue streams,Resignation of a key executive, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kim/</guid>
      <description>score:179
Chances: Kimco Realty Corp continues to expand its portfolio with the acquisition of RPT Realty, adding 56 open-air shopping centers The company received the top score of 100 on the Human Rights Campaign Foundation&amp;rsquo;s Corporate Equality Index, demonstrating its commitment to diversity and inclusion Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales have shown a positive shift in the retail sector, which may benefit Kimco Realty Corp Risks: Elevated inflation and soaring borrowing costs may impact the retail sector, including Kimco Realty Corp The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend performance and sustainability need to be closely monitored, especially in the current economic environment Score:179 chances characters count - risks characters count = 179</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ry/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: Royal Bank of Canada (RY) is a well-established financial institution with a strong presence in multiple segments including Personal and Commercial Banking, Wealth Management, Insurance, and Capital Markets. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion efforts, such as the proposed acquisition of HSBC Bank Canada and the RBC Training Ground program, indicate a commitment to growth and diversification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xrx/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Xerox reported a surge in full-year free cash flow, indicating improved operational efficiency. The company&amp;rsquo;s announcement of a new operating model and organizational structure shows a commitment to reinvention and adaptation. JPMorgan named Xerox as a top hardware stock to own, indicating positive market sentiment towards the company&amp;rsquo;s potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: U.S. Steel Corp. has the potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Nippon Steel Corp. made an aggressive all-cash offer for United States Steel Corp., indicating potential for a high acquisition price. Risks: The acquisition bid from Nippon Steel Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Full Truck Alliance&amp;rsquo;s stock price might be vulnerable due to the large stake held by institutions. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 40.2% in Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd. Sponsored ADR (YMM).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. has seen substantial growth in its share price, with over a 100% increase this year. The company has announced multiple acquisitions and agreements to expand its product offerings and market reach. Institutions have substantial holdings in Core &amp;amp; Main, indicating significant influence over the company&amp;rsquo;s direction and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-108
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s solid-state battery technology could revolutionize the electric vehicle industry. Investors are seeing the bright side in the electric vehicle space, which bodes well for QuantumScape. The company is a developer of an alternative to lithium-ion batteries for electric vehicles, showing potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson beat fourth-quarter expectations with strong performance in the medtech segment. The company reported adjusted earnings of $2.29 per share, up 11.7% year-over-year, beating the consensus. Sales increased by 7.3% year-over-year to $21.4 billion, surpassing the consensus. Risks: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s stock tumbled after the company reported lower profit margins in the medical device and technology unit last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GKOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Glaukos Corporation continues to benefit from a robust product portfolio and favorable clinical trial results. The FDA approval of Glaukos&amp;rsquo; iDose TR is likely to reshape glaucoma care, promising proactive and durable treatment. Risks: The insider transaction and sale of shares by the President &amp;amp; COO could raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TKO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tko/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: TKO Group Holdings, Inc. has secured a landmark 10-year deal with Netflix to stream WWE&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Raw&amp;rdquo; as part of its live sports streaming ventures starting in 2025. The addition of Dwayne &amp;ldquo;The Rock&amp;rdquo; Johnson to TKO&amp;rsquo;s board of directors signifies a strong strategic move that may bring fresh perspectives and expertise to the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: AppLovin has been hot, and the run higher might have some momentum. AppLovin (APP) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Risks: It&amp;rsquo;s always important to assess the risk involved in investing in a company, especially in the volatile tech sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WDC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wdc/</guid>
      <description>score:195
Chances: Morgan Stanley named Western Digital a &amp;lsquo;Top Pick&amp;rsquo;, replacing Nvidia, with a price target of $73 representing a potential 30% upside Analysts upgraded WDC&amp;rsquo;s rating from Hold to Buy, with price targets indicating a potential 25% upside from current levels Semiconductor analyst sees Western Digital offering the best risk-reward opportunity Risks: Potential vulnerability to stock price due to large stake held by institutions Macro economic headwinds and spending cutbacks may affect prospects Score:195 chances characters count - risks characters count = 195</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ns/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: The acquisition of NuStar Energy by Sunoco in a $7.3 billion deal presents a significant opportunity for both companies to diversify and expand their businesses. Sunoco&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of NuStar will provide synergies in fuel distribution, leading to potential growth and supply synergies for both companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:434
Chances: Pure Storage, Inc. is delivering innovative and disruptive data storage products and services, positioning them to maximize the value of data. The company is leveraging advanced data storage technologies to provide crucial value-added services to public and private sector organizations in Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:22
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s business segments including entertainment, ESPN, and parks, experiences, and products provide a diverse revenue stream. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into direct-to-consumer services and international markets presents growth opportunities. Potential for positive impact from new board members and shareholder activism. Risks: Cancellation of the planned merger with Sony Group Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:257
Chances: BlackBerry (BB) is introducing new initiatives like QNX Everywhere and QNX Sound, addressing the growing demand for skilled embedded systems developers and showcasing their commitment to innovation and growth. The collaboration with MIH Consortium and the deployment of the IVY platform for electric vehicle platform demonstrates BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s potential for expansion in the automotive industry, a promising opportunity for future revenue growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DELL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dell/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: PC sales rebounded in the fourth quarter of 2023 and are poised to increase this year AI integration into PCs will promise more personalized user experiences At least 40-50% of the PCs in the next three years will be AI-enabled Risks: Evidence is piling up that the near-term outlook for PC demand is deteriorating KeyBanc Capital Markets analyst lowered 2024 laptop PC unit forecast to 1% year-over-year growth from 3% Score:46 chances characters count - risks characters count = 46</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVGO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avgo/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Broadcom, Inc. shares are surging, ripping 9% year to date. The semiconductor powerhouse enjoyed a solid rally in 2023. Goldman Sachs analyst anticipates robust growth in Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s AI-related businesses, especially in high-speed networking and custom compute segments. TSMC projected 2024 revenue growth of more than 20% on booming demand for high-end chips used in artificial-intelligence applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/edr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/edr/</guid>
      <description>score:158
Chances: Endeavor Group Holdings Inc. has shown growth potential through its innovative rights deals and exclusive live events in the Owned Sports Properties segment. The company&amp;rsquo;s Events, Experiences &amp;amp; Rights segment owns and operates several successful events, including the Miami Open and New York Fashion Week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:210
Chances: RTX has a golden opportunity to restart a 40-year-old missile business. Raytheon, with its recent contract with the U.S. Airforce, is set to expand its footprint in the missiles defense market. RTX&amp;rsquo;s Raytheon is set to expand its footprint in the global radar market, with the GhostEye MR contributing to the needs of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Southwest Airlines Co. invites you to listen to a live webcast of its fourth quarter 2023 financial results, indicating transparency and potential positive news for investors. The future of the U.S. economy is promising, marked by a robust recovery in the travel sector, which could benefit Southwest Airlines and its stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arm/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Arm Holdings plc is set to report their financial results for the third quarter of fiscal year 2024 on February 7, 2024. Risks: The IPO debut of Arm Holdings in 2023 did not bring about the market excitement many had hoped for, which may indicate potential challenges for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-76
Chances: NU Holdings Ltd. has an impressive earnings surprise history, indicating potential for strong performance in its next quarterly report. The Brazilian neobank has achieved staggering growth and has its sights set on an even bigger market opportunity. If you’re looking for new growth opportunities, it would be wise to consider emerging market stocks, such as NU Holdings Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: The company is set to release its fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results, providing an opportunity for investors to assess its performance. Kraft Heinz has a strong presence in the US, Canada, and international markets, with popular brands like Velveeta and Oscar Meyer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/owl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/owl/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Blue Owl Capital Inc. and Blue Owl Capital Corporation are both scheduled to release their financial results for the fourth quarter, providing potential opportunities for investors to assess the performance of these companies. Risks: The volatility of the stock market and potential fluctuations in the financial performance of Blue Owl Capital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:86
Chances: Recovery in group and business transient travel demand, capital-recycling efforts and healthy balance sheet strength are likely to drive Host Hotels&amp;rsquo; performance in the quarters ahead. The pause in interest rate hikes and the likelihood of interest rate cuts in 2024 have generated strong appreciation of REITs, including Host Hotels, across multiple subsectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-132
Chances: Realty Income Corp. is acquiring Spirit Realty Capital, which indicates potential for growth and expansion in its real estate portfolio. The Federal Open Market Committee&amp;rsquo;s dovish outlook and prediction of rate cuts could benefit Realty Income Corp. as a real estate company with a focus on generating dependable monthly cash dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MANU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/manu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/manu/</guid>
      <description>score:-44
Chances: Manchester United Plc&amp;rsquo;s new investor deal with Raine Group could bring in fresh capital and strategic guidance for the club. Prologis CEO&amp;rsquo;s positive outlook for 2024 indicates potential growth opportunities for the company. Risks: Manchester United&amp;rsquo;s lowered sales forecast due to early elimination from the Champions League poses a challenge to its revenue and profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bti/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: The company&amp;rsquo;s geographical segmentation provides diversified revenue streams and market exposure. High-yield dividend stocks are offering potential bargain-bin prices for value investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s brands like Kent, Dunhill, Lucky Strike, and Pall Mall continue to resonate with consumers globally. Risks: Revenue decline and guidance cuts by the company raise concerns about its financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:50
Chances: Pfizer CEO is &amp;lsquo;all in&amp;rsquo; on Pfizer stock, showing confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future Pharmaceutical executives from various companies are looking to break into the lucrative obesity market, indicating potential for industry growth Pfizer is receiving unsolicited mini-tender offers, suggesting interest from potential investors Risks: Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s best days might be behind it as demand for its COVID-19 products slows down Pfizer shares dropped more than 40% last year, indicating potential instability in the stock Legal battles against diversity and inclusion programs could impact Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s image and operations Score:50 chances characters count - risks characters count = 50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:223
Chances: The e-commerce enabler made a substantial strategic mistake but managed to bounce back from the consequences. Some skyrocketing stocks are poised to keep rising for a long time, making money for investors along the way. Monster and Shopify look poised for bull runs in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:-55
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s product pipeline includes a wide range of modalities, such as prophylactic vaccines, cancer vaccines, and localized regenerative therapeutics, providing opportunities for significant future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on intratumoral immuno-oncology and systemic intracellular therapeutics reflects a strong commitment to addressing complex medical challenges with innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:152
Chances: Equitrans Midstream is setting up just below a buy point amid a run of more than 50% in 2023. Operational results for the third quarter of 2023 show a 12% transmission pipeline throughput growth. Equitrans Midstream delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 75% and 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:129
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) has been gaining attention from investors and analysts, indicating potential for growth in the stock&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The announcement of the industry’s only integrated secure networking solution with Wi-Fi 7 and the launch of a new access point and 10 Gigabit Power over Ethernet switch demonstrates Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and staying ahead in the cybersecurity market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-53
Chances: Coupang, Inc. is underfollowed on Wall Street, but has immense growth potential. The global e-commerce market is expected to reach $6.3 trillion for 2023, indicating a strong uptrend in e-commerce adoption. Emerging markets are likely to grow faster than most developed markets through the decade, presenting multibagger opportunities for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corporation Foundation offering STEM scholarships to support education and future talent in Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) disciplines. Risks: Inflation and higher natural gas prices are impacting utility investors and may lead to increased costs for customers. Score:40 chances characters count - risks characters count = 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: The release of the E100 5G Enterprise Router by Cradlepoint indicates a potential growth opportunity in the enterprise router market, especially for retail and small office applications. ODIDO&amp;rsquo;s selection of Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s billing system for upgrading its infrastructure shows confidence in Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and presents a promising revenue stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Toast received an upgrade from &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; by Goldman Sachs analysts There is optimism about the restaurant software provider&amp;rsquo;s ability to gain market share in 2024 Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies Risks: Etsy stock declined after Goldman Sachs downgraded it from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Charles Schwab shares came under pressure after a downgrade from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Elena Gomez, CFO of Toast Inc, executed a sale of company shares Score:16 chances characters count - risks characters count = 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Kenvue Inc. is poised to benefit from the favorable court ruling in a product-liability case, which has resulted in a nearly 5% increase in the company&amp;rsquo;s stock price. The Self Care segment, including cough, cold and allergy, pain care, digestive health, and smoking cessation, presents a strong opportunity for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Credo Technology Group Holding Ltd has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months. The company is an innovator in providing secure, high-speed connectivity solutions that deliver improved energy efficiency as data rates and bandwidth requirements increase. Risks: Notable insider transactions involving the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) may raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:218
Chances: Pinterest (PINS) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. With healthy fundamentals, Pinterest (PINS) appears primed for further appreciation. The top social media stocks of 2023 saw much relief, with many clocking in high double-digit percentage gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRWD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Shares of cybersecurity company CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) jumped 5.4% in the afternoon session after Morgan Stanley analyst Hamza Fodderwala upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Equal-Weight (Hold) to Overweight (Buy) and raised the price target from $203 to $304.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Gap Inc operates as a global apparel retail company with a strong presence in the market. The company has a diversified product range catering to men, women, and children, under various segments like Gap, Old Navy, Banana Republic, and Athleta. Strategic plans for revitalizing the business with a new CEO at the helm and a marketing background may lead to positive developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has entered into an agreement to acquire a worldwide license to Precision BioSciences, Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Azercabtagene Zapreleucel (azer-cel), an allogeneic CD19 CAR T cell therapy program for autoimmune diseases. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has a strong platform used by developers, artists, and designers across various industries. The company has a large user base, with over 1.1 million game creators relying on its software toolkit each month. Risks: Unity Software Inc. plans to lay off about 25% of its workforce, which could impact its operational capabilities and future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters reported strong growth in fourth quarter-to-date revenue, with the American Eagle segment growing in the high single digits and Aerie growing in the low teens. The company raised its fourth-quarter revenue and operating profit outlook, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Clarivate Plc has been consistently releasing new reports and products, indicating a strong focus on innovation and meeting the evolving needs of the healthcare and research industries. Risks: The company operates in a highly competitive market, and its success depends on the adoption of its products and solutions by academia, government, life sciences, and healthcare organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:294
Chances: AGNC Investment (AGNC) is a wise investment option at present due to an active portfolio-management strategy, decent liquidity and an attractive ROE. MPLX should have plenty of fuel to continue growing its big-time payout. Compared to this past year, 2024 is expected to be much better for the economy, and that means it will look even better for the stock market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YUMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Yum China (YUMC) has been ranked number one globally for the Restaurant &amp;amp; Leisure Facilities Industry in the S&amp;amp;P Global 2023 Corporate Sustainability Assessment, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability. Yum China&amp;rsquo;s KFC unveiled its 10,000th store in Hangzhou, indicating strategic growth and solidifying leadership in China&amp;rsquo;s dynamic restaurant market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Gold producers are raising bets on copper through deals and investments, indicating potential growth opportunities. Expectations of interest rate cuts and a weaker dollar have fueled the rise in gold prices, presenting a positive outlook for gold mining companies like Newmont Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ivz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ivz/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Invesco Ltd. continues to demonstrate its commitment to providing a better investment experience for its clients by implementing changes to its ETFs. The company is set to release its fourth quarter 2023 results, signaling transparency and accountability to its investors. Invesco&amp;rsquo;s position in the market may improve as the company explores the potential for launching exchange traded funds tied to the spot price of bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: The merger between DISH Network and EchoStar has the potential to create a stronger satellite empire. Expanding wireless plans for Samsung Galaxy devices could attract new customers and drive revenue growth for Boost Infinite. Inclusion in the S&amp;amp;P SmallCap 600 index could bolster EchoStar&amp;rsquo;s visibility and attract more investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: Pet care stocks are incredibly effective in diversifying investment portfolios, leveraging the robust growth of the pet care industry. Chewy stock (NYSE:CHWY) has experienced an endless plunge over the past two years, which may make the stock a prime M&amp;amp;A target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fl/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Foot Locker, Inc. is leveraging its omni-channel capabilities to bridge the digital world with physical stores, providing a competitive edge in the retail sector Cost-optimization program implemented by Foot Locker is expected to improve its performance and financial results Strong start of the holiday season and revenue growth reported by Foot Locker indicates a favorable market position Risks: Nike&amp;rsquo;s weak sales outlook and cost cuts may indicate challenges in the athletic apparel and footwear industry, potentially impacting companies like Foot Locker Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s stock jump might be a short-term trend and not indicative of long-term performance Competition from industry peers like Nike, Lululemon Athletica, and adidas AG poses a risk to Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s market share Score:14 chances characters count - risks characters count = 14</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: VinFast is taking advantage of IRA funding and infrastructure bill opportunities to expand in the US and North America. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in CES 2024 indicates its commitment to showcasing new EV concepts and models, signaling potential growth in the electric vehicle market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hims/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Hims &amp;amp; Hers Health, Inc. unveiled Weight Loss by Hims &amp;amp; Hers, a comprehensive and customizable clinical approach specifically designed to help people achieve their individual weight-loss goals. The company has appointed Craig Primack, a pioneer in the field of clinical obesity medicine, as SVP of Weight Management, indicating a strong focus on addressing the growing issue of obesity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:351
Chances: VF Corp. (VFC) shares fell over 7% Monday after the owner of the Vans and North Face shoe and apparel brands warned that the company’s business operations were disrupted by a cyberattack. VF said in a regulatory filing Monday that the hacker encrypted some IT systems and stole data, including personal information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: The merger between Warner Bros. Discovery and Paramount Global could result in a stronger position in the streaming world due to potential reshaping and reevaluation of portfolios Future mergers in the media and entertainment industry could lead to a lot of activity and potential bundling and deconsolidation of assets The opportunity for consumers to choose their own bundles in the future could be a positive development for the industry Risks: The disappointing box office performance of Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom raises concerns about the industry&amp;rsquo;s understanding of audience preferences Cord cutting, tough ad environment, and pressure to turn profits pose challenges for companies in the media and entertainment sector The unpredictability of box office performance and the potential impact on theater revenues may create uncertainty in the short term Score:27 chances characters count - risks characters count = 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Immunovant, Inc. announced that results from the initial cohort of patients in the Phase 2 clinical trial of batoclimab in Graves’ disease exceeded 50% response rates, indicating promising potential for the drug Risks: Oral brepocitinib failed to meet its primary endpoint of Systemic Lupus Erythematosus Responder Index (SRI-4) change of 4 at Week 52, indicating a setback in the drug&amp;rsquo;s development for this specific indication Score:2 chances characters count - risks characters count = 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: The Trade Desk Inc. has a strong position in the advertising technology sector, with a comprehensive platform that includes various advertising products and services. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent stock performance has shown resilience despite market fluctuations, indicating potential strength in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/onon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/onon/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: On Holding had another great quarter, and it has big plans for the next few years. The company is on a mission to double sales over the next three years. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. On Holding AG raised full-year sales guidance after posting another record quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YPF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</guid>
      <description>score:128
Chances: South America&amp;rsquo;s increased oil and gas production has huge implications for the global market Sweeping decree in Argentina opens the door for privatization of state-run companies Argentina&amp;rsquo;s U.S.-listed companies are enjoying a moment in the sun Risks: Argentina&amp;rsquo;s economy is broke and lacks funds Political instability in Argentina with the election of a far-right leader Score:128 chances characters count - risks characters count = -872</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:437
Chances: Solar power stocks received a boost from Jefferies, which initiated coverage on some of the biggest companies in the sector. Falling interest rates have fueled Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; stock this week. The projected fair value for Array Technologies is US$36.63 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity&amp;hellip; Jessica Lawrence-Vaca, Senior Vice President, Policy and External Affairs, Array Technologies ALBUQUERQUE, N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: India&amp;rsquo;s information technology firms are accepting tougher contract terms to win large deals from clients as they compete for fewer orders in an uncertain global economy. Generative AI technology can create more jobs than it is expected to eliminate, according to Tech Mahindra&amp;rsquo;s outgoing CEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gme/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: The investment landscape has been abuzz with the trend of meme stocks, a phenomenon ushered in by the remarkable and dramatic rise in GameStop’s stock in 2021. Investors know that the current expectations project rate cuts as early as March, which is a major positive for the economy overall and suggests that we have avoided a recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Organon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence shows a proactive approach to patient care and may lead to increased sales. The company&amp;rsquo;s exclusive distribution of Emgality and RAYVOW in Europe presents a significant opportunity for revenue growth in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/azn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/azn/</guid>
      <description>score:-135
Chances: AstraZeneca (AZN) closed at $65.95, indicating a +1.77% shift from the previous trading day. AstraZeneca (AZN) announces that it is buying vaccine company, Icosavax. The additional supply of RSV shot for infants by AstraZeneca and Sanofi indicates a positive outlook for meeting winter demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</guid>
      <description>score:115
Chances: Netflix (NFLX) stock has continued its robust rally off its mid-2022 lows. With Squid Game: The Challenge reality series leaning on the strength of its impressive Squid Game franchise and new plans for its video game business, it’s hard not to feel better about the company’s growth story moving into 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Masonite&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PGT Innovations creates a leading door and window solutions company with over $4 billion in combined revenue, indicating potential for growth and expansion in the industry. Products from PGT&amp;rsquo;s brands were used in every home featured on a popular HGTV show, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s strong presence and market influence in the fenestration industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Recent revenue results and global market trends help solidify Roku as a strong investment opportunity. Several stocks soared in November on increasing signs that the Federal Reserve could be done raising interest rates as well as rising speculation that rates could even start coming down in the first half of 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: Nio management provided significant insights into the direction of the business. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. (NIO). NIO Inc. (NIO) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: The acquisition of Abcam by Danaher for $5.7 billion presents an opportunity for Danaher to expand its Life Sciences portfolio and accelerate the drug discovery process The completion of the acquisition despite initial opposition from Abcam&amp;rsquo;s founder demonstrates the determination of Danaher to enhance its product and service offerings Abcam shareholders&amp;rsquo; approval of the acquisition indicates confidence in the potential synergies and benefits of the deal Risks: There might be integration challenges and cultural differences between Danaher and Abcam, which could impact the success of the acquisition The valuation of $24 per share for Abcam could be considered high, and if the expected synergies do not materialize, it may result in financial losses for Danaher Unforeseen regulatory or market challenges could affect the planned expansion of Danaher&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences portfolio Score:41 chances characters count - risks characters count = -959</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s expansion into energy generation and storage systems presents a significant opportunity for growth and diversification. Despite declining vehicle insurance registrations in China, Tesla is still aiming for record-setting quarterly deliveries and a strong year overall. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to save lives and prevent injuries with its Autopilot technology provides a positive outlook for its automotive segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s shares jumped 7.3% in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s after an investor group made a $5.8 billion offer to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private Risks: The retail industry is facing challenges such as stiff competition from online rivals and high inflation Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -980</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:-89
Chances: XP stock has gained 53% and has outperformed the S&amp;amp;P 500&amp;rsquo;s 20% gain year to date. Cutting underperforming stocks out of your portfolio could help maximize your gains in the new year. Robinhood&amp;rsquo;s long-winning streak and recent gains suggest a positive momentum in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cere/</guid>
      <description>score:197
Chances: AbbVie&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Cerevel Therapeutics for $8.7 billion indicates a significant growth opportunity in the neuroscience sector Cerevel Therapeutics has a robust pipeline of multiple clinical-stage and preclinical candidates with potential across several diseases like schizophrenia, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease, and mood disorders Risks: The success of Cerevel Therapeutics&amp;rsquo; product candidates such as CVL-231, Darigabat, Tavapadon, CVL-871, and CVL-936 is not guaranteed Score:197 chances characters count - risks characters count = -803</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-89
Chances: One Nasdaq 100 component, with a slew of competitive advantages, is cheaper than it&amp;rsquo;s ever been as a publicly traded company Three historically inexpensive, brand-name companies owned by one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful investors are ripe for the picking in December Recent filings with the SEC have revealed that Gilchrist Malcolm Ian Grant, a director of Liberty SiriusXM Group (NASDAQ:LSXMA), sold 3,258 shares of the company on November 28, 2023 Risks: You probably had a good month in the markets, but a fifth of the stocks out there are trading lower through the rally The Oracle of Omaha&amp;rsquo;s company is requesting secrecy as it builds up its stake in one or more businesses This year has been a little dry when it comes to Warren Buffett stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Aurora Innovation, Inc. has reported strong progress towards commercial launch with an Autonomy Readiness Measure (ARM) of 84% in Q3 2023 The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in industry conferences and events indicates a commitment to showcasing its technology and engaging with potential investors The opening of the industry’s first lane for driverless trucks supported by commercial-ready terminals in Dallas and Houston demonstrates Aurora&amp;rsquo;s advancement in autonomous vehicle technology Risks: The company&amp;rsquo;s significant net loss of US$414.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
