<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>expansion on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/expansion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in expansion on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/expansion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FUTU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/futu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/futu/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: S&amp;amp;P Expects A Steady Increase in Futu&amp;rsquo;s Overseas Client Base, Reaffirms Its BBB- Rating Futu Holdings Stock Shows Improved Relative Price Strength Futu Announces Plan for App Removal in Mainland China App Stores Moomoo Expands Into Malaysia Following Success In Singapore Futu Ranks #2 on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s 100 Fastest-Growing Companies List For 2022 Risks: Futu Announces Proposed Dual Primary Listing on The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong Limited Futu Provides Regulatory Update in China Futu Holdings Records Solid Growth in Q3 with US$247.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Expansion into new markets, such as opening casinos and online gaming products. Positive analyst outlook and investment recommendations. Potential growth in the sports betting and gambling industry. Partnership announcements with major media companies like ESPN. Strong investor interest and bullish sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:-13
Chances: Tesla gets approval for diner and drive-in theater, expanding its services. Top analyst believes Tesla&amp;rsquo;s business could generate $20 billion annually by 2030. Elon Musk teases a new Cybertruck as a &amp;lsquo;production candidate,&amp;rsquo; showing ongoing innovation. VinFast&amp;rsquo;s stock surge presents a potential opportunity for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
