<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UK on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UK on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:53:45 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Former Bank of England Governor Mervyn King Criticizes Rishi Sunak&#39;s Promise to Cut Inflation in Half</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/former-bank-of-england-governor-mervyn-king-criticizes-rishi-sunaks-promise-to-cut-inflation-in-half/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:53:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/former-bank-of-england-governor-mervyn-king-criticizes-rishi-sunaks-promise-to-cut-inflation-in-half/</guid>
      <description>Former Bank of England Governor Mervyn King Criticizes Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s Promise to Cut Inflation in Half Former Bank of England Governor Mervyn King has criticized UK Prime Minister Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s promise to cut inflation in half this year.
King said that the government has little control over prices and that Sunak&amp;rsquo;s promise is &amp;ldquo;not wise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Walters Warns of Lower Profits</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/robert-walters-warns-of-lower-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 08:19:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/robert-walters-warns-of-lower-profits/</guid>
      <description>Robert Walters, a global professional recruitment firm, has warned that its full-year profits will be lower than expected. The company said that the UK and US markets have been hit by a slowdown in hiring, while the Asia-Pacific region has been more resilient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Economy Regains Pre-Pandemic Level of Output With April Rise</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-economy-regains-pre-pandemic-level-of-output-with-april-rise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-economy-regains-pre-pandemic-level-of-output-with-april-rise/</guid>
      <description>UK Economy Grows in April The UK economy grew by 0.4% in April 2023, the highest growth rate since January 2022. The growth was driven by a strong performance in the services sector, which grew by 0.5%. The manufacturing sector also grew, by 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Sunday UK Briefing: Tories Risk &#39;Civil War&#39;; CBI Funding Fears</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-sunday-uk-briefing-tories-risk-civil-war-cbi-funding-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:31:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-sunday-uk-briefing-tories-risk-civil-war-cbi-funding-fears/</guid>
      <description>UK Politics in Turmoil: Tories Face &amp;lsquo;Civil War&amp;rsquo;, CBI Fears for Economy
The Conservative Party is facing a leadership crisis, with a group of Conservative MPs planning to submit letters of no confidence in Boris Johnson if he does not resign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak Hints at UK Crackdown on Airline-Style &#39;Drip Pricing&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/sunak-hints-at-uk-crackdown-on-airline-style-drip-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/sunak-hints-at-uk-crackdown-on-airline-style-drip-pricing/</guid>
      <description>UK Government Considers Crackdown on Drip Pricing The UK government is considering cracking down on a controversial pricing practice known as &amp;ldquo;drip pricing.&amp;rdquo; Drip pricing is when businesses advertise a low price for a product or service, but then add on extra fees for things like delivery or insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK House Prices Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:49:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-drop/</guid>
      <description>UK House Prices Drop House prices in the UK have fallen for the first time in three months, as buyers are stretched by rising interest rates and the cost of living.
The average price of a home in the UK fell by 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OECD Signals Tax Cuts Probably Out of Reach for UK Government</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/oecd-signals-tax-cuts-probably-out-of-reach-for-uk-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/oecd-signals-tax-cuts-probably-out-of-reach-for-uk-government/</guid>
      <description>OECD Says Tax Cuts Unlikely for UK Government
The Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) has said that tax cuts are unlikely for the UK government in the near future. The OECD said that the UK government needs to focus on reducing the deficit and debt, rather than cutting taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK House Prices Post First Annual Drop Since 2012, Halifax Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-post-first-annual-drop-since-2012-halifax-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-post-first-annual-drop-since-2012-halifax-says/</guid>
      <description>UK House Prices Fall for First Time in a Decade House prices in the UK fell by 0.3% in May, marking the first annual drop since 2012. The fall in house prices was driven by a slowdown in the market, as buyers became more cautious in the face of rising interest rates and the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Is Swimming Against the Tide on Taxes, Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s Tax Hikes: Swimming Against the Tide
The UK is facing a cost of living crisis, with inflation at a 40-year high and energy prices soaring. Chancellor Rishi Sunak has been criticized for raising taxes, rather than cutting them, to help people cope with the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Inquiry, Inheritance Tax, House Prices: The Readout</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:09:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</guid>
      <description>Key Issues in the UK News The UK news is dominated by a number of key issues in the coming weeks and months. These include:
The long-awaited public inquiry into the UK government&amp;rsquo;s handling of the Covid-19 pandemic. The government&amp;rsquo;s plans to raise the threshold at which people start to pay inheritance tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Respite Period For UK Housing Is Over</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:06:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</guid>
      <description>The UK housing market is showing signs of slowing down, with house prices stabilizing in May after a sharp rise in the fourth quarter of 2022. However, transaction volumes are falling, suggesting that further price falls are only a matter of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:35:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</guid>
      <description>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year According to Moody&amp;rsquo;s, the UK is headed for a &amp;ldquo;mild recession&amp;rdquo; this year. The recession is expected to be caused by higher-than-expected inflation and rising interest rates. Inflation in the UK is currently at a 40-year high, and interest rates have been raised four times since December.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
