<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Semiconductors on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/semiconductors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Semiconductors on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/semiconductors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Marvell&amp;rsquo;s AI revenue is showing promising growth, which could be a positive sign for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. Despite a recent pullback, institutional shareholders have seen a 7.2% return over the past year, indicating some level of confidence in Marvell. The company beat Q2 earnings and revenue estimates, which may suggest its resilience in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Intel stock has experienced a significant surge in 2023, suggesting potential growth opportunities. Intel is betting on artificial intelligence (AI) beyond the cloud, which could drive future innovation and demand. Partnerships and agreements with companies like Tower Semiconductor and Synopsys may strengthen Intel&amp;rsquo;s position in the semiconductor market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: AMD is expanding its client base and powering next-gen technologies, such as Hitachi Astemo&amp;rsquo;s AI-based camera system. AMD&amp;rsquo;s graphics card market share has bounced back, indicating strength in its core business. The CEO of AMD states that the AI market is &amp;lsquo;skyrocketing,&amp;rsquo; suggesting potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the AI and semiconductor sectors positions it for potential growth. Partnerships with companies like Reliance and Tata in India could open up new markets and opportunities for NVIDIA. The AI and semiconductor industries are expected to continue growing, benefiting NVIDIA as a major player.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
