<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Semiconductors on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/semiconductors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Semiconductors on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:03:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/semiconductors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ARM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arm/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Nvidia has become the undisputed leader in a stock market powered by AI hopes. Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s blowout earnings show the fear of missing out in the stock market rally is alive and well. Shares of Asian chip makers rose after strong earnings from Nvidia buttressed expectations of booming global demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVGO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avgo/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Broadcom, Inc. shares are surging, ripping 9% year to date. The semiconductor powerhouse enjoyed a solid rally in 2023. Goldman Sachs analyst anticipates robust growth in Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s AI-related businesses, especially in high-speed networking and custom compute segments. TSMC projected 2024 revenue growth of more than 20% on booming demand for high-end chips used in artificial-intelligence applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
