<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Surprise on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Surprise on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:05:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:-78
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co. (VRT) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The overly optimistic recommendations of Wall Street analysts make the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric questionable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:218
Chances: Pinterest (PINS) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. With healthy fundamentals, Pinterest (PINS) appears primed for further appreciation. The top social media stocks of 2023 saw much relief, with many clocking in high double-digit percentage gains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
