<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Surprise on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Surprise on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: Encouragement for homeowners and contractors to call 811 for utility line marking. Dividend payment of $0.6675 scheduled for September 20. Second-quarter earnings per share better than guidance due to lower operating expenses. Coastal Virginia Offshore Wind project on budget and track for completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</guid>
      <description>score:-55
Chances: Tapestry&amp;rsquo;s strong portfolio consisting of Coach, Kate Spade, and Stuart Weitzman brands. Positive earnings surprise history and favorable ingredients for potential quarterly beat. Risks: Integration challenges and execution risks associated with the acquisition of Capri Holdings. Mixed response from Wall Street and the industry to the acquisition deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:1294
Chances: Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; Q2 results may show increased megawatts shipment and strong margin performance from STI Norland acquisition. Array Technologies has an impressive earnings surprise history and a favorable combination for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The growth of solar energy and technological advancements create opportunities for solar stocks, including Array Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
