<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Surprise on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Surprise on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Medical Properties (MPW) delivered FFO and revenue surprises of 33.33% and 142.04%, respectively, for the quarter ended December 2023. The healthcare REIT sub sector has emerged as the new leader among REITs, indicating potential growth opportunities for Medical Properties Trust. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent performance has pleased investors despite the troubles of a major tenant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: First Horizon (FHN) delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended December 2023, indicating potential positive performance. The price-to-sales ratio suggests that stocks like FHN hold promise, especially for early development cycle investments. Upgrades to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) reflect growing optimism about First Horizon (FHN) earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:218
Chances: Pinterest (PINS) has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. With healthy fundamentals, Pinterest (PINS) appears primed for further appreciation. The top social media stocks of 2023 saw much relief, with many clocking in high double-digit percentage gains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
