<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Profitability on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/profitability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Profitability on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:53:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/profitability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Grab advances break-even timeline on boost from cost cuts, strong demand Grab Reports Second Quarter 2023 Results Grab Reports First Quarter 2023 Results Grab lifts revenue forecast, delivery business breaks even Grab targets Group Adjusted EBITDA breakeven by H2 2024 as it accelerates path to profitability Risks: Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Grab cuts 1,000 jobs to stay competitive Grab Holdings stock boosted despite falling delivery sales Indonesia’s GoTo Extends Stock Slump After Shaking Up Top Ranks Grab Sees Slower Growth While It Pursues 2024 Profitability HappyFresh Board Is Said to Hire Alvarez &amp;amp; Marsal for Review Score:12 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Rivian shows progress toward profitability and exceeding production forecasts. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s competitive advantage in the electric vehicle market. Positive response to Rivian&amp;rsquo;s electric pickup models R1T and R1S. Analysts seeing Rivian as a buy with raised price targets. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s improvements leading to narrower Q2 losses and increased sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/smci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/smci/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Consistent profitability reflected in the company&amp;rsquo;s Profitability Rank of 9 out of 10. Impressive growth in terms of revenue and profitability with a Growth Rank of 10 out of 10. Benefiting from the demand for AI servers, contributing to growth. Delivery of high-throughput, low latency E3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
