<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Profitability on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/profitability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Profitability on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/profitability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Bilibili Inc. has seen stronger profits and growth potential, as it benefits from generative AI and the Chinese tech sector&amp;rsquo;s growth. Despite recent losses, there is still an opportunity in Bilibili Inc. as it aims to rebound and overcome challenges. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings reports and revenue estimates suggest the potential for positive developments in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Ambev S.A. continues to see growth potential, with its net profit rising 36% in Q4, and its efforts to tap into the international beverage market. The demand for energy drinks could boost Ambev&amp;rsquo;s sales, as it navigates through inflationary pressures and explores growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: C3.ai is off to a strong start with significant traction across its business in Q1 2024. Ark Invest predicts that the AI industry will add $200 trillion to the economy by 2030, making AI stocks promising. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s Q1 loss was narrower than expected, and revenues rose year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Grab advances break-even timeline on boost from cost cuts, strong demand Grab Reports Second Quarter 2023 Results Grab Reports First Quarter 2023 Results Grab lifts revenue forecast, delivery business breaks even Grab targets Group Adjusted EBITDA breakeven by H2 2024 as it accelerates path to profitability Risks: Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Grab cuts 1,000 jobs to stay competitive Grab Holdings stock boosted despite falling delivery sales Indonesia’s GoTo Extends Stock Slump After Shaking Up Top Ranks Grab Sees Slower Growth While It Pursues 2024 Profitability HappyFresh Board Is Said to Hire Alvarez &amp;amp; Marsal for Review Score:12 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/smci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/smci/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Consistent profitability reflected in the company&amp;rsquo;s Profitability Rank of 9 out of 10. Impressive growth in terms of revenue and profitability with a Growth Rank of 10 out of 10. Benefiting from the demand for AI servers, contributing to growth. Delivery of high-throughput, low latency E3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
