<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stock price movement on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-price-movement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stock price movement on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:35:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-price-movement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:782
Chances: Affirm Holdings&amp;rsquo; recent stock price movement, closing at $15.52, with a -1.77% change from the previous session. Announcement of Affirm&amp;rsquo;s plan to publish its Q4 and fiscal year 2023 shareholder letter, financial results, and conference call details. Positive improvement in Affirm Holdings&amp;rsquo; Relative Strength (RS) Rating, upgrading from 85 to 92.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:-172
Chances: Transocean expects adjusted contract drilling revenues of $720 million in Q3 2023, indicating potential revenue growth. Total adjusted contract drilling revenues showed an increase in Q2 2023 compared to the first quarter, which might suggest improving business performance. The global demand for energy presents an opportunity for energy stocks, including Transocean, to capitalize on the need for various energy sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:942
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s sale of Simon &amp;amp; Schuster to buyout firm KKR for $1.6 billion in an all-cash deal indicates strategic moves to optimize its portfolio and focus on core businesses. Paramount Global-B (PARA) reported second-quarter results that beat Wall Street estimates, showcasing positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
