<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>electric vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in electric vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why America Isn&#39;t Ready For the EV Takeover</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-america-isnt-ready-for-the-ev-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-america-isnt-ready-for-the-ev-takeover/</guid>
      <description>Why America Isn&amp;rsquo;t Ready For the EV Takeover Despite the growing popularity of electric vehicles (EVs), there are still a number of challenges that are limiting their adoption in America. These challenges include:
Software glitches: EV software is still relatively new and can be buggy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultralong-Range Electric Cars Are Arriving. Say Goodbye to Charging Stops.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ultralong-range-electric-cars-are-arriving.-say-goodbye-to-charging-stops./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 23:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ultralong-range-electric-cars-are-arriving.-say-goodbye-to-charging-stops./</guid>
      <description>Ultralong-Range EVs: The Future of Electric Transportation A new class of electric vehicles (EVs) with ultralong range are arriving, making it possible to drive 1,000 miles or more without stopping to charge. These EVs are powered by new battery technology that is more efficient and can store more energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis Says No Deal Yet in Canada Battery Plant Subsidy Feud</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stellantis-says-no-deal-yet-in-canada-battery-plant-subsidy-feud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:40:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stellantis-says-no-deal-yet-in-canada-battery-plant-subsidy-feud/</guid>
      <description>Stellantis Puts Canadian EV Battery Plant on Hold Stellantis, the parent company of Chrysler, Dodge, and Jeep, has put a hold on construction of an electric-vehicle battery plant in Windsor, Ontario. The company is seeking government subsidies to help fund the $5 billion project, but the Canadian government has not yet committed to any funding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
