<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1103 ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:1103
Chances: ON Semiconductor exceeded expectations in its second-quarter 2023 results, driven by strong sales of chips for automotive and industrial applications. The company&amp;rsquo;s business transformation efforts led to profitable growth, with $100 million in business closeouts in Q2 2023 and $400 million since 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1120 CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:1120
Chances: Demand for EV charging is set to rise due to the increasing adoption of electric vehicles. International Energy Agency data indicates significant growth in electric vehicle sales, promising potential for EV charging companies. ChargePoint announced a new credit agreement, which may boost its financial position and growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1108 LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:1108
Chances: Li Auto deliveries surpassed 30,000 for the second straight month, with Li keeping the top spot among startups. Chinese electric-vehicle makers Li Auto, XPeng, and NIO deliver a combined 65,604 vehicles in July, a record and up more than 100% from last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: General Motors plans to boost employment next year despite concerns over the shift to electric vehicles, which could signal positive growth for the company. The expectation of offering unionized workers higher wages might indicate a positive outlook for General Motors&amp;rsquo; financial performance and workforce morale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0795 FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:795
Chances: Fisker announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, which could tap into the growing demand for electric trucks in the U.S. market. Fisker&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Henrik Fisker, expressed optimism about the demand for the Fisker Alaska pickup truck, especially if it is priced competitively and offers a &amp;lsquo;cool&amp;rsquo; product in the sub-$30,000 EV category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1162 F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:1162
Chances: Ford reported second-quarter revenue and adjusted diluted earnings per share that beat Wall Street estimates, which could be positive for the stock. General Motors&amp;rsquo; plans to boost employment for electric vehicle production may have a positive impact on the automotive industry, including Ford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STLA | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stla/</guid>
      <description>Chances: Stellantis is in early talks with officials in Canada and the United States on setting up a battery manufacturing plant in North America, indicating potential expansion in the EV market. GM&amp;rsquo;s manufacturing chief stated that Stellantis may not need fewer workers for EV production, which could bode well for the company&amp;rsquo;s employment plans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
