<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:03:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: The EV charging market is expected to reach $76.9 billion by 2027, creating growth opportunities for companies like ChargePoint. Global sales of electric vehicles (EVs) are expected to increase by 35% in 2023, driving demand for EV charging solutions. Demand for EVs and EV charging facilities is on the rise due to government support and climate change awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> XPEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xpev/</guid>
      <description>score:1055
Chances: The International Energy Agency anticipates a significant increase in electric vehicle (EV) sales, which could positively impact companies like XPeng. Earnings and sales boost for EV stocks driven by growing demand for electric vehicles and charging solutions. China&amp;rsquo;s EV manufacturers, including XPeng, gained ground as Tesla&amp;rsquo;s EV sales in China dropped more than 30%, potentially benefiting domestic competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Model Y SUV became the world&amp;rsquo;s best-selling car with 267,200 vehicles sold in the first three months of the year. Tesla plans to begin production at its Debrecan, Hungary plant in 2025 and its Munich plant in 2026. EV sales increased by 65% last year, indicating a growing market for electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
