<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:04:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:821
Chances: Toyota Motor stock has hit all-time highs. Ford reported strong earnings and an upbeat 2024 profit outlook and said the company will keep spending more on its EV transformation. The $19 billion deal between General Motors (GM) and LG Chem represents a landmark moment in the evolution of the EV industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-108
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s solid-state battery technology could revolutionize the electric vehicle industry. Investors are seeing the bright side in the electric vehicle space, which bodes well for QuantumScape. The company is a developer of an alternative to lithium-ion batteries for electric vehicles, showing potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: Nio management provided significant insights into the direction of the business. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. (NIO). NIO Inc. (NIO) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s expansion into energy generation and storage systems presents a significant opportunity for growth and diversification. Despite declining vehicle insurance registrations in China, Tesla is still aiming for record-setting quarterly deliveries and a strong year overall. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to save lives and prevent injuries with its Autopilot technology provides a positive outlook for its automotive segment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
