<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:05:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise robotaxi unit offering to pay $75,000 to resolve investigation shows willingness to address regulatory issues GM&amp;rsquo;s best vehicle sales since 2019 indicate potential for growth and competitive edge in the U.S. market Risks: California&amp;rsquo;s plan to require all new vehicles sold in the state to be electric or plug-in electric hybrids by 2035 may pose a challenge for GM&amp;rsquo;s traditional vehicle line The investigation into the pedestrian crash involving GM&amp;rsquo;s self-driving car could impact public perception and trust in the company Score:-64 chances characters count - risks characters count = -64</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Lucid Group has announced updates to the Air lineup, offering greater flexibility to customers and receiving recognition from Car and Driver for the Lucid Air Pure SiriusXM&amp;rsquo;s audio streaming entertainment experience is now available to all new and existing Canadian Lucid owners, potentially enhancing the overall customer experience Despite challenges and slowing sales growth in the electric vehicle market, there is potential for increased consumer adoption if the focus shifts from range to other factors Risks: The resignation of Lucid Group&amp;rsquo;s CFO, Sherry House, may raise concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial stability and leadership stability Downgrade by Needham analysts over weak demand for Lucid&amp;rsquo;s electric vehicles indicates potential challenges in the company&amp;rsquo;s market position and sales growth Waning U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: Nio management provided significant insights into the direction of the business. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. (NIO). NIO Inc. (NIO) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s expansion into energy generation and storage systems presents a significant opportunity for growth and diversification. Despite declining vehicle insurance registrations in China, Tesla is still aiming for record-setting quarterly deliveries and a strong year overall. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to save lives and prevent injuries with its Autopilot technology provides a positive outlook for its automotive segment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
