<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electric Vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PSNY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/psny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/psny/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Polestar reported record deliveries in the second quarter, growing 36% year-on-year, indicating strong momentum. Polestar is collaborating with Mobileye to build an integrated driver assist solution for its electric SUV coupé, Polestar 4. Polestar plans to adopt the North American Charging Standard to enable access to Tesla Supercharger network in the USA and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Fisker plans to significantly increase EV production in the fourth quarter, which could lead to higher revenues. Fisker is expanding its presence in Europe, opening up new markets and increasing its global reach. Fisker&amp;rsquo;s innovative and affordable electric vehicle, the Fisker Pear, is generating interest with its competitive pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:33
Chances: Swiss Bank doubled down on EV stock Rivian and achieved significant gains, indicating investor interest. Battery material price easing expected in the next year could benefit Rivian&amp;rsquo;s EV production. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia + Technology Conference suggests market engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: ChargePoint&amp;rsquo;s role in expanding EV charging infrastructure suggests growth potential due to the increasing demand for electric vehicles. Partnerships like the one with Tesla and Hilton could contribute to ChargePoint&amp;rsquo;s success and market presence. The need for more EV charging stations in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Lucid CEO mentions that Air EV price cuts were well received, indicating positive market response. Lucid announces final production specifications for the Lucid Air Sapphire, enhancing its product portfolio. Rivian, another EV maker, raises production targets, signaling potential growth in the EV market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Nio is pioneering the EV revolution, suggesting growth potential in the electric vehicle industry. Analysis on NIO Inc. from BestGrowthStocks.com may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s prospects. There are catalysts expected for Nio stock investors in 2023, indicating potential opportunities. Goldman Sachs includes NIO Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:57
Chances: Ford reveals a new electric vehicle challenge to compete with top Tesla models, indicating innovation in the EV market. Rising investments and job plans in the US battery cell venture suggest potential growth in the electric vehicle (EV) sector. Ford raises pay for 8,000 UAW workers in line with the 2019 contract, which may improve labor relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Tesla stock receives a huge price target hike, indicating potential for significant growth. Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s involvement in geopolitics could benefit Tesla&amp;rsquo;s global positioning. Tesla&amp;rsquo;s dominance in the Chinese EV market is a strong competitive advantage. Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Supercharger network expansion through deals with Hilton and Honda will enhance user experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
