<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Insurance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/insurance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Insurance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/insurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Banco Bradesco SA engages in the provision of financial and insurance services and operates through Banking and Insurance segments, indicating diversification and potential for growth Latin American stocks and currencies climbed due to China&amp;rsquo;s support for its markets, which may positively impact Banco Bradesco SA&amp;rsquo;s performance The new CEO of Banco Bradesco SA sees an open window for public offerings in Brazil next year, signaling potential growth opportunities Risks: The plan by two of Brazil&amp;rsquo;s largest banks to take payments company Cielo SA private faces pushback from minority stakeholders, which may impact market confidence in Brazilian financial institutions Latin America witnessed sluggish growth in 2023 due to high inflation and restricted monetary policies, which may pose challenges for Banco Bradesco SA&amp;rsquo;s performance in the region Banco Bradesco S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cccs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cccs/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: CCC Intelligent Solutions Holdings Inc. has announced strong year-end financials with revenue and adjusted EBITDA surpassing guidance, indicating a positive growth trajectory. The company&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based software as a service platform has the potential to revolutionize the property and casualty insurance economy by facilitating digital workflows and connecting trading partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
