<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock offering on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-offering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock offering on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-offering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GERN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gern/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Geron Corporation&amp;rsquo;s pipeline candidate, imetelstat, received FDA Committee backing for the treatment of transfusion-dependent anemia in adult patients with low-to-intermediate-1 risk myelodysplastic syndromes, indicating potential for future market approval. Shares of Geron Corporation (GERN) soar after positive news from the FDA&amp;rsquo;s Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee, showing investor optimism in the company&amp;rsquo;s potential drug approvals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. has seen substantial growth in its share price, with over a 100% increase this year. The company has announced multiple acquisitions and agreements to expand its product offerings and market reach. Institutions have substantial holdings in Core &amp;amp; Main, indicating significant influence over the company&amp;rsquo;s direction and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
