<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>inflation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/inflation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in inflation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:52:23 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/inflation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Visco Says He Would Have Preferred More Gradual Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:52:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Visco Prefers Gradual Approach to Rate Hikes European Central Bank (ECB) Governing Council member Ignazio Visco said on Tuesday that he would have preferred a more gradual approach to raising interest rates.
The ECB has raised interest rates by 375 basis points since December, and two more quarter-point moves are expected this month and next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Weekend Reading: With Debt Debacle Done, It&#39;s Back to Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Inflation: The Fed&amp;rsquo;s Tough Balancing Act The Federal Reserve has signaled that it will begin to raise interest rates in March, which is likely to lead to higher borrowing costs for businesses and consumers. Inflation is still running at a high level, and there is a risk that it could get worse if the Fed raises rates too quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam&#39;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:18:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control Vietnamese Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh has urged the government to focus on economic growth while keeping inflation under control.
Chinh made the remarks at a government meeting on Tuesday, as the country faces rising inflation and a slowdown in economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:11:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</guid>
      <description>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time Mexico&amp;rsquo;s central bank, Banxico, has signaled that it will keep interest rates high for a long period of time in order to tame inflation.
The bank&amp;rsquo;s decision comes as inflation in Mexico has reached a 20-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawkish Australian Economists See RBA Raising Key Rate to 4.6%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</guid>
      <description>RBA to Raise Cash Rate to 4.6%?
A group of Australian economists are predicting that the Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA) will raise the cash rate to 4.6% by the end of 2023. This would be the highest level for the cash rate since 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Says Core Price Trend Was &#39;Broadly Seen as Worrisome&#39; in May</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:57:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</guid>
      <description>ECB Concerned About Inflation The European Central Bank (ECB) is concerned about the path of inflation, according to the minutes of its May policy meeting. Core inflation, which excludes food and energy, rose to 3.8% in May from 3.5% in April. This was the highest level since December 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:43:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked European Central Bank (ECB) President Christine Lagarde said on Thursday that there is no clear evidence that underlying inflation has peaked.
Core inflation, which excludes food and energy prices, rose to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone Inflation Slows, but ECB to Keep Rates Low</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eurozone-inflation-slows-but-ecb-to-keep-rates-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eurozone-inflation-slows-but-ecb-to-keep-rates-low/</guid>
      <description>Eurozone Inflation Slows, but ECB to Keep Rates Low Inflation in the eurozone slowed to 3.0% in May from 3.5% in April, but the European Central Bank (ECB) is likely to keep interest rates low for now.
The ECB has said that it will keep rates low until at least the end of 2023, even if inflation falls below its target of 2%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
