<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>climate change on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/climate-change/</link>
    <description>Recent content in climate change on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:00:09 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/climate-change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>California Floods Show the Limits of Man-Made Solutions</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/california-floods-show-the-limits-of-man-made-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/california-floods-show-the-limits-of-man-made-solutions/</guid>
      <description>California Floods Show the Limits of Man-Made Solutions California is experiencing a series of historic floods that have caused widespread damage. The floods are a result of a combination of factors, including climate change, development, and poor infrastructure. Man-made solutions, such as levees and dams, have not been able to prevent the floods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change Policy: Where&#39;s the Justice in Net Zero?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-policy-wheres-the-justice-in-net-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-policy-wheres-the-justice-in-net-zero/</guid>
      <description>Climate Change Policy: Where&amp;rsquo;s the Justice in Net Zero? The concept of &amp;ldquo;net zero&amp;rdquo; emissions is gaining traction as a way to address climate change. However, there are concerns that net zero could exacerbate existing inequalities, particularly between rich and poor countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change and Natural Disasters: The Direst Predictions</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-and-natural-disasters-the-direst-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-and-natural-disasters-the-direst-predictions/</guid>
      <description>Natural disasters seem to be on the rise, and many are wondering if climate change is the main cause. While it&amp;rsquo;s not the only factor, climate change is certainly exacerbating the problem. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how climate change is making natural disasters worse than our direst predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric Vehicles Are an Imperfect Answer to Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/electric-vehicles-are-an-imperfect-answer-to-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 12:00:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/electric-vehicles-are-an-imperfect-answer-to-climate-change/</guid>
      <description>Electric Vehicles Are an Imperfect Answer to Climate Change Electric vehicles (EVs) are becoming increasingly popular as a way to reduce greenhouse gas emissions. EVs produce zero emissions while driving, which makes them a promising option for reducing our reliance on fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
