<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investing on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: Bilibili Inc. has announced that it is doubling down on its live-streaming business, which could significantly expand its revenue streams and attract more users. The Company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainable development and publication of its 2023 ESG Report demonstrates good governance and responsible business practices, which could enhance its reputation and appeal to socially conscious investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:507
Chances: Newmont Corporation (NEM) concluded the recent trading session at $38.64, signifying a -1.1% move from its prior day&amp;rsquo;s close. Gold declined after surging to a fresh record as investors booked profit in a price rally that’s seen as overextended. The latest trading day saw Newmont Corporation (NEM) settling at $39.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Coupang (NYSE:CPNG) stock broke out and jumped 11.4% in the afternoon session after the company announced it would raise its WOW membership by 58% Significantly high institutional ownership implies Coupang&amp;rsquo;s stock price is sensitive to their trading Earnings results often give us a good indication of what direction a company will take in the months ahead Risks: Coupang shares remain down more than 60% from their initial public offering price The post-pandemic era witnessed significant readjustments in terms of shifting back to shopping in physical stores There were revisions on the downside for some of the major e-commerce players Score:82 chances characters count - risks characters count = 82</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:104
Chances: Merck&amp;rsquo;s (MRK) stock has shown a 7.0% increase over the past three months, indicating positive growth potential. Early-stage study data shows positive clinical response for Moderna&amp;rsquo;s (MRNA) experimental cancer therapy, potentially boosting the healthcare industry. Merck (MRK) has initiated a Phase 3 clinical trial for its investigational oral selective KRAS G12C inhibitor, indicating a strong pipeline for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NRG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nrg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nrg/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: NRG Energy has achieved A- scores in both the 2023 Climate Change and Water Security reports. Investors are moving fast to buy up value stocks in the S&amp;amp;P 500 while they&amp;rsquo;re still cheap. The smart home market is forecasted to experience significant long-term expansion, creating opportunities for NRG&amp;rsquo;s residential solar and electric vehicle services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: When it comes to investing in fintech companies and the financing concept of BNPL — buy now, pay later — Affirm still comes to top of mind. The stock for this buy now, pay later company should be bought and held.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: IBM closed positively at $193.34, showing potential for growth in the near future. IBM has been paying close attention to by Zacks.com users, indicating investor interest in the stock. Risks: The company has undergone significant changes and may not be the same as it used to be, posing potential risks for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
