<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investing on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investing on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:14:59 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stock Rally That Keeps Going Could Be &#39;Dangerous&#39; Right Now: Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-rally-that-keeps-going-could-be-dangerous-right-now-qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:14:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-rally-that-keeps-going-could-be-dangerous-right-now-qa/</guid>
      <description>The stock market has been on a tear in recent months, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 index up more than 10% year-to-date. However, some experts are warning that the rally could be unsustainable, and that a correction could be on the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poker, &#39;The Price of Time,&#39; Tsunamis and Other Views of Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/poker-the-price-of-time-tsunamis-and-other-views-of-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:06:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/poker-the-price-of-time-tsunamis-and-other-views-of-markets/</guid>
      <description>The Price of Time: A Look at Different Views of Markets Markets are complex and can be viewed in many different ways. Some people view markets as a game of poker, where the goal is to outwit and outplay your opponents. Others view markets as a reflection of the underlying value of assets, and believe that prices will eventually converge to their true value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Today: U.S.-China Trade Deal, Fed Pause, AI Boom</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-today-u.s.-china-trade-deal-fed-pause-ai-boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-today-u.s.-china-trade-deal-fed-pause-ai-boom/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Today: U.S.-China Trade Deal, Fed Pause, AI Boom The stock markets are expected to be positive today, as investors are optimistic about the U.S.-China trade deal and the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s pause on interest rate hikes. The AI boom is also a positive sign for the economy, as it is expected to create new jobs and boost productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stocks: Are They Overvalued?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-stocks-are-they-overvalued/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-stocks-are-they-overvalued/</guid>
      <description>Tech stocks have been on a tear in recent years, with the Nasdaq Composite Index more than doubling in value since the start of 2019. However, there are some signs that the tech rally may be coming to an end. In recent weeks, tech stocks have started to decline, with the Nasdaq Composite Index down about 10% from its all-time high.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
