<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investing on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:03:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/be/</guid>
      <description>score:163
Chances: With governments around the world continuing to push for greener energy solutions, new environmental technology opportunities emerge every day. There are some great hydrogen stocks for investors to buy as we enter into March. The drive for decarbonization across the globe, coupled with the increasing need to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, makes the hydrogen industry attractive for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arm/</guid>
      <description>score:49
Chances: Semiconductor valuations remain expensive even after selloff Nvidia has become the undisputed leader in a stock market powered by AI hopes Shares of Asian chip makers rose after strong earnings from Nvidia Intel unveiled its Intel Foundry services in the AI landscape Smaller players catching the AI wave Risks: Valuations are lofty for the chip maker and other tech giants, signaling a possible bubble Investors may be forgetting basic principles of investing to chase hot AI stocks Fear of missing out in the stock market rally may lead to irrational investment decisions Score:49 chances characters count - risks characters count = 49</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: Shares of Robinhood (HOOD) jumped 7.3% in the afternoon session after major indices rose The company announced plans for a dual listing to increase liquidity of its shares and reach investors in more markets The continued focus on providing retail brokerage, trading in U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Global-e has a huge growth runway. Consumers worldwide are increasing the percentage of spending allocated online. Recent challenges are in the rearview mirror and Shopify is poised for continued growth. Risks: The e-commerce platform specialist is struggling with weak demand. Shopify has had problems with profitability in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: IBM closed positively at $193.34, showing potential for growth in the near future. IBM has been paying close attention to by Zacks.com users, indicating investor interest in the stock. Risks: The company has undergone significant changes and may not be the same as it used to be, posing potential risks for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
