<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investing on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:05:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:286
Chances: Schlumberger (SLB) has been receiving an average brokerage recommendation equivalent to a Buy, indicating positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts. The recent trading session saw Schlumberger (SLB) closing at $54.48, representing a +1.97% move from its previous day&amp;rsquo;s close. De-risking the Welchau play in Austria may not just be a big step toward Austrian energy independence, it may also ease Europe&amp;rsquo;s $800 billion energy crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Global-e has a huge growth runway. Consumers worldwide are increasing the percentage of spending allocated online. Recent challenges are in the rearview mirror and Shopify is poised for continued growth. Risks: The e-commerce platform specialist is struggling with weak demand. Shopify has had problems with profitability in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: IBM closed positively at $193.34, showing potential for growth in the near future. IBM has been paying close attention to by Zacks.com users, indicating investor interest in the stock. Risks: The company has undergone significant changes and may not be the same as it used to be, posing potential risks for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/be/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: Bloom Energy Inc. is teaming up with Shell Plc. to study decarbonization solutions, utilizing Bloom’s proprietary hydrogen electrolyzer technology. Projected to reach nearly $258 billion by 2028, the hydrogen technology industry may be a new gold mine for investors. Risks: Earnings weren&amp;rsquo;t what investors expected this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
