<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oil and Gas on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/oil-and-gas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oil and Gas on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/oil-and-gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Equitrans Midstream is the IBD Stock Of The Day, with a run of more than 50% in 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s operational results for the third quarter of 2023 show a 12% transmission pipeline throughput growth. Risks: Equitrans Midstream is reportedly considering a sale, which could potentially impact the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: Permian Resources Corp. is engaging in an underwritten public offering, indicating a potential increase in capital and growth opportunities. The company&amp;rsquo;s consistent focus on responsible acquisition and development of crude oil suggests a sustainable approach to driving returns. The declaration of quarterly cash dividends reflects a commitment to delivering value to shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YPF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</guid>
      <description>score:128
Chances: South America&amp;rsquo;s increased oil and gas production has huge implications for the global market Sweeping decree in Argentina opens the door for privatization of state-run companies Argentina&amp;rsquo;s U.S.-listed companies are enjoying a moment in the sun Risks: Argentina&amp;rsquo;s economy is broke and lacks funds Political instability in Argentina with the election of a far-right leader Score:128 chances characters count - risks characters count = -872</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
