<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings beat on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings beat on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:04:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:-94
Chances: Revenues and earnings beat in first-quarter fiscal 2024. Direct-to-consumer revenues rose 4% in the quarter. Exploration of potential wholesale partnerships in various retail channels. Positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Launch of &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program to engage loyal consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:72
Chances: AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s revised stockholder settlement was approved, clearing the way for the company to sell more shares and pay down some of its debt. AMC reported second-quarter results that beat analyst estimates on both the top and bottom lines, with the third quarter off to an &amp;rsquo;explosive start&amp;rsquo; due to strong movie performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Strong earnings and revenue beat ratios for the healthcare sector. Attractive dividend yield of 4.7%, making it appealing for income-seeking investors. Global presence and strong fundamentals of Pfizer as a pharmaceutical heavyweight. Risks: Challenges related to declining sales of Covid products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
