<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings beat on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings beat on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>YMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: Why Full Truck Alliance Stock Is Jumping Today Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd. Just Recorded A 100% EPS Beat: Here&amp;rsquo;s What Analysts Are Forecasting Next Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s (NYSE:YMM) Fundamentals Look Pretty Strong: Could The Market Be Wrong About The Stock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iot/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Samsara Earnings Top Estimates On Big Spending Customers Samsara Inc. (IOT) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Samsara Announces Appointment of Todd Bluedorn to Board of Directors Samsara To Announce Second Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results On August 31, 2023 Samsara Officially Named As A 2023 UK’s Best Workplace for Women™ Risks: Samsara Reports First Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results Samsara Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: PDD Holdings Jumps 15% On Earnings Beat; Revenue Up 66% PDD ADRs Surge as Online Shoppers Send Sales Soaring at Parent of Pinduoduo and Temu Pinduoduo-owner PDD beats revenue expectations as promotions lure consumers Temu-Owner PDD Soars After Strong Sales Defy Chinese Gloom China-Founded Rivals Shein and Temu Ramp Up War for American Shoppers Risks: PDD Holdings Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Under Armour reports Q1 earnings beat and maintains fiscal outlook. Under Armour launches new &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s growth strategies appear encouraging. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Positive impact from executive changes and growth strategies. Risks: Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s revenue slips amid challenging retail environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Sands extends capacity-building support for Asian Community Development Council. LVS reports Q2 earnings and revenues beating estimates. LPGA Tour Champion Minjee Lee and LVS collaborate to showcase women&amp;rsquo;s sports. LVS involved in partnerships supporting youth homelessness solutions. Macao reclaims crown from Vegas as world&amp;rsquo;s top gambling hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:24
Chances: NYCB reports Q2 earnings beat, stock rises by 5.1%. Expansion of private banking business with hires and acquisitions. Positive response to the company&amp;rsquo;s quarterly cash dividend on preferred stock. Analysts bullish on bank growth and share potential. Successful implementation of AFSVision® at Flagstar Bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Monthly dividend payments providing attractive income to investors. Strong Q2 earnings beat on net spread and dollar roll. Positive outlook for AGNC Investment Corp. as a high-dividend stock. Bullish views from Wall Street analysts. Consistent dividend declarations and monthly common stock dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Stellar returns of 211% over the past three years for FCX investors. Strong Q2 earnings and revenue beats despite international obstacles. Positive outlook for the mining sector and commodity stocks. Potential growth opportunities in the electrification and EV trend. Strategic importance of copper in various industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: Dividend payout of $0.40 indicates commitment to shareholders. Recognition of $25 billion opportunity in schools. Positive transition in leadership with appointment of new CEO. Strong brand portfolio strength and earnings beat in Q2. Potential for income and upside as a dividend stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line reports strong Q2 financial results. Earnings and revenues surpass estimates in Q2. Introduction of the all-new Norwegian Viva in Europe. Positive outlook for travel industry and consumer spending. Solid bookings expected to aid Q2 earnings. Risks: Guidance misses forecasts due to cost pressures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: JD.com beats earnings estimates despite China&amp;rsquo;s economic challenges. Strong net profit growth in the second quarter. Partnership with Gucci and digital flagship store launch. Positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts. Investment potential in high-growth tech stocks. Risks: JD.com stock impacted by China&amp;rsquo;s economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Solid financial performance and earnings beat. Positive market gains and stock outperformance. Strategic organizational updates and repurchase of outstanding warrants. Support for communities impacted by wildfires. Dividend increase and strong fundamentals. Risks: Vulnerability to oil price fluctuations. Production shutdowns due to wildfires and refinery issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/extr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/extr/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Extreme Networks surpasses Q4 earnings and revenue estimates. Extreme Networks recognized as a Gartner Peer Insights™ Customers&amp;rsquo; Choice. Favorable industry outlook highlighting networking stocks. High institutional ownership indicates investor confidence. Positive response to innovative products and solutions. Risks: Uncertain future affecting the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for outperformance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:-52
Chances: Kinross Gold beats earnings and revenue estimates in Q2. Kinross granted right to earn 70% interest in Launi East. Routine renewal of NCIB and redemption of senior notes. Successful unsecured notes offering to refinance outstanding notes. Positive industry outlook highlighting Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: TAL Education Group beats earnings expectations for full year 2023. Institutional investors show interest with a significant ownership stake. TAL Education Group files its annual report on Form 20-F. TAL Education Group&amp;rsquo;s strong week for shareholders doesn&amp;rsquo;t alleviate long-term losses. Top-line decline in Q3 attributed to seasonality and forex fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: BlackBerry added CA$671 million to its market cap in the past 7 days. BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s Q1 earnings and revenues beat estimates and were up year-over-year. BlackBerry selected by Mobility in Harmony (MIH) Consortium for next-gen EV development. Private equity firm Veritas makes takeover offer for BlackBerry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Marvell&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings slightly beat estimates, suggesting positive performance. Launch of industry&amp;rsquo;s first 800G ZR/ZR+ modules for data center interconnects. Positive returns of 7.2% for institutional shareholders despite recent pullback. Solid Q2 earnings and revenue beats reported by Marvell Technology. Marvell&amp;rsquo;s strong position as an AI play in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-117
Chances: Walmart Inc. (WMT) is a well-established retail giant with a long track record of performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s brand is synonymous with quality products and services. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s willingness to pay increasing dividends to shareholders indicates a commitment to rewarding investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s dominance in the retail sector, especially in groceries, is seen as &amp;lsquo;unstoppable&amp;rsquo; and offers growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
