<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Beat on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Beat on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:-48
Chances: Wayfair Inc. beat earnings expectations in the fourth quarter of 2023, with reported EPS of $-0.11 compared to expectations of $-0.22. The company&amp;rsquo;s free cash flow of $62 million beat analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates, indicating improved cash generation. Wayfair reported an increase in active customers, showing positive growth in its customer base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gh/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: GH anticipates continued expansion with 2024 revenue outlook set between $655 to $670 million. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 109.9% in Guardant Health (GH). Guardant Health (GH) possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.4451, compared to expectations of $0.37. Plains All American Pipeline, L.P. and Plains GP Holdings LP combined Earnings Call indicates positive outlook for future growth in crude production in the Permian basin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FLEX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flex/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Flex Ltd. beat earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.71 compared to expectations of $0.62. Increased demand for Flex&amp;rsquo;s solutions in the industrial and automotive segments is likely to have positively impacted the company&amp;rsquo;s third-quarter performance. The completion of the spin-off of Nextracker Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Valero Energy Corp&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings beat Wall Street estimates, indicating operational strength amid market challenges. The company&amp;rsquo;s premium refining operations have shown resilience, even in a carbon-constrained business operating environment. Lower refinery maintenance and ethanol production have positively impacted the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings in Q4.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
