<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings beat on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings beat on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: JD.com reports earnings beat in the second quarter, outperforming estimates despite economic challenges in China. Gucci and JD.com announce a digital partnership and the launch of an official Gucci flagship store, indicating growth in the luxury e-commerce segment. Analysts suggest JD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Freeport-McMoRan has shown attractive financial prospects, which could make it an appealing investment opportunity. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price increased, rewarding institutional investors with strong returns. Freeport-McMoRan&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat estimates, indicating strong performance despite challenges. Risks: The international obstacles, such as production issues and challenges in Indonesia, pose a risk to the company&amp;rsquo;s profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wu/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: Western Union is paying a dividend of $0.235, which can be attractive to income-focused investors. The company has opened its first-ever concept store in Jordan, which could potentially enhance its presence in the region and attract new customers. Western Union reported strong Q2 earnings, beating estimates and raising its annual profit outlook, indicating positive growth in its core business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MDLZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mdlz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mdlz/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Mondelez International (MDLZ) reported better-than-expected Q2 earnings and raised its full-year sales guidance, leading to a rise in its stock price. MDLZ is favored by institutional investors who own 79% of the company, indicating strong institutional confidence. The company thrives on strategic buyouts and demonstrates strength in the snacking category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) reported Q2 earnings that beat estimates, leading to a 5.1% rise in its stock price. The company has a history of offering high yields to its investors, making it attractive for income-seeking investors. NYCB has shown steady growth in high margins despite facing cost-related challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: Kinross Gold announced positive earnings and revenue beats in the last quarter, leading to a 7.6% increase in stock price. The company was granted the right to earn a 70% interest in Launi East, potentially unlocking new growth opportunities. Kinross Gold declared a quarterly dividend, offering returns to its shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: Cenovus Energy has delivered a solid 57% CAGR over the past 3 years, indicating positive performance for shareholders. The company beat quarterly profit estimates, with shares climbing as a result, suggesting strong financial performance. Cenovus Energy&amp;rsquo;s fundamentals appear strong, indicating potential growth opportunities in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Las Vegas Sands has announced various charitable contributions and initiatives, showcasing its commitment to social responsibility. The company&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat Wall Street estimates, indicating a positive performance in key markets like Macao and Singapore. Macao reclaimed its position as the world&amp;rsquo;s top gambling hub, which could benefit Las Vegas Sands&amp;rsquo; operations in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: PDD Holdings Inc. (PDD) has reported strong revenue growth, with sales soaring and beating expectations. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock jumped 15% after an earnings beat, reflecting positive investor sentiment. Pinduoduo-owner PDD&amp;rsquo;s growth has been defying Chinese economic challenges, making it a notable player in e-commerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vsh/</guid>
      <description>score:91
Chances: Vishay Intertechnology reported Q2 earnings that beat estimates, and revenues showed a year-over-year increase. Vishay is expanding its product offerings and capabilities, such as adding new devices and enhancing its opto capabilities. The company has opened a new state-of-the-art resistors manufacturing facility and signed agreements to bundle haptic technology licenses with its products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: Why Full Truck Alliance Stock Is Jumping Today Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd. Just Recorded A 100% EPS Beat: Here&amp;rsquo;s What Analysts Are Forecasting Next Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s (NYSE:YMM) Fundamentals Look Pretty Strong: Could The Market Be Wrong About The Stock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iot/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Samsara Earnings Top Estimates On Big Spending Customers Samsara Inc. (IOT) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Samsara Announces Appointment of Todd Bluedorn to Board of Directors Samsara To Announce Second Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results On August 31, 2023 Samsara Officially Named As A 2023 UK’s Best Workplace for Women™ Risks: Samsara Reports First Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results Samsara Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Under Armour reports Q1 earnings beat and maintains fiscal outlook. Under Armour launches new &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s growth strategies appear encouraging. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Positive impact from executive changes and growth strategies. Risks: Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s revenue slips amid challenging retail environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/extr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/extr/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Extreme Networks surpasses Q4 earnings and revenue estimates. Extreme Networks recognized as a Gartner Peer Insights™ Customers&amp;rsquo; Choice. Favorable industry outlook highlighting networking stocks. High institutional ownership indicates investor confidence. Positive response to innovative products and solutions. Risks: Uncertain future affecting the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for outperformance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: TAL Education Group beats earnings expectations for full year 2023. Institutional investors show interest with a significant ownership stake. TAL Education Group files its annual report on Form 20-F. TAL Education Group&amp;rsquo;s strong week for shareholders doesn&amp;rsquo;t alleviate long-term losses. Top-line decline in Q3 attributed to seasonality and forex fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-117
Chances: Walmart Inc. (WMT) is a well-established retail giant with a long track record of performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s brand is synonymous with quality products and services. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s willingness to pay increasing dividends to shareholders indicates a commitment to rewarding investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s dominance in the retail sector, especially in groceries, is seen as &amp;lsquo;unstoppable&amp;rsquo; and offers growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
