<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings beat on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings beat on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:05:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-beat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: Li Auto reported impressive earnings for Q2 2023, beating expectations with reported EPS of $2.18 compared to the expected $0.88. The company&amp;rsquo;s aim to outsell established luxury car brands like BMW, Mercedes-Benz, and Audi in China by 2024 demonstrates ambitious growth targets and market confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: Under Armour reported a revenue and earnings beat in the first quarter of fiscal 2024, with direct-to-consumer revenues rising 4%. Under Armour is assessing potential wholesale partners in various retail channels, indicating potential expansion opportunities. Positive earnings and revenue surprises in the previous quarter suggest potential positive momentum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: PagSeguro Digital is expected to have the right combination of key factors for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Increasing sales figures and vertical market growth could positively impact PagSeguro Digital&amp;rsquo;s business in 2023. The positive trend in earnings estimate revisions suggests a potential upside in PagSeguro Digital&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Lloyds Banking Group&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in beating earnings expectations in Q2 2023 reflects the bank&amp;rsquo;s positive financial outlook. Lloyds&amp;rsquo; prediction of a lower Bank of England interest rate peak and a positive economic growth forecast could bode well for the bank&amp;rsquo;s operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teva/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teva/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Teva Pharmaceutical&amp;rsquo;s strong second-quarter results and beating earnings and sales estimates are positive indicators. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on launching biosimilars and brand-name drugs like Ajovy presents growth prospects. Teva&amp;rsquo;s settlement agreement to pay U.S. hospitals and provide naloxone indicates the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to resolving legal issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-117
Chances: Walmart Inc. (WMT) is a well-established retail giant with a long track record of performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s brand is synonymous with quality products and services. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s willingness to pay increasing dividends to shareholders indicates a commitment to rewarding investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s dominance in the retail sector, especially in groceries, is seen as &amp;lsquo;unstoppable&amp;rsquo; and offers growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Bristol-Myers Squibb Company (BMY) is a pharmaceutical company known for developing lifesaving drugs. The company&amp;rsquo;s drug repotrectinib has shown durable efficacy benefits in treating patients with specific types of lung cancer. Bristol Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s strong second-quarter earnings beat and revenue beat ratios for the healthcare sector are impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Nu Holdings Ltd. beat earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.05, surpassing the expected $0.04. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid revenue growth and customer expansion could indicate positive prospects. Nu Holdings is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest digital financial services platforms, which could lead to further growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
