<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>job cuts on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/job-cuts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in job cuts on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:03:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/job-cuts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 09:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Nike&amp;rsquo;s track record of winning has made it a dominant industry leader. Risks: The industry leader faces a key risk that investors need to monitor. A planned round of job cuts suggests demand could keep slipping in 2024. Score:-74 chances characters count - risks characters count = -74</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:78
Chances: Comcast&amp;rsquo;s expansion of its broadband network to seven cities shows a commitment to investing in future growth opportunities Partnership with Volkswagen of America to target consumers across NBCU&amp;rsquo;s portfolio indicates potential for increased advertising revenue Investment in Showmax&amp;rsquo;s video streaming platform in partnership with MultiChoice Group demonstrates potential for growth in the streaming market Risks: Competition in the pay-TV market has been intensifying, with Charter overtaking Comcast as the No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: Nio management provided significant insights into the direction of the business. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. (NIO). NIO Inc. (NIO) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
