<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Erdogan on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/erdogan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Erdogan on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:10:35 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/erdogan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&#39;s Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:10:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</guid>
      <description>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Economy
Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has appointed a new finance minister and central bank governor, signaling a shift in economic policy. The new finance minister, Mehmet Simsek, is a former investment banker who has pledged to restore confidence in the Turkish economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Pins NATO Ambitions on Terror Law in Bid to Sway Erdogan</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/sweden-pins-nato-ambitions-on-terror-law-in-bid-to-sway-erdogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/sweden-pins-nato-ambitions-on-terror-law-in-bid-to-sway-erdogan/</guid>
      <description>Sweden has passed a new terror law in an effort to sway Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan to approve the Nordic country&amp;rsquo;s accession to NATO.
The law, which was passed by the Swedish parliament on May 27, defines terrorism as &amp;ldquo;any act that is intended to create a state of terror or fear in a population or in a particular group of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Turkey&#39;s President Faces the Biggest Election Challenge in Years</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Presidential Election: Erdogan Faces His Biggest Challenge in Years
Incumbent Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan faces his biggest challenge in 20 years in Sunday’s runoff election against opposition candidate Kemal Kilicdaroglu. WSJ’s Jared Malsin explains why this is one of the world’s most important votes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
