<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings impact on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-impact/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings impact on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-impact/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Medical Properties Trust beats Q2 FFO estimates, narrows 2023 view. Updates in capital allocation strategy to enhance long-term value creation. Positive impact of potential dividend sustainability. The company&amp;rsquo;s response to recent news articles and reports. Long-term value creation strategy for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Steady dividend payouts with attractive yields. Positive stock performance and returns over the last three years. Strong institutional ownership indicating investor confidence. Q2 earnings beat and positive financial results. Potential growth opportunities with pipeline expansion plans. Risks: Shutdown of compressor station affecting operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: Positive outlook for value investing and dividend payments. Announcement of strategic collaborations and partnerships. Expanding cloud services and hybrid cloud leadership. High institutional ownership indicating favorability among big investors. Positive earnings report and stock performance in recent times. Risks: Volatility in tech stocks and potential market fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
