<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Grab Holdings Limited is the leading GMV-based superapp in Southeast Asia, operating in eight countries and providing access to a wide range of services including food delivery, digital financial services, and more. The company reported positive financial results for Q4 2023, with significant revenue growth, positive profit, and improved adjusted EBITDA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-119
Chances: Shopify (SHOP) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately, indicating a potential positive sentiment towards the stock. Great companies in steadily growing industries can deliver enviable returns through the years, suggesting a positive outlook for Shopify&amp;rsquo;s future growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:-182
Chances: Palantir is expected to rapidly expand earnings per share over several years. The company is taking a visionary leap The path could be wide open for Palantir stock to climb even higher from here on out. Risks: Will generative artificial intelligence boost Palantir stock in the commercial market amid slowing revenue growth for the company?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-66
Chances: AppLovin (APP) has been a big mover in the stock market with higher-than-average trading volume, indicating strong investor interest. The latest trend in earnings estimate revisions might help the stock continue moving higher in the near term, suggesting potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
