<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Alibaba has unveiled new B2B products for small businesses, indicating efforts to expand its offerings. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s move to expand its B2B business in the US suggests growth potential in the American e-commerce market. Individual and institutional investors have profited from Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s recent surge, indicating investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:-50
Chances: Oracle is considered a heavily in-demand stock, indicating strong investor interest. Analysts have predicted &amp;lsquo;solid&amp;rsquo; multiyear growth for Oracle, driven by AI potential. Oracle&amp;rsquo;s AI cloud outlook has prompted upgrades, indicating optimism about its future prospects. Risks: Oracle stock may face a downside correction, which could impact its short-term performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: C3.ai is off to a strong start with significant traction across its business in Q1 2024. Ark Invest predicts that the AI industry will add $200 trillion to the economy by 2030, making AI stocks promising. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s Q1 loss was narrower than expected, and revenues rose year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:-69
Chances: Amazon is leading the market and showing strength in its stock. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s AWS (Amazon Web Services) is gaining new clients like BMW Group, which could boost its revenue. The company&amp;rsquo;s competitive advantage appears to be unstoppable, indicating long-term growth potential. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Shopify could have positive implications for its business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
