<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:76
Chances: UiPath (PATH) concluded the recent trading session at $23.48, signifying a +1.43% move from its prior day&amp;rsquo;s close. Big tech crushed it in 2023; who will provide the next huge gains? The market still has several fantastic stocks that can be purchased at a reasonable price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Shares of ZoomInfo jumped 6.9% after a notable analyst upgrade, indicating positive market sentiment towards the stock. The stock trades at a 50% discount valuation to its software peers, leaving lots of runway for multiple expansion. Risks: The company is considered controversial, which could lead to increased volatility in the stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Investors are jubilant after the Fed’s clear signal that it would begin cutting interest rates in 2024. US stock markets jumped recently as investors cheered the much-awaited Nvidia’s results which showed the chip company enjoying strong sales. Risks: America’s position as a globally dominant force is under threat due to divisive politics and potential US China war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:249
Chances: Gen Digital Inc. has a strong focus on consumer cyber safety through its business solutions, which could be highly beneficial in the current digital landscape The partnership with Dan Levy to raise awareness about cybersecurity through Norton Genie shows a commitment to public education and could positively impact the brand&amp;rsquo;s reputation The release of fiscal 2024 third quarter financial results and hosting a conference call could provide insight into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and future prospects Risks: The potential for lower interest rates creates a general risk for all companies, including Gen Digital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
