<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0950 ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:950
Chances: ZoomInfo executives participating in investor events could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s future plans and growth prospects. TRUSTe GDPR and CCPA Practices Validations, as well as ISO 27001 and 27701 certifications, could enhance ZoomInfo&amp;rsquo;s credibility and attract investor interest. Tech stocks, including ZoomInfo, could present better buying opportunities after the recent selloff following their quarterly reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1168 FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Tim Stone joining Farfetch as Chief Financial Officer may bring new insights and strategies to enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s upcoming second quarter 2023 financial results release may provide valuable information for investors to assess the company&amp;rsquo;s current performance and growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0979 DOCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docn/</guid>
      <description>score:979
Chances: The growth in cloud computing and the demand for cloud services from startups and SMBs could positively impact DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s revenue. DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s strategic acquisitions and strong customer growth may contribute to positive financial performance in the second quarter. Enhanced offerings from DigitalOcean could drive customer adoption and revenue growth in the cloud computing market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1114 GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:1114
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s cloud segment grew 28% annually and posted its first profitable quarter, indicating potential growth opportunities in the cloud services business. The mixed results from Q1, with the advertising segment declining marginally but the cloud segment showing growth, suggest that investors are betting on Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s AI hype, which has contributed to the stock&amp;rsquo;s gain of 44% this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0995 MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:995
Chances: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s strong cloud business is expected to support its growth and revenue generation. Cybersecurity shares often outperform other tech stocks during economic downturns, which could benefit Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity offerings. The overall stock market has staged an extraordinary recovery in 2023, and this positive sentiment could have a favorable impact on Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
