<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:03:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$35.37 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity Shares of ride sharing service Lyft (NASDAQ: LYFT) jumped 5.4% in the afternoon session after major indices rose Risks: Lyft shares more than doubled over the last year, but the stock underperformed when compared with Uber The future of Uber and Lyft in Minneapolis has garnered concern and debate due to new regulations Score:-6 chances characters count - risks characters count = -6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-119
Chances: Shopify (SHOP) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately, indicating a potential positive sentiment towards the stock. Great companies in steadily growing industries can deliver enviable returns through the years, suggesting a positive outlook for Shopify&amp;rsquo;s future growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:-182
Chances: Palantir is expected to rapidly expand earnings per share over several years. The company is taking a visionary leap The path could be wide open for Palantir stock to climb even higher from here on out. Risks: Will generative artificial intelligence boost Palantir stock in the commercial market amid slowing revenue growth for the company?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-66
Chances: AppLovin (APP) has been a big mover in the stock market with higher-than-average trading volume, indicating strong investor interest. The latest trend in earnings estimate revisions might help the stock continue moving higher in the near term, suggesting potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zi/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Shares of ZoomInfo jumped 6.9% after a notable analyst upgrade, indicating positive market sentiment towards the stock. The stock trades at a 50% discount valuation to its software peers, leaving lots of runway for multiple expansion. Risks: The company is considered controversial, which could lead to increased volatility in the stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
