<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DDOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ddog/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Datadog&amp;rsquo;s impressive earnings surprise history and strong positioning in the AI space indicate a potential for future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s upcoming Investor Day and financial results announcements could bring positive updates and investor confidence. Risks: The recent sale of shares by the Chief Technology Officer may raise concerns about insider sentiment and future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docu/</guid>
      <description>score:80
Chances: DocuSign saw a significant share price rise of 65% in the past couple of months on the NASDAQGS. DocuSign is at a pivotal point in its history. DocuSign shows rising price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating from 78 to 89.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:162
Chances: Shares in enterprise software maker Salesforce rose amid an upgrade from Baird, which expects upside for CRM stock from price increases. For the most part, analysts are optimistic about Salesforce’s growth prospects in 2024. Amazon partners with Salesforce to integrate Buy with Prime into the latter&amp;rsquo;s Commerce Cloud platform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
