<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Market on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-market/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Market on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ARM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arm/</guid>
      <description>score:49
Chances: Semiconductor valuations remain expensive even after selloff Nvidia has become the undisputed leader in a stock market powered by AI hopes Shares of Asian chip makers rose after strong earnings from Nvidia Intel unveiled its Intel Foundry services in the AI landscape Smaller players catching the AI wave Risks: Valuations are lofty for the chip maker and other tech giants, signaling a possible bubble Investors may be forgetting basic principles of investing to chase hot AI stocks Fear of missing out in the stock market rally may lead to irrational investment decisions Score:49 chances characters count - risks characters count = 49</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BROS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bros/</guid>
      <description>score:-455
Chances: Up-and-coming drive-thru coffee chain Dutch Bros delivers exactly what younger generations want. Drive-through coffee chain Dutch Bros. (BROS) announced a public offering of its Class A common stock. Dutch Bros stock: The coffee leader is breaking out past a new buy point on the stock market today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: IBM closed positively at $193.34, showing potential for growth in the near future. IBM has been paying close attention to by Zacks.com users, indicating investor interest in the stock. Risks: The company has undergone significant changes and may not be the same as it used to be, posing potential risks for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:225
Chances: In the closing of the recent trading day, Medical Properties (MPW) stood at $4.19, denoting a +0.24% change from the preceding trading day. As Q1 winds to a close and the economy strengthens, it is time to look at three top-performing dividend stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Kenvue Inc. is poised to benefit from the favorable court ruling in a product-liability case, which has resulted in a nearly 5% increase in the company&amp;rsquo;s stock price. The Self Care segment, including cough, cold and allergy, pain care, digestive health, and smoking cessation, presents a strong opportunity for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s shares jumped 7.3% in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s after an investor group made a $5.8 billion offer to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private Risks: The retail industry is facing challenges such as stiff competition from online rivals and high inflation Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -980</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
