<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stock market on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-market/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stock market on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:03:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:220
Chances: VF Corp. (VFC) shares fell over 7% Monday after the owner of the Vans and North Face shoe and apparel brands warned that the company’s business operations were disrupted by a cyberattack. U.S. stocks gained ground on Monday as market participants parsed mounting expectations of interest rate cuts from the Federal Reserve in the coming year and looked ahead to a week of crucial economic data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:81
Chances: Compared to this past year, 2024 is expected to be much better for the economy, and that means it will look even better for the stock market. With interest rates likely to come down in the new year, REITs may become even more attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s shares jumped 7.3% in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s after an investor group made a $5.8 billion offer to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private Risks: The retail industry is facing challenges such as stiff competition from online rivals and high inflation Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -980</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
