<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Market on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-market/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Market on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: HPQ is well-positioned to benefit from the growing demand for personal computing and other access devices. The company&amp;rsquo;s division into HP Inc. and Hewlett Packard Enterprise has allowed for focused growth and strategic acquisitions. Risks: The potential merger of Hewlett Packard Enterprise with Juniper Networks could introduce integration challenges and uncertainties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Kenvue Inc. is poised to benefit from the favorable court ruling in a product-liability case, which has resulted in a nearly 5% increase in the company&amp;rsquo;s stock price. The Self Care segment, including cough, cold and allergy, pain care, digestive health, and smoking cessation, presents a strong opportunity for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s shares jumped 7.3% in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s after an investor group made a $5.8 billion offer to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private Risks: The retail industry is facing challenges such as stiff competition from online rivals and high inflation Score:20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -980</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
