<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: SCHW&amp;rsquo;s inorganic growth efforts are expected to be earnings accretive, potentially benefiting profits. Despite occasional stumbles, shares of SCHW have historically beaten the market over the long haul. Charles Schwab&amp;rsquo;s integration of TD Ameritrade into its business could lead to long-term benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Chevron&amp;rsquo;s share price increased due to an uptick in oil prices, contributing to positive investor sentiment. Analysts have upgraded Chevron&amp;rsquo;s stock and raised price targets, noting its constructive performance within the Oil &amp;amp; Gas sector. Chevron&amp;rsquo;s energy projects play a significant role in supplying a portion of the global LNG market, which could positively impact its earnings potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: DraftKings has entered a significant partnership with Penn Entertainment for sports betting, which could potentially lead to revenue growth. Despite recent stock price declines, DraftKings remains a major player in the sports betting industry, benefiting from the popularity of &amp;lsquo;parlays&amp;rsquo;. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnership with ESPN and its exclusive access to ESPN content through ESPN Bet could bring in new users and competition in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s recent trading sessions show movement and potential opportunities for investors in the artificial intelligence space. The growing interest in AI applications has led to a surge in C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s stock price in 2023, reflecting the potential of the enterprise AI software provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wba/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Walgreens Boots Alliance named Employer of the Year by Disability:IN is a positive recognition for the company. The rollout of in-store vouchers, off-site vaccination clinics, and a combined flu and COVID-19 test reflects Walgreens&amp;rsquo; efforts to offer convenient services. Positive consumer survey results indicating preference for local pharmacies can potentially benefit Walgreens&amp;rsquo; business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: Tech stocks have bounced back in 2023, benefiting AMD&amp;rsquo;s potential growth. AI excitement and improving economic conditions could drive demand for semiconductors. Synopsys&amp;rsquo; CEO discusses chip demand, highlighting the importance of AI and smart devices. Investors may be overlooking AMD&amp;rsquo;s potential in artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Outstanding operational execution and production beat. Positive stock performance with a significant 11% increase. Increase in production guidance for 2023. Projected fair value analysis indicating potential. Retirement of two Executive Officers in the company. Risks: Uncertainty due to conflicting market indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Fortinet is expanding cybersecurity knowledge and skill sets to address the cybersecurity talent shortage. Discussion of best cybersecurity ETFs and potential opportunities in the cloud security sector. Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s top analyst calls, including upgrades and cybersecurity market trends. Focus on improving cybersecurity strategies to address vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:1024
Chances: Highlighting the use of Zacks Earnings ESP to find stocks expected to beat quarterly earnings estimates. Discussing Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report and the key expectations. Announcing the scheduled earnings call and unaudited financial results reporting for Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:1044
Chances: SentinelOne (NYSE: S) is helping counteract the increase in cybersecurity threats with its AI technologies. SentinelLabs announced a premier cybersecurity research conference, LABScon 2023. Cybersecurity investment opportunities are significant due to the rising instances of data breaches. Demand for high-performance cybersecurity services is expected to increase as work processes go digital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Cybersecurity ETFs are discussed as potential investments in the growing cybersecurity market. Palo Alto Networks announced the release of its fiscal fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. Strong potential is identified in Internet software stocks like PANW for the rest of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
