<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stock performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stock performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Positive Q2 and Q1 earnings results announced. Announcement of unaudited financial results and transcripts. Stock upgraded to &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; by MSCI ESG Rating. CEO&amp;rsquo;s holdings reduced by 13%, but still a significant shareholder. Risks: Declining stock performance over the past year. Volatility and fluctuations in stock value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Bullish views on NextEra Energy as a smart bet on green energy and rising payout. Strong performance in renewable energy sector and positive outlook. Better value option compared to competitors. Dividend growth and strong track record of raising payouts. Positive market response to insider activity and strong earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Positive earnings call and financial results for Q2 2023. Potential for Bilibili to beat earnings estimates. Bilibili stock recently breaking out above key moving averages. Recent gains and improved sentiment among institutional owners. Publishing of positive environmental, social, and governance report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Steady dividend payouts with attractive yields. Positive stock performance and returns over the last three years. Strong institutional ownership indicating investor confidence. Q2 earnings beat and positive financial results. Potential growth opportunities with pipeline expansion plans. Risks: Shutdown of compressor station affecting operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Positive earnings performance and beating estimates. Improved technical strength in Marathon Oil stock. Interest from notable investors and billionaires. Potential for dividend payouts. Strong year-over-year stock performance. Risks: Market volatility impacting energy stocks. Potential for declining earnings and financial performance. Fluctuations in oil prices affecting profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: Positive revenue performance and beating estimates. Announcement of significant contracts and awards. Strong year-over-year stock performance. Growth potential in the energy sector rebound. Investor interest and insider buying signals. Risks: Market volatility impacting energy stocks. Potential for declining earnings and financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: TAL Education Group beats earnings expectations for full year 2023. Institutional investors show interest with a significant ownership stake. TAL Education Group files its annual report on Form 20-F. TAL Education Group&amp;rsquo;s strong week for shareholders doesn&amp;rsquo;t alleviate long-term losses. Top-line decline in Q3 attributed to seasonality and forex fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sea Limited reports strong revenue growth despite missing estimates. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and upside according to Wall Street. Investing in Sea five years ago would have delivered a significant gain. TikTok signs payment pact with Atome for Malaysia e-commerce. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s intrinsic value is potentially 50% above its share price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:-58
Chances: ExxonMobil plans to develop sixth oil project in Guyana. ExxonMobil receives award worth $77M against Venezuela. Exxon Mobil Corporation&amp;rsquo;s stock is going strong. Exxon awarded $77 million in claim against Venezuela. ExxonMobil stock sloshed higher today. Risks: Insiders sell $2.4M of Exxon Mobil stock, signaling caution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Peloton announces partnerships with colleges to engage students and athletes. Positive sales performance and surpassing revenue estimates in Q4. Potential for rebound in Peloton stock with improved subscriber outlook. Peloton&amp;rsquo;s initiative to reach a broader audience with fitness apps and partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: VinFast Auto stock surged significantly, jumping over 300% in a week. Positive market reception of VinFast Auto&amp;rsquo;s debut and trading on Nasdaq. VinFast&amp;rsquo;s expansion plans, including opening a Vietnamese plant. Investors show interest in VinFast Auto despite increasing losses. VinFast&amp;rsquo;s successful business combination and debut on Nasdaq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Chevron&amp;rsquo;s share price increased due to an uptick in oil prices, contributing to positive investor sentiment. Analysts have upgraded Chevron&amp;rsquo;s stock and raised price targets, noting its constructive performance within the Oil &amp;amp; Gas sector. Chevron&amp;rsquo;s energy projects play a significant role in supplying a portion of the global LNG market, which could positively impact its earnings potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Outstanding operational execution and production beat. Positive stock performance with a significant 11% increase. Increase in production guidance for 2023. Projected fair value analysis indicating potential. Retirement of two Executive Officers in the company. Risks: Uncertainty due to conflicting market indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Fortinet is expanding cybersecurity knowledge and skill sets to address the cybersecurity talent shortage. Discussion of best cybersecurity ETFs and potential opportunities in the cloud security sector. Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s top analyst calls, including upgrades and cybersecurity market trends. Focus on improving cybersecurity strategies to address vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Cybersecurity ETFs are discussed as potential investments in the growing cybersecurity market. Palo Alto Networks announced the release of its fiscal fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. Strong potential is identified in Internet software stocks like PANW for the rest of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
