<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>stock performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in stock performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Outstanding operational execution and production beat. Positive stock performance with a significant 11% increase. Increase in production guidance for 2023. Projected fair value analysis indicating potential. Retirement of two Executive Officers in the company. Risks: Uncertainty due to conflicting market indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: KeyBank Foundation&amp;rsquo;s charitable donations to support community programs. Positive impact of empowerment programs for youth and young adults. Recognition as a Community Champion by Mile High United Way. Stock price rebound and outperformance in July. Commitment to enhancing banking experience and services for clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Fortinet is expanding cybersecurity knowledge and skill sets to address the cybersecurity talent shortage. Discussion of best cybersecurity ETFs and potential opportunities in the cloud security sector. Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s top analyst calls, including upgrades and cybersecurity market trends. Focus on improving cybersecurity strategies to address vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:892
Chances: Share price movement and percentage change in the latest trading sessions. Discussion about volatility as a risk and focusing on avoiding it. Overview of stock market corrections, bear markets, and the performance of major U.S. stock indexes. Observation on Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s stock performance and its recent run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:1601
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line (NCL) welcomes the first guests aboard the all-new Norwegian Viva, marking an important milestone. Discussing the inclusion of Carnival, Norwegian Cruise Line, and Gentherm in the Zacks Screen of the Week article. Exploring the strong performance of travel stocks due to consumers&amp;rsquo; confidence in travel despite economic concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:1219
Chances: Freeport-McMoRan Inc. (FCX) is investigating a cybersecurity incident affecting its information systems. Reviewing the industry outlook and highlighting Freeport-McMoRan, along with other companies, in the sector. Analyzing the near-term prospects for the Zacks Mining - Non Ferrous industry, considering low metal prices and strong demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:1024
Chances: Highlighting the use of Zacks Earnings ESP to find stocks expected to beat quarterly earnings estimates. Discussing Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report and the key expectations. Announcing the scheduled earnings call and unaudited financial results reporting for Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:1065
Chances: Highlighting high-yield dividend stocks with rapid growth, where UWM Holdings ranks as a leading mortgage lender. Announcing the hiring of Michele Celestino as EVP and Head of Commercial and Private Banking, Southeast at Flagstar Bank, N.A., a subsidiary of NYCB. Announcing the successful completion of Flagstar Bank&amp;rsquo;s MortgageTech Accelerator program by fintech graduates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:618
Chances: Discussing the top 11 stock picks of ARK Invest and mentioning Shopify as one of the key holdings. Highlighting the movement in the options market for Shopify and its significance for investors. Providing insights into Shopify&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value and its potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sirius XM&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results reflect improvement in average revenue per user amid declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which could provide insights into the stock&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend payment announcement and trading at a specific price level could attract investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:129
Chances: Carvana&amp;rsquo;s impressive revival from near bankruptcy has captured attention. Carvana raised its profit outlook, indicating momentum from an early-year turnaround. Positive update on future profits, with expected gross profit per unit and adjusted EBITDA above expectations. An analyst hiked the price target for Carvana&amp;rsquo;s shares due to the optimistic profit outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary Waymo and GM&amp;rsquo;s Cruise received regulatory approval for expanding driverless robotaxi services. GOOG&amp;rsquo;s positive cash flow generation and potential spending opportunities. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s stock still within a buy zone after a recent breakout. Risks: Tech companies cutting spending on the future may impact GOOG&amp;rsquo;s long-term growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-24
Chances: JD.com&amp;rsquo;s stock has had a significant 19% run-up over the last month. Projected fair value for JD.com is $63.64 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. Global AI market growth potentially benefiting AI-driven companies like JD.com. JD.com is a leading supply chain-based technology and service provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:102
Chances: American Airlines&amp;rsquo; efforts to reduce aviation&amp;rsquo;s environmental impact through contrail avoidance, as verified by satellite imagery, could enhance its environmental reputation and sustainability practices. The improvement in American Airlines&amp;rsquo; stock price performance and its IBD Relative Strength Rating upgrade suggest positive market sentiment and potential for further growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-29
Chances: Wayfair&amp;rsquo;s potential gains in sales and profits could indicate a positive trend that might indirectly benefit companies like General Motors. Driverless robotaxi services, including General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise, being granted permission to expand their business could open up new growth opportunities for GM in the autonomous vehicle sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: The popularity of &amp;lsquo;parlays&amp;rsquo; is leading to fatter profits for DraftKings and similar sites, potentially indicating increased revenue. The partnership between DraftKings and ESPN&amp;rsquo;s rebranded sportsbook, ESPN Bet, could provide a new platform for growth and user acquisition. Penn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s $2 billion investment in ESPN Bet and the partnership between ESPN and PENN could have positive implications for DraftKings as the sports betting market evolves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s fiscal third-quarter results were well-received, initially sending shares higher, indicating positive investor sentiment. Efforts to reduce account sharing, following the model of Netflix, could potentially increase Disney&amp;rsquo;s revenue and strengthen its position in the streaming market. The return of the writers union to the bargaining table could lead to positive developments for Disney and other major studios affected by the Hollywood strikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:112
Chances: NIO&amp;rsquo;s stock hitting an all-time high in the past indicates its potential for significant growth during periods of strong deliveries and investor enthusiasm. NIO&amp;rsquo;s achievement of new record-high monthly deliveries showcases its ability to increase vehicle sales, which could positively impact its stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:1126
Chances: Under Armour announced the launch of its &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, aiming to strengthen customer connections and brand loyalty. The company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance customer connections, innovations, and a new loyalty program are expected to contribute to brand growth. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s senior executive leadership team changes are aligned with the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to drive consistent profitable growth and returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:1044
Chances: SentinelOne (NYSE: S) is helping counteract the increase in cybersecurity threats with its AI technologies. SentinelLabs announced a premier cybersecurity research conference, LABScon 2023. Cybersecurity investment opportunities are significant due to the rising instances of data breaches. Demand for high-performance cybersecurity services is expected to increase as work processes go digital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PANW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/panw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/panw/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Cybersecurity ETFs are discussed as potential investments in the growing cybersecurity market. Palo Alto Networks announced the release of its fiscal fourth-quarter and full-year 2023 financial results. Strong potential is identified in Internet software stocks like PANW for the rest of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:1127
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock has reached a new 52-week low, with charts and indicators indicating a weak setup due to a downward trend. Despite market fluctuations, the value of Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock is being assessed, considering its potential amidst challenges. Moderna&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call revealed a miss on earnings expectations, which could impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
