<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fintech on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fintech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fintech on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:03:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fintech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: SoFi stock is growing profits by leaps and bounds, and an $11 price target could be conservative. The fintech has been in rough waters, but analysts are taking a more favorable view of the situation. Analysts think this stock should be worth 30% more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 09:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-50
Chances: Liberty Savings Bank Selects Upstart for Personal Lending There are seven disruptive stocks that should be on every investor’s radar Upstart and Affirm might bounce back This fintech enterprise certainly has huge upside Risks: Investors are losing confidence in this one-time market darling The Fed’s interest rate hikes flushed a lot of losers out of the market Investors need to dig past the performance of the share price Investors should avoid rushing to buy stocks just for their AI pedigree Score:-50 chances characters count - risks characters count = -50</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: When it comes to investing in fintech companies and the financing concept of BNPL — buy now, pay later — Affirm still comes to top of mind. The stock for this buy now, pay later company should be bought and held.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fis/</guid>
      <description>score:299
Chances: Fidelity National Information Services, Inc. (FIS) shareholders should be happy to see the share price up 17%. The latest trading day saw Fidelity National Information Services (FIS) settling at $62.96, representing a -1.08% change from its previous close. FIS and Banked have formed a partnership to create new pay-by-bank solutions by leveraging the power of open banking, APIs and real-time payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
