<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fintech on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fintech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fintech on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:04:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fintech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: SoFi Technologies is diversifying its business operations beyond lending, which could lead to new revenue sources The company&amp;rsquo;s financial results have been impressive, indicating strong potential for growth Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s continued interest in the stock suggests a positive outlook for investors The thriving digital banking sector presents a lucrative opportunity for SoFi Technologies The technology platform segment of the company is poised for growth and increased revenue Risks: Investors may remain cautious about the company&amp;rsquo;s transition away from its core lending business The market&amp;rsquo;s perception of SoFi Technologies as a real, chartered bank may impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s valuation Shorting hot stocks like SoFi Technologies may carry significant risk due to market irrationality The transformation in traditional banking may pose challenges and uncertainties for the company Competition in the fintech and digital banking space could affect SoFi Technologies&amp;rsquo; market position Score:-20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fis/</guid>
      <description>score:299
Chances: Fidelity National Information Services, Inc. (FIS) shareholders should be happy to see the share price up 17%. The latest trading day saw Fidelity National Information Services (FIS) settling at $62.96, representing a -1.08% change from its previous close. FIS and Banked have formed a partnership to create new pay-by-bank solutions by leveraging the power of open banking, APIs and real-time payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
