<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fintech on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fintech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fintech on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fintech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fis/</guid>
      <description>score:299
Chances: Fidelity National Information Services, Inc. (FIS) shareholders should be happy to see the share price up 17%. The latest trading day saw Fidelity National Information Services (FIS) settling at $62.96, representing a -1.08% change from its previous close. FIS and Banked have formed a partnership to create new pay-by-bank solutions by leveraging the power of open banking, APIs and real-time payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: SoFi turned a profit in the fourth quarter for the first time ever, showing solid business momentum Optimism in the air with expectations of the stock market to continue hitting new highs Fintech industry, particularly SoFi, is reshaping traditional practices and disrupting the financial sector Risks: Stock is down 18% this year despite solid performance, indicating potential uncertainty in market perception Possible downbeat outlook for SOFI stock following a widely publicized post-earnings downgrade by a sell-side analyst Uncertainty surrounding interest rate fluctuations and their impact on consumer behavior Score:-20 chances characters count - risks characters count = -20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
