<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fintech on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fintech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fintech on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:05:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fintech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: PayPal has a strong suite of digital payment solutions that cater to both merchants and consumers worldwide. The company&amp;rsquo;s long-term growth potential and commitment to rewarding shareholders make it an attractive investment option. Despite recent stock price fluctuations, PayPal&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach to financial services and its resilience in the face of competition position it for future success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: Shares of Robinhood (HOOD) jumped 7.3% in the afternoon session after major indices rose The company announced plans for a dual listing to increase liquidity of its shares and reach investors in more markets The continued focus on providing retail brokerage, trading in U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:125
Chances: SoFi&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter results showed rapid growth and effective monetization among millennials and Generation Z. The fintech operates through three segments: lending, financial services, and a technology platform. There may still be some uncertainty over interest rates, but high-quality growth stocks should still be considered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fis/</guid>
      <description>score:299
Chances: Fidelity National Information Services, Inc. (FIS) shareholders should be happy to see the share price up 17%. The latest trading day saw Fidelity National Information Services (FIS) settling at $62.96, representing a -1.08% change from its previous close. FIS and Banked have formed a partnership to create new pay-by-bank solutions by leveraging the power of open banking, APIs and real-time payments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: PagSeguro (PAGS) has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months, and belongs to a strong industry as well. Brazil-focused fintechs, including PagSeguro, are thriving amid a strong economy, internet user growth and the unbanked. PagSeguro Digital Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
