<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Transformation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/digital-transformation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Transformation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/digital-transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: Salesforce.com (CRM) has healthy fundamentals and upward estimate revisions. The company&amp;rsquo;s merger synergies with the recent Slack deal will be key for future growth. Rising corporate spending on digital transformation projects has boosted CRM stock. AI advancements have had a major impact on productivity and are expected to benefit companies like Salesforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:520
Chances: STZ excels in its beer segment with sustained growth and strategic financial management. Beverages - Soft Drinks companies like KO, PEP, MNST, KOF and BROS look strong on improved innovation efforts and digital transformation. Coca-Cola Europacific Partners&amp;rsquo; estimated fair value is €112 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: The release of the E100 5G Enterprise Router by Cradlepoint indicates a potential growth opportunity in the enterprise router market, especially for retail and small office applications. ODIDO&amp;rsquo;s selection of Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s billing system for upgrading its infrastructure shows confidence in Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and presents a promising revenue stream.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
