<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Transformation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/digital-transformation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Transformation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/digital-transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IBN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: ICICI Bank Ltd. is well positioned to outperform the market, exhibiting above-average growth in financials. Efforts to bolster fee income, dependence on domestic loans, and digitization of banking services will keep supporting ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s financials. Rise in loan balance, higher net interest income (NII) and non-interest income, and improving credit quality support ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s fiscal Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Salesforce (CRM) has been performing well in the market and has seen a significant increase in stock value in the past year. The company&amp;rsquo;s solutions in sales force automation, customer service, marketing automation, and digital commerce make it well-positioned for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: The release of the E100 5G Enterprise Router by Cradlepoint indicates a potential growth opportunity in the enterprise router market, especially for retail and small office applications. ODIDO&amp;rsquo;s selection of Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s billing system for upgrading its infrastructure shows confidence in Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and presents a promising revenue stream.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
