<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Transformation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/digital-transformation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Transformation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:03:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/digital-transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:-53
Chances: According to average brokerage recommendation, one should consider investing in Salesforce.com (CRM) Rising corporate spending on digital transformation projects has boosted CRM stock Advancements in artificial intelligence have been a major story and could have a positive impact on CRM&amp;rsquo;s future Risks: Debatable effectiveness of average brokerage recommendation as analysts tend to be overly optimistic Merger synergies from the Slack deal will be key, but it also poses integration and execution risks Potential risk in the impact of generative AI on companies like Verizon Communications, which could affect data transmission and network performance Score:-53 chances characters count - risks characters count = -53</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: The release of the E100 5G Enterprise Router by Cradlepoint indicates a potential growth opportunity in the enterprise router market, especially for retail and small office applications. ODIDO&amp;rsquo;s selection of Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s billing system for upgrading its infrastructure shows confidence in Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and presents a promising revenue stream.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
