<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>penny stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/penny-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in penny stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/penny-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Announcement of significant milestone in developing solar-driven cement production technology. Double-digit price hikes and strong peso contributing to a slight rise in second-quarter net profit. Positive growth in revenue, up by 13% in the second quarter. Cemex&amp;rsquo;s focus on scaling technology for solar-driven cement production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Increase in revenues due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Operational and financial results in-line with expectations for Q2 2023. Positive outlook for penny stocks, including BTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:274
Chances: Comparisons of Ambev with other stocks like DEO and CABGY in terms of value could highlight its investment potential. Tracking Ambev&amp;rsquo;s performance compared to Beyond Meat and other stocks within the sector provides insights into its relative strength. Exploring dividend penny stocks and identifying Ambev as a potential candidate for investment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
