<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:-3
Chances: Microsoft Corp. has a strong and dominant position in the tech industry, making it a near-monopoly stock in the US. The company has a proven track record of creating millionaires through its successful business operations and innovation. The potential for future growth and profitability is high given its impressive performance in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Toast received an upgrade from &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; by Goldman Sachs analysts There is optimism about the restaurant software provider&amp;rsquo;s ability to gain market share in 2024 Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies Risks: Etsy stock declined after Goldman Sachs downgraded it from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Charles Schwab shares came under pressure after a downgrade from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Elena Gomez, CFO of Toast Inc, executed a sale of company shares Score:16 chances characters count - risks characters count = 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has a strong platform used by developers, artists, and designers across various industries. The company has a large user base, with over 1.1 million game creators relying on its software toolkit each month. Risks: Unity Software Inc. plans to lay off about 25% of its workforce, which could impact its operational capabilities and future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
