<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: President Joe Biden has spent $23 billion of the $39 billion he has to spur chipmaking in the US, spreading it to companies that plan new activities in several states. Micron Technology Inc has introduced groundbreaking 4150AT SSD, catering to the evolving needs of intelligent vehicles with unparalleled flexibility and power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:211
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) has released the latest version of its operating system, FortiOS 7.6, along with updates to its cybersecurity platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio includes network security, secure access service edge, enterprise networking, security operations, application security, and operational technology, indicating a diverse and comprehensive offering for its customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rum/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Rumble Inc. beats earnings expectations with reported EPS of $-0.14 compared to expectations of $-0.22 Full Year 2023 Revenue Increased 106% to $81.0 Million Achieved Company’s Largest Milestone To-Date with Public Launch of Rumble Cloud The current market’s volatility is ripe for momentum investing Risks: Rumble Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has a strong platform used by developers, artists, and designers across various industries. The company has a large user base, with over 1.1 million game creators relying on its software toolkit each month. Risks: Unity Software Inc. plans to lay off about 25% of its workforce, which could impact its operational capabilities and future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
