<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:53:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Investors are advised to keep an eye on midstream stocks like Kinder Morgan (KMI) amid heightened volatility. Despite industry challenges, Kinder Morgan (KMI), Williams Companies (WMB), MPLX, and Plains (PAGP) are surviving. Kinder Morgan is one of the largest energy transportation and storage companies in North America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:-149
Chances: Transocean expects adjusted contract drilling revenues of $720 million in Q3 2023, which could positively impact its financial performance. Contracts with Eni and BP could provide Transocean with new business opportunities and revenue streams. Positive market conditions and an uptrend in the market could benefit Transocean&amp;rsquo;s performance, especially with a focus on growth stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s recent trading sessions show movement and potential opportunities for investors in the artificial intelligence space. The growing interest in AI applications has led to a surge in C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s stock price in 2023, reflecting the potential of the enterprise AI software provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:-57
Chances: Opendoor Technologies Inc. (OPEN) has attracted attention from investors, indicating potential interest in the stock. The projected fair value for Opendoor Technologies suggests a certain valuation based on free cash flow to equity. While the housing market has faced challenges, Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s role as an e-commerce platform for real estate transactions is noteworthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: AMC Entertainment, once a hot meme stock, is facing challenges due to a stock conversion plan and dilution concerns. The court&amp;rsquo;s approval of the settlement for converting preferred equity units into common shares is expected to strengthen AMC&amp;rsquo;s finances. AMC&amp;rsquo;s resilience in overcoming opposition from meme investors and winning court approval indicates its determination to navigate challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: Improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. Cooperating with an investigation into &amp;lsquo;brokerage execution quality&amp;rsquo;. Retail crypto trading volumes potentially shifting to Robinhood. Defeating an appeal by investors over restricting purchases of &amp;lsquo;meme stocks&amp;rsquo;. Risks: Regulatory and legal proceedings faced by the online brokerage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:178
Chances: Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, which could drive the stock higher in the near term. Stocks like GGB are attracting investor attention due to their higher dividend yields compared to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
