<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: Improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. Cooperating with an investigation into &amp;lsquo;brokerage execution quality&amp;rsquo;. Retail crypto trading volumes potentially shifting to Robinhood. Defeating an appeal by investors over restricting purchases of &amp;lsquo;meme stocks&amp;rsquo;. Risks: Regulatory and legal proceedings faced by the online brokerage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:178
Chances: Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects, which could drive the stock higher in the near term. Stocks like GGB are attracting investor attention due to their higher dividend yields compared to the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: U.S. Bancorp&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown a significant 39% increase in the last quarter, which could attract investor attention. Some S&amp;amp;P 500 constituents, including U.S. Bancorp, have experienced double-digit gains, indicating potential positive sentiment. Eli Lilly&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings and guidance, along with Moody&amp;rsquo;s consideration of credit ratings, might impact U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: AMC successfully secured court approval for a stock conversion plan, allowing the company to raise capital. The company&amp;rsquo;s marketing efforts are being led by experienced professionals, potentially driving positive brand awareness. AMC reported second-quarter results that beat analyst estimates on both revenue and earnings, with an explosive start to the third quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:1168
Chances: Roku reported strong Q2 results, exceeding Wall Street estimates. Roku&amp;rsquo;s stock price rose 50.5% in July due to impressive business performance. Positive outlook for Roku as a growth stock to consider buying. Potential for significant returns for Roku shareholders based on market share and opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
