<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Cisco Systems Inc has been emphasizing sustainability and reducing their environmental footprint, demonstrating a long-standing commitment to a responsible approach to business. The company recently announced a dividend of $0.39 per share, with a strong dividend performance, yield, and growth rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: The merger between DISH Network and EchoStar Corp. is a strategic move that could lead to potential growth and synergies The reuniting of Charlie Ergen&amp;rsquo;s satellite empire may create opportunities for cost savings and increased market competitiveness With EchoStar replacing DISH Network in the S&amp;amp;P SmallCap 600, there&amp;rsquo;s potential for increased visibility and investor interest Risks: There may be challenges in integrating the operations and cultures of DISH Network and EchoStar Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:124
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corp. is focused on sustainability and affordable energy for customers, which could drive long-term growth The company is exploring emerging technologies such as unmanned aerial systems for utility operations, showing a commitment to innovation The biggest US convertible bond issue in nearly two years confirms the comeback of convertible bonds as a cost-effective debt option for companies Risks: The energy sector has been going through significant volatility over the past few years, which could impact PG&amp;amp;E Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
