<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BROS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bros/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Dutch Bros raises guidance as profit doubles, indicating strong financial performance. The company is focused on new markets and expansion, which may lead to growth opportunities. Dutch Bros reports second-quarter 2023 financial results, reflecting positive performance. The company has caught the attention of institutional investors with a sizeable 35% stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</guid>
      <description>score:25
Chances: VinFast Auto gained significant attention and experienced a massive rally in August, indicating investor interest in the company&amp;rsquo;s potential. The Vietnamese EV maker, VinFast, has made its U.S. debut, signaling its expansion into international markets, which could offer growth opportunities. VinFast&amp;rsquo;s successful business combination with Black Spade Acquisition Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/umc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/umc/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Positive Q2 2023 results reported. Announcement of 40nm RFSOI platform for 5G mmWave applications. Collaboration with Cadence on 3D-IC Hybrid Bonding Reference Flow. Leadership in semiconductor foundries as per Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. Partnership extension with Infineon for 40nm eNVM Microcontroller Production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Expected to beat earnings estimates and move higher. Positive earnings call transcripts and potential value. Potential for strong rally and upside potential. Highlighted by analysts as a potential value stock. Positive financial results and profit beating forecasts. Risks: Stock price volatility and potential declines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Strong contender in the media industry with good outperformance potential. Positive Q2 earnings match and potential growth. Dividend declaration and positive financial results. Recent stock price surge and analyst upgrades. Participation in important industry conferences. Risks: Stock price volatility and short-squeeze focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings beat on lower operating costs. Positive investor sentiment with notable returns in the past three years. Expectations of beating earnings estimates for upcoming quarters. Several instances of beating revenue and earnings estimates. Potential undervaluation of Southwestern Energy Company (SWN) based on analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:54
Chances: Improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. Cooperating with an investigation into &amp;lsquo;brokerage execution quality&amp;rsquo;. Retail crypto trading volumes potentially shifting to Robinhood. Defeating an appeal by investors over restricting purchases of &amp;lsquo;meme stocks&amp;rsquo;. Risks: Regulatory and legal proceedings faced by the online brokerage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
