<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:04:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ARDX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: Ardelyx (ARDX) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), indicating growing optimism about its earnings prospects. The biotech market is projected to experience robust growth from 2024 to 2030, with an expanding clinical trial pipeline and strong regulatory support for startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/owl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/owl/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Blue Owl Capital Inc. and Blue Owl Capital Corporation are both scheduled to release their financial results for the fourth quarter, providing potential opportunities for investors to assess the performance of these companies. Risks: The volatility of the stock market and potential fluctuations in the financial performance of Blue Owl Capital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:-55
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s product pipeline includes a wide range of modalities, such as prophylactic vaccines, cancer vaccines, and localized regenerative therapeutics, providing opportunities for significant future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on intratumoral immuno-oncology and systemic intracellular therapeutics reflects a strong commitment to addressing complex medical challenges with innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
