<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Energy Sector on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Energy Sector on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: ConocoPhillips Proves Why A Gap Down In Price Is Not Always Bad ConocoPhillips expands full year production guidance with company-wide records ConocoPhillips (NYSE:COP) Looks Like A Good Stock, And It&amp;rsquo;s Going Ex-Dividend Soon Risks: ConocoPhillips Misses Earnings Expectations Despite Record Production ConocoPhillips misses on profit, hikes full-year output forecast ConocoPhillips (COP) Lags on Q2 Earnings, Ups &amp;lsquo;23 Output View Score:29 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Devon Energy (DVN): A Comprehensive Analysis of Its Market Value Prediction: These 2 Stocks Could Skyrocket in the Next Bull Market 16 Growing Dividend Stocks with Low PE Ratios 3 Crucial Catalysts Could Push Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s Dividend a Lot Higher in 2024 Devon Energy Is Becoming a Super Bargain Risks: Why Did Devon Energy Cut Its Dividend Again?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Permian Resources announces acquisition of Earthstone Energy, creating a premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P. Positive announcements of quarterly cash dividends and portfolio optimization transactions. Improvement in 2023 guidance and potential for growth in the energy sector. Senior leadership changes and improved performance indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BKR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: UBS analysts raised price targets on Baker Hughes, indicating positive sentiment towards the company&amp;rsquo;s stock. Baker Hughes&amp;rsquo; estimated fair value is provided based on Free Cash Flow to Equity analysis. The analysis includes Baker Hughes in discussions about energy sector investment themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: U.S. Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s removal of obstacles for completing the Mountain Valley Pipeline project. Expected completion of the Mountain Valley Pipeline project by the end of 2023. Positive Q2 2023 financial results with earnings and revenue surprises. Ratification of federal approvals for the pipeline project by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
