<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Energy Sector on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Energy Sector on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:58:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:1269
Chances: Formation of strategic partnership between WaterBridge NDB and Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary, yielding the largest private water infrastructure. Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend reduction due to weaker oil and gas prices. Discussion on investing in the energy sector for income stocks. Analysis of Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s dividend cut and its impact on passive income investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:929
Chances: Exxon Mobil is part of the Zacks top Analyst Blog, indicating positive sentiment. Oil prices experienced a winning streak aided by Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s production cuts. Insiders within Exxon Mobil have been actively buying company shares. Risks: Exxon Mobil&amp;rsquo;s shale assets in Argentina are under review, potentially impacting its future investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Energy Transfer reports strong performance in operations with record volumes, including NGL exports. Ares Capital offers a high dividend yield of nearly 9.7%, attracting investors seeking income. Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s expanded operations in the Permian Basin and strong export volumes likely benefit Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:1078
Chances: Transocean&amp;rsquo;s securing of a significant ultra-deepwater drillship contract worth $518 million reflects its ability to strengthen its market position. Total contract drilling revenues of $729 million, compared to $649 million in the first quarter of 2023, indicate a revenue increase and potentially positive business performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
