<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Energy Sector on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Energy Sector on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BKR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: UBS analysts raised price targets on Baker Hughes, indicating positive sentiment towards the company&amp;rsquo;s stock. Baker Hughes&amp;rsquo; estimated fair value is provided based on Free Cash Flow to Equity analysis. The analysis includes Baker Hughes in discussions about energy sector investment themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Investors are advised to keep an eye on midstream stocks like Kinder Morgan (KMI) amid heightened volatility. Despite industry challenges, Kinder Morgan (KMI), Williams Companies (WMB), MPLX, and Plains (PAGP) are surviving. Kinder Morgan is one of the largest energy transportation and storage companies in North America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:185
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s declining total operating costs and expenses in Q2 have positively impacted its earnings, indicating potential cost management and efficiency improvements. The company&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023 could indicate a potential favorable direction for the stock, suggesting strong operational performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: U.S. Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s removal of obstacles for completing the Mountain Valley Pipeline project. Expected completion of the Mountain Valley Pipeline project by the end of 2023. Positive Q2 2023 financial results with earnings and revenue surprises. Ratification of federal approvals for the pipeline project by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
