<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Energy Sector on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Energy Sector on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:34:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/energy-sector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Valero Energy Corp has experienced a surprising 27% stock rally, indicating a positive momentum in the stock. Valero Energy is considered a fairly valued powerhouse in the oil &amp;amp; gas industry with strong financial prospects. The company recently reported Q2 earnings that beat estimates, showcasing its resilience in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EQT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: EQT Corporation recently completed the acquisition of Tug Hill and XcL Midstream, which could potentially enhance its operational capabilities and revenue streams. The company&amp;rsquo;s acquisition received approval from the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC), allowing it to proceed without regulatory hurdles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Permian Resources announced a $500.0 million private placement of senior notes due in 2032, indicating its ability to raise capital. The company is set to acquire Earthstone Energy in an all-stock transaction, creating a $14 billion premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P, which may lead to growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:42:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cve/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: Cenovus Energy has delivered a solid 57% CAGR over the past 3 years, indicating positive performance for shareholders. The company beat quarterly profit estimates, with shares climbing as a result, suggesting strong financial performance. Cenovus Energy&amp;rsquo;s fundamentals appear strong, indicating potential growth opportunities in the energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Marathon Oil&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings beat expectations, driven by higher domestic output, indicating positive performance. Billionaires are showing confidence in Marathon Oil, with notable investments, which might attract other investors. Marathon Oil has gained 287% over the past three years, showcasing strong long-term growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: ConocoPhillips Proves Why A Gap Down In Price Is Not Always Bad ConocoPhillips expands full year production guidance with company-wide records ConocoPhillips (NYSE:COP) Looks Like A Good Stock, And It&amp;rsquo;s Going Ex-Dividend Soon Risks: ConocoPhillips Misses Earnings Expectations Despite Record Production ConocoPhillips misses on profit, hikes full-year output forecast ConocoPhillips (COP) Lags on Q2 Earnings, Ups &amp;lsquo;23 Output View Score:29 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: U.S. Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s removal of obstacles for completing the Mountain Valley Pipeline project. Expected completion of the Mountain Valley Pipeline project by the end of 2023. Positive Q2 2023 financial results with earnings and revenue surprises. Ratification of federal approvals for the pipeline project by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
