<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Semiconductor Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Semiconductor Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) expected to approve construction of a €10 billion facility in Dresden, Germany. TSMC&amp;rsquo;s leading position as the world&amp;rsquo;s top contract chip manufacturer makes it an intriguing investment. Growing trend of artificial intelligence (AI) and TSMC&amp;rsquo;s involvement in chip production for AI applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s support for new iPhone models suggests improved chip volumes for the current quarter. Positive results from tech giants&amp;rsquo; quarterly reports despite some being muted. Formation of a new company by chipmakers, including Qualcomm, to develop RISC-V technology. Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s daily gain and EPS performance raise questions about its valuation and potential for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:946
Chances: Intel Corporation&amp;rsquo;s decision to open an innovation hub in China to support local technology startups indicates a commitment to growth and innovation despite geopolitical tensions. Shares of Intel have experienced a 35% gain this year, recovering from previous losses and demonstrating positive momentum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:880
Chances: Advanced Micro Devices&amp;rsquo; (AMD) MI300 AI chip set is gaining attention and seen as a potential competitor to Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s AI hardware. AI-driven investment has positively impacted Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s stock and could have a similar effect on AMD&amp;rsquo;s stock. Long-term investing in strong businesses like AMD can be life-changing and rewarding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
