<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Semiconductor Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Semiconductor Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:08:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:154
Chances: TSMC&amp;rsquo;s stock has reached its highest-ever level, tracking a global rally in chip stocks fueled by optimism about artificial intelligence. The U.S. is considering the need for a &amp;lsquo;CHIPS Act 2.0&amp;rsquo; to bolster its semiconductor industry further and compete with global leaders like China and Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arm/</guid>
      <description>score:162
Chances: Nvidia has become the undisputed leader in a stock market powered by AI hopes, indicating a strong potential for growth and profitability. Shares of Asian chip makers rose after strong earnings from Nvidia, reflecting the positive impact of AI technology on the semiconductor industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WOLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 09:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wolf/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Wolfspeed is the global leader in silicon carbide technology, which is a promising and rapidly growing sector in the semiconductor industry. The expansion and extension of long-term wafer supply agreements with leading semiconductor companies indicate strong demand for Wolfspeed&amp;rsquo;s products and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMAT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amat/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: The semiconductor industry is booming, and Applied Materials is well-positioned to benefit from this growth.The company is undervalued on a DCF basis and has a predictable business.State-of-the-art toolset will bridge academic innovations and industry pathways to scale for semiconductors, microelectronics and other critical technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
