<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Semiconductor Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Semiconductor Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:06:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:115
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSM) is a leading player in the AI revolution, positioning it for growth. TSMC&amp;rsquo;s August sales indicate a promising start, boosting market confidence. TSMC may decide to invest in Arm IPO, signaling strategic opportunities for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Micron Technology (MU) has been considered one of the best stocks to invest in according to AI algorithms. The company has shown rising performance and an RS rating of 84, indicating its strength in the market. Micron launched a Memory Expansion Module Portfolio to accelerate CXL 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Qualcomm (QCOM) has partnerships with BMW and Mercedes to supply chips for displays and voice features, driving innovation. The company is considered a market leader in the semiconductor industry and has reported positive returns on capital. Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s involvement in 5G technology positions it as one of the top 5G stocks to consider for investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) could benefit from a bullish trendline that might drive its stock price closer to record highs. The auto and industrial chip sector&amp;rsquo;s potential for accelerating growth and profit expansion in the coming year could positively impact ON Semiconductor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
