<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interest rates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interest rates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FNMA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fnma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fnma/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Fannie Mae&amp;rsquo;s February 2024 Monthly Summary report indicates positive year-to-date activities for its gross mortgage portfolio and interest rate risk measures. The company&amp;rsquo;s recognition by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency for its energy-efficiency contributions further highlights its positive impact on the housing sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/colb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 09:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/colb/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Regional bank stocks showed a positive trend in late 2023 in anticipation of interest rate cuts, which could potentially have a positive impact on Columbia Banking System&amp;rsquo;s stock price. The company&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, Clint Stein, is scheduled to present at two high-profile investor conferences, indicating potential positive news or announcements in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: First Horizon (FHN) delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended December 2023, indicating potential positive performance. The price-to-sales ratio suggests that stocks like FHN hold promise, especially for early development cycle investments. Upgrades to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) reflect growing optimism about First Horizon (FHN) earnings prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:437
Chances: Solar power stocks received a boost from Jefferies, which initiated coverage on some of the biggest companies in the sector. Falling interest rates have fueled Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; stock this week. The projected fair value for Array Technologies is US$36.63 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity&amp;hellip; Jessica Lawrence-Vaca, Senior Vice President, Policy and External Affairs, Array Technologies ALBUQUERQUE, N.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
