<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interest rates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interest rates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:09:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-139
Chances: Realty Income Corporation is known for generating dependable monthly cash dividends from a consistent cash flow from operations. Risks: The US housing market is experiencing a turn as affordability is dampening demand, potentially impacting Real Estate companies like Realty Income. Higher e-commerce adoption and high interest rates are worrisome for companies like Realty Income and Simon Property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:437
Chances: Solar power stocks received a boost from Jefferies, which initiated coverage on some of the biggest companies in the sector. Falling interest rates have fueled Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; stock this week. The projected fair value for Array Technologies is US$36.63 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity&amp;hellip; Jessica Lawrence-Vaca, Senior Vice President, Policy and External Affairs, Array Technologies ALBUQUERQUE, N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Recent revenue results and global market trends help solidify Roku as a strong investment opportunity. Several stocks soared in November on increasing signs that the Federal Reserve could be done raising interest rates as well as rising speculation that rates could even start coming down in the first half of 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
