<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interest rates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in interest rates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:02:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:123
Chances: Newmont Corporation is well-positioned to benefit from the recent surge in gold prices, with the company&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in North America and South America The company&amp;rsquo;s diversified portfolio of gold properties, along with other metals such as copper, silver, lead, and zinc, provides a hedge against volatility in the commodity markets Expectations of multiple rate cuts and expansionary policies bode well for Newmont&amp;rsquo;s future prospects Risks: Volatility in gold and other metal prices could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s revenue and profitability Operational challenges in mining and exploration activities pose a risk to Newmont&amp;rsquo;s production levels Geopolitical factors and regulatory changes in the regions where Newmont operates could affect the company&amp;rsquo;s operations Score:123 chances characters count - risks characters count = 123</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:81
Chances: Compared to this past year, 2024 is expected to be much better for the economy, and that means it will look even better for the stock market. With interest rates likely to come down in the new year, REITs may become even more attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arry/</guid>
      <description>score:437
Chances: Solar power stocks received a boost from Jefferies, which initiated coverage on some of the biggest companies in the sector. Falling interest rates have fueled Array Technologies&amp;rsquo; stock this week. The projected fair value for Array Technologies is US$36.63 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity&amp;hellip; Jessica Lawrence-Vaca, Senior Vice President, Policy and External Affairs, Array Technologies ALBUQUERQUE, N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Recent revenue results and global market trends help solidify Roku as a strong investment opportunity. Several stocks soared in November on increasing signs that the Federal Reserve could be done raising interest rates as well as rising speculation that rates could even start coming down in the first half of 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
