<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interest rates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in interest rates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rates Latest: Get Ready for Pause and Assess Effect of Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-get-ready-for-pause-and-assess-effect-of-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-get-ready-for-pause-and-assess-effect-of-hikes/</guid>
      <description>Fed to Hike Rates by 0.75%, Pause After July
The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates by 0.75% at its meeting on Wednesday, July 13. This would be the largest rate hike since 1994. The Fed is raising rates in an effort to combat inflation, which is at a 40-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNB&#39;s Jordan Puts Switzerland&#39;s Neutral Interest Rate Around 2%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/snbs-jordan-puts-switzerlands-neutral-interest-rate-around-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/snbs-jordan-puts-switzerlands-neutral-interest-rate-around-2/</guid>
      <description>SNB&amp;rsquo;s Jordan Puts Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s Neutral Interest Rate Around 2% The Swiss National Bank (SNB) has kept its benchmark interest rate at -0.75%, but President Thomas Jordan said that the neutral interest rate for Switzerland is around 2%. This suggests that the SNB is ready to raise interest rates in the near future, as inflation in Switzerland is running at its highest level in years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Readings on the Inflation, Interest Rates Coming Next Week</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fresh-readings-on-the-inflation-interest-rates-coming-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:34:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fresh-readings-on-the-inflation-interest-rates-coming-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Fresh Readings on Inflation and Interest Rates Coming Next Week The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) will release its latest Consumer Price Index (CPI) report on Wednesday, June 15. The CPI is a measure of inflation, and it is closely watched by investors and policymakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banxico to Hold Key Rate for &#39;as Long as Possible&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-hold-key-rate-for-as-long-as-possible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:34:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-hold-key-rate-for-as-long-as-possible/</guid>
      <description>Banxico to Hold Key Rate for &amp;lsquo;as Long as Possible&amp;rsquo; The Bank of Mexico (Banxico) will hold its key interest rate at 11.25% for &amp;ldquo;as long as possible,&amp;rdquo; according to Jonathan Heath, a member of the bank&amp;rsquo;s board.
Heath said that the bank is still concerned about the high level of inflation in Mexico, which is running at an annual rate of 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serbia Surprises With Rate Hike After Hitting Pause Last Month</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/serbia-surprises-with-rate-hike-after-hitting-pause-last-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:00:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/serbia-surprises-with-rate-hike-after-hitting-pause-last-month/</guid>
      <description>Serbia Surprises With Rate Hike After Hitting Pause Last Month Serbia&amp;rsquo;s central bank raised its benchmark interest rate by 0.5 percentage points to 3.9 percent on Wednesday, surprising analysts who had expected the bank to hold rates steady.
The hike was the first since December and comes as Serbia grapples with rising inflation, which hit a 10-year high of 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK House Prices Post First Annual Drop Since 2012, Halifax Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-post-first-annual-drop-since-2012-halifax-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-post-first-annual-drop-since-2012-halifax-says/</guid>
      <description>UK House Prices Fall for First Time in a Decade House prices in the UK fell by 0.3% in May, marking the first annual drop since 2012. The fall in house prices was driven by a slowdown in the market, as buyers became more cautious in the face of rising interest rates and the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bond Bulls Bet Fed Is Right in Anticipating Low Rates to Return</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</guid>
      <description>Bond Investors Bet on Lower Interest Rates Bond investors are betting that the Federal Reserve will be unable to sustain its current rate-hike cycle and that interest rates will eventually return to low levels. This is a reversal of the trend that has been in place for the past decade, during which the Fed has steadily raised rates in an effort to combat inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOE Considers Ending Corporate Bond Sales Program</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/boe-considers-ending-corporate-bond-sales-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:55:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/boe-considers-ending-corporate-bond-sales-program/</guid>
      <description>BOE Considers Ending Corporate Bond Sales Program The Bank of England (BOE) is considering ending its active corporate bond sales program as soon as next month. The program was launched in 2020 to help businesses finance their operations during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Visco Says He Would Have Preferred More Gradual Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:52:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Visco Prefers Gradual Approach to Rate Hikes European Central Bank (ECB) Governing Council member Ignazio Visco said on Tuesday that he would have preferred a more gradual approach to raising interest rates.
The ECB has raised interest rates by 375 basis points since December, and two more quarter-point moves are expected this month and next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Weekend Reading: With Debt Debacle Done, It&#39;s Back to Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Inflation: The Fed&amp;rsquo;s Tough Balancing Act The Federal Reserve has signaled that it will begin to raise interest rates in March, which is likely to lead to higher borrowing costs for businesses and consumers. Inflation is still running at a high level, and there is a risk that it could get worse if the Fed raises rates too quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:11:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</guid>
      <description>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time Mexico&amp;rsquo;s central bank, Banxico, has signaled that it will keep interest rates high for a long period of time in order to tame inflation.
The bank&amp;rsquo;s decision comes as inflation in Mexico has reached a 20-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Says Core Price Trend Was &#39;Broadly Seen as Worrisome&#39; in May</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:57:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</guid>
      <description>ECB Concerned About Inflation The European Central Bank (ECB) is concerned about the path of inflation, according to the minutes of its May policy meeting. Core inflation, which excludes food and energy, rose to 3.8% in May from 3.5% in April. This was the highest level since December 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Things You Need to Know to Start Your Day</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/five-things-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:30:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/five-things-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-day/</guid>
      <description>Five Things to Know to Start Your Day The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates by 0.50% today. The stock market is expected to open lower today. Oil prices are rising today. The yield on the 10-year Treasury note is rising today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:43:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked European Central Bank (ECB) President Christine Lagarde said on Thursday that there is no clear evidence that underlying inflation has peaked.
Core inflation, which excludes food and energy prices, rose to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Mortgage Lending Unexpectedly Falls After Interest Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-mortgage-lending-unexpectedly-falls-after-interest-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:46:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-mortgage-lending-unexpectedly-falls-after-interest-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>UK Mortgage Lending Falls Unexpectedly After Interest Rate Hikes Mortgage lending in the UK fell unexpectedly in April, after the Bank of England raised interest rates for the fifth time in a row.
Lenders authorized 48,700 home loans in April, down sharply from the 51,500 approved in March.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
