<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interest Rates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interest Rates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:00:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FITB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fitb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fitb/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: Fifth Third Bancorp reported strong second-quarter 2023 earnings, beating estimates, and showcasing potential for growth. Organic growth is supporting Fifth Third (FITB) despite high costs, indicating resilience in a challenging environment. The bank is opening eight new branches in strategic locations, which could expand its customer base and revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyg/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: Lloyds Banking Group (LYG) has reported an increase in profits, beating forecasts, as lenders anticipate a Bank of England rate hike. UK business confidence is at an 18-month high despite inflation and a cost of living crisis, which could positively impact Lloyds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xp/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: XP Inc. reports positive earnings growth, indicating its potential for profitability and growth. The company announces the termination of a shareholders agreement, which might lead to strategic changes. Despite recent market cap fluctuations, institutional investors have benefited from long-term gains in XP Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Bank of America is favored by institutional owners, with 58% ownership, indicating investor confidence. Higher interest rates have historically benefited Bank of America, which could lead to improved profitability. Bank of America is expanding its credit card cashback rewards, which may attract more customers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
