<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interest rates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in interest rates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/interest-rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:-115
Chances: Huntington Bancshares Incorporated&amp;rsquo;s investors are due to receive a dividend payment per share, which could attract investors looking for income. Huntington Bancshares beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit, earning more from rising interest rates and experiencing strong demand for commercial loans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Higher rates and expectations of reduced delinquency rates in Brazil&amp;rsquo;s banking industry could benefit Itaú Unibanco (ITUB). Growth in commissions, fees, insurance operations, and strategic acquisitions support Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s financials. Revised projections for 2023 and dividend payments indicate management&amp;rsquo;s commitment to shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Medical Properties Trust is a real estate investment trust (REIT) that specializes in hospital properties. Favorable healthcare industry trends and capital recycling efforts could positively impact Medical Properties Trust&amp;rsquo;s earnings. Quarterly dividend payments of $0.29 per share demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to rewarding shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Regions Bank introduces digital solutions for business clients to manage billing and communications. Appointment of Alison Rand to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Bank increases prime lending rate to 8.50%. Enhancement of Treasury Management suite of products and services to meet customer needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
