<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:-118
Chances: The company&amp;rsquo;s diverse segments, including natural gas transportation, midstream, NGL and refined products transportation, and crude oil transportation, provide opportunities for growth and revenue. Securing contracts worth approximately $200 million by Oceaneering&amp;rsquo;s Manufactured Products segment and the acquisition deals for Utica and Northern Delaware Basin assets by Northern positions the company for future success and expansion in major U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:55
Chances: The new law regarding the gig economy from the Biden administration may lead to increased employee classification for gig economy workers, potentially improving their rights and protections. DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s exclusive early release of the new Golden Carolina BBQ Tenders as part of their partnership with Cracker Barrel Old Country Store may attract more customers and drive sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hims/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Hims &amp;amp; Hers Health, Inc. unveiled Weight Loss by Hims &amp;amp; Hers, a comprehensive and customizable clinical approach specifically designed to help people achieve their individual weight-loss goals. The company has appointed Craig Primack, a pioneer in the field of clinical obesity medicine, as SVP of Weight Management, indicating a strong focus on addressing the growing issue of obesity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
