<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>regulation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in regulation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: EQT&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Equitrans Midstream for $5.5 billion unveils the CEO&amp;rsquo;s vision for AI-driven growth. Equitrans is the majority owner of a pipeline situated in one of the fastest growing AI data center hubs. The company&amp;rsquo;s water segment includes water pipelines, impoundment facilities, and pumping stations, which could signify stability and growth potential in the water infrastructure sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Snap Inc. is responding to concerns about its Snapchat feature causing teen anxiety by making adjustments to the Solar System ranking system. The company is piloting new features with large global agencies, indicating a focus on innovation and expansion. The rise of artificial intelligence presents a significant opportunity for social media companies like Snap to drive growth and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hims/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Hims &amp;amp; Hers Health, Inc. unveiled Weight Loss by Hims &amp;amp; Hers, a comprehensive and customizable clinical approach specifically designed to help people achieve their individual weight-loss goals. The company has appointed Craig Primack, a pioneer in the field of clinical obesity medicine, as SVP of Weight Management, indicating a strong focus on addressing the growing issue of obesity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
