<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Coinbase is outpacing stock market gains, indicating strong performance in the crypto industry. The company is expanding its services and targeting regulatory clarity for international expansion. Coinbase-backed insurance alternative OpenCover debuts on Layer 2 blockchain Base, showing innovation. Coinbase announces interim results and extension and upsizing of cash tender offer for its outstanding senior notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Alphabet is a leader in the tech industry with strong growth potential. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Invest has shown interest in unique AI growth stocks, which could benefit Alphabet. Google&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sundar Pichai, believes that AI could be a significant market, suggesting potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Pfizer Inc. (PFE) is a trending stock, indicating strong market interest. Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s COVID-era growth may influence investment decisions. Pfizer and BioNTech receive positive CHMP opinion for Omicron XBB.1.5-adapted COVID-19 vaccine in the European Union, indicating potential market expansion. Risks: Big Pharma&amp;rsquo;s battle with the Biden administration could have long-lasting consequences, posing regulatory risks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
