<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gaming on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gaming on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:-24
Chances: Las Vegas Sands&amp;rsquo; fourth-quarter 2023 results are likely to benefit from improved visitation in Macao and Singapore. The revenue and EPS for Las Vegas Sands give a sense of how its business performed in the quarter ended December 2023. Las Vegas Sands&amp;rsquo; expected performance for the quarter ended December 2023 is likely to exceed conventional Wall Street top-and-bottom-line estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Baillie Gifford&amp;rsquo;s increased investment in Sea Ltd indicates confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects. Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock has seen positive movement in the recent trading sessions. The growth-fueled Nasdaq Composite presents potential opportunities for Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock. Risks: Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock price has fallen 16% in the last quarter, signaling potential challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has a strong platform used by developers, artists, and designers across various industries. The company has a large user base, with over 1.1 million game creators relying on its software toolkit each month. Risks: Unity Software Inc. plans to lay off about 25% of its workforce, which could impact its operational capabilities and future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
