<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>natural gas on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/natural-gas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in natural gas on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:06:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/natural-gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s strong cash flow despite lower commodity prices suggests resilience in the face of market fluctuations The longer-term bull case for natural gas, including expanding U.S. exports, bodes well for Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s future prospects Institutional ownership implies the stock price sensitivity, indicating potential for significant movements in response to market conditions Risks: The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price is sensitive to broader macroeconomic environment, which could lead to fluctuations in value Higher oil production and reduction in marketing purchases may not be sustainable over the long term The company&amp;rsquo;s performance is closely tied to the supply and demand dynamics in the natural gas and oil market, which can be unpredictable Score:39 chances characters count - risks characters count = 39</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corporation Foundation offering STEM scholarships to support education and future talent in Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) disciplines. Risks: Inflation and higher natural gas prices are impacting utility investors and may lead to increased costs for customers. Score:40 chances characters count - risks characters count = 40</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
