<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Natural Gas on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/natural-gas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Natural Gas on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:02:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/natural-gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:-44
Chances: EQT&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Equitrans Midstream for $5.5 billion reveals the CEO&amp;rsquo;s vision for AI-driven growth, indicating potential for technological advancement and expansion in the natural gas sector. Equitrans is the majority owner of a pipeline situated in one of the fastest growing AI data center hubs, suggesting opportunities for strategic growth and increased demand for data center services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EQT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</guid>
      <description>score:-71
Chances: The 2024 outlook for E&amp;amp;Ps largely surprises to the upside with conservative budgets and steady volumes. Energy stocks, particularly those focused on natural gas, look particularly interesting at the moment as prices are expected to recover. Risks: The burgeoning power demands of artificial intelligence applications are reshaping the energy landscape, presenting both challenges and opportunities for the natural gas industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corporation Foundation offering STEM scholarships to support education and future talent in Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) disciplines. Risks: Inflation and higher natural gas prices are impacting utility investors and may lead to increased costs for customers. Score:40 chances characters count - risks characters count = 40</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
