<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Natural Gas on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/natural-gas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Natural Gas on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:02:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/natural-gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: Energy Transfer LP (ET) has shown consistent growth and an increase in quarterly cash distribution, indicating a positive outlook for potential returns. The company&amp;rsquo;s diverse segments, including natural gas transportation, crude oil transportation, and midstream operations, provide a strong foundation for stable revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corporation Foundation offering STEM scholarships to support education and future talent in Science, Technology, Engineering and Math (STEM) disciplines. Risks: Inflation and higher natural gas prices are impacting utility investors and may lead to increased costs for customers. Score:40 chances characters count - risks characters count = 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:83
Chances: Southwestern Energy Co. engages in the exploration, development, and production of natural gas, oil, and natural gas liquids (NGLs) Optimism prevails in the renewable energy industry despite recent downturns in renewable energy companies The United States is rich in natural gas resources found in multiple key basins and regions Risks: Recent downturns in renewable energy companies such as FirstSolar and Plug Power may impact the overall performance of the renewable energy sector Investors should be cautious about investing in &amp;lsquo;story stocks&amp;rsquo; that promise to be &amp;rsquo;the next big thing&amp;rsquo; Score:83 chances characters count - risks characters count = 83</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
