<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>consumer spending on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/consumer-spending/</link>
    <description>Recent content in consumer spending on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/consumer-spending/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s has announced a quarterly dividend, which could attract income-focused investors. Collaborations with brands like Gap on a sleepwear collection suggest potential for increased sales and brand partnerships. Despite challenges, consumers are spending, and there is optimism for a potential rebound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Target expands key advantage over Walmart, Amazon. Target Sees Slowdown But Is Still a Strong Retail Buy. Dirt-Cheap Dividend King raises its payout to a record high. Positive analyst calls for Target. Strong consumer spending noted for retail sector. Risks: Retail theft affecting profits and outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s beats profit estimates on cost cuts and leaner inventory. Earnings surpass estimates, maintains full-year guidance. Strategic efforts aiding growth in Kohl&amp;rsquo;s. Back-to-school shopping convenience and affordable prices. Positive takeaways from Q2 earnings call. Risks: Profits plunge more than 50% annually on weak sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Gap surpasses Q2 earnings estimates despite a weak forecast. Positive focus on profit beat and strong Q2 earnings performance. Gap reports profit beat and slight revenue miss, comp. sales dip. Analysts highlight potential for Gap&amp;rsquo;s growth after positive Q2 performance. Gap&amp;rsquo;s strategic partnerships and limited-edition collections contribute to opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jwn/</guid>
      <description>score:-48
Chances: Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenue beat estimates, indicating positive performance. Resilient demand leads to Nordstrom&amp;rsquo;s quarterly revenue estimates being surpassed. Strong performance of Nordstrom stock in the midst of challenging market conditions. Nordstrom reiterates annual guidance after Q2 results exceed expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TJX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: TJX Companies (TJX) reported earnings, indicating consumers&amp;rsquo; preferences for trade-down purchases in retail chains over department stores. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to adapt to changing consumer spending habits due to inflation and high rates might positively impact its performance. TJX&amp;rsquo;s strategic pricing, merchandise initiatives, and focus on memberships could contribute to its consistent sales growth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
