<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Consumer Spending on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/consumer-spending/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Consumer Spending on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:29:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/consumer-spending/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:78
Chances: Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and a positive Zacks Earnings ESP suggest a potential earnings beat for Gap in its upcoming report. The announcement of a third quarter fiscal year 2023 dividend of $0.15 per share could indicate confidence in Gap&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TJX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tjx/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: TJX Companies (TJX) reported earnings, indicating consumers&amp;rsquo; preferences for trade-down purchases in retail chains over department stores. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to adapt to changing consumer spending habits due to inflation and high rates might positively impact its performance. TJX&amp;rsquo;s strategic pricing, merchandise initiatives, and focus on memberships could contribute to its consistent sales growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s is set to report earnings, which could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The appointment of Massimo Magni as chief customer and digital officer could signal a focus on digital transformation and customer engagement. Macy&amp;rsquo;s back-to-school season offerings and efforts to provide a unique shopping experience could drive customer engagement and sales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
