<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Public Offering on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/public-offering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Public Offering on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/public-offering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:684
Chances: Announcement of Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; second quarter 2023 financial and operational results. Declaration of a quarterly base and variable cash dividend by Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; Board of Directors. Notice of Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; second quarter 2023 financial and operating results reporting date. Discussion on Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; potential earnings beat based on options market movements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Announcement of QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s successful closing of an underwritten public offering, raising $300 million. Discussing the decline in QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s stock price despite gains in Chinese stocks and reasons behind the drop. Reviewing QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s financial position and assessing the risk of running out of money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:1093
Chances: Aurora Innovation announced positive First Half 2023 results with a narrowed net loss of US$414.0 million. The company is scheduled to present at the Canaccord Genuity 43rd Annual Growth Conference, indicating efforts to engage with investors. Aurora&amp;rsquo;s second quarter 2023 results have been released, and its shareholder letter and financial results are available for review on its investor relations website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
