<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Electric Vehicle Market on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicle-market/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Electric Vehicle Market on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:34:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/electric-vehicle-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Despite challenges in the renewable energy sector, Sunrun has shown growth in revenue and networked storage capacity, indicating potential for expansion. Strong performance in the electric vehicle market and increased demand for charging could positively impact Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s business. Growing storage attachment rates and networked storage capacity highlight Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s ability to adapt to market trends and offer value-added services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Lucid Group is gaining attention and interest despite reporting an earnings miss and falling short of EV deliveries, possibly due to the unveiling of its final specs and design for the highly anticipated Lucid Air Sapphire model. The EV manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s focus on luxury electric vehicles, such as the Lucid Air, has garnered recognition, including winning the 2023 World Luxury Car Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:80
Chances: NIO&amp;rsquo;s stock price closed with a positive move, potentially indicating short-term upside. The company is a pioneer and leading player in the premium smart electric vehicle market. NIO is set to report its second-quarter 2023 financial results, which could impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
