<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metaverse on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/metaverse/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Metaverse on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:39:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/metaverse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1074 RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:1074
Chances: Roblox is joining the Roblox Partner Program, which could amplify the company&amp;rsquo;s position in delivering impactful programs for brands on the global immersive platform. The metaverse is a growing trend, and Roblox is at the forefront of delivering immersive experiences across virtual platforms, which could open avenues for substantial gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1045 U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1045
Chances: Unity Software&amp;rsquo;s revenue rose 11% YoY on a pro forma basis, exceeding analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations, indicating potential growth opportunities. Unity Software Inc. delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, suggesting positive financial performance. Steady demand for Unity Software&amp;rsquo;s software solutions, expanding client base, and the launch of AI services may have contributed to its Q2 performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0802 META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:802
Chances: Over three billion people a day use a Meta product, indicating a large user base and potential for growth. Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta has delivered impressive results, garnering positive reactions from investors. Meta&amp;rsquo;s investment in building chatbots with different personalities for its social media sites may indicate its commitment to innovation and user engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
