<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Season on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-season/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Season on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:54:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-season/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:144
Chances: Continued recovery in leisure demand and business transient demand may benefit Q2 earnings. Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is the largest lodging real estate investment trust (REIT) and an S&amp;amp;P 500 company. Investor presentation provides insights into Q2 2023 results. Moderating rates at resorts impacting comparable hotel Revenue Per Available Room (RevPAR) growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Schlumberger has been closely watched by Zacks.com users, indicating interest in the stock. Revenue for Q2 2023 increased by 20% despite a downturn in North America rig counts. Positive signs of breakout as U.S. oil prices rise. Rapidly changing climate creating opportunities in clean energy and related sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:986
Chances: Major U.S. airlines request an extension of cuts to minimum flight requirements at congested airports due to air traffic control staffing issues. Flights to Europe have significantly increased, with a 600% rise in Americans traveling to Europe from 2021 to 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:1030
Chances: Kraft Heinz reports sales growth in North America and International regions due to solid pricing. Earnings season impact on Kraft Heinz&amp;rsquo;s sales and demand from cost-conscious consumers. Positive outlook for the economy and economic performance. Continued focus on pricing strategy and maintaining higher prices for products.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
