<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supply Chain on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/supply-chain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supply Chain on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/supply-chain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WOLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wolf/</guid>
      <description>score:123
Chances: Wolfspeed&amp;rsquo;s leadership in silicon carbide technology positions the company to capitalize on the growing demand for power devices in electric vehicle (EV) applications. The shipment of a Purion H200™ SiC ion implant system to Wolfspeed from Axcelis Technologies indicates the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing its production capabilities for power devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/smci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/smci/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: Consistent profitability reflected in the company&amp;rsquo;s Profitability Rank of 9 out of 10. Impressive growth in terms of revenue and profitability with a Growth Rank of 10 out of 10. Benefiting from the demand for AI servers, contributing to growth. Delivery of high-throughput, low latency E3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
