<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fed on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fed on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to the Fed&#39;s Interest Rate Decision: Pause With Option to Hike</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-guide-to-the-feds-interest-rate-decision-pause-with-option-to-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-guide-to-the-feds-interest-rate-decision-pause-with-option-to-hike/</guid>
      <description>Fed Expected to Pause Interest Rate Hikes The Federal Reserve is expected to keep interest rates on hold at its June meeting, according to a Bloomberg survey of economists. This would mark the first time since March 2022 that the Fed has not raised rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traders Position for a Fed Pause But Start Unwinding Cut Wagers</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/traders-position-for-a-fed-pause-but-start-unwinding-cut-wagers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/traders-position-for-a-fed-pause-but-start-unwinding-cut-wagers/</guid>
      <description>Traders Position for Fed Pause Traders are positioning for a Fed pause in the interest rate hike cycle, but are also starting to unwind their bets on rate cuts later this year. This shift in sentiment is likely due to the recent rise in inflation, which has raised concerns about the pace of monetary tightening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rates Latest: Inflation Hop, Policy Skip May Set Dissent Jump</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-inflation-hop-policy-skip-may-set-dissent-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:16:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-inflation-hop-policy-skip-may-set-dissent-jump/</guid>
      <description>Fed Faces Difficult Balancing Act as Inflation Rises
The Federal Reserve is facing a difficult balancing act as it tries to bring down inflation without causing a recession.
In recent months, the Fed has raised interest rates in an effort to cool the economy and bring down inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rates Latest: Get Ready for Pause and Assess Effect of Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-get-ready-for-pause-and-assess-effect-of-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-get-ready-for-pause-and-assess-effect-of-hikes/</guid>
      <description>Fed to Hike Rates by 0.75%, Pause After July
The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates by 0.75% at its meeting on Wednesday, July 13. This would be the largest rate hike since 1994. The Fed is raising rates in an effort to combat inflation, which is at a 40-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Readings on the Inflation, Interest Rates Coming Next Week</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fresh-readings-on-the-inflation-interest-rates-coming-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:34:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fresh-readings-on-the-inflation-interest-rates-coming-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Fresh Readings on Inflation and Interest Rates Coming Next Week The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) will release its latest Consumer Price Index (CPI) report on Wednesday, June 15. The CPI is a measure of inflation, and it is closely watched by investors and policymakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bond Bulls Bet Fed Is Right in Anticipating Low Rates to Return</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</guid>
      <description>Bond Investors Bet on Lower Interest Rates Bond investors are betting that the Federal Reserve will be unable to sustain its current rate-hike cycle and that interest rates will eventually return to low levels. This is a reversal of the trend that has been in place for the past decade, during which the Fed has steadily raised rates in an effort to combat inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Done: The Bloomberg Close, Asia Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/almost-done-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:11:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/almost-done-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</guid>
      <description>Markets in Asia were mixed on Tuesday as investors awaited the outcome of the US Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s meeting. The Nikkei 225 in Japan was down 0.3%, while the Hang Seng in Hong Kong was up 0.2%.
The US dollar was stronger against most currencies, as investors expected the Fed to raise interest rates by 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
