<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings report on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings report on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:24:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s beats profit estimates on cost cuts and leaner inventory. Earnings surpass estimates, maintains full-year guidance. Strategic efforts aiding growth in Kohl&amp;rsquo;s. Back-to-school shopping convenience and affordable prices. Positive takeaways from Q2 earnings call. Risks: Profits plunge more than 50% annually on weak sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: Continued expansion of the gaming platform&amp;rsquo;s footprint. Announcement of partnership with Hamilton Simulator. Revenues rising in Q2 2023 despite stock crash. Potential bargain levels of Roblox stock. Positive investor sentiment amid dip in stock price. Risks: Stock crash of 21% following Q2 earnings report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Resumption of 737 Max deliveries to China after a 4-year halt. Boeing&amp;rsquo;s focus on sustainability and hiring &amp;lsquo;Elon Musk engineers&amp;rsquo; for green initiatives. Positive recognition of Boeing&amp;rsquo;s top-performing suppliers. Securing an order for Dreamliner jets from Qantas. Potential rebound after a 7% drop since the last earnings report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Luminar reported Q2 2023 results in line with expectations and maintains full-year financial guidance. Luminar delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with automakers like Polestar and Nissan indicate growth prospects. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s focus on advanced semiconductor capabilities and AI technologies is positioning it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Lufax Holding is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China. Lufax reported unaudited financial results for Q1 2023 with positive earnings and revenue surprises. Change in non-executive director and appointments within the company&amp;rsquo;s board. Risks: Lufax reported an 86% YoY decline in profit for Q1 2023 due to China&amp;rsquo;s lackluster economic recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APLS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/apls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/apls/</guid>
      <description>score:-69
Chances: Apellis Pharmaceuticals reported better-than-expected second-quarter 2023 results, indicating strong performance in its financials. Positive data on SYFOVRE&amp;rsquo;s reduction of nonsubfoveal GA lesion growth could reflect the potential effectiveness of Apellis&amp;rsquo; products. Equity awards granted to new employees could attract and incentivize talented individuals to join the company, contributing to its growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:724
Chances: Gilead Sciences expects a third of sales to come from its cancer treatments by 2030, driving optimism and stock price movement. Gilead Sciences is focused on developing therapies for life-threatening infectious diseases and expanding its portfolio to include pulmonary, cardiovascular diseases, and cancer treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
