<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Report on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Report on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:771
Chances: Bilibili to report second quarter 2023 unaudited financial results, showcasing its growth and financial performance. Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s record high stock price in 2021 indicates strong investor interest and growth potential. Technical performance and Relative Strength Rating upgrade suggest improving trends for Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:825
Chances: Infosys benefits from strong demand for cloud, data analytics, IoT, and security products amid the ongoing digital transformation wave. Optimism returns for India&amp;rsquo;s IT companies as easing odds of a US recession and the emergence of AI as a revenue source drive a rebound in stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:724
Chances: Gilead Sciences expects a third of sales to come from its cancer treatments by 2030, driving optimism and stock price movement. Gilead Sciences is focused on developing therapies for life-threatening infectious diseases and expanding its portfolio to include pulmonary, cardiovascular diseases, and cancer treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:966
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results show increases in sales and earnings, driven by brand strength and pricing. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter, and it raised its full-year 2023 net sales growth forecast. Keurig Dr Pepper appointed Monique Oxender as Interim Chief Corporate Affairs Officer, overseeing corporate responsibility and communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:1034
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s is set to report its second quarter 2023 sales and earnings results, with a call and webcast hosted by company executives. Retailers like Macy&amp;rsquo;s are expanding their use of &amp;lsquo;breathable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cooling&amp;rsquo; fabrics to boost sales amid high demand for heat-relief clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:1126
Chances: Under Armour announced the launch of its &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, aiming to strengthen customer connections and brand loyalty. The company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance customer connections, innovations, and a new loyalty program are expected to contribute to brand growth. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s senior executive leadership team changes are aligned with the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to drive consistent profitable growth and returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: Li Auto is expected to report strong earnings and revenue growth, with analysts predicting about 24 cents/share of earnings on revenue of $3.7 billion. Li Auto delivered 34,134 vehicles in July 2023, an increase of 227.5% year over year, surpassing the 30,000 mark for the second consecutive month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:999
Chances: Occidental Petroleum reported a surprise profit in Q2 2023 despite the impact of soft commodity prices. Permian Basin production remains strong, contributing to Occidental&amp;rsquo;s production volumes for the year. Sunrise&amp;rsquo;s surprise profit, DXC&amp;rsquo;s guidance, and Wayfair&amp;rsquo;s performance could provide insights into Occidental&amp;rsquo;s industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:1112
Chances: Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) announces a transition plan for CFO Tarek Robbiati, who will assume an external CEO role. HPE expands its Bare Metal Cloud platform with cloud-native HPE ProLiant RL300 Gen11 servers, enhancing AI inferencing and cloud-native workloads. ZoomInfo delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, potentially impacting HPE&amp;rsquo;s stock and market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:1124
Chances: Barrick Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to benefit from higher gold and copper production along with cost reduction. Barrick Gold aims to restart operations at the Porgera gold mine in Papua New Guinea, potentially contributing to future production. Barrick Gold Corporation is actively engaging in transparency by disclosing site-level tailings storage facility (TSF) information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:1098
Chances: Sirius XM (SIRI) experienced improvement in average revenue per user in Q2 2023, despite declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM delivered earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, holding potential clues for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. The Liberty Media tracking stock, which includes Sirius XM, trades at a significant discount to the value of the company&amp;rsquo;s Live Nation Stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:1127
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock has reached a new 52-week low, with charts and indicators indicating a weak setup due to a downward trend. Despite market fluctuations, the value of Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock is being assessed, considering its potential amidst challenges. Moderna&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call revealed a miss on earnings expectations, which could impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:1350
Chances: Disney CEO Bob Iger returned after a short retirement and expressed surprise at the problems discovered at the company, including challenges in the traditional television business and box office disappointments. Investors are eager to assess Disney&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings, focusing on theme park performance, broadcast partnerships for ESPN, and Bob Iger&amp;rsquo;s strategic plans for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s shares are well-positioned for a potential bullish market wave. Uber&amp;rsquo;s solid results and improved profitability could have positive implications for Lyft&amp;rsquo;s performance. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s upcoming second-quarter earnings report could provide insights into its financial performance and competitive positioning. Risks: Lyft faces pressure from the market&amp;rsquo;s reaction to its peer Uber&amp;rsquo;s mixed second-quarter report and profit-taking after a recent strong run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:1188
Chances: Viatris shares advanced after posting better-than-expected Q2 2023 results and announcing planned divestitures, including a new multiple sclerosis treatment in collaboration with Mapi Pharma. Viatris CEO plans $9 billion in divestitures to optimize the company&amp;rsquo;s business lines and products, a third of which is already completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:992
Chances: Southwestern Energy reports positive Q2 2023 earnings with lower operating costs and expenses. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show potential positive momentum for Southwestern Energy (SWN). Strong sector performance by Permian Resources, Civitas Resources, and Northern Oil &amp;amp; Gas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:953
Chances: AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results are expected to benefit from robust Admissions and Food and Beverage revenues. The strong performance of &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; at the box office could have a lasting financial impact on companies in fashion, entertainment, and home decor industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:962
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings report for Q2 2023 and its first profit since Covid are indications of the company&amp;rsquo;s recovery from the pandemic. Investors and traders may consider buying the dip in Norwegian Cruise Line shares following the earnings report, as the company&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown resilience and a robust recovery trend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
