<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings report on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings report on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:101
Chances: RLX Technology to report unaudited financial results for the second quarter, indicating transparency and accountability. Positive market sentiment towards Chinese stocks&amp;rsquo; recovery and potential stimulus. Shares of RLX Technology showing upward movement. Notable performance metrics, such as best value and best performance in comparison to peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Luminar reported Q2 2023 results in line with expectations and maintains full-year financial guidance. Luminar delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with automakers like Polestar and Nissan indicate growth prospects. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s focus on advanced semiconductor capabilities and AI technologies is positioning it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:144
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s kicks off the back-to-school season with a wide range of fashion and accessories. The consumer cyclical sector is gaining steam this year. Macy&amp;rsquo;s to report second quarter 2023 sales and earnings results on August 22, 2023. Retailers like Macy&amp;rsquo;s expanding use of &amp;lsquo;breathable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cooling&amp;rsquo; fabrics to boost sales during heat waves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Lufax Holding is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China. Lufax reported unaudited financial results for Q1 2023 with positive earnings and revenue surprises. Change in non-executive director and appointments within the company&amp;rsquo;s board. Risks: Lufax reported an 86% YoY decline in profit for Q1 2023 due to China&amp;rsquo;s lackluster economic recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APLS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/apls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/apls/</guid>
      <description>score:-69
Chances: Apellis Pharmaceuticals reported better-than-expected second-quarter 2023 results, indicating strong performance in its financials. Positive data on SYFOVRE&amp;rsquo;s reduction of nonsubfoveal GA lesion growth could reflect the potential effectiveness of Apellis&amp;rsquo; products. Equity awards granted to new employees could attract and incentivize talented individuals to join the company, contributing to its growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amc/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: AMC successfully secured court approval for a stock conversion plan, allowing the company to raise capital. The company&amp;rsquo;s marketing efforts are being led by experienced professionals, potentially driving positive brand awareness. AMC reported second-quarter results that beat analyst estimates on both revenue and earnings, with an explosive start to the third quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Lucid Group raised its production guidance for the year after a better-than-expected second quarter. Despite an earnings miss and falling short of EV deliveries, Lucid Group&amp;rsquo;s stock is still seeing positive movement. The unveiling of final production specs for the Lucid Air Sapphire model showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s innovation in electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Plug Power reported record revenue in its second-quarter results, reaffirming its full-year sales estimate. Despite recent losses and challenges, Plug Power remains one of the most hyped hydrogen stocks with potential. The hydrogen technology company has hydrogen production plants in various states, contributing to its revenue drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:252
Chances: SoFi&amp;rsquo;s differentiation in the fintech space through low fees and an extensive suite of digital financial services is resonating with customers. SoFi&amp;rsquo;s strong revenue growth and significant increase in its member base showcase the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for expansion. The positive earnings report and revenue growth have contributed to a more than 100% increase in SOFI stock in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:724
Chances: Gilead Sciences expects a third of sales to come from its cancer treatments by 2030, driving optimism and stock price movement. Gilead Sciences is focused on developing therapies for life-threatening infectious diseases and expanding its portfolio to include pulmonary, cardiovascular diseases, and cancer treatments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:1126
Chances: Under Armour announced the launch of its &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, aiming to strengthen customer connections and brand loyalty. The company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance customer connections, innovations, and a new loyalty program are expected to contribute to brand growth. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s senior executive leadership team changes are aligned with the company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to drive consistent profitable growth and returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrna/</guid>
      <description>score:1127
Chances: Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock has reached a new 52-week low, with charts and indicators indicating a weak setup due to a downward trend. Despite market fluctuations, the value of Moderna&amp;rsquo;s stock is being assessed, considering its potential amidst challenges. Moderna&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call revealed a miss on earnings expectations, which could impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:1188
Chances: Viatris shares advanced after posting better-than-expected Q2 2023 results and announcing planned divestitures, including a new multiple sclerosis treatment in collaboration with Mapi Pharma. Viatris CEO plans $9 billion in divestitures to optimize the company&amp;rsquo;s business lines and products, a third of which is already completed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
