<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Report on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Report on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:08:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SONO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sono/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 09:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sono/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Sonos (SONO) reported better-than-expected quarterly results and teased an important new product. Investments in innovative solutions that enhance communications experience are likely to aid Sonos (SONO) in the long run. Risks: The ambitious foray into the headphone market has hit a software snag, delaying production of the device and its release date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Pure Storage&amp;rsquo;s strong quarterly earnings and sales performance, including a double beat on earnings, indicate a positive outlook for the company&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into the Puerto Rico and Central America market with Empresas Berríos demonstrates its ability to drive business growth and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zm/</guid>
      <description>score:199
Chances: Zoom Video reported Q4 earnings and revenue that topped estimates amid strength in the enterprise market. Shares of video conferencing platform Zoom (NASDAQ:ZM) jumped 13.5% in the pre-market session after the company reported fourth-quarter results, with its revenue narrowly outperforming Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s estimates, though EPS beat by a more convincing margin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:-82
Chances: The company plans to release its third quarter fiscal 2024 financial results soon, which could provide valuable insights into its performance. Fans will soon be able to purchase the Australia women&amp;rsquo;s goalkeeper kit, which may boost sales and brand visibility for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRSP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crsp/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: CRISPR Therapeutics has shown improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. The company is focused on creating transformative gene-based medicines for serious diseases, and has announced conditional marketing authorization for its gene edited therapy, CASGEVY. Risks: The company doesn&amp;rsquo;t possess the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co. has demonstrated its commitment to expanding its animal health business through the recent acquisition of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s aqua business. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong earnings report and solid guidance indicate that it is well-positioned to thrive despite potential challenges such as the expiration of its patent on Keytruda.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
