<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Report on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Report on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:31:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0681 EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:681
Chances: Expedia Group, Inc. beat earnings expectations in the second quarter of 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89, higher than the expected $2.32. Earnings reports from online travel companies, including Expedia, show that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer trips, indicating strengthening travel demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: PPL Corporation reported second-quarter 2023 earnings, indicating ongoing capital investments and operation cost savings. PPL has been recognized for cultivating a collaborative, inclusive, and equitable culture, ranking No. 4 on DiversityInc&amp;rsquo;s Top Utilities list. PPL Electric Utilities is enhancing the reliability of its power delivery to customers through innovative technology, Dynamic Line Rating (DLR).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0922 TXN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/txn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/txn/</guid>
      <description>score:922
Chances: Texas Instruments has typically been seen as a safe-haven blue-chip stock, with the largest scale and lowest-cost manufacturing in analog and embedded chips. The company&amp;rsquo;s disciplined expansion and focus on &amp;lsquo;mature&amp;rsquo; chip manufacturing have led to sustained free-cash-flow-per-share growth. Semiconductors are increasingly crucial as economies become more digitized, which bodes well for top semiconductor stocks like Texas Instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0848 SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:848
Chances: Spirit AeroSystems&amp;rsquo; Q2 revenues of $1,365 million surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 7.4%, indicating strong performance in the quarter. The top line of Spirit AeroSystems rose 8% on a year-over-year basis, which may signal growth in the company&amp;rsquo;s business. Although the stock reported disappointing Q2 results, there may be a chance for a turnaround if the supply chain issues and labor costs are effectively addressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1118 RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:1118
Chances: RLX Technology saw significant share gains despite not being widely known, indicating potential growth opportunities. Shares of RLX Technology rose nearly 15% as China&amp;rsquo;s central bank trimmed one of its short-term interest rates and rumors of stimulus circulated, which may signal positive sentiment towards the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1349 VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:1349
Chances: Vertiv Holdings reported strong second-quarter net sales of $1,734 million, showing a 24% increase compared to the same quarter last year, and a 25% organic net sales increase, indicating positive financial performance. Shares of Vertiv rose significantly, driven by ongoing demand for data center equipment in both the cloud/hyperscale and colocation markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1040 ABNB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abnb/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Airbnb, Inc. beat earnings expectations in the second quarter, reporting an EPS of $0.98 compared to the expected $0.77, indicating positive financial performance. The U.S. economy has shown resilience, and companies like Airbnb that stand to grow rapidly in such an environment might have a chance for further expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1033 BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:1033
Chances: B2Gold reported positive second-quarter 2023 earnings and revenue surprises, indicating potential growth and financial strength. Revenues rose year-over-year in the second quarter due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1104 MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1104
Chances: Monster Beverage reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1 percent to $1.85 billion, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Gains from strong brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions may contribute to Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s future growth. The completion of the acquisition of Bang Energy and its beverages could open new opportunities and expand Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Permian Resources Corporation announced its second quarter 2023 financial and operational results, which may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The declaration of a quarterly base and variable cash dividend by Permian Resources may attract income-seeking investors. Investors may find interest in participating in the earnings conference call to gain more insights into Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; performance and future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1009 DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:1009
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s operating income increased by 23% in one of its segments, indicating positive growth opportunities. The upcoming report on Disney&amp;rsquo;s fiscal third-quarter results may provide insights into its plans for ESPN, Disney+, and other segments. Liberty Media delivered impressive earnings and revenue surprises, which might indicate positive momentum for Disney as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1100 HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:1100
Chances: Robinhood reported its first profitable quarter as a publicly traded company, which is a positive sign for investors. The company beat expectations on profit and revenue, indicating strong financial performance. Robinhood shares have filled a big chunk of the early downside price gap, showing signs of improvement in share prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1005 MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Marathon Oil reported second quarter 2023 net income of $287 million or $0.47 per diluted share, and adjusted net income was $295 million or $0.48 per diluted share. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, indicating positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0771 LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:771
Chances: Lyft will report its second-quarter earnings, and investors will be closely watching the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance and response to rival Uber&amp;rsquo;s first operating profit. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results may benefit from improved profitability and increased revenues, considering the positive results posted by its peer, Uber Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0795 FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:795
Chances: Fisker announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, which could tap into the growing demand for electric trucks in the U.S. market. Fisker&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Henrik Fisker, expressed optimism about the demand for the Fisker Alaska pickup truck, especially if it is priced competitively and offers a &amp;lsquo;cool&amp;rsquo; product in the sub-$30,000 EV category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0977 ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:977
Chances: Energy Transfer had strong performance from its operations, delivering record volumes across its segments, which may be positively received by investors. The company offers a prodigious income stream, and its monster distribution significantly exceeded reported net income, which could attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1274 CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:1274
Chances: Clarivate Plc&amp;rsquo;s CEO and CFO are scheduled to present at Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo;s 26th Annual Technology, Internet &amp;amp; Communications Conference, which could generate positive interest from investors. The company reported results for the second quarter, and positive financial performance may attract positive sentiment from investors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
