<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>institutional ownership on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/institutional-ownership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in institutional ownership on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:06:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/institutional-ownership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:159
Chances: Fortinet has caught the eye of investors, indicating potential investment opportunities. The company won Google Cloud Technology Partner of the Year Award for Security, showcasing its capabilities. Fortinet expands its SASE solution to provide cloud-delivered enterprise-grade protection, positioning itself for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teva/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Teva Pharmaceutical Industries is set to present data for various products, indicating ongoing research and potential for growth. Teva&amp;rsquo;s CEO sees &amp;lsquo;significant&amp;rsquo; potential for a trio of branded drugs, which could drive future revenue and profits. Teva&amp;rsquo;s strategic evaluation, including the potential sale of its active ingredients unit, might create opportunities for restructuring and focus on core operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Gilead&amp;rsquo;s Phase 2 EVOKE-02 Study of Trodelvy in Combination with KEYTRUDA demonstrates promising clinical activity in first-line metastatic non-small cell lung cancer, indicating potential growth opportunities. Gilead Sciences has a high institutional ownership of 86%, suggesting confidence from major investors. The FDA approval for Veklury to treat COVID-19 in people with hepatic impairment is a positive development for Gilead&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JPM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jpm/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. is favored by institutional owners who hold 72% of the company, indicating strong investor confidence. The company could launch a blockchain-based deposit token &amp;lsquo;relatively quickly&amp;rsquo; after regulatory approval, showcasing its innovative potential. JPMorgan&amp;rsquo;s CEO Jamie Dimon recently delivered a stern warning to remote workers, suggesting adaptability to changing work trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: NextEra Energy has a strong institutional ownership of 80%, which may indicate confidence among large investors. Wall Street analysts seem bullish on NextEra Energy, suggesting a positive outlook for the company&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s involvement in renewable energy projects positions it well in the growing green energy sector, offering long-term growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: U.S. Bancorp is experiencing revenue growth despite high costs, which could be seen as a positive sign for investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s business banking segment, Elavon, has launched a new product called Talech Terminal, indicating innovation and potential market expansion. U.S. Bancorp has strong institutional backing, with 76% ownership, which may instill confidence in investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: ConocoPhillips Proves Why A Gap Down In Price Is Not Always Bad ConocoPhillips expands full year production guidance with company-wide records ConocoPhillips (NYSE:COP) Looks Like A Good Stock, And It&amp;rsquo;s Going Ex-Dividend Soon Risks: ConocoPhillips Misses Earnings Expectations Despite Record Production ConocoPhillips misses on profit, hikes full-year output forecast ConocoPhillips (COP) Lags on Q2 Earnings, Ups &amp;lsquo;23 Output View Score:29 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Steady dividend payouts with attractive yields. Positive stock performance and returns over the last three years. Strong institutional ownership indicating investor confidence. Q2 earnings beat and positive financial results. Potential growth opportunities with pipeline expansion plans. Risks: Shutdown of compressor station affecting operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/extr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/extr/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Extreme Networks surpasses Q4 earnings and revenue estimates. Extreme Networks recognized as a Gartner Peer Insights™ Customers&amp;rsquo; Choice. Favorable industry outlook highlighting networking stocks. High institutional ownership indicates investor confidence. Positive response to innovative products and solutions. Risks: Uncertain future affecting the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for outperformance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: TAL Education Group beats earnings expectations for full year 2023. Institutional investors show interest with a significant ownership stake. TAL Education Group files its annual report on Form 20-F. TAL Education Group&amp;rsquo;s strong week for shareholders doesn&amp;rsquo;t alleviate long-term losses. Top-line decline in Q3 attributed to seasonality and forex fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/c/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Citigroup enters Latin America FX space, invests in Rextie. Citigroup launches relationship tiers, simplifies banking. Positive impact of NII and streamlining efforts on Citigroup. Strategic investment in Rextie for FX services. Citi&amp;rsquo;s focus on simplifying retail banking for customer benefit. Risks: Challenges from accelerated settlements identified in Citi survey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:-46
Chances: Uber raises minimum age for most California drivers to 25. Collaboration with Oracle and White House CancerX Project. Bullish tech stocks for market rebound. Uber CEO&amp;rsquo;s participation in fireside chat hosted by Goldman Sachs. Positive outlook for growth and investment in tech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
