<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Analysis on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Analysis on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:55:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Plug Power has enormous potential if it can get its costs under control. The Fed forecasting more rate cuts than initially expected in 2024, leading to rally mode in beaten-down areas of the market. 10 best hydrogen and fuel cell stocks to buy for 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: TG Therapeutics stock saw a welcome improvement to its Relative Strength (RS) Rating, rising from 87 to 93. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.8%. The positive trend in earnings estimate revisions might translate into an upside in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:-81
Chances: UiPath shares have been gaining and might continue moving higher in the near term, as indicated by solid earnings estimate revisions. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock led the NYSE and has beaten the market by a significant margin this year. Risks: There was a notable insider transaction where the General Counsel and Chief Legal Officer sold 105,000 shares of the company, which may raise concerns about insider confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
