<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Analysis on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Analysis on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:05:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: When it comes to investing in fintech companies and the financing concept of BNPL — buy now, pay later — Affirm still comes to top of mind. The stock for this buy now, pay later company should be bought and held.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Pinterest stock has shown a recent uptrend, including a 6% jump following reports of a potential advertising partnership with Google. The company&amp;rsquo;s RS Rating has increased from 67 to 75, indicating potential for continued rebound and growth. The platform&amp;rsquo;s top trends predictions and expansion strategy suggest potential for increased market monetization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:112
Chances: Wayfair stock reached an important technical milestone, seeing its Relative Strength (RS) Rating jump into the 80-plus percentile with an improvement to 83, up from 78 the day before. The prospect of price stabilization and cheaper credit is positive for consumers, as are the current low rate of unemployment and recent improvements in real wage growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: In the closing of the recent trading day, Snap (SNAP) stood at $11.45, denoting a +1.24% change from the preceding trading day. nCino (NCNO) delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 75% and 0.71%, respectively, for the quarter ended January 2024. Integral Ad Science (Nasdaq: IAS) announced a first-to-market partnership with Snap Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 09:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: Schlumberger is making a significant move in the carbon capture industry by acquiring 80% of Aker Carbon Capture, indicating a push towards sustainable and eco-friendly technologies. The company&amp;rsquo;s digital and integration segment, focusing on digital solutions and data products, shows potential for growth and innovation in the energy technology sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mmm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mmm/</guid>
      <description>score:283
Chances: 3M has invested in EVOLOH, a cleantech company that&amp;rsquo;s working to scale up manufacturing of its electrolyzers to make green hydrogen affordable and efficient. The industrial conglomerate&amp;rsquo;s management recently delivered some excellent news to investors. A Barclays analyst is getting increasingly bullish on the turnaround prospects of this high-yield dividend stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:-182
Chances: Palantir is expected to rapidly expand earnings per share over several years. The company is taking a visionary leap The path could be wide open for Palantir stock to climb even higher from here on out. Risks: Will generative artificial intelligence boost Palantir stock in the commercial market amid slowing revenue growth for the company?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: PayPal has a strong suite of digital payment solutions that cater to both merchants and consumers worldwide. The company&amp;rsquo;s long-term growth potential and commitment to rewarding shareholders make it an attractive investment option. Despite recent stock price fluctuations, PayPal&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach to financial services and its resilience in the face of competition position it for future success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:215
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) closed at $71.46, indicating a +0.15% shift from the previous trading day. Fortinet delivers a range of secure and integrated WLAN/LAN solutions, catering to various environments. Windstream Enterprise (WE) unveiled Secure Flex Premium, powered by Fortinet, providing a fully customizable cybersecurity infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:122
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co. (VRT) closed at $61.67, indicating a +1.53% shift from the previous trading day. Services activity in the United States is expanding, which is helping stocks like Vertiv Holdings Co (VRT). The average brokerage recommendation (ABR) for Vertiv Holdings Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 09:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ymm/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Full Truck Alliance&amp;rsquo;s stock price might be vulnerable due to the large stake held by institutions. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 40.2% in Full Truck Alliance Co. Ltd. Sponsored ADR (YMM).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OWL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/owl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/owl/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Blue Owl Capital Inc. and Blue Owl Capital Corporation are both scheduled to release their financial results for the fourth quarter, providing potential opportunities for investors to assess the performance of these companies. Risks: The volatility of the stock market and potential fluctuations in the financial performance of Blue Owl Capital Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETRN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/etrn/</guid>
      <description>score:152
Chances: Equitrans Midstream is setting up just below a buy point amid a run of more than 50% in 2023. Operational results for the third quarter of 2023 show a 12% transmission pipeline throughput growth. Equitrans Midstream delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 75% and 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRWD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crwd/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: CrowdStrike (CRWD) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately. Shares of cybersecurity company CrowdStrike (NASDAQ:CRWD) jumped 5.4% in the afternoon session after Morgan Stanley analyst Hamza Fodderwala upgraded the stock&amp;rsquo;s rating from Equal-Weight (Hold) to Overweight (Buy) and raised the price target from $203 to $304.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has a strong platform used by developers, artists, and designers across various industries. The company has a large user base, with over 1.1 million game creators relying on its software toolkit each month. Risks: Unity Software Inc. plans to lay off about 25% of its workforce, which could impact its operational capabilities and future developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
