<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Analysis on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Analysis on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Kenvue Inc. stock closed up 1.4% on Dec. 13 and was priced at $21.04 at the end of the after-hours trading session. With a dividend yield of 1.98% and a payout of $0.40 per share, the company reported a total dividend expense of $383 million from January to September.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:197
Chances: Pinterest (PINS) closed at $38.04 in the latest trading session, marking a +0.9% move from the prior day. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Invest bought 172,894 shares of Pinterest Monday, a move that, based on the stock&amp;rsquo;s closing price of $37.70, was valued at roughly $6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:89
Chances: The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.8% in TG Therapeutics (TGTX) which is a positive trend in earnings estimate revisions might translate into an upside in the stock. TG Therapeutics stock saw a welcome improvement to its Relative Strength (RS) Rating, rising from 87 to 93 which indicates good potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: Plug Power has enormous potential if it can get its costs under control. Hydrogen stocks might not have been the best of performers during the year, but a strong stage is being set for stellar growth in the hydrogen economy beyond the current decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s expansion of the Shanghai Disney Resort with a Zootopia-themed attraction is expected to capitalize on the post-pandemic desire for travel and experiences in China. Risks: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s removal of the Disney+ app from its EVs amid ongoing feud between Elon Musk and Disney CEO Bob Iger may impact Disney&amp;rsquo;s revenue from in-car entertainment services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
