<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AMCR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</guid>
      <description>score:151
Chances: Amcor launches high-barrier performance paper packaging in North America, indicating growth opportunities. The company reported fiscal 2023 results and provided an outlook for fiscal 2024, which may attract investors. Amcor announces intent to acquire Moda Systems, showcasing expansion strategies. Amcor becomes the first flexible packaging company to offer certified-circular plastics in Australia and New Zealand, demonstrating sustainability efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs signs a tentative labor agreement with USW, potentially stabilizing labor relations. U.S. Steel explores strategic alternatives amid acquisition proposals, indicating potential growth opportunities. Steelworkers&amp;rsquo; support for Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;rsquo; bid for U.S. Steel could tip the scales in favor of the acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kim/</guid>
      <description>score:-34
Chances: Kimco Realty to acquire RPT Realty in a $2 billion all-stock transaction, which can bolster growth prospects. Kimco expands its portfolio with the acquisition of Stonebridge at Potomac Town Center, further strengthening its assets. Strong leasing demand from grocers and positive Q2 results demonstrate Kimco Realty&amp;rsquo;s potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EQT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eqt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: EQT Corporation recently completed the acquisition of Tug Hill and XcL Midstream, which could potentially enhance its operational capabilities and revenue streams. The company&amp;rsquo;s acquisition received approval from the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC), allowing it to proceed without regulatory hurdles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Newmont Corporation is proceeding with its acquisition of Newcrest, having received regulatory clearances from Australia and Korea, which could open up new growth opportunities. The company is operating in the gold mining industry, which tends to perform well during economic uncertainties, making it an attractive investment option for investors seeking a safe haven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Permian Resources announced a $500.0 million private placement of senior notes due in 2032, indicating its ability to raise capital. The company is set to acquire Earthstone Energy in an all-stock transaction, creating a $14 billion premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P, which may lead to growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enb/</guid>
      <description>score:103
Chances: Enbridge recently closed a significant common equity offering, raising CDN$4.6 billion, which could provide additional financial resources for the company&amp;rsquo;s growth plans. The acquisition of natural gas utilities from Dominion Energy for $14 billion is expected to bolster Enbridge&amp;rsquo;s position in the energy sector and contribute to its high-yielding payout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Charles Schwab experienced a successful weekend, converting TD Ameritrade clients and advisors, potentially leading to increased assets under management. Bond investors are showing confidence in Schwab after its cost-cutting measures, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health. Schwab&amp;rsquo;s trader survey indicates that recession fears are receding, suggesting positive sentiment among traders and investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:-47
Chances: Energy Transfer LP has shown market leadership with a jump to an 82 RS (Relative Strength) rating. The acquisition of Crestwood Equity Partners in a $7.1 billion deal could potentially boost ET&amp;rsquo;s payout. Investors are attracted to Energy Transfer LP, which offers a 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Danaher (DHR) to Acquire Abcam, Boost Life Sciences Unit Danaher Buys Abcam for $5.7 Billion to Expand Its Product Offerings Here’s Why Abcam plc (ABCM) Outperformed in Q2 Abcam Highlights Successful Execution of Strategic Priorities to Drive Shareholder Value NanoString and Abcam Expand Collaboration to Advance Spatial Multiomics Research Risks: Abcam shares fall after $5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tpr/</guid>
      <description>score:-55
Chances: Tapestry&amp;rsquo;s strong portfolio consisting of Coach, Kate Spade, and Stuart Weitzman brands. Positive earnings surprise history and favorable ingredients for potential quarterly beat. Risks: Integration challenges and execution risks associated with the acquisition of Capri Holdings. Mixed response from Wall Street and the industry to the acquisition deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDCE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdce/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Chevron&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PDC Energy and the approval from shareholders could bolster Chevron&amp;rsquo;s U.S. oil and gas operations, potentially leading to increased operational efficiency and growth opportunities. Despite the all-stock transaction and expected transitional leadership changes, the successful closure of the deal between Chevron and PDC Energy may result in a strengthened combined entity with enhanced market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UNVR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</guid>
      <description>score:1087
Chances: Univar Solutions has completed an acquisition by Apollo Funds, maintaining its global presence under the Univar Solutions name and brand. The company has expanded its distribution relationship with Kalsec Inc. for hop ingredients in the United States, enhancing its specialty ingredient offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CPB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpb/</guid>
      <description>score:910
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao’s pasta sauce and noosa yogurt, aims for strategic growth and expansion. The acquisition of Sovos Brands for $2.7 billion demonstrates Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing its grocery business. Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s deal with Sovos Brands offers a premium to shareholders and has positively impacted its stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SOVO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sovo/</guid>
      <description>score:877
Chances: Campbell Soup&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Sovos Brands, including Rao&amp;rsquo;s pasta sauces and noosa yogurt, aligns with its strategy to strengthen its grocery business. The $2.7 billion deal for Sovos Brands presents a growth opportunity for Campbell Soup to expand its presence in frozen meals and premium pasta sauce markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BKI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bki/</guid>
      <description>score:1173
Chances: Black Knight&amp;rsquo;s Data &amp;amp; Analytics division releases August 2023 Mortgage Monitor Report highlighting the heating housing market and rising home prices. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) dismisses federal court case against Intercontinental Exchange&amp;rsquo;s proposed acquisition of Black Knight, clearing the regulatory path for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
