<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:32:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0871 HL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hl/</guid>
      <description>score:871
Chances: Hecla Mining&amp;rsquo;s silver production for the second quarter of 2023 is on track to reach 3.8 million ounces, contributing to a total target of 17 million ounces for the year. The acquisition of ATAC Resources Ltd. and the investment in Cascadia Minerals Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1037 NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:1037
Chances: Newmont Corporation receives PNG Competition Commission clearance for the acquisition of Newcrest, indicating positive progress in their growth strategy. Investing in Newmont Corporation along with other industry-leading stocks can result in a dividend yield of 3.5%, providing potential returns for income investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1104 MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1104
Chances: Monster Beverage reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1 percent to $1.85 billion, which could positively impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. Gains from strong brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions may contribute to Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s future growth. The completion of the acquisition of Bang Energy and its beverages could open new opportunities and expand Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UNVR | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</guid>
      <description>Chances: Univar Solutions Inc. completed the acquisition by Apollo Funds, including a minority investment from the Abu Dhabi Investment Authority, which may strengthen the company&amp;rsquo;s position and global presence. Univar Solutions announced expanded distribution relationships with Kalsec® Inc. and Leprino Foods Company, which could lead to increased revenue and market opportunities in the specialty ingredients and chemicals sector.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
