<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:02:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. signs agreement to acquire assets of a distributor of storm drainage products, indicating potential for expansion and growth in their offerings. Shares of Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. have more than doubled, up 107% this year, showcasing strong performance and investor interest in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has entered into an agreement to acquire a worldwide license to Precision BioSciences, Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Azercabtagene Zapreleucel (azer-cel), an allogeneic CD19 CAR T cell therapy program for autoimmune diseases. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:169
Chances: ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s solid earnings estimate revisions and Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) designation indicate growing optimism about its earnings prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s pipeline of antibody-drug conjugates, including Mirvetuximab Soravtansine, IMGN632, IMGC936, and IMGN151, shows potential for improving outcomes for cancer patients. Recent inducement grants and findings from Phase 1b/2 studies demonstrate ongoing progress and development within the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:152
Chances: Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s gene therapy for the treatment of a rare inherited bleeding disorder has been approved in Canada and is pending approval in the U.S., indicating potential positive developments in the company&amp;rsquo;s product pipeline. Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Seagen Inc. for $43 billion and its full-year 2024 revenue guidance suggest potential growth opportunities for the company in the coming years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: The acquisition by Clearlake Capital and Insight Partners could bring in new strategic direction and investment to help Alteryx regain market share. The premium of 29.1% from Alteryx’s last closing share price indicates investor confidence in the deal. Risks: Fierce competition from big rivals like Microsoft and Oracle could continue to impact Alteryx’s market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Masonite&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PGT Innovations creates a leading door and window solutions company with over $4 billion in combined revenue, indicating potential for growth and expansion in the industry. Products from PGT&amp;rsquo;s brands were used in every home featured on a popular HGTV show, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s strong presence and market influence in the fenestration industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: The acquisition of Abcam by Danaher for $5.7 billion presents an opportunity for Danaher to expand its Life Sciences portfolio and accelerate the drug discovery process The completion of the acquisition despite initial opposition from Abcam&amp;rsquo;s founder demonstrates the determination of Danaher to enhance its product and service offerings Abcam shareholders&amp;rsquo; approval of the acquisition indicates confidence in the potential synergies and benefits of the deal Risks: There might be integration challenges and cultural differences between Danaher and Abcam, which could impact the success of the acquisition The valuation of $24 per share for Abcam could be considered high, and if the expected synergies do not materialize, it may result in financial losses for Danaher Unforeseen regulatory or market challenges could affect the planned expansion of Danaher&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences portfolio Score:41 chances characters count - risks characters count = -959</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cere/</guid>
      <description>score:197
Chances: AbbVie&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Cerevel Therapeutics for $8.7 billion indicates a significant growth opportunity in the neuroscience sector Cerevel Therapeutics has a robust pipeline of multiple clinical-stage and preclinical candidates with potential across several diseases like schizophrenia, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease, and mood disorders Risks: The success of Cerevel Therapeutics&amp;rsquo; product candidates such as CVL-231, Darigabat, Tavapadon, CVL-871, and CVL-936 is not guaranteed Score:197 chances characters count - risks characters count = -803</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
