<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DOOR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/door/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/door/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: The acquisition by Owens Corning presents a new growth platform for Masonite, indicating potential for increased market share and expansion opportunities. The termination of the merger agreement with PGTI and the acceptance of a deal termination fee suggest that Masonite is focused on maximizing shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:135
Chances: ImmunoGen has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months,ImmunoGen (IMGN) might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects ImmunoGen Announces Inducement Grants Under Nasdaq Listing Rule 5635(c)(4) Risks: AbbVie Inc. announced its plans to acquire ImmunoGen in an all-cash transaction valued at roughly $10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Alteryx&amp;rsquo;s fair value estimate is US$56.24, indicating potential for upside. Appointment of Kevin Rubin as Interim CEO could bring positive changes to the company. Risks: Fierce competition from bigger rivals such as Microsoft and Oracle may pose a challenge. Setbacks in winning new business have suppressed Alteryx&amp;rsquo;s valuation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KIM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kim/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kim/</guid>
      <description>score:179
Chances: Kimco Realty Corp continues to expand its portfolio with the acquisition of RPT Realty, adding 56 open-air shopping centers The company received the top score of 100 on the Human Rights Campaign Foundation&amp;rsquo;s Corporate Equality Index, demonstrating its commitment to diversity and inclusion Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales have shown a positive shift in the retail sector, which may benefit Kimco Realty Corp Risks: Elevated inflation and soaring borrowing costs may impact the retail sector, including Kimco Realty Corp The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend performance and sustainability need to be closely monitored, especially in the current economic environment Score:179 chances characters count - risks characters count = 179</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: U.S. Steel Corp. has the potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Nippon Steel Corp. made an aggressive all-cash offer for United States Steel Corp., indicating potential for a high acquisition price. Risks: The acquisition bid from Nippon Steel Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has entered into an agreement to acquire a worldwide license to Precision BioSciences, Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Azercabtagene Zapreleucel (azer-cel), an allogeneic CD19 CAR T cell therapy program for autoimmune diseases. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pgti/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Masonite&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of PGT Innovations creates a leading door and window solutions company with over $4 billion in combined revenue, indicating potential for growth and expansion in the industry. Products from PGT&amp;rsquo;s brands were used in every home featured on a popular HGTV show, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s strong presence and market influence in the fenestration industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: The acquisition of Abcam by Danaher for $5.7 billion presents an opportunity for Danaher to expand its Life Sciences portfolio and accelerate the drug discovery process The completion of the acquisition despite initial opposition from Abcam&amp;rsquo;s founder demonstrates the determination of Danaher to enhance its product and service offerings Abcam shareholders&amp;rsquo; approval of the acquisition indicates confidence in the potential synergies and benefits of the deal Risks: There might be integration challenges and cultural differences between Danaher and Abcam, which could impact the success of the acquisition The valuation of $24 per share for Abcam could be considered high, and if the expected synergies do not materialize, it may result in financial losses for Danaher Unforeseen regulatory or market challenges could affect the planned expansion of Danaher&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences portfolio Score:41 chances characters count - risks characters count = -959</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cere/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cere/</guid>
      <description>score:197
Chances: AbbVie&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Cerevel Therapeutics for $8.7 billion indicates a significant growth opportunity in the neuroscience sector Cerevel Therapeutics has a robust pipeline of multiple clinical-stage and preclinical candidates with potential across several diseases like schizophrenia, Parkinson&amp;rsquo;s disease, and mood disorders Risks: The success of Cerevel Therapeutics&amp;rsquo; product candidates such as CVL-231, Darigabat, Tavapadon, CVL-871, and CVL-936 is not guaranteed Score:197 chances characters count - risks characters count = -803</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
