<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>US on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in US on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US inflation may be moderating, but China&#39;s is even slower</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-inflation-may-be-moderating-but-chinas-is-even-slower/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-inflation-may-be-moderating-but-chinas-is-even-slower/</guid>
      <description>US Inflation May Be Moderating, but China&amp;rsquo;s Is Even Slower US inflation is likely to slow down in a key report due on Tuesday, but it is still expected to be too high for the Federal Reserve. China&amp;rsquo;s inflation is even slower than the US, at 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: US-China Relations Stay Distant Despite Talks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</guid>
      <description>US-China Relations Remain Distant Despite Talks on Supply Chains The United States and China held high-level talks on supply chain issues on June 3, but the two sides remain divided on a number of issues, including technology transfer and intellectual property rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Says US Allies Can Have Productive Ties With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Minister Richard Marles has said that US allies can have productive ties with China, even as they maintain a longstanding defense alliance with the US.
Marles said that navigating the two relationships is complex and requires discussion, but he believes it is possible to have both a productive relationship with China and a strong defense alliance with the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top US Treasury Official Meets China Ambassador as Contacts Grow</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:24:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</guid>
      <description>US Treasury Official Meets with China&amp;rsquo;s Ambassador Top US Treasury official Janet Yellen met with China&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to the United States Qin Gang on Tuesday. The meeting comes as the two countries have been engaged in a number of disputes, including over trade, Taiwan, and human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The US-Led World Order Faces a New Challenge</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-us-led-world-order-faces-a-new-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:58:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-us-led-world-order-faces-a-new-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The US-led world order is facing a new challenge from the BRICS bloc, which is made up of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa. These countries are all emerging economies with large populations and growing economic clout. They are seeking to challenge the dominance of the US and the European Union in the global economy and geopolitics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BRICS Ministers to Challenge US With More Members, Common Currency</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brics-ministers-to-challenge-us-with-more-members-common-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brics-ministers-to-challenge-us-with-more-members-common-currency/</guid>
      <description>BRICS Ministers to Challenge US With More Members, Common Currency The BRICS bloc of emerging economies is looking to expand and create a common currency in a challenge to the US-led global order.
The bloc&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministers met in Cape Town on Wednesday to discuss the expansion of the group, which currently consists of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
