<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. is a health care company engaged in the provision of health solutions through prescription medicines, vaccines, biologic therapies, animal health, and consumer care products. The company operates in segments including Pharmaceutical, Animal Health, and Other, indicating diversified revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: Energy Transfer LP (ET) has shown consistent growth and an increase in quarterly cash distribution, indicating a positive outlook for potential returns. The company&amp;rsquo;s diverse segments, including natural gas transportation, crude oil transportation, and midstream operations, provide a strong foundation for stable revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s recent trading performance shows a positive movement, indicating potential for growth. Dividend-paying companies with strong fundamentals and dividend growth history, like Coca-Cola, are expected to gain traction among investors. Risks: The company may face competition in the beverage industry, affecting its market share and profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Businesses&amp;rsquo; and consumers&amp;rsquo; access to AI — without having to go through the cloud — is about to change, says HP CEO Enrique Lores. The advent of AI-powered PCs has the focus of many on Wall Street as the AI race enters its second lap in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
