<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:1031
Chances: Ambev&amp;rsquo;s stock performance is compared to other companies like Beyond Meat and Carlsberg in terms of value. Investors are looking into dividend penny stocks, including Ambev, as potential investment options. Despite high inflation, there are opportunities for affordable stocks like Ambev that offer potential returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Energy Transfer reports strong performance in operations with record volumes, including NGL exports. Ares Capital offers a high dividend yield of nearly 9.7%, attracting investors seeking income. Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s expanded operations in the Permian Basin and strong export volumes likely benefit Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:1071
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson is allowing shareholders to swap for shares of Kenvue, which has brands like Tylenol, at a discount. Dividend stocks like Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (JNJ) are considered a stable investment option, especially for risk-averse investors. Boasting brands like Band-Aid and Benadryl, Kenvue has become the largest pure-play consumer health company, offering potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
