<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:27:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:99
Chances: Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest lodging real estate investment trust, which could indicate its market influence and stability. Continued recovery in leisure demand and business transient demand might benefit HST&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings. The company&amp;rsquo;s active involvement in the lodging real estate sector positions it to benefit from the rebound in the travel and hospitality industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Devon Energy&amp;rsquo;s potential rebound in dividend suggests positive outlook for income generation, making it an attractive option for dividend-focused investors. The formation of NDB Midstream LLC through a strategic partnership between WaterBridge NDB and Devon Energy highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s innovation and potential growth in the oil and gas sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: Barclays PLC is a well-established financial institution with a global presence, indicating stability and experience in the industry. The company has announced strategic appointments and changes in its investment banking and sustainable finance divisions, showing efforts to adapt to market trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dependable dividend payer makes it attractive to income-focused investors seeking stable income over time. Strong financial performance, including robust revenue growth and consecutive dividend increases, adds confidence to Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s investment potential. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s resilience and innovation are highlighted, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to thrive and adapt in changing market conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xom/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: Exxon Mobil Corporation (XOM) experienced a gain of 2.3% in mid-afternoon trading due to higher oil prices, contributing to positive investor sentiment. An in-depth evaluation of Exxon Mobil&amp;rsquo;s valuation, financial strength, profitability, and growth could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:-78
Chances: Verizon Communications Inc. (VZ) is a high-yield dividend stock that can appeal to income-seeking investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnership with the Washington Commanders and being named the &amp;lsquo;Official 5G Network&amp;rsquo; suggests a focus on expanding its technology solutions. Verizon&amp;rsquo;s efforts to restore network coverage in West Maui after recent wildfires showcases its commitment to providing reliable services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:158
Chances: ITUB being mentioned in various Zacks articles and industry outlook pieces suggests ongoing interest and coverage, potentially indicating its significance in the banking sector. Positive mentions in relation to being a better value option and benefiting from higher interest rates could indicate favorable conditions for ITUB&amp;rsquo;s stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
