<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1222 MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1222
Chances: Manulife Investment Management has announced new leadership appointments on its real estate investment team, which could lead to a stronger global real estate investment strategy and portfolio growth. Investing in dividend-paying stocks like Manulife Financial may provide steady returns amid market volatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1073 KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:1073
Chances: Coca-Cola is known for its reliable long-term gains, making it a potential positive return investment. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment in Coca-Cola indicates it could be a good long-term investment based on his successful track record. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s decision to discontinue underperforming brands in its portfolio demonstrates the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to strategic optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1037 NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:1037
Chances: Newmont Corporation receives PNG Competition Commission clearance for the acquisition of Newcrest, indicating positive progress in their growth strategy. Investing in Newmont Corporation along with other industry-leading stocks can result in a dividend yield of 3.5%, providing potential returns for income investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1043 CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s top stocks often make for good long-term investments, and Chevron is one of his holdings. Oil prices have quietly rallied over the past month, which could benefit Chevron and the energy sector. Chevron and Chevron U.S.A. Inc. announced an exchange offer for Senior Notes, indicating potential financial opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0984 ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:984
Chances: Ambev&amp;rsquo;s stock has been compared to other stocks like Diageo (DEO) and Carlsberg A/S (CABGY) in terms of value options, suggesting potential opportunities for investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance has been discussed in comparison to other stocks like Beyond Meat (BYND), indicating its relative position in the sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1034 AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:1034
Chances: The worst appears to be over for AGNC Investment as the Federal Reserve hiked interest rates, which may make it a worthy buy. AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s commitment to repositioning its portfolio in the current volatile interest rate scenario may optimize its performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0977 ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:977
Chances: Energy Transfer had strong performance from its operations, delivering record volumes across its segments, which may be positively received by investors. The company offers a prodigious income stream, and its monster distribution significantly exceeded reported net income, which could attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1174 BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:1174
Chances: Amazon.com will launch a credit card offering in Brazil in partnership with Banco Bradesco SA, expanding the bank&amp;rsquo;s fintech offering. Banco Bradesco expects bankrupt retailer Americanas SA and its lenders to reach a reasonable deal on debts, potentially resolving a financial issue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
