<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ctra/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Coterra Energy reports positive second-quarter 2023 results and announces a quarterly dividend. Goldman Sachs likes Coterra Energy as a top dividend stock yielding as high as 10%. Coterra Energy investors have seen a respectable 75% return over the last three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: B2Gold declared a dividend of $0.04 per share for the third quarter of 2023, which may attract income-oriented investors. Strong Q2 2023 operating results and lower costs position B2Gold well to achieve its 2023 annual guidance. B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s updated mineral resource estimate for the Anaconda Area in Mali indicates growth potential for the company&amp;rsquo;s operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: An intrinsic calculation suggests that Occidental Petroleum Corporation (OXY) is potentially undervalued by 32%, which could present a buying opportunity for investors. Occidental Petroleum offers dividends, making it an attractive option for income-focused investors. The company is making acquisitions and investments, such as the acquisition of Carbon Engineering, indicating a strategic focus on growth and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:-94
Chances: AGNC Investment Corp. has outperformed the stock market, indicating positive investor sentiment. Wall Street analysts view AGNC Investment as a good investment opportunity, suggesting potential growth. The company offers a high dividend yield, making it attractive for income-seeking investors. Risks: AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s stock performance has seen fluctuations, and it has dipped since the last earnings report, which may raise concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KHC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/khc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/khc/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Kraft Heinz is innovating and expanding its product lines, such as Oscar Mayer&amp;rsquo;s On-The-Go Refrigerated Breakfast and FUNdamental Textbooks. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment in Kraft Heinz suggests long-term stability and dividend potential. The company is participating in conferences like the 2023 Barclays Global Consumer Staples Conference, indicating an interest in investor engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Medical Properties Trust is actively working to pay down debt, which could strengthen its financial position in the long term. Investors looking for high-yield dividend stocks might find value in Medical Properties Trust, especially if it recovers. The company has updated its capital allocation strategy to enhance long-term value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: Verizon increases dividend for the 17th consecutive year, indicating a strong commitment to dividend payments. Verizon launches new technologies and connectivity solutions, potentially expanding its customer base. The company extends partnerships with the NFL and MetLife Stadium, showcasing a focus on sports and entertainment sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Bank of America is favored by institutional owners, with 58% ownership, indicating investor confidence. Higher interest rates have historically benefited Bank of America, which could lead to improved profitability. Bank of America is expanding its credit card cashback rewards, which may attract more customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cop/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: ConocoPhillips Proves Why A Gap Down In Price Is Not Always Bad ConocoPhillips expands full year production guidance with company-wide records ConocoPhillips (NYSE:COP) Looks Like A Good Stock, And It&amp;rsquo;s Going Ex-Dividend Soon Risks: ConocoPhillips Misses Earnings Expectations Despite Record Production ConocoPhillips misses on profit, hikes full-year output forecast ConocoPhillips (COP) Lags on Q2 Earnings, Ups &amp;lsquo;23 Output View Score:29 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dependable dividend payer makes it attractive to income-focused investors seeking stable income over time. Strong financial performance, including robust revenue growth and consecutive dividend increases, adds confidence to Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s investment potential. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s resilience and innovation are highlighted, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to thrive and adapt in changing market conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
