<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chinese stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/chinese-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chinese stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/chinese-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:101
Chances: RLX Technology to report unaudited financial results for the second quarter, indicating transparency and accountability. Positive market sentiment towards Chinese stocks&amp;rsquo; recovery and potential stimulus. Shares of RLX Technology showing upward movement. Notable performance metrics, such as best value and best performance in comparison to peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:1029
Chances: Discussion about the labor contract negotiations of Ford and General Motors, and their impact on related stocks. Coverage of shopping app Temu&amp;rsquo;s popularity and its implications for Amazon. Highlighting Chinese stocks worth watching or potentially buying, including PDD Holdings. Coverage of online sellers&amp;rsquo; legal battles and competition in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:981
Chances: TAL Education Group share price has gained 56% in the last period. TAL Education Group announces unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. TAL Education Group to release unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. Chinese hedge funds add TAL Education Group to their portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
