<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EU on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/eu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EU on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>China Lobbies EU Over Proposal to Punish Firms Supplying Russia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</guid>
      <description>China Lobbies EU Over Proposed Trade Restrictions China is lobbying the European Union to scrap proposed trade restrictions on Chinese companies that the bloc says are enabling Russia&amp;rsquo;s war machine in Ukraine.
The EU is considering sanctions on Chinese companies that provide Russia with semiconductors, telecommunications equipment, and other technologies that could be used for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU to Challenge Poland Over Law Aimed at Opposition Leader Tusk</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eu-to-challenge-poland-over-law-aimed-at-opposition-leader-tusk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:30:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eu-to-challenge-poland-over-law-aimed-at-opposition-leader-tusk/</guid>
      <description>The European Commission has challenged Poland at the European Court of Justice over a new law that could be used to target opposition leader Donald Tusk.
The law, which was passed by the Polish parliament last week, gives the government the power to strip former prime ministers of their immunity from prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simson Says EU Still in Talks on Renewables Deal (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/simson-says-eu-still-in-talks-on-renewables-deal-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:24:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/simson-says-eu-still-in-talks-on-renewables-deal-video/</guid>
      <description>The European Union is in talks with member states to increase the bloc&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy target to 40% by 2030. The current target is 32%.
The talks are being led by Energy Commissioner Kadri Simson. Simson said on Tuesday that she is confident that a deal can be reached.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
