<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>first amendment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/first-amendment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in first amendment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 21:24:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/first-amendment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Sues Montana Over State&#39;s Ban of Its Service</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-sues-montana-over-states-ban-of-its-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 21:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-sues-montana-over-states-ban-of-its-service/</guid>
      <description>TikTok Sues Montana Over State&amp;rsquo;s Ban of Its Service
TikTok has sued the state of Montana over a law that would ban the popular video-sharing app in the state. The law, which was signed by Montana Gov. Greg Gianforte on May 17, would take effect on January 1, 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Creators Sue Montana Over State&#39;s Ban of Platform</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-creators-sue-montana-over-states-ban-of-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-creators-sue-montana-over-states-ban-of-platform/</guid>
      <description>TikTok Creators Sue Montana Over State&amp;rsquo;s Ban of Platform A group of TikTok creators have filed a lawsuit against Montana&amp;rsquo;s attorney general, alleging that the state&amp;rsquo;s ban on the social media platform is unconstitutional and violates the First Amendment.
The lawsuit argues that the ban is an attempt to censor speech and that it is based on unfounded fears about TikTok&amp;rsquo;s security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Ban Signed in Montana, Paving Way for First Amendment Legal Battle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-ban-signed-in-montana-paving-way-for-first-amendment-legal-battle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tiktok-ban-signed-in-montana-paving-way-for-first-amendment-legal-battle/</guid>
      <description>Montana Bans TikTok, Setting Off First Amendment Legal Battle Montana became the first state in the U.S. to ban TikTok when Governor Greg Gianforte signed a bill into law on Wednesday afternoon. The law prohibits anyone in the state from downloading or using the app, and also applies to app stores that offer TikTok for download.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
