<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retail Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/retail-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retail Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/retail-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Chewy, Inc. announced strong Q2 2023 financial results, beating earnings and revenue estimates, which may attract investors. Chewy&amp;rsquo;s CEO mentioned that helping customers with ease drives loyalty to the brand, which could lead to sustained growth. Some Wall Street analysts believe that Chewy has significant growth potential, with projections of over 50% gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters (AEO) reported strong Q2 earnings and sales, exceeding Wall Street estimates, and raised its revenue forecast. The company has been upgraded to &amp;lsquo;Strong Buy&amp;rsquo;, indicating positive sentiment among analysts. AEO is showing signs of being a fast-paced momentum stock and may be considered a bargain investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Kohl&amp;rsquo;s beats profit estimates on cost cuts and leaner inventory. Earnings surpass estimates, maintains full-year guidance. Strategic efforts aiding growth in Kohl&amp;rsquo;s. Back-to-school shopping convenience and affordable prices. Positive takeaways from Q2 earnings call. Risks: Profits plunge more than 50% annually on weak sales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
