<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Healthcare on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/healthcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Healthcare on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:06:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ABT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abt/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Abbott Laboratories is expected to post stellar quarterly growth when they report Q4 results on January 24. The company is seeing favorable earnings estimate revision activity and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season. The strength of the Pharmacy &amp;amp; Consumer Wellness and Health Services segments is likely to reflect positively on CVS Health&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter 2023 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:72
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s spin-off of its consumer health division may lead to increased focus and growth in its pharmaceutical and medtech segments The addition of serious warnings for cancer therapies may lead to increased caution and monitoring for potential adverse effects, which could impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:93
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. continues to deliver positive news with the FDA approval of Keytruda for cervical cancer treatment. The Pharmaceutical segment of the company includes human health pharmaceutical and vaccine products, which positions it well in the current healthcare market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Kenvue Inc. is poised to benefit from the favorable court ruling in a product-liability case, which has resulted in a nearly 5% increase in the company&amp;rsquo;s stock price. The Self Care segment, including cough, cold and allergy, pain care, digestive health, and smoking cessation, presents a strong opportunity for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gdrx/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Shares of GoodRx (GDRX) popped after reporting upbeat preliminary fourth quarter and full year 2023 results. GoodRx unveiled preliminary fourth-quarter revenue that topped analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company has seen &amp;ldquo;great demand&amp;rdquo; for its products, indicating potential growth opportunities. Risks: The company operates in the highly competitive healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Clarivate Plc has been consistently releasing new reports and products, indicating a strong focus on innovation and meeting the evolving needs of the healthcare and research industries. Risks: The company operates in a highly competitive market, and its success depends on the adoption of its products and solutions by academia, government, life sciences, and healthcare organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hims/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hims/</guid>
      <description>score:108
Chances: Hims &amp;amp; Hers Health, Inc. unveiled Weight Loss by Hims &amp;amp; Hers, a comprehensive and customizable clinical approach specifically designed to help people achieve their individual weight-loss goals. The company has appointed Craig Primack, a pioneer in the field of clinical obesity medicine, as SVP of Weight Management, indicating a strong focus on addressing the growing issue of obesity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Organon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence shows a proactive approach to patient care and may lead to increased sales. The company&amp;rsquo;s exclusive distribution of Emgality and RAYVOW in Europe presents a significant opportunity for revenue growth in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/azn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/azn/</guid>
      <description>score:-135
Chances: AstraZeneca (AZN) closed at $65.95, indicating a +1.77% shift from the previous trading day. AstraZeneca (AZN) announces that it is buying vaccine company, Icosavax. The additional supply of RSV shot for infants by AstraZeneca and Sanofi indicates a positive outlook for meeting winter demand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
