<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA approval on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fda-approval/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FDA approval on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fda-approval/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/azn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/azn/</guid>
      <description>score:176
Chances: The FDA approval of AstraZeneca&amp;rsquo;s Fasenra for patients with severe asthma aged six to 11 years presents a strong opportunity for growth in this market segment. Despite investor backlash over high executive pay, AstraZeneca&amp;rsquo;s continued approval of new drugs and expansion of its product line indicates potential for future success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GERN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gern/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Geron Corporation&amp;rsquo;s pipeline candidate, imetelstat, received FDA Committee backing for the treatment of transfusion-dependent anemia in adult patients with low-to-intermediate-1 risk myelodysplastic syndromes, indicating potential for future market approval. Shares of Geron Corporation (GERN) soar after positive news from the FDA&amp;rsquo;s Oncologic Drugs Advisory Committee, showing investor optimism in the company&amp;rsquo;s potential drug approvals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:239
Chances: Bristol Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s Krazati, in combination with cetuximab, demonstrates clinically meaningful activity as a targeted treatment option for patients with previously treated KRASG12C-mutated colorectal cancer. Bristol Myers wins FDA approval for CAR T cell immunotherapy, Abecma, in earlier lines of treatment for patients with relapsed or refractory multiple myeloma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iova/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iova/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Iovance Biotherapeutics&amp;rsquo; revenue is set to grow, indicating potential for increased stock value. The FDA has lifted a partial clinical hold on Iovance&amp;rsquo;s mid-stage study, showing positive regulatory progress. Risks: Iovance Biotherapeutics reported a net loss of $116.4 million in Q4, reflecting financial risk and potential impact on stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GKOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Glaukos Corporation continues to benefit from a robust product portfolio and favorable clinical trial results. The FDA approval of Glaukos&amp;rsquo; iDose TR is likely to reshape glaucoma care, promising proactive and durable treatment. Risks: The insider transaction and sale of shares by the President &amp;amp; COO could raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
