<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Approval on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fda-approval/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FDA Approval on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fda-approval/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IOVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iova/</guid>
      <description>score:106
Chances: The U.S. health regulator has granted an accelerated approval for Iovance Biotherapeutics&amp;rsquo; cell therapy for advanced melanoma, making it the first such treatment for the deadliest form of skin cancer. The approval allows use in patients who have been previously treated with other therapies, but their cancer has spread to other parts of the body and cannot be removed with surgery, providing a significant market opportunity for Iovance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</guid>
      <description>score:152
Chances: ImmunityBio, Inc. continues to make significant progress in its clinical-stage immunotherapy treatments, with positive interim results from the QUILT 3.032 study of N-803 plus BCG in BCG-unresponsive non-muscle invasive bladder cancer (NMIBC) and timely completion of its Biologics License Application (BLA) resubmission for FDA review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GKOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Glaukos Corporation continues to benefit from a robust product portfolio and favorable clinical trial results. The FDA approval of Glaukos&amp;rsquo; iDose TR is likely to reshape glaucoma care, promising proactive and durable treatment. Risks: The insider transaction and sale of shares by the President &amp;amp; COO could raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
