<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FDA Approval on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/fda-approval/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FDA Approval on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:07:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/fda-approval/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:227
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. is a well-established company with a strong presence in the healthcare sector, offering a wide range of prescription medicines, vaccines, biologic therapies, and consumer care products. The company has a diversified business model with segments in pharmaceuticals, animal health, and other healthcare services, providing multiple revenue streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GKOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gkos/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Glaukos Corporation continues to benefit from a robust product portfolio and favorable clinical trial results. The FDA approval of Glaukos&amp;rsquo; iDose TR is likely to reshape glaucoma care, promising proactive and durable treatment. Risks: The insider transaction and sale of shares by the President &amp;amp; COO could raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: ImmunityBio, Inc. is participating in the 35th Annual Piper Sandler Healthcare Conference, which is a positive sign for potential collaborations and investor interest. The new data showing the potential benefits of Memory Cytokine-Enriched Natural Killer cells (M-ceNK) for patients with small cell lung cancer and other types of neuroendocrine tumors indicates promising developments in the company’s immunotherapy platform.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
