<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tech Layoffs 2023: Cut Workers Now Called &#39;Among Those Impacted&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-layoffs-2023-cut-workers-now-called-among-those-impacted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-layoffs-2023-cut-workers-now-called-among-those-impacted/</guid>
      <description>Tech Layoffs 2023 Tech companies have been laying off workers in 2023, with more than 147,000 jobs lost so far. The layoffs have been driven by a number of factors, including the economic slowdown, rising inflation, and the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Tech Giants Are Slowly Cutting Off Hong Kong Internet Users</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</guid>
      <description>In a move that could have a significant impact on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy and innovation ecosystem, American tech giants are slowly cutting off internet users in the city.
Google and OpenAI have not rolled out AI chatbots to Hong Kong, putting it alongside mainland China and North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech, an Early Booster of Remote Work, Wants People Back in the Office</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-an-early-booster-of-remote-work-wants-people-back-in-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-an-early-booster-of-remote-work-wants-people-back-in-the-office/</guid>
      <description>Tech Companies Reverse Course on Remote Work Many tech companies that were early adopters of remote work are now requiring their employees to return to the office. This reversal is creating tension for workers who have adjusted to the flexibility of working from home and have arranged their lives accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stocks: Are They Overvalued?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-stocks-are-they-overvalued/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-stocks-are-they-overvalued/</guid>
      <description>Tech stocks have been on a tear in recent years, with the Nasdaq Composite Index more than doubling in value since the start of 2019. However, there are some signs that the tech rally may be coming to an end. In recent weeks, tech stocks have started to decline, with the Nasdaq Composite Index down about 10% from its all-time high.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
