<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:06:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s solid-state battery cells have shown a lot of promise so far. Volkswagen is holding talks with France&amp;rsquo;s Blue Solutions about potentially adapting their solid-state battery design for cars. The company has a pretty big lead over others developing solid-state batteries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:132
Chances: Micron Technology has introduced industry&amp;rsquo;s first standard low-power compression attached memory module (LPCAMM2) which is likely to drive higher performance, energy-efficiency, and space savings. The company&amp;rsquo;s revenue and earnings growth rates are expected to sharply accelerate, leading to a significant jump in its stock value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:77
Chances: The advancements in artificial intelligence, particularly generative AI, have the potential to significantly impact various industries, including healthcare, finance, and technology. Leaders and top executives from prominent companies have expressed enthusiasm and belief in the transformative power of AI, indicating a positive trajectory for its development and adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: The global chip industry is showing signs of relief after a tough year, which could benefit Nokia&amp;rsquo;s operations. Nokia and Zayo achieving a new North American distance record for 800Gb/s transmission showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s technological advancements and potential for high-capacity network solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:105
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co. engages in the design, manufacture, and service of critical digital infrastructure technology that powers, cools, deploys, secures and maintains electronics that process, store and transmit data. The company offers power management products, thermal management products, integrated rack systems, modular solutions, and management systems for monitoring and controlling digital infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 09:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:55
Chances: Oracle Corp. has been recognized as a Leader in the cloud database management systems by Gartner, indicating strong positioning in the cloud market. The company continues to introduce new capabilities to its cloud enterprise performance management, showcasing a commitment to innovation and addressing customer needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: HPQ is well-positioned to benefit from the growing demand for personal computing and other access devices. The company&amp;rsquo;s division into HP Inc. and Hewlett Packard Enterprise has allowed for focused growth and strategic acquisitions. Risks: The potential merger of Hewlett Packard Enterprise with Juniper Networks could introduce integration challenges and uncertainties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Credo Technology Group Holding Ltd has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months. The company is an innovator in providing secure, high-speed connectivity solutions that deliver improved energy efficiency as data rates and bandwidth requirements increase. Risks: Notable insider transactions involving the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) may raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:423
Chances: UiPath is well positioned to have a phenomenal decade. UiPath and CrowdStrike will continue their 2023 success into the new year. UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Market catalysts and internal growth make it likely that these stocks will continue to rally in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
