<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:24:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bk/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: BNY Mellon launches an open banking payments solution, Bankify, indicating a move towards modern banking technology. BNY Mellon appoints Sinead Colton-Grant as Chief Investment Officer, showcasing strategic leadership changes. BNY Mellon joins the FedNow® Service, advancing the U.S. payment system, which could lead to new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: HP CEO discusses the potential impact of the AI boom on computers, hinting at future innovations. Miro and HP collaborate to accelerate collaboration and innovation, which may drive business growth. HP matches Q3 earnings estimates, indicating a degree of stability and meeting investor expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Meta is developing a new, more powerful AI system, indicating potential for technological advancement. Meta Platforms is poised for a trillion-dollar valuation next year, which suggests growth potential. Meta&amp;rsquo;s push into artificial intelligence could be a driving force behind its turnaround story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Alphabet is a leader in the tech industry with strong growth potential. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Invest has shown interest in unique AI growth stocks, which could benefit Alphabet. Google&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sundar Pichai, believes that AI could be a significant market, suggesting potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
