<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Unity Software Inc. has seen a surge in technological advancements and a strong finish to the year, indicating a positive outlook for the company. Artificial intelligence (AI) and metaverse scaling are opportunities for growth for Unity, as they play a pivotal role in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:423
Chances: UiPath is well positioned to have a phenomenal decade. UiPath and CrowdStrike will continue their 2023 success into the new year. UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Market catalysts and internal growth make it likely that these stocks will continue to rally in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: Nokia is actively managing its Cloud and Network Services (CNS) business group portfolio in order to invest in other strategic areas and enhance technology leadership. Nokia Technologies segment is expanding its patent licensing business and reintroducing the Nokia brand to smartphones through brand licensing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: Fortinet Inc provides a comprehensive suite of cybersecurity solutions catering to various businesses including enterprises, communication service providers, and small businesses. The company operates through multiple segments including Network Security, Infrastructure Security, Cloud Security, and Endpoint Protection, Internet of Things and Operational Technology, indicating a diversified product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
