<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:26:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to Allow South Korean, Taiwan Chip Makers to Keep Operations in China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. government has reversed its previous policy and will now allow South Korean and Taiwanese chipmakers to keep their operations in China. This is a major shift in policy, as the U.S. had previously discouraged chipmakers from investing in China due to concerns about China&amp;rsquo;s growing technological capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chatbot Was Designed to Help Prevent Eating Disorders. Then It Gave Dieting Tips.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chatbot-was-designed-to-help-prevent-eating-disorders.-then-it-gave-dieting-tips./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chatbot-was-designed-to-help-prevent-eating-disorders.-then-it-gave-dieting-tips./</guid>
      <description>Lily Chatbot Shut Down After Giving Dieting Tips A chatbot called Lily was designed to help prevent eating disorders by providing support and advice to users. Lily was created by the National Eating Disorders Association (NEDA) and was based on the experiences of people who had recovered from eating disorders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Regulator Says AI is Focus of Marquee Fintech Festival</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/singapore-regulator-says-ai-is-focus-of-marquee-fintech-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:12:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/singapore-regulator-says-ai-is-focus-of-marquee-fintech-festival/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence to be Key Focus of Singapore FinTech Festival The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has said that artificial intelligence (AI) will be a key focus of the upcoming Singapore FinTech Festival. The festival, which will be held from November 14-17, 2023, will bring together over 25,000 participants from over 150 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How AI Is Catapulting Nvidia Toward the $1 Trillion Club</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-ai-is-catapulting-nvidia-toward-the-1-trillion-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-ai-is-catapulting-nvidia-toward-the-1-trillion-club/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is a chipmaker that specializes in artificial intelligence (AI). The company&amp;rsquo;s chips are used in a wide range of applications, including self-driving cars, robotics, and medical imaging. Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s chips are becoming increasingly important as AI becomes more widely adopted.
The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price has surged in recent years, and it is now valued at over $700 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
