<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: Toast has continued to execute on its mandate to transform the restaurant industry with technology The business has continued to thrive, expanding its customer base, increasing sales, and paring its losses There are terrific buying opportunities in beaten-down growth stocks right now Risks: Toast has been beaten up since coming public The red flags can&amp;rsquo;t be ignored Bank of America downgrades fintech company PayPal and restaurant software developer Toast stocks from &amp;ldquo;Buy&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Neutral&amp;rdquo; Score:88 chances characters count - risks characters count = -912</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:132
Chances: Cisco Systems Inc. has reported strong earnings and is enjoying record-setting fiscal performance, indicating positive growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on secure, agile networks, end-to-end security, and optimized application experiences positions it well in the rapidly evolving technology industry. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s grant recipients and initiatives for inclusivity and transformational tech demonstrate a commitment to social impact and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:153
Chances: Roblox stock has cleared a buy point following a bullish Wall Street call. RBLX stock has been on a strong recent run, rising around 74%. Wells Fargo initiates coverage of the gaming platform Roblox (RBLX) with an &amp;ldquo;Overweight&amp;rdquo; rating on the stock and a price target of $49 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
