<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:182
Chances: Toast may turn the tide of a growth drop-off with cutting-edge digital solutions and a forward-thinking approach. As we prepare to ring in 2024, there is optimism that growth stocks could continue to rebound to greater highs next year. Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies that had difficulty accessing capital last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: Cisco Systems (CSCO) settled at $50.08, representing a -0.85% change from its previous close. Cisco recently announced a dividend of $0.39 per share, payable on 2024-01-24. The outlook for CSCO stock depends on trends for cloud computing, plus corporate and telecom networks amid the shift to remote work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RKLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</guid>
      <description>score:24
Chances: Rocket Lab USA shares have skyrocketed after winning a U.S. government contract worth up to $515 million, indicating strong growth potential for the company. The successful launch of its tenth Electron rocket and deployment of a satellite for a Japan-based Earth imaging company showcases Rocket Lab&amp;rsquo;s continued execution and technological capabilities in the space industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:251
Chances: Fortinet provides cybersecurity solutions to a variety of businesses, including enterprises, communication service providers, and small businesses, making it well-positioned for growth as cybersecurity becomes increasingly important Cloud security companies may be better positioned as corporate budgets tighten, indicating potential growth for Fortinet in the cloud security segment The cybersecurity industry is growing rapidly, implying a bright future for Fortinet and its solutions Risks: Cybersecurity stocks have underperformed in 2023, posing a risk to Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s performance Cyberattacks continue to grow each year, indicating the continuous need for cybersecurity solutions but also the potential for increased competition Score:251 chances characters count - risks characters count = 251</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:185
Chances: DISH Network Corp. and EchoStar Corp. have completed their merger, reuniting Charlie Ergen’s satellite empire once again. DISH&amp;rsquo;s newest subscription service, offering customers the latest Samsung Galaxy device on us, and a new Samsung Galaxy smartphone every year at no extra cost while enjoying unlimited talk, text and data EchoStar Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:423
Chances: UiPath is well positioned to have a phenomenal decade. UiPath and CrowdStrike will continue their 2023 success into the new year. UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Market catalysts and internal growth make it likely that these stocks will continue to rally in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
