<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NOK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nok/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nok/</guid>
      <description>score:344
Chances: Nokia&amp;rsquo;s disinvestment deal to offload its Device Management and Software Management business reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s strategic focus on key growth areas such as SaaS, 5G core, and Network as a Code. The acquisition of Device Management and Service Management Platform businesses by Lumine Group enhances Nokia&amp;rsquo;s software portfolio and allows Nokia to focus on investing in other strategic areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-75
Chances: A focus on its core business sets the company up for years of profitable growth. The e-commerce software provider is finally generating a profit. Shedding light on e-commerce giant Shopify&amp;rsquo;s lasting success and its rising appeal in today&amp;rsquo;s stock market. In an environment of low market interest rates, growth stocks, especially in the technology sector, tend to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Cisco Systems Inc. has announced its intent to acquire Isovalent, a leader in open source cloud native networking and security, to bolster its secure networking capabilities across public clouds. The outlook for CSCO stock depends on trends for cloud computing, plus corporate and telecom networks amid the shift to remote work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:131
Chances: UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Market catalysts and internal growth make it likely that these stocks will continue to rally in 2024. Each of these businesses experienced substantial year-over-year revenue growth. In this article, we discuss the 14 best automation stocks to buy now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: Investors are hoping for things to take a huge turn for the better. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. Toast completed its initial public offering (IPO) in September of 2021 and has since gone on to increase its number of clients, broaden its offerings across the industry, and lift revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: Fortinet Inc provides a comprehensive suite of cybersecurity solutions catering to various businesses including enterprises, communication service providers, and small businesses. The company operates through multiple segments including Network Security, Infrastructure Security, Cloud Security, and Endpoint Protection, Internet of Things and Operational Technology, indicating a diversified product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
