<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 09:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Schlumberger (SLB) has been receiving a Buy rating from the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), indicating positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts. The recent upward move in Schlumberger (SLB) stock price shows potential for further gains in the near future. De-risking the Welchau play in Austria may not just be a big step toward Austrian energy independence, it may also ease Europe&amp;rsquo;s $800 billion energy crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibm/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: IBM closed positively at $193.34, showing potential for growth in the near future. IBM has been paying close attention to by Zacks.com users, indicating investor interest in the stock. Risks: The company has undergone significant changes and may not be the same as it used to be, posing potential risks for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Pure Storage&amp;rsquo;s strong quarterly earnings and sales performance, including a double beat on earnings, indicate a positive outlook for the company&amp;rsquo;s future. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into the Puerto Rico and Central America market with Empresas Berríos demonstrates its ability to drive business growth and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:87
Chances: General Motors Co. is making significant investments in innovative technologies such as software-defined radar, indicating a strong potential for future growth and expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into the EV market with electric F-150 pickup sales doubling in February showcases a promising outlook for GM&amp;rsquo;s position in the electric vehicle industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WDC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wdc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wdc/</guid>
      <description>score:-121
Chances: Western Digital has made significant progress towards completing the separation of its flash memory and traditional hard-disk drive businesses. The company has named chief executives for the soon-to-be separated businesses, indicating a clear path forward. It has received recognition as one of the World’s Most Ethical Companies for 2024, which could positively impact investor sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uber/</guid>
      <description>score:103
Chances: Uber continues to strengthen its position in the ride-sharing and delivery market, with a strong focus on technology and innovation. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into the freight segment shows potential for growth in a new market and diversification of revenue streams. Partnerships with companies like Domino&amp;rsquo;s Pizza and potential testing of dynamic pricing and AI-enabled menu changes indicate an opportunity for increased revenue and market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/zm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/zm/</guid>
      <description>score:199
Chances: Zoom Video reported Q4 earnings and revenue that topped estimates amid strength in the enterprise market. Shares of video conferencing platform Zoom (NASDAQ:ZM) jumped 13.5% in the pre-market session after the company reported fourth-quarter results, with its revenue narrowly outperforming Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s estimates, though EPS beat by a more convincing margin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:121
Chances: Micron Technology, Inc. is experiencing a significant increase in demand for its memory and storage solutions, particularly with the incorporation of its high-performance LPDDR5X and UFS 4.0 into Samsung’s flagship Galaxy S24 series. The company has also started mass production of its HBM3E memory chips for Nvidia’s latest chip for artificial intelligence, which is expected to contribute to a boost in performance and reduce data center operating costs by consuming about 30% less power than competing offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cm/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: CIBC has provided growth financing to InsightRX, a software company leveraging quantitative pharmacology and AI to improve therapeutic decision-making, indicating the bank&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and investment in emerging technologies. The smaller-than-expected increase in US crude stockpiles has added to signs of a tightening physical market, which could positively impact the bank&amp;rsquo;s capital markets and direct financial services segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: PPL&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings are better than estimates and the company continues to make substantial investment to further strengthen its existing operations. Robust Capital Investment Plan and Dividend Growth Announced PPL&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$20.44 based on Dividend Discount Model Risks: PPL Corporation misses on earnings expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella has achieved significant growth for the company, with the stock rising over 1,200% during his tenure. The acquisition of Activision-Blizzard and major investments in AI show Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s Intelligent Cloud segment, including Azure and other cloud services, continues to drive growth and revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Z</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/z/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/z/</guid>
      <description>score:-104
Chances: Zillow Group, Inc. has launched Zillow Immerse, a new interactive way to explore home listings, which may attract more users to the platform. The company is introducing new features such as reporting renters&amp;rsquo; on-time payments to credit bureaus, potentially adding value to its rental marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMAT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amat/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: The semiconductor industry is booming, and Applied Materials is well-positioned to benefit from this growth.The company is undervalued on a DCF basis and has a predictable business.State-of-the-art toolset will bridge academic innovations and industry pathways to scale for semiconductors, microelectronics and other critical technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:22
Chances: Cisco Systems (CSCO) settling at $52.24, representing a -0.1% change from its previous close. Cisco, Microsoft Corp. and Samsung Electronics announced new meeting room solutions for enhanced collaboration experiences. Cisco released its 2024 Data Privacy Benchmark Study, highlighting growing privacy concerns and trust challenges with AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Businesses&amp;rsquo; and consumers&amp;rsquo; access to AI — without having to go through the cloud — is about to change, says HP CEO Enrique Lores. The advent of AI-powered PCs has the focus of many on Wall Street as the AI race enters its second lap in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:257
Chances: BlackBerry (BB) is introducing new initiatives like QNX Everywhere and QNX Sound, addressing the growing demand for skilled embedded systems developers and showcasing their commitment to innovation and growth. The collaboration with MIH Consortium and the deployment of the IVY platform for electric vehicle platform demonstrates BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s potential for expansion in the automotive industry, a promising opportunity for future revenue growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DELL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dell/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: PC sales rebounded in the fourth quarter of 2023 and are poised to increase this year AI integration into PCs will promise more personalized user experiences At least 40-50% of the PCs in the next three years will be AI-enabled Risks: Evidence is piling up that the near-term outlook for PC demand is deteriorating KeyBanc Capital Markets analyst lowered 2024 laptop PC unit forecast to 1% year-over-year growth from 3% Score:46 chances characters count - risks characters count = 46</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Credo Technology Group Holding Ltd has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past two months. The company is an innovator in providing secure, high-speed connectivity solutions that deliver improved energy efficiency as data rates and bandwidth requirements increase. Risks: Notable insider transactions involving the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) may raise concerns among investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
