<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Walmart&amp;rsquo;s expansion into artificial intelligence and drones shows a commitment to technological innovation and enhancing customer experience. The launch of new AI-powered tools and AR social commerce platform demonstrates Walmart&amp;rsquo;s proactive approach to staying ahead of industry trends. Partnership with Andy Cohen to &amp;lsquo;Save Your Resolutions&amp;rsquo; through Walmart+ program highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to engage and retain customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: Pure Storage Inc. is set to replace another company in the S&amp;amp;P MidCap 400 index, which could lead to increased visibility and potential investment from index funds. The company&amp;rsquo;s all-flash storage platform is being leveraged by Toss Bank in South Korea, indicating the adoption of Pure Storage&amp;rsquo;s technology by a fast-growing financial institution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:423
Chances: UiPath is well positioned to have a phenomenal decade. UiPath and CrowdStrike will continue their 2023 success into the new year. UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Market catalysts and internal growth make it likely that these stocks will continue to rally in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:-56
Chances: The Fed meeting spurred confidence in lower inflation and lower interest rates in 2024. Analysts are expecting solar stocks to rebound on increased solar panel installations in 2024. Risks: Solar industry growth in Europe has decelerated due to surplus inventories and reduced demand in crucial markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: The White House&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the first grant for semiconductor manufacturing in the U.S. is a positive catalyst for chip stocks. Analysts believe that Nvidia Corporation controls roughly 80% of the AI chip market, but its rivals, including Advanced Micro Devices Inc, are making significant efforts to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bb/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: BlackBerry&amp;rsquo;s decision to appoint a new CEO and streamline its operations indicates a potential for positive change and strategic restructuring. The partnership with ECARX Holdings Inc. and Black Sesame Technologies demonstrates a focus on expanding into the global mobility technology market, which could lead to new revenue opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
