<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Competition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Competition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:48:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 64.2% in NIO Inc. NIO Inc. might move higher on growing optimism about its earnings prospects Risks: Nio may undertake further job cuts after the company announced plans to cut 10% of its workforce last month Nio was pressured to slash prices, thinning its margins, in response to the price war that Tesla Inc ignited at the beginning of the year Score:-63 chances characters count - risks characters count = -1063</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Sea Ltd. operates in the Digital Entertainment, E-Commerce, and Digital Financial Services segments, providing a diverse range of online gaming, marketplace, and financial services. The company&amp;rsquo;s Shopee mobile app and websites connect buyers and sellers, offering a strong potential for growth in the e-commerce segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:177
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. operates in the power and sensing solutions industry, which is experiencing growth due to the electrification of the automotive industry. The company&amp;rsquo;s segments offer a wide range of semiconductor products that cater to various application functions, indicating a diverse product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KSS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kss/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: Shares of department store chain Kohl’s (NYSE:KSS) jumped 7.3% in the morning session after retail stocks soared in solidarity with Macy&amp;rsquo;s. Risks: The proposal from Arkhouse Management and Brigade Capital to take Macy&amp;rsquo;s private could indicate increased competition for Kohl&amp;rsquo;s in the department store space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: The FCC approval of the merger between Dish Network and EchoStar is a positive development for the company, easing debt worries and reuniting the telecom empire to tackle growing competition. Dish Network&amp;rsquo;s expansion beyond satellite TV into streaming TV and mobile telecom services shows potential for growth and competitive positioning in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
