<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Competition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Competition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 09:05:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: Costco has a reputation for being a good employer, with above-average wages and worker benefits. Amazon is on the cusp of surpassing Walmart as the world’s biggest retailer. The profitability of large-cap companies, including Walmart, is a key factor to consider when investing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RKLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 09:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rklb/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: Rocket Lab USA has secured a significant U.S. government contract worth up to $515 million, showcasing strong growth potential and increasing market presence. The successful launch of the tenth Electron rocket this year demonstrates Rocket Lab&amp;rsquo;s consistent execution and ability to meet its ambitious launch schedule, highlighting its competitive edge in the space economy race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ayx/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: The acquisition by Clearlake Capital and Insight Partners could bring in new strategic direction and investment to help Alteryx regain market share. The premium of 29.1% from Alteryx’s last closing share price indicates investor confidence in the deal. Risks: Fierce competition from big rivals like Microsoft and Oracle could continue to impact Alteryx’s market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
