<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Competition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Competition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:990
Chances: Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s recent appointment of Tim Stone as Chief Financial Officer is a positive move that could contribute to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial management and strategic direction. Riding Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s love for innovative tech businesses, Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s stock had soared in the past, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for growth and investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:1098
Chances: Sirius XM (SIRI) experienced improvement in average revenue per user in Q2 2023, despite declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM delivered earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, holding potential clues for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. The Liberty Media tracking stock, which includes Sirius XM, trades at a significant discount to the value of the company&amp;rsquo;s Live Nation Stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:1350
Chances: Disney CEO Bob Iger returned after a short retirement and expressed surprise at the problems discovered at the company, including challenges in the traditional television business and box office disappointments. Investors are eager to assess Disney&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings, focusing on theme park performance, broadcast partnerships for ESPN, and Bob Iger&amp;rsquo;s strategic plans for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s shares are well-positioned for a potential bullish market wave. Uber&amp;rsquo;s solid results and improved profitability could have positive implications for Lyft&amp;rsquo;s performance. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s upcoming second-quarter earnings report could provide insights into its financial performance and competitive positioning. Risks: Lyft faces pressure from the market&amp;rsquo;s reaction to its peer Uber&amp;rsquo;s mixed second-quarter report and profit-taking after a recent strong run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> APE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ape/</guid>
      <description>score:1000
Chances: AMC Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results are expected to benefit from robust Admissions, and Food and Beverage revenues. The ongoing success of the movie &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; at the box office could potentially have a lasting financial impact on companies in fashion, entertainment, and home decor industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Alphabet Inc.&amp;rsquo;s subsidiary Waymo and General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise are seeking approval to expand self-driving car services in San Francisco, presenting growth opportunities in the emerging autonomous vehicle industry. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s (GOOG) return-to-office tactic of offering employees discounts to hotels on the Google campus reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to transition back to in-person work and maintain a collaborative work environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Verizon offers exclusive bundle savings and special offer for NFL Sunday Ticket from YouTube and YouTubeTV. Verizon provides value through myPlan and +play, offering customers a limited-time offer for Netflix&amp;rsquo;s Premium Plan. Verizon and Nokia to showcase 5G innovations, highlighting the power of 5G through dynamic demonstrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:977
Chances: American Airlines explores new narrowbody jet order with Airbus and Boeing amid travel boom. American Airlines considering new jet order with Airbus and Boeing, indicating potential expansion. Over the last year, airlines have been exploring flight subscription models for travelers. American Airlines in talks with Boeing and Airbus for narrowbody aircraft needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery plans to add live sports to its streaming service Max, potentially launching with MLB playoffs in October. Paramount reported Q2 results beating estimates and announced a $1.62 billion deal with KKR for Simon &amp;amp; Schuster business. Barbie movie grossed $1 billion globally in just 17 days, marking a milestone for director Greta Gerwig and potential changes in film production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:759
Chances: Rivian Automotive is experiencing favorable earnings estimate revisions and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season. The International Energy Agency predicts a significant increase in electric vehicle sales, which could benefit companies like Rivian. Risks: Shares of Rivian, along with other EV hopefuls, fell in response to caution sparked by price cuts and competition in the electric vehicle market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:870
Chances: Lucid Group reaffirmed its production goals for the year, aiming to produce 10,000 vehicles. Lucid Air, the luxury electric vehicle by Lucid Group, won the 2023 World Luxury Car Award, highlighting its industry recognition. Several companies, including Lucid, are reporting quarterly results, providing insights into the automotive industry and economic conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TSLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsla/</guid>
      <description>score:932
Chances: Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Model Y SUV became the world&amp;rsquo;s best-selling car with 267,200 vehicles sold in the first three months of the year. Tesla plans to begin production at its Debrecan, Hungary plant in 2025 and its Munich plant in 2026. EV sales increased by 65% last year, indicating a growing market for electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:919
Chances: DraftKings&amp;rsquo; stock has nearly tripled from its December lows, driven by better-than-hoped financials, including a surprising profit last quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s revenue outlook for the second quarter has been hoisted for the second time in a row, indicating strong growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:935
Chances: Ford is adjusting its EV production targets and positioning itself as a long-term winner in the industry. Ford&amp;rsquo;s higher dividend yield of over 4.6% could make it an appealing dividend stock for investors. Ford beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue and earnings, showing strong performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Luminar&amp;rsquo;s announcement of new key executives joining the company suggests a potential positive impact on its leadership and strategic direction. Autonomous driving stocks are expected to experience significant growth over the next decade, indicating a potential market opportunity for Luminar. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading global automotive technology company may position it well to benefit from the growth in autonomous driving and AI advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Micron Technology is expanding its CXL ecosystem by offering sample availability of the Micron CZ120 memory expansion modules, which could contribute to revenue growth. The CZ120 modules&amp;rsquo; high capacities and memory read/write bandwidth could position Micron to meet the increasing demand for advanced memory solutions in data-intensive applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
