<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Turkey on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/turkey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Turkey on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:06:02 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/turkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Turkey State Lenders Return to Lira&#39;s Defense After Sharp Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:06:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</guid>
      <description>The Turkish lira recovered some ground on Thursday after the government intervened in the market to sell dollars. The lira had fallen to a record low against the US dollar on Wednesday, after the government suspended a program that allowed state lenders to sell dollars to support the currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&#39;s Win</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:56:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</guid>
      <description>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s Win Turkish banks are divided over the size of rate hikes that the central bank will need to implement after President Recep Tayyip Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s re-election victory.
Some banks believe that the central bank will need to raise rates by 500 basis points or more in order to curb inflation, which is currently running at 70%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Turkey&#39;s President Faces the Biggest Election Challenge in Years</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Presidential Election: Erdogan Faces His Biggest Challenge in Years
Incumbent Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan faces his biggest challenge in 20 years in Sunday’s runoff election against opposition candidate Kemal Kilicdaroglu. WSJ’s Jared Malsin explains why this is one of the world’s most important votes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
