<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Turkey on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/turkey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Turkey on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:59:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/turkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Blesses New Economy Team But Says Rates View Is Same</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/erdogan-blesses-new-economy-team-but-says-rates-view-is-same/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:59:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/erdogan-blesses-new-economy-team-but-says-rates-view-is-same/</guid>
      <description>Erdogan Appoints New Economy Team, But Says Rates View Remains the Same
Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan appointed a new central bank governor and other economic officials on Saturday, but he said his view on interest rates remains the same.
Erdogan has long argued that high interest rates cause inflation, and he has resisted calls from economists and investors to raise rates to combat rising prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Embrace Crypto Stablecoins Like Tether (USDT) as Lira Slides</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/turkish-embrace-crypto-stablecoins-like-tether-usdt-as-lira-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/turkish-embrace-crypto-stablecoins-like-tether-usdt-as-lira-slides/</guid>
      <description>Turkish Embrace Crypto Stablecoins Like Tether (USDT) as Lira Slides The Turkish lira has been in a state of decline for several years. In the past year, the lira has lost about 50% of its value against the U.S. dollar. This has led to a surge in demand for crypto stablecoins in Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&#39;s Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:10:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</guid>
      <description>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Economy
Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has appointed a new finance minister and central bank governor, signaling a shift in economic policy. The new finance minister, Mehmet Simsek, is a former investment banker who has pledged to restore confidence in the Turkish economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey State Lenders Return to Lira&#39;s Defense After Sharp Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:06:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</guid>
      <description>The Turkish lira recovered some ground on Thursday after the government intervened in the market to sell dollars. The lira had fallen to a record low against the US dollar on Wednesday, after the government suspended a program that allowed state lenders to sell dollars to support the currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&#39;s Win</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:56:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</guid>
      <description>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s Win Turkish banks are divided over the size of rate hikes that the central bank will need to implement after President Recep Tayyip Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s re-election victory.
Some banks believe that the central bank will need to raise rates by 500 basis points or more in order to curb inflation, which is currently running at 70%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Turkey&#39;s President Faces the Biggest Election Challenge in Years</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Presidential Election: Erdogan Faces His Biggest Challenge in Years
Incumbent Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan faces his biggest challenge in 20 years in Sunday’s runoff election against opposition candidate Kemal Kilicdaroglu. WSJ’s Jared Malsin explains why this is one of the world’s most important votes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
