<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:52:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: KE Holdings Inc. Announces Upsizing and Extension of Share Repurchase Program and a Special Cash Dividend KE Holdings Stock Sees Rising Market Leadership; Earns 83 RS Rating Beike Joined &amp;lsquo;1t.org&amp;rsquo; China Action Even though KE Holdings (NYSE:BEKE) has lost US$1.9b market cap in last 7 days, shareholders are still up 24% over 1 year Bears are Losing Control Over KE Holdings Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Implied Volatility Surging for Nu Holdings (NU) Stock Options This Unstoppable Fintech Keeps Crushing Analyst Estimates Nu Holdings Ltd. (NU) Surpasses Q2 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Buffett-Backed Nubank Bets on Mexico for ‘Pivotal’ Growth Wall Street Bulls Look Optimistic About Nu Holdings Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Schwab Q3 trader sentiment survey indicates improving outlook. Bond investors show confidence in Schwab after cost-cutting. Acquisitions to aid Schwab&amp;rsquo;s top line amid cost woes. Schwab&amp;rsquo;s asset growth slows down. Crypto exchange EDX Markets taps Anchorage as custody provider. Risks: Schwab caught up in banking selloff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/asx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/asx/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: ASE Technology Holding achieves the best overall performance on the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. ASE&amp;rsquo;s Bumping Factory in Kaohsiung, Taiwan inducted into the World Economic Forum’s Global Lighthouse Network. ASE announces advancements under the VIPack™ Platform. ASX reports positive Q2 2023 earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:49
Chances: Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s AI-fueled quarter marks the beginning of a new computing era. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s revised deal to obtain UK approval for Activision acquisition. Positive performance of AI stocks, with Nvidia earnings boosting the sector. Continued growth of major technology companies despite market challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: Bank of America may be a buy due to its upcoming dividend payout. Expansion of credit card cashback rewards and benefits for customers. Positive growth and gains in trading desks for Bank of America. Enhancements in credit card rewards for electric vehicle owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nio/</guid>
      <description>score:-51
Chances: Positive gains for NIO Inc. despite market performance. Announcement of strong vehicle deliveries for NIO in July 2023. Potential for NIO stock to accelerate higher due to positive news. Solid-state innovation defining a new era in EVs for NIO. Strategic equity investment from CYVN benefiting NIO Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QCOM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qcom/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s support for new iPhone models suggests improved chip volumes for the current quarter. Positive results from tech giants&amp;rsquo; quarterly reports despite some being muted. Formation of a new company by chipmakers, including Qualcomm, to develop RISC-V technology. Qualcomm&amp;rsquo;s daily gain and EPS performance raise questions about its valuation and potential for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAYW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hayw/</guid>
      <description>score:996
Chances: Hayward Holdings reported strong earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating positive performance and potential growth prospects. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pool and outdoor living technology aligns with evolving consumer preferences for outdoor leisure, potentially driving demand for its products.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
