<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>debt ceiling on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/debt-ceiling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in debt ceiling on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:00:13 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/debt-ceiling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Debt-Ceiling Debate Is a Farce, But Fiscal Policy Is a Fiasco</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-debt-ceiling-debate-is-a-farce-but-fiscal-policy-is-a-fiasco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 11:00:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-debt-ceiling-debate-is-a-farce-but-fiscal-policy-is-a-fiasco/</guid>
      <description>The debt ceiling is a self-imposed limit on the amount of money the US government can borrow. It has been raised 78 times since 1960, most recently in 2019. The current debt ceiling debate is a farce because it is clear that the US government will never default on its debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Ceiling Is Kevin McCarthy&#39;s Problem to Fix, Not Joe Biden&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-is-kevin-mccarthys-problem-to-fix-not-joe-bidens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:15:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-is-kevin-mccarthys-problem-to-fix-not-joe-bidens/</guid>
      <description>In recent weeks, the U.S. debt ceiling debate has been heating up, with Speaker Kevin McCarthy finding himself in a difficult position. The New York Times reports that McCarthy is facing a dilemma as he tries to navigate the competing interests of his Republican caucus and the Biden administration[^1].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quirky Federal Spending Speeds Up Debt-Ceiling Clash</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/quirky-federal-spending-speeds-up-debt-ceiling-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/quirky-federal-spending-speeds-up-debt-ceiling-clash/</guid>
      <description>Quirky Federal Spending Speeds Up Debt-Ceiling Clash A bigger-than-anticipated federal deficit has pushed up the deadline for dealing with the US debt ceiling from sometime in the third quarter to any day now, according to a recent article published on Bloomberg Opinion ^1^.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
