<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Stability on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-stability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Stability on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-stability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>COTY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coty/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Coty successfully completes refinancing of its revolving credit facility, signaling financial stability. Coty focuses on boosting its global presence and ups its FY23 view, indicating growth prospects. Marc Jacobs and Coty expand their license partnership to beauty, potentially driving brand sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: First Horizon has been recognized as one of the best-in-state employers and banks by Forbes, reflecting a positive company image. The company has received awards and designations, such as the Savings Excellence Award and Best Employers for Women, highlighting its commitment to excellence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Medical Properties Trust is actively working to pay down debt, which could strengthen its financial position in the long term. Investors looking for high-yield dividend stocks might find value in Medical Properties Trust, especially if it recovers. The company has updated its capital allocation strategy to enhance long-term value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
