<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:06:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AMAT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amat/</guid>
      <description>score:-135
Chances: The semiconductor market is expected to grow by double digits in 2024. A jump in semiconductor equipment spending could supercharge this company that&amp;rsquo;s trading at an attractive valuation today. Risks: The artificial intelligence (AI) trade is alive and kicking, but there are always risks associated with market fluctuations and technological advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:313
Chances: Shares of automation software company UiPath (NYSE:PATH) jumped 5.7% in the afternoon session as yields fell after the U.S. Treasury Department lowered the borrowing estimate for the first quarter of 2024. Deloitte and UiPath (NYSE: PATH) today announced an alliance expansion to accelerate the transformation of their clients&amp;rsquo; businesses through a new focus on bringing AI-powered Intelligent Automation solutions to SAP implementations and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
