<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) expected to approve construction of a €10 billion facility in Dresden, Germany. TSMC&amp;rsquo;s leading position as the world&amp;rsquo;s top contract chip manufacturer makes it an intriguing investment. Growing trend of artificial intelligence (AI) and TSMC&amp;rsquo;s involvement in chip production for AI applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:1021
Chances: Shares of AI software company C3.ai (NYSE: AI) experienced a 7% decline after analysts raised concerns about AI stocks being in a potential bubble. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s shift to a consumption-based business model for fiscal 2024 may help lower entry barriers for new customers and quickly strike deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s AI platform, launched in April, is gaining traction with over 100 organizations and talks with more than 300 additional companies. Palantir raised its annual revenue forecast and announced a $1 billion stock buyback plan, indicating confidence in its growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Micron Technology is expanding its CXL ecosystem by offering sample availability of the Micron CZ120 memory expansion modules, which could contribute to revenue growth. The CZ120 modules&amp;rsquo; high capacities and memory read/write bandwidth could position Micron to meet the increasing demand for advanced memory solutions in data-intensive applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
