<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:05:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-66
Chances: AppLovin (APP) has been a big mover in the stock market with higher-than-average trading volume, indicating strong investor interest. The latest trend in earnings estimate revisions might help the stock continue moving higher in the near term, suggesting potential for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: Meta Platforms is set to receive initial shipments of Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s new flagship artificial intelligence chip, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s AI capabilities and drive future growth. The reemergence of Facebook&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;poke&amp;rdquo; feature may attract a younger demographic, indicating potential for increased user engagement and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/soun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/soun/</guid>
      <description>score:177
Chances: SoundHound AI has reported substantial year-over-year gains with a record quarter, indicating a positive trajectory for the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s in-vehicle voice assistant using a large language model completely on the edge while running on the NVIDIA DRIVE platform is an innovative and promising development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: The market continues to hit highs, fueled by AI stocks, but is looking extended. A number of artificial intelligence-related stocks posted strong gains this week with potential entry opportunities. The robotics sector stands at the forefront of transformative growth, with certain stocks displaying the utmost potential for surefire success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:2215
Chances: Roblox (RBLX) reached $42.66 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.79% change compared to its last close. Roblox and Paycom could be poised for massive rebounds in 2024. This growth stock is giving developers artificial intelligence tools to optimize their creations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
