<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:03:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: HP CEO discusses the potential impact of the AI boom on computers, hinting at future innovations. Miro and HP collaborate to accelerate collaboration and innovation, which may drive business growth. HP matches Q3 earnings estimates, indicating a degree of stability and meeting investor expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: C3.ai is off to a strong start with significant traction across its business in Q1 2024. Ark Invest predicts that the AI industry will add $200 trillion to the economy by 2030, making AI stocks promising. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s Q1 loss was narrower than expected, and revenues rose year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Meta is developing a new, more powerful AI system, indicating potential for technological advancement. Meta Platforms is poised for a trillion-dollar valuation next year, which suggests growth potential. Meta&amp;rsquo;s push into artificial intelligence could be a driving force behind its turnaround story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/goog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/goog/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Alphabet is a leader in the tech industry with strong growth potential. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Invest has shown interest in unique AI growth stocks, which could benefit Alphabet. Google&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Sundar Pichai, believes that AI could be a significant market, suggesting potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: UiPath stock has joined an elite rank with a Composite Rating of over 95, indicating strong performance. UiPath shares surged as revenue increased significantly due to soaring demand for AI products. UiPath Automation Cloud™ achieved HITRUST Risk-based, 2-year Certification, demonstrating a high level of information protection assurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s AI software business is expected to be its fastest to reach $10 billion in revenue, indicating growth potential. Microsoft pledges copyright protection for Copilot users, which could boost its appeal to developers and software creators. Bill Gates&amp;rsquo; investment in Anheuser-Busch InBev could pay off, potentially benefiting Microsoft indirectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s expansion into artificial intelligence (AI) is seen as a growth opportunity, with AI software potential to be a $14 trillion market. Google CEO Sundar Pichai&amp;rsquo;s belief in the significance of AI technology presents potential for long-term growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Intel stock has experienced a significant surge in 2023, suggesting potential growth opportunities. Intel is betting on artificial intelligence (AI) beyond the cloud, which could drive future innovation and demand. Partnerships and agreements with companies like Tower Semiconductor and Synopsys may strengthen Intel&amp;rsquo;s position in the semiconductor market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: AMD is expanding its client base and powering next-gen technologies, such as Hitachi Astemo&amp;rsquo;s AI-based camera system. AMD&amp;rsquo;s graphics card market share has bounced back, indicating strength in its core business. The CEO of AMD states that the AI market is &amp;lsquo;skyrocketing,&amp;rsquo; suggesting potential growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the AI and semiconductor sectors positions it for potential growth. Partnerships with companies like Reliance and Tata in India could open up new markets and opportunities for NVIDIA. The AI and semiconductor industries are expected to continue growing, benefiting NVIDIA as a major player.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
