<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:07:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1116 TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor is the leading contract chip manufacturer in the world, making it an intriguing investment with its crucial position in the market. The demand for artificial intelligence (AI) and the potential for large language models (LLMs) to improve search capabilities could positively impact Taiwan Semiconductor&amp;rsquo;s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1100 UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:1100
Chances: Upstart has experienced an impressive rally, with its stock up more than 450% since May 1, driven by excitement over artificial intelligence, signs of an economic recovery, and a short squeeze. Upstart is a leader in alternative loan approval methods, utilizing AI to assess borrowers&amp;rsquo; creditworthiness and make unbiased opinions on loan default risks, making it a hot commodity associated with artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1209 AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:1209
Chances: C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s guidance for fiscal 2024 suggests that the shift in its business model from a subscription-based one to a consumption-based one is likely to work, which may attract investors looking for growth potential. The company made a strategic change to a pay-as-you-go model to reduce the entry barrier for new customers, leading to quicker deal closures and potential business growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1052 NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Artificial intelligence (AI) driving strong gains for the stock market is benefiting NVIDIA, leading to a whopping 209% gain for the year. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI leadership and strong earnings performance have contributed to the stock&amp;rsquo;s skyrocketing success. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI chip demand and potential for new growth phases thanks to AI technology indicate positive future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1179 PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:1179
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s strong prospects in the field of artificial intelligence could boost its stock in the commercial market. Palantir&amp;rsquo;s multi-year enterprise expansion with WesTrac Pty Ltd to deploy Foundry across core operations indicates potential growth opportunities. Analyst Stephen Guilfoyle&amp;rsquo;s positive view on Palantir&amp;rsquo;s stock and its surging AI spending could be favorable for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>Chances: Luminar Technologies has announced the addition of two new key executives, indicating potential growth and expansion of the company&amp;rsquo;s leadership team. Millionaire-maker growth stocks have seen significant appreciation this year, and Luminar Technologies, as a leading global automotive technology company, may have the potential to benefit from the ongoing bull market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>Chances: UiPath is on a roll with shares up more than 40% in 2023, driven by investors&amp;rsquo; enthusiasm for AI-related stocks. UiPath is showing improved profitability as it leans into artificial intelligence, which may contribute to its growth potential. As generative artificial intelligence platforms gain popularity, companies like UiPath may benefit from their disruptive capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DBX | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dbx/</guid>
      <description>Chances: Dropbox, Inc. reported financial results for its second quarter ended June 30, 2023, indicating a positive update on the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Dropbox and DocuSign have simplified business processes with their digital platforms, which could drive further growth and adoption of their services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
