<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geopolitical Risks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/geopolitical-risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Geopolitical Risks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:04:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/geopolitical-risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: RTX has an impressive earnings surprise history and currently possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategy makes sense, and 2024 could be a better year for this aerospace and defense company if the analyst&amp;rsquo;s projections hold true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YPF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: YPF SA is the biggest oil and gas producer in Argentina and is actively divesting aging oil fields to invest in shale push in the Vaca Muerta formation, showing a focus on long-term growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s Upstream, Gas and Power, and Downstream segments show a diversified business model, allowing it to capitalize on different aspects of the oil and gas industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ry/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: Royal Bank of Canada (RY) is a well-established financial institution with a strong presence in multiple segments including Personal and Commercial Banking, Wealth Management, Insurance, and Capital Markets. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion efforts, such as the proposed acquisition of HSBC Bank Canada and the RBC Training Ground program, indicate a commitment to growth and diversification.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
