<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>geopolitical risks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/geopolitical-risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in geopolitical risks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/geopolitical-risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:-98
Chances: Kinross Gold Corporation is benefiting from rising gold production due to higher grades and recoveries at its mining sites. The company&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates growth in production, which could lead to improved financial performance. Selected penny stocks, like Riot Platforms, have shown the potential for massive upside in the penny stock space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s declaration of a dividend raise after passing stress tests suggests the bank&amp;rsquo;s confidence and strong financial position. Special-purpose credit programs to address homeownership barriers could contribute to Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s growth and address customer needs. Mary Mack&amp;rsquo;s role in leading Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s post-scandal transformation adds to the bank&amp;rsquo;s credibility and potential for positive change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:183
Chances: Synopsys&amp;rsquo; positive Q3 earnings and announcement of a new CEO highlight the growing importance of chip design software, reflecting potential opportunities for Intel&amp;rsquo;s offerings. The demand for semiconductors is unprecedented due to the increasing prevalence of smart devices and the growing need for sophisticated chips to support AI applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Increase in revenues due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Operational and financial results in-line with expectations for Q2 2023. Positive outlook for penny stocks, including BTG.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
