<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:02:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:179
Chances: eBay stock gained in early trading Wednesday after the e-commerce company announced plans to lay off 9% of its staff. The job cuts should save eBay about $200 million a year, says one analyst, and &amp;lsquo;suggest business remains under pressure.&amp;rsquo; The company has a revenue-generating business model, but faces formidable competition from other global e-commerce retailers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:22
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s business segments including entertainment, ESPN, and parks, experiences, and products provide a diverse revenue stream. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into direct-to-consumer services and international markets presents growth opportunities. Potential for positive impact from new board members and shareholder activism. Risks: Cancellation of the planned merger with Sony Group Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:145
Chances: China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce landscape is still showing promising signs of growth and potential opportunities for investors. PDD Holdings has built a strong network of capabilities that support its underlying businesses, positioning it well for future growth in the digital economy. The introduction of new policies by Chinese e-commerce players may raise concerns, but there are still opportunities for growth and innovation in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
