<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:56:37 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Imran Khan Says Generals Want to Stop Him From Winning Election</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/imran-khan-says-generals-want-to-stop-him-from-winning-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:56:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/imran-khan-says-generals-want-to-stop-him-from-winning-election/</guid>
      <description>Imran Khan Accuses Generals of Trying to Stop Him from Winning Election Former Pakistani Prime Minister Imran Khan has accused the country&amp;rsquo;s generals of trying to stop him from winning the next election. Khan made the accusation in a speech to supporters on Friday, saying that the generals are &amp;ldquo;afraid&amp;rdquo; of him because he is a &amp;ldquo;threat&amp;rdquo; to their power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Is Swimming Against the Tide on Taxes, Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s Tax Hikes: Swimming Against the Tide
The UK is facing a cost of living crisis, with inflation at a 40-year high and energy prices soaring. Chancellor Rishi Sunak has been criticized for raising taxes, rather than cutting them, to help people cope with the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &#39;Economic Collapse&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:05:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &amp;lsquo;Economic Collapse&amp;rsquo; President Biden on Tuesday defended the recent debt deal, saying it was necessary to avoid an &amp;ldquo;economic collapse.&amp;rdquo;
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, which will allow the government to continue borrowing money to pay its bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt-Limit Deal With McCarthy Gives Biden 2024 Campaign Fodder</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-limit-deal-with-mccarthy-gives-biden-2024-campaign-fodder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:36:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-limit-deal-with-mccarthy-gives-biden-2024-campaign-fodder/</guid>
      <description>President Biden and House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) reached a deal on a debt-limit increase on Tuesday, averting a potential default on U.S. debt.
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, enough to cover the government&amp;rsquo;s borrowing needs through early December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Inquiry, Inheritance Tax, House Prices: The Readout</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:09:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</guid>
      <description>Key Issues in the UK News The UK news is dominated by a number of key issues in the coming weeks and months. These include:
The long-awaited public inquiry into the UK government&amp;rsquo;s handling of the Covid-19 pandemic. The government&amp;rsquo;s plans to raise the threshold at which people start to pay inheritance tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats, Don&#39;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</guid>
      <description>Democrats, Don&amp;rsquo;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle In 2011, Republicans held the debt ceiling hostage in an attempt to extract concessions from Democrats. The crisis caused significant economic damage, and it could have been avoided if Democrats had not caved to Republican demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Lawmakers Plan Impeachment Proceedings Against Ken Paxton</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/texas-lawmakers-plan-impeachment-proceedings-against-ken-paxton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/texas-lawmakers-plan-impeachment-proceedings-against-ken-paxton/</guid>
      <description>Texas Lawmakers Plan Impeachment Proceedings Against Ken Paxton
Texas lawmakers are planning to begin impeachment proceedings against Attorney General Ken Paxton. The articles of impeachment drafted against Paxton include conspiracy, dereliction of duty, misapplication of public resources, and unfitness for office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Turns His Attention to 2024 White House Race</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk has purchased Twitter, and many are wondering what this means for the 2024 election. Musk has said that he wants to make Twitter a more open and free platform for speech, but some experts worry that he could use the platform to give himself an unfair advantage in the race.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
