<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clinical Trials on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/clinical-trials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clinical Trials on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/clinical-trials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:77
Chances: TG Therapeutics stock saw a welcome improvement to its Relative Strength (RS) Rating on Thursday, rising from 87 to 93. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.8% in TG Therapeutics (TGTX). The positive trend in earnings estimate revisions might translate into an upside in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:-45
Chances: The successful results from the initial cohort of patients in the Phase 2 trial of batoclimab in patients with Graves&amp;rsquo; disease indicate a promising future for Roivant&amp;rsquo;s autoimmune disease treatments. The acquisition of Telavant by Roche for $7.1 billion reflects the value of RVT-3101, a potential therapy for inflammatory bowel disease, and showcases Roivant&amp;rsquo;s ability to generate significant returns through strategic partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/imgn/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: ImmunoGen has a strong pipeline of antibody-drug conjugates, which shows promising potential for improving cancer patient outcomes The acquisition by AbbVie for $10.1 billion indicates a positive outlook for ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s future prospects Recent presentations of findings from Phase 1b/2 studies demonstrate ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s commitment to advancing cancer treatments Risks: There may be integration and operational challenges as ImmunoGen becomes part of AbbVie&amp;rsquo;s portfolio The future success of ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s pipeline candidates is subject to clinical trial results and regulatory approvals The competitive landscape in the biotech industry poses potential challenges for ImmunoGen&amp;rsquo;s market positioning Score:32 chances characters count - risks characters count = -968</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
