<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clinical trials on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/clinical-trials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clinical trials on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/clinical-trials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. is engaged in the provision of health solutions through its prescription medicines, vaccines, biologic therapies, animal health, and consumer care productsThe company operates in Pharmaceutical, Animal Health, and Other segmentsIt has entered into a clinical trial collaboration agreement with LAVA Therapeutics NV for evaluation of its anti-PD-1 therapy Keytruda Risks: The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price might be vulnerable to the large stake held by institutionsUncertainty around the future of stock markets remains highThe Senate HELP committee is seeking testimony from the company Score:174 chances characters count - risks characters count = 174</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has entered into an agreement to acquire a worldwide license to Precision BioSciences, Inc.&amp;rsquo;s Azercabtagene Zapreleucel (azer-cel), an allogeneic CD19 CAR T cell therapy program for autoimmune diseases. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
