<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clinical trials on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/clinical-trials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clinical trials on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/clinical-trials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Roivant Sciences Ltd. has shown impressive financial growth, with a 118% increase in revenue in the third quarter of 2024. The completion of the sale of Telavant to Roche for $7.1B with an additional $150M in cash payable upon the completion of a near-term milestone shows strong financial achievements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</guid>
      <description>score:153
Chances: Recent publication of preclinical data in the online issue of Science, First Release indicating potential for managing HIV without antiretroviral treatment Phase 1 pilot study showing potential for reducing viral load in people living with HIV Completion of safety portions of clinical trial studying investigational cancer vaccine for participants with Lynch syndrome Risks: Need for further clinical trials to validate the potential of N-803 and natural killer cells for managing HIV Uncertainty around regulatory approval for commercialization efforts despite significant financial resources Score:153 chances characters count - risks characters count = 153</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cbay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cbay/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Gilead Sciences, Inc. has completed the acquisition of CymaBay Therapeutics, Inc. for $4.3 billion in total equity value, adding to its liver portfolio and aligning with its commitment to liver health. CymaBay’s lead product candidate, seladelpar, for the treatment of primary biliary cholangitis (PBC) including pruritus, has shown promising results in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:113
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has announced the presentation of data from the ULTIMATE I &amp;amp; II Phase 3 trials evaluating BRIUMVI® in patients with relapsing forms of multiple sclerosis, indicating potential positive outcomes from the trials. The company has reported strong financial results, with BRIUMVI U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SANA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sana/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Sana Biotechnology has successfully cleared IND for B-cell mediated autoimmune diseases with initial clinical data expected in 2024 Early data from ongoing ARDENT trial suggests the ability to dose safely, demonstrate the desired immune evasion profile, and early clinical efficacy Risks: Markets are awaiting the latest inflation numbers and the debate regarding soft vs hard landing is expected to persist on Wall Street High institutional ownership implies Sana Biotechnology&amp;rsquo;s stock price is sensitive to their decisions Score:46 chances characters count - risks characters count = 46</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
