<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:37:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1003 MWA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mwa/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Mueller Water Products achieved net sales of $326.6 million in the third quarter, which may indicate positive revenue performance. Mueller Water Products announced a quarterly dividend of 6.10 cents per share, which could attract income-focused investors. The stock increased significantly by 22% over a specific period, suggesting potential positive momentum in MWA&amp;rsquo;s stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1025 JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: The projected fair value for JD.com is US$63.64 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity, suggesting potential upside in the stock. JD.com plans to release its unaudited financial results for the three months and six months ended June 30, 2023, which could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1151 CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:1151
Chances: Coupang&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$25.12 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. E-commerce industry indicators, such as predictions of growth for Amazon and other players, suggest a potential bounce back for Coupang. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s stock saw a double-digit share price rise in the recent past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1139 AMCR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</guid>
      <description>score:1139
Chances: Amcor plc (AMCR) will announce its Full Year 2023 results after the US market closes on August 16, 2023. Amcor announced its latest Amcor Lift-Off winner, Greyparrot, a growth-stage start-up that will receive a $500,000 investment and access to Amcor&amp;rsquo;s world-class capabilities in sustainability and packaging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1074 RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:1074
Chances: Roblox is joining the Roblox Partner Program, which could amplify the company&amp;rsquo;s position in delivering impactful programs for brands on the global immersive platform. The metaverse is a growing trend, and Roblox is at the forefront of delivering immersive experiences across virtual platforms, which could open avenues for substantial gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR | Stock Analysis by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 05:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>Chances: Luminar Technologies has announced the addition of two new key executives, indicating potential growth and expansion of the company&amp;rsquo;s leadership team. Millionaire-maker growth stocks have seen significant appreciation this year, and Luminar Technologies, as a leading global automotive technology company, may have the potential to benefit from the ongoing bull market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
