<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/growth-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:06:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/growth-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-75
Chances: A focus on its core business sets the company up for years of profitable growth. The e-commerce software provider is finally generating a profit. Shedding light on e-commerce giant Shopify&amp;rsquo;s lasting success and its rising appeal in today&amp;rsquo;s stock market. In an environment of low market interest rates, growth stocks, especially in the technology sector, tend to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: Investors are hoping for things to take a huge turn for the better. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. Toast completed its initial public offering (IPO) in September of 2021 and has since gone on to increase its number of clients, broaden its offerings across the industry, and lift revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</guid>
      <description>score:115
Chances: Netflix (NFLX) stock has continued its robust rally off its mid-2022 lows. With Squid Game: The Challenge reality series leaning on the strength of its impressive Squid Game franchise and new plans for its video game business, it’s hard not to feel better about the company’s growth story moving into 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
