<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>semiconductor on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in semiconductor on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:07:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/semiconductor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1116 TSM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tsm/</guid>
      <description>score:1116
Chances: Taiwan Semiconductor is the leading contract chip manufacturer in the world, making it an intriguing investment with its crucial position in the market. The demand for artificial intelligence (AI) and the potential for large language models (LLMs) to improve search capabilities could positively impact Taiwan Semiconductor&amp;rsquo;s business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1006 MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:1006
Chances: Investors are looking to buy Marvell Technology stock as it is considered a relatively cheap AI stock, which could attract more investment. Marvell Technology is a top AI chip stock and a key player in the AI industry, which is experiencing a surge in stock values due to AI advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0969 INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:969
Chances: Intel still sees China as a great market for its chips, especially in emerging sectors such as 5G and electric vehicles, indicating growth potential. Semiconductor stocks, including Intel, have been performing well in 2023, despite the slowdown in chip demand in some markets, implying investor interest in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1052 NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Artificial intelligence (AI) driving strong gains for the stock market is benefiting NVIDIA, leading to a whopping 209% gain for the year. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI leadership and strong earnings performance have contributed to the stock&amp;rsquo;s skyrocketing success. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI chip demand and potential for new growth phases thanks to AI technology indicate positive future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1184 AMD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amd/</guid>
      <description>score:1184
Chances: AMD&amp;rsquo;s new MI300 AI chip set appears capable of competing with Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s hardware, signaling potential growth opportunities. AMD&amp;rsquo;s stock has shown a daily gain of 3.79% and has an Earnings Per Share (EPS) of 0.23, indicating the potential for higher returns in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
