<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Market Competition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Market Competition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: Fisker plans to significantly increase EV production in the fourth quarter, which could lead to higher revenues. Fisker is expanding its presence in Europe, opening up new markets and increasing its global reach. Fisker&amp;rsquo;s innovative and affordable electric vehicle, the Fisker Pear, is generating interest with its competitive pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CARR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/carr/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Carrier Global Corp (CARR) has been expanding its offerings and recently added new heat pumps to its HVAC products, indicating growth potential. The company reported strong Q2 2023 earnings, with revenues and earnings beating estimates, suggesting robust financial performance. Carrier Global is set to present at Morgan Stanley&amp;rsquo;s 11th Annual Laguna Conference, which may provide insights into its future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Shopify&amp;rsquo;s landmark deal with Amazon to integrate &amp;lsquo;Buy with Prime&amp;rsquo; is expected to boost its sales and market presence. The company has been consistently growing, and its stock has outperformed the broader market in recent times. Investors are showing strong interest in Shopify as it continues to innovate and expand its partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates, showing growth year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s valuation remains relatively cheap and attractive for passive income investors. Positive signs of tech-led business reimagination using AI. Better than expected Q2 2023 results reported by eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/extr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/extr/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Extreme Networks surpasses Q4 earnings and revenue estimates. Extreme Networks recognized as a Gartner Peer Insights™ Customers&amp;rsquo; Choice. Favorable industry outlook highlighting networking stocks. High institutional ownership indicates investor confidence. Positive response to innovative products and solutions. Risks: Uncertain future affecting the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for outperformance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kr/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Kroger&amp;rsquo;s potential acquisition of Albertsons to address pharmacy deserts and provide better access to medicines could improve its social impact and customer reach. Competing with dominant retailers like Walmart, Costco, and Amazon could drive Kroger&amp;rsquo;s motivation to merge with Albertsons for increased size and scale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) could benefit from a bullish trendline that might drive its stock price closer to record highs. The auto and industrial chip sector&amp;rsquo;s potential for accelerating growth and profit expansion in the coming year could positively impact ON Semiconductor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Monster Beverage Corporation reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1% to $1.85 billion, driven by gains in brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions. Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to reflect gains from continued strength in the energy drinks category and robust product innovation plans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
