<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hospitality on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/hospitality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hospitality on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/hospitality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:-24
Chances: Las Vegas Sands&amp;rsquo; fourth-quarter 2023 results are likely to benefit from improved visitation in Macao and Singapore. The revenue and EPS for Las Vegas Sands give a sense of how its business performed in the quarter ended December 2023. Las Vegas Sands&amp;rsquo; expected performance for the quarter ended December 2023 is likely to exceed conventional Wall Street top-and-bottom-line estimates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:86
Chances: Recovery in group and business transient travel demand, capital-recycling efforts and healthy balance sheet strength are likely to drive Host Hotels&amp;rsquo; performance in the quarters ahead. The pause in interest rate hikes and the likelihood of interest rate cuts in 2024 have generated strong appreciation of REITs, including Host Hotels, across multiple subsectors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
