<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investor Sentiment on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investor-sentiment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investor Sentiment on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investor-sentiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DIDIY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/didiy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/didiy/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: XPeng inks $744M deal with ride-share giant Didi, linking two of China&amp;rsquo;s biggest tech names XPeng Shares Rise after Announcing Strategic Partnership with DiDi Risks: Disney defends Bob Iger, Didi gets approval to register users, FAA investigates near-crash at JFK&amp;hellip; Score:61 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: Fintech giant Ant Group expands Alipay+ cross-border payments service in South Korea with ZeroPay tie-up Alibaba.com&amp;rsquo;s Super September is Back with Competitive Prices and Spotlight on Sustainability China stocks see gains amid property market pressures Alibaba scores a win with Taobao debut of China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;most famous teacher&amp;rsquo; as live-streaming e-commerce race heats up Alibaba and Other China Stocks Rise Again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings beat on lower operating costs. Positive investor sentiment with notable returns in the past three years. Expectations of beating earnings estimates for upcoming quarters. Several instances of beating revenue and earnings estimates. Potential undervaluation of Southwestern Energy Company (SWN) based on analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
