<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Market Analysis on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Market Analysis on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:182
Chances: Toast may turn the tide of a growth drop-off with cutting-edge digital solutions and a forward-thinking approach. As we prepare to ring in 2024, there is optimism that growth stocks could continue to rebound to greater highs next year. Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies that had difficulty accessing capital last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: First Horizon (FHN) has an impressive earnings surprise history. The company possesses the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely beat in its next quarterly report. The price-to-sales ratio suggests promise for the stock. Risks: Need to monitor market trends and competition in the financial industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/onon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/onon/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: On Holding had another great quarter, and it has big plans for the next few years. The company is on a mission to double sales over the next three years. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. On Holding AG raised full-year sales guidance after posting another record quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
