<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>india on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/india/</link>
    <description>Recent content in india on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:00:20 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Opens Biggest Office Outside New York in Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/goldman-sachs-opens-biggest-office-outside-new-york-in-mumbai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/goldman-sachs-opens-biggest-office-outside-new-york-in-mumbai/</guid>
      <description>Goldman Sachs Opens Biggest Office Outside New York in Mumbai Goldman Sachs has opened its biggest office outside of New York City in Mumbai, India. The new office will employ 6,000 people and focus on areas such as investment banking, asset management, and securities services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India&#39;s Inflation to Cool Gradually, Central Bank Chief Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/indias-inflation-to-cool-gradually-central-bank-chief-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:43:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/indias-inflation-to-cool-gradually-central-bank-chief-says/</guid>
      <description>India&amp;rsquo;s Inflation to Cool Gradually India&amp;rsquo;s inflation is expected to cool gradually from October, Reserve Bank of India Governor Shaktikanta Das said. The central bank has raised interest rates by 90 basis points in the last two months in an attempt to control inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sizzling Rally in Indian Property Stocks Seen Extending on Rates</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/sizzling-rally-in-indian-property-stocks-seen-extending-on-rates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/sizzling-rally-in-indian-property-stocks-seen-extending-on-rates/</guid>
      <description>Rally in Indian Property Stocks Seen Extending on Rates Indian property stocks have rallied sharply in recent months, with the NSE Nifty Realty Index gaining more than 36% since March lows. The rally has been driven by a number of factors, including expectations that the central bank may start cutting interest rates next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: India Decoupling From China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-india-decoupling-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-india-decoupling-from-china/</guid>
      <description>India Decouples From China India is increasingly decoupling from China in terms of its supply chains. This is due to a number of factors, including the ongoing trade war between the United States and China, as well as India&amp;rsquo;s own economic growth and ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India: Vedanta Chip Setback Shows Cracks in Modi&#39;s Economic Push</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</guid>
      <description>Modi&amp;rsquo;s Economic Push Hits a Major Setback
The Indian government&amp;rsquo;s $24 billion plan to boost manufacturing in the country has hit a major setback, with Vedanta Resources Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s $10 billion chip unit being delayed.
The delay is a blow to Prime Minister Narendra Modi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to make India a global manufacturing hub and comes at a time when the country&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing headwinds from rising inflation and a slowdown in growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Rupee Trap Is Adding to $147 Billion Hoard Stuck Abroad</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Rupee Trap Russia has been selling oil to India in exchange for rupees, but it has been difficult for Russia to use these rupees to buy goods and services from India. This is because India has strict foreign exchange controls that make it difficult for foreigners to repatriate rupees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
