<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/real-estate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Real Estate on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/real-estate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SBRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sbra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sbra/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Sabra Health Care REIT has announced its participation in several healthcare and real estate conferences, indicating an active presence in the industry. The company has published its third annual sustainability report, reflecting a commitment to sustainability and responsible business practices. Despite recent stock price declines, there&amp;rsquo;s potential for a 20% rise in dividend yields, as suggested by Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: Wall Street analysts see a 27.77% upside potential in KE Holdings Inc., indicating optimism about its future growth prospects. KE Holdings Inc. recently announced an upsizing and extension of its share repurchase program and a special cash dividend, which may attract investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bx/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Blackstone&amp;rsquo;s private credit fund secured $2.4 billion, indicating strong demand for their offerings. Blackstone is set to join the S&amp;amp;P 500 Index, potentially leading to further upside for the stock. Blackstone&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Vornado Realty Trust to create Manhattan&amp;rsquo;s first film-and-TV studio is a notable development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
