<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>real estate on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/real-estate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in real estate on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/real-estate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vienna Home Prices Face Slow Correction Rather Than Sudden Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vienna-home-prices-face-slow-correction-rather-than-sudden-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vienna-home-prices-face-slow-correction-rather-than-sudden-drop/</guid>
      <description>Vienna Home Prices Face Slow Correction The Austrian National Bank (ANB) expects a slow correction in home prices in Vienna over the next few years. The ANB cites several factors for its forecast, including:
Low risk of forced sales: There are few homeowners in Vienna who are at risk of being forced to sell their homes due to financial hardship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sizzling Rally in Indian Property Stocks Seen Extending on Rates</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/sizzling-rally-in-indian-property-stocks-seen-extending-on-rates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/sizzling-rally-in-indian-property-stocks-seen-extending-on-rates/</guid>
      <description>Rally in Indian Property Stocks Seen Extending on Rates Indian property stocks have rallied sharply in recent months, with the NSE Nifty Realty Index gaining more than 36% since March lows. The rally has been driven by a number of factors, including expectations that the central bank may start cutting interest rates next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK House Prices Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:49:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-drop/</guid>
      <description>UK House Prices Drop House prices in the UK have fallen for the first time in three months, as buyers are stretched by rising interest rates and the cost of living.
The average price of a home in the UK fell by 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
