<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Investing on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-investing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Investing on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:972
Chances: Bristol Myers Squibb has a history of consistently paying dividends for the last 90 years. Pharmaceutical company AbbVie reports better-than-expected Q2 sales for its arthritis medication Humira. Discounted blue-chip stocks with potential upside may offer investment opportunities in a market with some lagging stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:903
Chances: Medical Properties Trust&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings may benefit from favorable healthcare industry trends and capital recycling efforts. Investors looking for super-high-yield dividend stocks may consider Medical Properties Trust with its dividend yield of about 11.6%. Medical Properties Trust will host a conference call to discuss its Q2 2023 financial results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: AGNC Investment (AGNC) may be worthy of consideration as the worst effects of interest rate hikes appear to be over. AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s commitment to repositioning its portfolio in the current interest rate scenario may optimize performance. Dividend-focused investors may find AGNC Investment appealing due to its high yield and potential income.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
