<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Market Trends on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Market Trends on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:1129
Chances: Oracle leads stocks to watch with AI and cloud play, along with Amazon rival MercadoLibre. Oracle announces new Oracle Cloud for Australian Government and Defense to meet growing global demand. Wendy&amp;rsquo;s implements Oracle Fusion Cloud Applications Suite and moves to Oracle Cloud Infrastructure for improved business insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:991
Chances: Coupang&amp;rsquo;s stock increased significantly by 6.9% over the past period. Coupang is estimated to have a fair value of US$25.12 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. E-commerce players like Coupang are expected to grow by 9% or greater levels in both 2023 and 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:1124
Chances: Barrick Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to benefit from higher gold and copper production along with cost reduction. Barrick Gold aims to restart operations at the Porgera gold mine in Papua New Guinea, potentially contributing to future production. Barrick Gold Corporation is actively engaging in transparency by disclosing site-level tailings storage facility (TSF) information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:1098
Chances: Sirius XM (SIRI) experienced improvement in average revenue per user in Q2 2023, despite declining advertising revenues. Sirius XM delivered earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, holding potential clues for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. The Liberty Media tracking stock, which includes Sirius XM, trades at a significant discount to the value of the company&amp;rsquo;s Live Nation Stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ai/</guid>
      <description>score:1021
Chances: Shares of AI software company C3.ai (NYSE: AI) experienced a 7% decline after analysts raised concerns about AI stocks being in a potential bubble. C3.ai&amp;rsquo;s shift to a consumption-based business model for fiscal 2024 may help lower entry barriers for new customers and quickly strike deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:992
Chances: Southwestern Energy reports positive Q2 2023 earnings with lower operating costs and expenses. Earnings and revenue surprises in Q2 2023 show potential positive momentum for Southwestern Energy (SWN). Strong sector performance by Permian Resources, Civitas Resources, and Northern Oil &amp;amp; Gas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVDA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvda/</guid>
      <description>score:744
Chances: Nvidia (NVDA) is set to report its quarterly results on August 23, and analysts are optimistic about the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The recent positive performance of other tech companies, such as Meta and Google, in terms of online ad spend rates, may indicate positive trends for Nvidia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:759
Chances: Rivian Automotive is experiencing favorable earnings estimate revisions and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season. The International Energy Agency predicts a significant increase in electric vehicle sales, which could benefit companies like Rivian. Risks: Shares of Rivian, along with other EV hopefuls, fell in response to caution sparked by price cuts and competition in the electric vehicle market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
