<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Market Trends on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Market Trends on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:153
Chances: Roblox stock has cleared a buy point following a bullish Wall Street call. RBLX stock has been on a strong recent run, rising around 74%. Wells Fargo initiates coverage of the gaming platform Roblox (RBLX) with an &amp;ldquo;Overweight&amp;rdquo; rating on the stock and a price target of $49 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:-79
Chances: Rivian Automotive is looking to challenge Tesla, Ford, and General Motors with its adventure-styled electric vehicles. RIVN shares surged after Tesla began initial deliveries of its Cybertruck, indicating increasing interest in electric-pickup trucks. Risks: Rivian let go of 20 members of its long-range battery cell development team, including the company&amp;rsquo;s lead cell engineer and former Tesla senior manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Recent revenue results and global market trends help solidify Roku as a strong investment opportunity. Several stocks soared in November on increasing signs that the Federal Reserve could be done raising interest rates as well as rising speculation that rates could even start coming down in the first half of 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
