<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>switzerland on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/switzerland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in switzerland on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/switzerland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SNB&#39;s Jordan Puts Switzerland&#39;s Neutral Interest Rate Around 2%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/snbs-jordan-puts-switzerlands-neutral-interest-rate-around-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/snbs-jordan-puts-switzerlands-neutral-interest-rate-around-2/</guid>
      <description>SNB&amp;rsquo;s Jordan Puts Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s Neutral Interest Rate Around 2% The Swiss National Bank (SNB) has kept its benchmark interest rate at -0.75%, but President Thomas Jordan said that the neutral interest rate for Switzerland is around 2%. This suggests that the SNB is ready to raise interest rates in the near future, as inflation in Switzerland is running at its highest level in years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourists Flock to Swiss Alps and Cities — Defying Strong Franc</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tourists-flock-to-swiss-alps-and-cities-defying-strong-franc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:33:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tourists-flock-to-swiss-alps-and-cities-defying-strong-franc/</guid>
      <description>Tourists Flock to Swiss Alps and Cities Despite Strong Franc
The strong Swiss franc did not deter international tourists from visiting Switzerland last winter. The number of overnight stays in Swiss hotels between November and April 2023 was 17.4 million, up 18% from the previous year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Cash Use Drops in Reality Check for Bill-and-Coin Haven</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/swiss-cash-use-drops-in-reality-check-for-bill-and-coin-haven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/swiss-cash-use-drops-in-reality-check-for-bill-and-coin-haven/</guid>
      <description>Swiss Cash Use Declines The use of cash in Switzerland has declined significantly in recent years. In 2017, 70% of all transactions were made in cash. By 2022, that number had fallen to 36%.
There are a number of factors that have contributed to the decline in cash use, including the rise of digital payments, the COVID-19 pandemic, and government efforts to reduce tax evasion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
