<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>industry competition on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/industry-competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in industry competition on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/industry-competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Merger and consolidation efforts to enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s position. Strategic partnership with Amazon for wireless services. Expansion into the 5G network with coverage for a significant portion of the U.S. population. Positive market response to the merger deal with EchoStar. Billionaire Charlie Ergen&amp;rsquo;s influence and leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T generates growth in a stagnant industry, offering potential opportunities. Launch of 5G wireless home internet and catching up to rivals is a positive sign. High dividend yield, potential passive income, and undervalued stock are favorable factors. Positive moves like expanding Xfinity 10G Network and 5G wireless home internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Ambev S.A. sees higher Q4 net profit, indicating growth in the company&amp;rsquo;s financials. Ambev&amp;rsquo;s market share gains are positively viewed, signaling potential business strength. ABEV&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2023 earnings call transcript is available, offering insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Positive performance of Boston Beer (SAM) could impact ABEV&amp;rsquo;s growth strategies positively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-160
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing next-generation solid-state lithium-metal batteries showcases its commitment to innovative technology, which could position it well in the evolving EV industry. Despite recent fluctuations in QS stock, the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to raise significant capital through underwritten public offerings demonstrates investor interest and support for its growth initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Aramark recognized as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Companies for Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion&amp;rsquo; Positive movement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating. Strong performance in Q3 2023 results. Upcoming spin-off of Aramark Uniform Services (AUS) as an independent public company. Dividend payment announcement for August.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
