<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: The &amp;lsquo;buy now, pay later&amp;rsquo; trend could result in increased consumer spending and potential returns for investors in e-commerce stocks like Shopify. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based commerce platform is likely to benefit from the growing trend of online retail and the integration of Buy with Prime into Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Commerce Cloud platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: Sea Limited has shown consistent growth and diversification in its business segments, including Digital Entertainment, E-Commerce, and Digital Financial Services. The e-commerce market is still growing, and Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s Shopee mobile app and marketplace have the potential for further expansion and increased market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: Walmart is integrating generative artificial intelligence to make it simpler for shoppers to find what they&amp;rsquo;re looking for and streamlining associates&amp;rsquo; workflows. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s stock reached $161.29 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.24% change compared to its last close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters reported strong growth in fourth quarter-to-date revenue, with the American Eagle segment growing in the high single digits and Aerie growing in the low teens. The company raised its fourth-quarter revenue and operating profit outlook, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
