<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Shopify (SHOP) is benefiting from an expanding clientele and a robust portfolio. They&amp;rsquo;ve got solid sales momentum, and profits are on the upswing, too. With 2024 likely to witness a low-interest-rate environment, the market could specifically have these four stocks on its radar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:156
Chances: Pet care stocks are incredibly effective in diversifying investment portfolios, leveraging the robust growth of the pet care industry. Chewy stock has made exceptional progress in expanding its subscriber base and revenues. Risks: Chewy stock has experienced an endless plunge over the past two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-87
Chances: Sea Ltd. has a strong presence in the digital entertainment, e-commerce, and digital financial services segments, which presents significant growth opportunities. The company&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is promising, indicating potential for stock growth. Despite intense competition, there are favorable factors working in Sea&amp;rsquo;s favor, leading to potential for success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
