<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:04:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s Digital Entertainment and E-Commerce segments offer strong growth potential in the online gaming and third-party marketplace sectors. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into Digital Financial Services through SeaMoney provides opportunities for further revenue diversification and growth. Positive trends in the e-commerce industry and the increasing adoption of online gaming are favorable for Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s business prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:223
Chances: The e-commerce enabler made a substantial strategic mistake but managed to bounce back from the consequences. Some skyrocketing stocks are poised to keep rising for a long time, making money for investors along the way. Monster and Shopify look poised for bull runs in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-53
Chances: Coupang, Inc. is underfollowed on Wall Street, but has immense growth potential. The global e-commerce market is expected to reach $6.3 trillion for 2023, indicating a strong uptrend in e-commerce adoption. Emerging markets are likely to grow faster than most developed markets through the decade, presenting multibagger opportunities for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:145
Chances: China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce landscape is still showing promising signs of growth and potential opportunities for investors. PDD Holdings has built a strong network of capabilities that support its underlying businesses, positioning it well for future growth in the digital economy. The introduction of new policies by Chinese e-commerce players may raise concerns, but there are still opportunities for growth and innovation in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters reported strong growth in fourth quarter-to-date revenue, with the American Eagle segment growing in the high single digits and Aerie growing in the low teens. The company raised its fourth-quarter revenue and operating profit outlook, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
