<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: The global e-commerce industry is expected to continue its uptrend in 2024 with potential for growth in emerging markets. Coupang has underperformed since its IPO in 2021, but there are bullish signs for the stock in 2024 due to its expanding addressable market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Shopify has seen a 240% rise in stock price, indicating strong market performance New alliance with Manhattan Associates to enhance omnichannel shopping experiences for retailers Expansion of client portfolio to over 20,000 SMB merchants with AI technology Risks: Etsy underperformed its peers in 2023, indicating potential market challenges for e-commerce companies Amazon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Salesforce could pose competition in the e-commerce space Uncertain market climate and potential impact on consumer spending Score:3 chances characters count - risks characters count = 3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: The PDD Holdings, Inc. is strategically positioned to benefit from the growth of the digital economy in East Asia, particularly in China. Risks: The new &amp;lsquo;refund only&amp;rsquo; policies introduced by Chinese e-commerce players could potentially impact the revenue and profitability of PDD Holdings, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-17
Chances: The growth-fueled Nasdaq Composite remains 7% below its all-time high, which means bargains can still be found. The S&amp;amp;P 500 index is trading near a record high, but there are still pockets of value in this market. The global e-commerce industry has gone through a challenging period with growth adjustments in a post-pandemic world, but global e-commerce adoption is in an uptrend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-64
Chances: Walmart is integrating generative artificial intelligence to make it simpler for shoppers to find what they&amp;rsquo;re looking for and streamlining associates&amp;rsquo; workflows. Walmart&amp;rsquo;s stock reached $161.29 at the closing of the latest trading day, reflecting a +1.24% change compared to its last close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters reported strong growth in fourth quarter-to-date revenue, with the American Eagle segment growing in the high single digits and Aerie growing in the low teens. The company raised its fourth-quarter revenue and operating profit outlook, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
