<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:03:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: Grab Holdings Ltd has achieved success in the field of e-wallets, food distribution, and mobile and financial services in Southeast Asia. The company operates in eight countries in Southeast Asia and provides millions of people access to various services through its superapp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-119
Chances: Shopify (SHOP) has received quite a bit of attention from Zacks.com users lately, indicating a potential positive sentiment towards the stock. Great companies in steadily growing industries can deliver enviable returns through the years, suggesting a positive outlook for Shopify&amp;rsquo;s future growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:-71
Chances: Carvana (CVNA) is showing resilience in the used car market, with a significant rally in its stock price. The company&amp;rsquo;s financial metrics have shown improvement, indicating underlying strength beyond just speculative trading. Risks: The CFO of Carvana sold a significant number of shares, which may raise concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance or outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-41
Chances: JD.com, Inc. (JD) experienced a +0.71% change in the recent trading day, indicating potential for growth. Risks: JD.com&amp;rsquo;s overseas expansion efforts and potential acquisition of Currys Plc could pose risks due to the current market conditions and competition. Score:-41 chances characters count - risks characters count = -41</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: The Chinese online marketplace is taking the U.S. by storm as Etsy and Wayfair are already struggling to expand their audience. This high-growth Chinese e-commerce company still has plenty of room to grow. Among the blue-chip stocks, certain tech giants stand on the brink of a monumental surge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter 2023 results are likely to reflect strong momentum across Promoted Listings and Managed payments The company is hosting an epic one-day event featuring ultra-rare cards and collectibles at accessible price points, which could drive significant sales and customer engagement Risks: Softness in the marketplace platform may impact eBay&amp;rsquo;s overall performance Analysts are concerned about the declining transaction take rates of the digital payment giant Score:126 chances characters count - risks characters count = 126</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Baillie Gifford&amp;rsquo;s increased investment in Sea Ltd indicates confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects. Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock has seen positive movement in the recent trading sessions. The growth-fueled Nasdaq Composite presents potential opportunities for Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock. Risks: Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock price has fallen 16% in the last quarter, signaling potential challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-53
Chances: Coupang, Inc. is underfollowed on Wall Street, but has immense growth potential. The global e-commerce market is expected to reach $6.3 trillion for 2023, indicating a strong uptrend in e-commerce adoption. Emerging markets are likely to grow faster than most developed markets through the decade, presenting multibagger opportunities for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
