<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:08:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: American Eagle&amp;rsquo;s strategic efforts, including the Real Power Real Growth Plan, appear encouraging The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing differentiated assortments is helping its business strategies Risks: Facing macroeconomic challenges impacting consumer spending Challenges in active client retention Score:95 chances characters count - risks characters count = 95</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
