<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:54:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:236
Chances: Although it&amp;rsquo;s battling intense competition, there is still much that can work in Sea&amp;rsquo;s favor. The retail sector has faced multiple challenges in the current year, but some of the best retail stocks are showing attractive valuation. Each of the major stock market indexes has gained more than 20% from their bear market lows, fueled by easing inflation and the expectation that the Federal Reserve Bank may be done raising interest rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: The internet has continued to propel the exchange of goods and services with Shopify (SHOP) being one of the fastest-growing commerce platforms. In an environment of low market interest rates, growth stocks, especially in the technology sector, such as Shopify, tend to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-106
Chances: Walmart is on the cusp of being surpassed by Amazon as the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest retailer, indicating potential growth opportunities in the e-commerce space. Risks: The company is facing competition from Amazon and may need to invest heavily in online presence to maintain market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:-495
Chances: Unity Software Inc. (U) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Shares of game engine maker Unity (NYSE:U) jumped 6.5% in the afternoon session after The Federal Reserve maintained its key interest rate for the third consecutive time, holding it within the targeted range of 5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
