<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>e-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in e-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:29:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1025 JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: The projected fair value for JD.com is US$63.64 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity, suggesting potential upside in the stock. JD.com plans to release its unaudited financial results for the three months and six months ended June 30, 2023, which could provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1151 CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:1151
Chances: Coupang&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$25.12 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. E-commerce industry indicators, such as predictions of growth for Amazon and other players, suggest a potential bounce back for Coupang. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s stock saw a double-digit share price rise in the recent past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1036 W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:1036
Chances: Shares of Wayfair (W) beat the market this week, gaining 9% through Thursday trading compared to a 2% decline in the wider market. Wayfair made important progress in the second quarter, particularly on the cost-cutting front, boosting its gross margin and reducing operating costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1142 BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:1142
Chances: The outlook for e-commerce players like Alibaba is strengthening, making it a viable space to invest in for 2023 and beyond. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s cloud computing unit releasing open-source AI models could expand the company&amp;rsquo;s influence in the field of generative AI and drive innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1052 CVNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvna/</guid>
      <description>score:1052
Chances: Carvana&amp;rsquo;s stock (CVNA) has experienced significant gains of approximately 900% this year, showing positive momentum and strong performance. Carvana launched same-day delivery in Arizona, introducing a new level of speed and convenience for customers, which could enhance customer satisfaction and boost sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0889 SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:889
Chances: Despite Shopify posting better-than-expected second-quarter revenue and adjusted earnings per share, analysts upgraded their 12-month price targets for the stock after digesting the solid results. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results benefited from growth in merchant solutions revenues and an expanding merchant base. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s President, Harley Finkelstein, discussed how the e-commerce company is approaching a potential U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1244 AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:1244
Chances: Amazon.com, Inc. beats earnings expectations with an EPS of $0.65 compared to the expected $0.34. The e-commerce and cloud-computing leader, Amazon.com, showed strong growth and gained over 8% in stock value after reporting quarterly earnings. The outlook for e-commerce players, including Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
