<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: JD.com, Inc. (JD) stood at $23.96, denoting a +0.71% change from the preceding trading day. JD.com&amp;rsquo;s management will hold a conference call to discuss its unaudited fourth quarter and full year 2023 financial results. Risks: JD.com is considering an offer for British electronics retailer Currys, which may involve a bidding war and potential financial risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>W</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/w/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/w/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: Wayfair Inc. reported strong fourth-quarter results, including a 10.4% jump in stock price, free cash flow of $62 million beating analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates, and an increase in active customers. The company&amp;rsquo;s improvements in availability, speed, and price competitiveness led to robust share expansion and increased customer loyalty, indicating potential for continued growth and success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 09:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter results are likely to reflect strong momentum across Promoted Listings and Managed payments The Catch 151 auction event could attract enthusiasts and drive sales for eBay Appointment of Zane Rowe to eBay&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors could bring fresh perspective and expertise Risks: Softness in the marketplace platform could impact eBay&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter results Declining transaction take rates for digital payment could pose a risk for eBay Competition and disruptive forces in the e-commerce industry may impact eBay&amp;rsquo;s growth Score:45 chances characters count - risks characters count = 45</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pdd/</guid>
      <description>score:88
Chances: PDD Holdings, Inc. is making significant investments in advertising and expansion, indicating a potential for growth in its underlying businesses. The network of sourcing, logistics, and fulfillment capabilities built by PDD Holdings, Inc. supports the company&amp;rsquo;s aim to bring more businesses and people into the digital economy, presenting a promising opportunity for increased productivity and new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Baillie Gifford&amp;rsquo;s increased investment in Sea Ltd indicates confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects. Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock has seen positive movement in the recent trading sessions. The growth-fueled Nasdaq Composite presents potential opportunities for Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock. Risks: Sea Ltd&amp;rsquo;s stock price has fallen 16% in the last quarter, signaling potential challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:223
Chances: The e-commerce enabler made a substantial strategic mistake but managed to bounce back from the consequences. Some skyrocketing stocks are poised to keep rising for a long time, making money for investors along the way. Monster and Shopify look poised for bull runs in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-53
Chances: Coupang, Inc. is underfollowed on Wall Street, but has immense growth potential. The global e-commerce market is expected to reach $6.3 trillion for 2023, indicating a strong uptrend in e-commerce adoption. Emerging markets are likely to grow faster than most developed markets through the decade, presenting multibagger opportunities for investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AEO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aeo/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: American Eagle Outfitters reported strong growth in fourth quarter-to-date revenue, with the American Eagle segment growing in the high single digits and Aerie growing in the low teens. The company raised its fourth-quarter revenue and operating profit outlook, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
