<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: Shopify (SHOP) concluded the recent trading session at $79.11, signifying a +0.98% move from its prior day&amp;rsquo;s close. Shopify (SHOP) is benefiting from an expanding clientele and a robust portfolio. Management is pivoting toward efficiency as sales growth slows. The e-commerce software provider is finally generating a profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:-133
Chances: Growth stock investors could be in for an excellent year in 2024. Sea&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$73.00 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity. Risks: Geopolitical tensions between the United States and China as well as renewed conflict in the Middle East could impact Sea&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: Chewy stock has reached a three-month high after breaking out of a double bottom pattern, indicating potential for further price appreciation. Jefferies has initiated coverage on Chewy with a &amp;ldquo;Buy&amp;rdquo; rating, signaling positive sentiment from analysts and potential for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:-247
Chances: Walmart (WMT) closed at $157.65 in the latest trading session, marking a +0.05% move from the prior day. Walmart (WMT) is poised to keep its growth story going with its robust store and online operations. Gains from higher-margin ventures, such as advertising, are also noteworthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: The Federal Reserve raised interest rates at the fastest clip since the 1980s, which may affect the overall market sentiment and possibly impact the stock price of META. Spending on e-commerce and digital ads is expected to accelerate next year, which could benefit Meta Platforms and lead to potential gains in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:350
Chances: Alibaba Group Holding Limited stock is trading higher amid reports of China approving 105 domestic games following recent industry restrictions, indicating a potential easing pressure on the company The growth-stock-driven Nasdaq Composite remains 8% below its all-time high, which means bargains still abound for opportunistic investors Shares of tech conglomerate Tencent were down more than 12% Friday morning amid an $80 billion market selloff in Chinese gaming stocks, sparked by new, unexpected restrictions from Beijing Risks: After dropping 18% in 2023, Alibaba’s U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
