<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-commerce on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-commerce on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 10:42:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WMT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 10:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wmt/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Costco&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a good employer may give it a competitive edge over rivals like Target and Walmart. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s potential to surpass Walmart as the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest retailer could indicate a shift in the retail landscape. Retailers&amp;rsquo; complaints about the impact of climbing retail theft on their bottom line may lead to increased focus on security measures and loss prevention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 10:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:125
Chances: Sea Ltd. operates in the digital entertainment, e-commerce, and digital financial services segments, with potential for growth in each area. The company&amp;rsquo;s online gaming services and third-party marketplace have the potential for significant expansion in the coming years. Investors may have the opportunity to capitalize on Sea&amp;rsquo;s growth potential in the digital entertainment and e-commerce sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 10:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fl/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Foot Locker, Inc. has shown signs of recovery with a 66% increase in share price in the last year. The company is expected to benefit from leaner inventories at year-end, enabling it to introduce trendy styles in 2024. Risks: Nike&amp;rsquo;s recent warnings of flagging sales growth and cost cuts in the industry may impact Foot Locker&amp;rsquo;s performance and market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: The internet has continued to propel the exchange of goods and services with Shopify (SHOP) being one of the fastest-growing commerce platforms. In an environment of low market interest rates, growth stocks, especially in the technology sector, such as Shopify, tend to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
