<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Innovation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Innovation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Intel to create a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s technological capabilities and competitiveness. Cradlepoint&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Ericsson in modernizing network infrastructure for Los Angeles County showcases Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s involvement in innovative and impactful projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:1002
Chances: PayPal launches its own U.S. dollar-backed stablecoin, PYUSD, for payments and transfers. PYPL stock surges on the news of the stablecoin launch in the cryptocurrency market. Introduction of stablecoin by a major fintech firm like PayPal can drive further cryptocurrency adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GOOGL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/googl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/googl/</guid>
      <description>score:1031
Chances: Alphabet Inc. is seeking regulatory approval to expand self-driving car services in San Francisco, indicating potential growth in this emerging market. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s strategic move to offer employee discounts to hotels on the Google campus as part of its return-to-office tactic could encourage employees to return to the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Micron Technology is expanding its CXL ecosystem by offering sample availability of the Micron CZ120 memory expansion modules, which could contribute to revenue growth. The CZ120 modules&amp;rsquo; high capacities and memory read/write bandwidth could position Micron to meet the increasing demand for advanced memory solutions in data-intensive applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
