<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Innovation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Innovation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:06:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s solid-state battery cells have shown a lot of promise so far Volkswagen is holding talks with France&amp;rsquo;s Blue Solutions about adapting their solid-state battery design for cars Risks: Investors have found a reason to worry about QuantumScape A report suggests QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s key partner could be looking for other sources of solid-state batteries Score:27 chances characters count - risks characters count = 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:160
Chances: Advancements in artificial intelligence have been a major trend, and companies like Salesforce are well positioned to benefit from this technological shift. Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s CEO Marc Benioff believes in the potential of AI, and the company&amp;rsquo;s solutions in customer relationship management will likely see increased demand as AI becomes more pervasive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/orcl/</guid>
      <description>score:170
Chances: Oracle has been recognized as a Leader in the cloud database management systems and has introduced new capabilities to Oracle Fusion Cloud Enterprise Performance Management, indicating potential for growth and innovation. Institutions&amp;rsquo; substantial holdings in Oracle imply significant influence over the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance and direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:129
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) has been gaining attention from investors and analysts, indicating potential for growth in the stock&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The announcement of the industry’s only integrated secure networking solution with Wi-Fi 7 and the launch of a new access point and 10 Gigabit Power over Ethernet switch demonstrates Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and staying ahead in the cybersecurity market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Clarivate Plc has been consistently releasing new reports and products, indicating a strong focus on innovation and meeting the evolving needs of the healthcare and research industries. Risks: The company operates in a highly competitive market, and its success depends on the adoption of its products and solutions by academia, government, life sciences, and healthcare organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
