<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ECB on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/ecb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ECB on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:22:48 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/ecb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>European Stocks Tread Water as Inditex Gains Fail to Lift Mood</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-tread-water-as-inditex-gains-fail-to-lift-mood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:22:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-tread-water-as-inditex-gains-fail-to-lift-mood/</guid>
      <description>European markets were mixed on Wednesday as investors awaited the outcome of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) policy meeting. The Stoxx Europe 600 index was down 0.1% at 417.95 points by 0815 GMT.
Inditex shares rose 2.9% after the company reported a 16% rise in first-half profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Visco Says He Would Have Preferred More Gradual Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:52:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Visco Prefers Gradual Approach to Rate Hikes European Central Bank (ECB) Governing Council member Ignazio Visco said on Tuesday that he would have preferred a more gradual approach to raising interest rates.
The ECB has raised interest rates by 375 basis points since December, and two more quarter-point moves are expected this month and next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Says Core Price Trend Was &#39;Broadly Seen as Worrisome&#39; in May</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:57:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</guid>
      <description>ECB Concerned About Inflation The European Central Bank (ECB) is concerned about the path of inflation, according to the minutes of its May policy meeting. Core inflation, which excludes food and energy, rose to 3.8% in May from 3.5% in April. This was the highest level since December 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:43:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked European Central Bank (ECB) President Christine Lagarde said on Thursday that there is no clear evidence that underlying inflation has peaked.
Core inflation, which excludes food and energy prices, rose to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone Inflation Slows, but ECB to Keep Rates Low</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eurozone-inflation-slows-but-ecb-to-keep-rates-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eurozone-inflation-slows-but-ecb-to-keep-rates-low/</guid>
      <description>Eurozone Inflation Slows, but ECB to Keep Rates Low Inflation in the eurozone slowed to 3.0% in May from 3.5% in April, but the European Central Bank (ECB) is likely to keep interest rates low for now.
The ECB has said that it will keep rates low until at least the end of 2023, even if inflation falls below its target of 2%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
