<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solar Power on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/solar-power/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Solar Power on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/solar-power/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: Are You Looking for a Top Momentum Pick? Why Cemex (CX) is a Great Choice Cemex and Synhelion make further progress toward the world’s first fully solar-powered cement plant Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Cemex profit climbs modestly on price hikes, strong peso Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Cemex beats profit estimates on price hikes, easing inflation Volvo Trucks and CEMEX Unveil First Fully Electric Heavy Concrete Mixer Truck Risks: Cemex Explores Sale of Dominican Republic Business Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Cemex posts surprise quarterly loss; shares drop Statement on the Illegal Occupation of Vulcan&amp;rsquo;s Property in Mexico US firm says Mexican authorities illegally seized its port terminal CEMEX Contributes to Circular Economy With Launch of Its Regenera Waste Management Score:62 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ENPH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enph/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Enphase Energy is strategically expanding its presence in the renewable energy market, particularly in Europe where sales are growing. The global alternative energy market is showing strong growth, offering significant investment opportunities for Enphase Energy. Solar energy is projected to become the largest source of power globally by 2027, providing a favorable outlook for Enphase Energy&amp;rsquo;s solar-based solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
