<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customer Experience on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/customer-experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customer Experience on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:56:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/customer-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aal/</guid>
      <description>score:-165
Chances: American Airlines Flight Attendants Vote to Authorize a Strike Busy Labor Day Weekend Awaits US Airlines: 3 Stocks to Watch U.S. airline passengers are finding low-cost business class fares American Airlines Pilots Ratify New Contract Risks: Pilot shortages, air traffic control are &amp;rsquo;lingering problems&amp;rsquo; for airlines: Expert American Airlines passenger lashes out at people reclining seats American Airlines may have a big problem on its hands (customers won&amp;rsquo;t like it) American Airlines fined $4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates, showing growth year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s valuation remains relatively cheap and attractive for passive income investors. Positive signs of tech-led business reimagination using AI. Better than expected Q2 2023 results reported by eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Verizon announces new partnerships to enhance customer experience. Verizon wins awards for its solutions and advancements in 5G technology. Positive trends for dividend investors with Verizon&amp;rsquo;s dividend income. Verizon expands its network coverage and improves customer connectivity. Verizon&amp;rsquo;s position in the 5G broadband market and technological gains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
