<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:823
Chances: The aerospace industry is recovering, and Chinese airlines&amp;rsquo; need to renew their fleets could present an opportunity for Boeing. The launch of electric vertical takeoff and landing aircraft by companies like Joby and Archer could offer potential upside for Boeing. Positive performance of blue chip stocks, including Boeing, contributed to higher market benchmarks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Ukraine reports significant results from U.S. Patriot and German IRIS-T defense systems against attacks by Russia. RTX faces quality and durability concerns with its single-aisle jetliner bet in the aerospace and defense sector. RTX beats Q2 earnings estimates with organic sales growth of 12% year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: AGNC Investment (AGNC) may be worthy of consideration as the worst effects of interest rate hikes appear to be over. AGNC Investment&amp;rsquo;s commitment to repositioning its portfolio in the current interest rate scenario may optimize performance. Dividend-focused investors may find AGNC Investment appealing due to its high yield and potential income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:960
Chances: Fisker Inc. announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, targeting a popular segment in the U.S. market. The Fisker Alaska pickup truck, priced at $45,400 before incentives, is expected to capitalize on demand for affordable electric trucks. The company&amp;rsquo;s decision to manufacture cars in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:1025
Chances: Increased political instability contributes to cybersecurity market growth, potentially benefiting companies like Fortinet. Cloud security companies may be better positioned in the cybersecurity market as corporate budgets tighten. Collaboration across sectors and investment in AI-powered security services are important for disrupting cybercrime, potentially benefiting Fortinet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:1092
Chances: Vertiv Holdings Co announced an underwritten secondary offering of its Class A common stock, indicating potential investor interest and capital infusion. Strong demand for data center equipment, driven by cloud and colocation markets, has contributed to Vertiv&amp;rsquo;s stock rise, with positive full-year earnings guidance updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Warner Bros. Discovery plans to add live sports to its streaming service Max, potentially launching with MLB playoffs in October. Paramount reported Q2 results beating estimates and announced a $1.62 billion deal with KKR for Simon &amp;amp; Schuster business. Barbie movie grossed $1 billion globally in just 17 days, marking a milestone for director Greta Gerwig and potential changes in film production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> F</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/f/</guid>
      <description>score:935
Chances: Ford is adjusting its EV production targets and positioning itself as a long-term winner in the industry. Ford&amp;rsquo;s higher dividend yield of over 4.6% could make it an appealing dividend stock for investors. Ford beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter revenue and earnings, showing strong performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
