<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PSNY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/psny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/psny/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Polestar reported record deliveries in the second quarter, growing 36% year-on-year, indicating strong momentum. Polestar is collaborating with Mobileye to build an integrated driver assist solution for its electric SUV coupé, Polestar 4. Polestar plans to adopt the North American Charging Standard to enable access to Tesla Supercharger network in the USA and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: Toast announces the launch of a Catering &amp;amp; Events platform to help restaurants streamline event management and improve guest experience. Toast is transforming the restaurant industry with its restaurant technology platform, which could drive future growth. Toast is approved for use in Marriott Select Service Hotels in the United States and Canada, expanding its market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:-3
Chances: Tencent Music Entertainment reports rising quarterly revenue, although it warns of a potential decline ahead. Tencent Music&amp;rsquo;s implied volatility is surging for its stock options, indicating increased market interest. Tencent Music Entertainment sees increased revenue from paying users, which could drive future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper (KDP) reports strong Q2 earnings that top estimates and provide an optimistic sales view. Keurig Dr Pepper makes a strategic move by partnering with La Colombe to expand its reach. Solid market gains are expected to aid Keurig Dr Pepper amid cost woes, potentially driving growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COTY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coty/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Coty successfully completes refinancing of its revolving credit facility, signaling financial stability. Coty focuses on boosting its global presence and ups its FY23 view, indicating growth prospects. Marc Jacobs and Coty expand their license partnership to beauty, potentially driving brand sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wrk/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: WestRock engages in merger talks with Smurfit Kappa, indicating potential for growth and expansion. The proposed merger with Smurfit Kappa could create a $20 billion packaging giant, offering strategic advantages. WestRock beats profit estimates in its fiscal third quarter, showing resilience in a dynamic environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BKR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</guid>
      <description>score:57
Chances: Baker Hughes secured a deal to supply equipment for the Driftwood LNG project, potentially contributing to revenue growth. The company signed agreements and expanded equipment supply partnerships with Venture Global, supporting its long-term expansion plans. Despite market fluctuations, Baker Hughes shareholders have earned a 38% CAGR over the last three years, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Transocean secured a $222 million drilling contract from ONGC, indicating a potential revenue boost. Transocean announced a $518 million ultra-deepwater drillship contract, which could contribute to future earnings. Transocean&amp;rsquo;s stock has gained 3.3% over the past week, showing positive market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GOLD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gold/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: Barrick Gold beat quarterly profit estimates on the back of higher gold prices, indicating potential for strong financial performance. Barrick Gold is progressing with the extension of its long-term value delivery runway, suggesting a positive outlook. Gulf nations are poised to invest billions in Pakistan, which could benefit Barrick Gold as it explores opportunities in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ebay/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: eBay&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates, showing growth year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s valuation remains relatively cheap and attractive for passive income investors. Positive signs of tech-led business reimagination using AI. Better than expected Q2 2023 results reported by eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Selected by Farmers Insurance Federal Credit Union for personal lending. Potential for significant upside due to AI technology in the financial sector. Stock&amp;rsquo;s impressive rally of over 400% since May 2023. Strong performance among the best performing stocks in the last 3 and 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/uaa/</guid>
      <description>score:4
Chances: Under Armour reports Q1 earnings beat and maintains fiscal outlook. Under Armour launches new &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s growth strategies appear encouraging. Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Positive impact from executive changes and growth strategies. Risks: Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s revenue slips amid challenging retail environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TWNK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/twnk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/twnk/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Hostess Brands reports strong Q2 earnings, beating estimates. Positive performance and earnings beat in Q1 2023. Hostess Brands completes refinancing transaction, enhancing financial position. Launch of new products like Hostess &amp;lsquo;Mashup&amp;rsquo; and Zero Sugar Mini Wafers. Participation at investor conferences and corporate responsibility efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gps/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: Gap surpasses Q2 earnings estimates despite a weak forecast. Positive focus on profit beat and strong Q2 earnings performance. Gap reports profit beat and slight revenue miss, comp. sales dip. Analysts highlight potential for Gap&amp;rsquo;s growth after positive Q2 performance. Gap&amp;rsquo;s strategic partnerships and limited-edition collections contribute to opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cah/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: Cardinal Health&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings call indicated that the company beat earnings expectations, showcasing its ability to perform well financially. The positive response to weight loss drugs and its impact on revenue growth signals a potential market opportunity and positive outlook for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COHR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cohr/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: Coherent Corp. being a global leader in materials, networking, and lasers positions it well in innovative technology segments. Upgrades from analysts and positive performance by the U.S. oil &amp;amp; gas sector indicate some positive sentiment in the market. Investor interest in the company&amp;rsquo;s shareholder letter and updated presentation could imply a focus on transparency and strategic direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
