<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>twitter on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/twitter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in twitter on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 17:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Musk Says Twitter Advertisers Are Coming Back</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-says-twitter-advertisers-are-coming-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 17:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-says-twitter-advertisers-are-coming-back/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Says Twitter Advertisers Are Coming Back Elon Musk said in an interview in Paris that he believes Twitter advertisers are coming back. Musk said that he wants to make Twitter a more attractive place for advertisers, and that he believes he can do this by making the platform more engaging and user-friendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#39;s Twitter vs. Bad Bots: The Battle Goes On</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/elon-musks-twitter-vs.-bad-bots-the-battle-goes-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/elon-musks-twitter-vs.-bad-bots-the-battle-goes-on/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Threatens to Walk Away from Twitter Deal Over Fake Accounts Elon Musk has threatened to walk away from his $44 billion deal to buy Twitter if the company does not provide more information about the number of fake accounts on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Loses Second Safety Executive in Days</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-loses-second-safety-executive-in-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-loses-second-safety-executive-in-days/</guid>
      <description>Twitter has lost two top safety executives in days, as A.J. Brown, head of brand safety and ad quality, is leaving the company. Brown&amp;rsquo;s departure comes after Ella Irwin, Twitter&amp;rsquo;s head of trust and safety, left on Thursday.
The departures come as concerns about Twitter&amp;rsquo;s content moderation policies grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter&#39;s Top Content Moderation and Safety Executive Leaves</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitters-top-content-moderation-and-safety-executive-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitters-top-content-moderation-and-safety-executive-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Top Content Moderation Executive Resigns Twitter&amp;rsquo;s top content moderation and safety executive, Ella Irwin, has resigned.
Irwin, who declined to discuss her reason for leaving, departed on a day when Elon Musk said Twitter employees erred in how they handled a documentary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Turns His Attention to 2024 White House Race</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk has purchased Twitter, and many are wondering what this means for the 2024 election. Musk has said that he wants to make Twitter a more open and free platform for speech, but some experts worry that he could use the platform to give himself an unfair advantage in the race.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
