<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>oil on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/oil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in oil on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:36:08 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/oil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Lack of Oil Cuts Will Test Saudi Patience</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-lack-of-oil-cuts-will-test-saudi-patience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:36:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-lack-of-oil-cuts-will-test-saudi-patience/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Oil Production Tests Saudi Patience Russia has refused to join Saudi Arabia in cutting oil production, despite calls from the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and other major oil producers. This has led to a sharp increase in global oil supply, which has put downward pressure on prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday
The stock market was down on Tuesday as investors continued to worry about the war in Ukraine and the impact of rising inflation.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.5%, while the Nasdaq Composite was down 1.2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEC&#43; Faces Oil Market Torn by Demand Rebound and Recession Risks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/opec&#43;-faces-oil-market-torn-by-demand-rebound-and-recession-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:29:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/opec&#43;-faces-oil-market-torn-by-demand-rebound-and-recession-risks/</guid>
      <description>OPEC+ Faces Oil Market Torn by Demand Rebound and Recession Risks OPEC+ is facing a difficult balancing act as the oil market is torn between demand rebounding from the COVID-19 pandemic and recession risks.
The International Energy Agency (IEA) has warned that the global oil market could be in a deficit of 1 million barrels per day (bpd) in the third quarter of 2023, if Russian output falls by 3 million bpd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
