<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>partnership on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/partnership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in partnership on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/partnership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PTON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pton/</guid>
      <description>score:-297
Chances: Peloton Interactive, Inc. Announces Participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia &amp;amp; Technology Conference Peloton&amp;rsquo;s return to positive cash flow hit by bike recall, shares slide Peloton Interactive, Inc. Reports Fourth Quarter and Full-Year Fiscal 2023 Financial Results Peloton and the University of Michigan Announce Partnership Reaching Students, Athletes and Alumni Risks: Is Peloton in Trouble?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: SentinelOne raises full-year forecast, adds partnership with Wiz still on SentinelOne Announces Second Quarter Fiscal Year 2024 Financial Results SentinelOne Leads the Way in XDR SentinelOne and Netskope Team to Secure Modern Workforce SentinelOne Stock: Bull vs. Bear Risks: SentinelOne scraps Wiz partnership nearly a week after bid interest SentinelOne Might Be Up for Sale &amp;ndash; What Should You Do if You Own the Stock?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: JD.com beats earnings estimates despite China&amp;rsquo;s economic challenges. Strong net profit growth in the second quarter. Partnership with Gucci and digital flagship store launch. Positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts. Investment potential in high-growth tech stocks. Risks: JD.com stock impacted by China&amp;rsquo;s economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Merger and consolidation efforts to enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s position. Strategic partnership with Amazon for wireless services. Expansion into the 5G network with coverage for a significant portion of the U.S. population. Positive market response to the merger deal with EchoStar. Billionaire Charlie Ergen&amp;rsquo;s influence and leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Lucid announces plans for Gravity SUV reveal in November, potentially boosting interest. Lucid&amp;rsquo;s Air EV price cuts are well received by the market, indicating positive response. Lucid remains on track for annual production guidance of over 10,000 vehicles. Lucid strikes EV technology deal with Aston Martin, leading to partnership and stock jump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TECK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teck/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Teck Resources collaborates with NORDEN to reduce carbon emissions in its steelmaking coal supply chain. Teck Resources works on reducing carbon dioxide emissions in the steelmaking coal supply chain through a partnership with NORDEN. Teck Resources aims to reduce annual emissions from its shipments handled by NORDEN by 25%, contributing to environmental sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
