<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partnership on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/partnership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partnership on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/partnership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:771
Chances: Charlie Ergen is nearing a deal to merge Dish Network and EchoStar for a nationwide wireless network. DISH Network partners with Amazon to sell Boost Infinite wireless plans to Prime members. Risks: Uncertainties related to the successful completion of the merger between Dish Network and EchoStar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:1298
Chances: Affirm&amp;rsquo;s upcoming publication of its Q4 and fiscal year 2023 shareholder letter, financial results, and conference call may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance and strategic outlook. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Cathay Pacific to become its exclusive U.S. pay-over-time partner could open new growth opportunities in the airline industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:883
Chances: Banco Bradesco SA is partnering with Amazon.com to launch a credit card offering in Brazil, expanding the bank&amp;rsquo;s fintech offerings. The launch of the credit card is expected next week and will be managed by Banco Bradesco, powered by Mastercard. The collaboration with Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:1058
Chances: IonQ&amp;rsquo;s leadership in the quantum computing industry positions the company well to capitalize on the growing demand for advanced computing solutions. The partnership with South Korea&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Science and ICT reflects IonQ&amp;rsquo;s commitment to education and the development of a local quantum ecosystem, potentially expanding its market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
