<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partnership on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/partnership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partnership on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/partnership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TECK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teck/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Teck Resources collaborates with NORDEN to reduce carbon emissions in its steelmaking coal supply chain. Teck Resources works on reducing carbon dioxide emissions in the steelmaking coal supply chain through a partnership with NORDEN. Teck Resources aims to reduce annual emissions from its shipments handled by NORDEN by 25%, contributing to environmental sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-11
Chances: JD.com&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Gucci for launching a digital flagship store on its platform could provide a boost to the company&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce presence. JD.com&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report beat expectations, indicating strong financial performance and growth in revenue. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to maintain revenue growth, despite broader economic concerns in China, demonstrates its resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: DraftKings has entered a significant partnership with Penn Entertainment for sports betting, which could potentially lead to revenue growth. Despite recent stock price declines, DraftKings remains a major player in the sports betting industry, benefiting from the popularity of &amp;lsquo;parlays&amp;rsquo;. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnership with ESPN and its exclusive access to ESPN content through ESPN Bet could bring in new users and competition in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
