<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:09:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why 16 Should Be the Minimum Age for Social Media</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-16-should-be-the-minimum-age-for-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-16-should-be-the-minimum-age-for-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Why the Minimum Age for Social Media Should Be Raised to 16 The current minimum age for social media is 13, but many experts believe that this is too young. There is a growing body of research that suggests that social media can have negative effects on young people, including increased anxiety, depression, and cyberbullying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case for Banning TikTok and Other Socials for Kids Under 16</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-case-for-banning-tiktok-and-other-socials-for-kids-under-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-case-for-banning-tiktok-and-other-socials-for-kids-under-16/</guid>
      <description>The Case for Banning TikTok and Other Socials for Kids Under 16 Social media has become a ubiquitous part of our lives, but it is important to remember that it is not without its risks. In particular, social media can have a negative impact on children&amp;rsquo;s mental health, well-being, and data privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combative Consumers Change the Marketing Strategy for Target and Bud Light</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/combative-consumers-change-the-marketing-strategy-for-target-and-bud-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/combative-consumers-change-the-marketing-strategy-for-target-and-bud-light/</guid>
      <description>In the past, brands have often shrugged off criticism of their stands on social issues. However, the incidents involving Target and Bud Light show that even huge corporations can be made to bend. This is because consumers are increasingly using social media to voice their concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
