<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:04:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-39
Chances: Meta Platforms, Inc. is investing heavily in developing new tools and technologies, including a nudity filter in direct messages and AI research, indicating a commitment to innovation and growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing its own AI accelerator chip, Artemis, shows a strategic shift towards reducing reliance on external semiconductor companies and increasing efficiency and cost savings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/snap/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Snap (NYSE: SNAP) is making adjustments to its Solar System feature to address teen anxiety, showing a proactive approach to user concerns. The company is seeking large global agencies to sign on, indicating potential for expanding its user base and advertising reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Based on the average brokerage recommendation (ABR), Pinterest (PINS) should be added to one&amp;rsquo;s portfolio. The company&amp;rsquo;s business revived as efforts to bolster its platform bore fruit. Risks: Wall Street analysts&amp;rsquo; overly optimistic recommendations cast doubt on the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
