<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson recently completed the separation of Kenvue, which could lead to better focus and growth opportunities in the pharmaceutical and medical tech sectors. The company forecasts double-digit earnings growth after the Kenvue spin-off, indicating a positive outlook. J&amp;amp;J continues to generate strong free cash flow, supporting its dividend decisions and financial stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xp/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: XP Inc. reports positive earnings growth, indicating its potential for profitability and growth. The company announces the termination of a shareholders agreement, which might lead to strategic changes. Despite recent market cap fluctuations, institutional investors have benefited from long-term gains in XP Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Positive analyst recommendations and growth potential. Strong second quarter results and raised full-year outlook. Significant surge in stock price and momentum. Participation in secondary offerings and announcements. Recognition as a strong growth stock in various lists. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Strong performance with positive earnings and revenue growth. Investor confidence due to Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI potential and cheap valuation. Successful sustainability efforts and focus on AI technology. Trending stock with potential for growth and long-term investment. Positive industry outlook and potential for technology sector.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
