<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ultron Bloom on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/ultron-bloom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ultron Bloom on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:03:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/ultron-bloom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Emerging Markets: Trump&#39;s Policies and the Potential for Investors</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/emerging-markets-trumps-policies-and-the-potential-for-investors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/emerging-markets-trumps-policies-and-the-potential-for-investors/</guid>
      <description>Emerging Markets: Trump&amp;rsquo;s Policies and the Potential for Investors The election of Donald Trump has had a significant impact on global markets, and emerging markets are no exception. Trump&amp;rsquo;s policies, such as his focus on trade protectionism and his skepticism of free trade agreements, have raised concerns about the potential for negative impacts on emerging markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Africa’s Ramaphosa Is No Peacemaker for Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/south-africas-ramaphosa-is-no-peacemaker-for-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/south-africas-ramaphosa-is-no-peacemaker-for-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>South Africa’s Ramaphosa Attempts to Mediate Ukraine Conflict South African President Cyril Ramaphosa has been trying to mediate a ceasefire between Russia and Ukraine, but he has so far been unsuccessful. Ramaphosa has been criticized for his close ties to Russia, and some have accused him of being too soft on the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Museum&#39;s Big China Show Treads on Tricky Ground</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/british-museums-big-china-show-treads-on-tricky-ground/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/british-museums-big-china-show-treads-on-tricky-ground/</guid>
      <description>British Museum&amp;rsquo;s China Exhibition Treads on Tricky Ground The British Museum is hosting a major exhibition of Chinese art, but the show has been met with criticism from some Chinese scholars who say it does not do enough to address the country&amp;rsquo;s colonial past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change Policy: Where&#39;s the Justice in Net Zero?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-policy-wheres-the-justice-in-net-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-policy-wheres-the-justice-in-net-zero/</guid>
      <description>Climate Change Policy: Where&amp;rsquo;s the Justice in Net Zero? The concept of &amp;ldquo;net zero&amp;rdquo; emissions is gaining traction as a way to address climate change. However, there are concerns that net zero could exacerbate existing inequalities, particularly between rich and poor countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crypto Market Is a Gamble. Regulating It Shouldn&#39;t Be.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-crypto-market-is-a-gamble.-regulating-it-shouldnt-be./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-crypto-market-is-a-gamble.-regulating-it-shouldnt-be./</guid>
      <description>The Crypto Market Is a Gamble. Regulating It Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t Be. The cryptocurrency market is a highly volatile and risky place to invest. Prices can fluctuate wildly in a short period of time, and there is no guarantee that cryptocurrency will ever be a viable currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The EU&#39;s Grab for the Swaps Market Poses a Systemic Risk</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-eus-grab-for-the-swaps-market-poses-a-systemic-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-eus-grab-for-the-swaps-market-poses-a-systemic-risk/</guid>
      <description>The EU&amp;rsquo;s Grab for the Swaps Market Poses a Systemic Risk The European Union is trying to force all over-the-counter (OTC) interest rate swaps to be cleared through central clearing counterparties (CCPs). This could lead to a systemic risk if a CCP fails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Commerce: Are Open Digital Markets India&#39;s Next Big Thing?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/e-commerce-are-open-digital-markets-indias-next-big-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/e-commerce-are-open-digital-markets-indias-next-big-thing/</guid>
      <description>Open Digital Markets: India&amp;rsquo;s Next Big Thing in E-Commerce? Open digital markets (ODMs) are a new way of organizing e-commerce that allows buyers and sellers to connect directly with each other without the need for a third-party platform. ODMs have the potential to revolutionize e-commerce in India by making it more affordable, accessible, and transparent for buyers and sellers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Limit Talks: Biden&#39;s Debt Ceiling Crisis Has No Magical Solution</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-limit-talks-bidens-debt-ceiling-crisis-has-no-magical-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:15:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-limit-talks-bidens-debt-ceiling-crisis-has-no-magical-solution/</guid>
      <description>Debt Limit Crisis: No Easy Solution The U.S. government is approaching its debt limit, and there is no agreement between Democrats and Republicans on how to raise it. If the debt limit is not raised, the government will be unable to pay its bills and could default on its debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change and Natural Disasters: The Direst Predictions</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-and-natural-disasters-the-direst-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/climate-change-and-natural-disasters-the-direst-predictions/</guid>
      <description>Natural disasters seem to be on the rise, and many are wondering if climate change is the main cause. While it&amp;rsquo;s not the only factor, climate change is certainly exacerbating the problem. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how climate change is making natural disasters worse than our direst predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The World&#39;s Biggest IPO Market Is Not Healthy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-worlds-biggest-ipo-market-is-not-healthy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 20:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-worlds-biggest-ipo-market-is-not-healthy/</guid>
      <description>The initial public offering (IPO) market is a key barometer of the health of the global economy. In recent years, China has emerged as the dominant player in this market, with the number of IPOs in the country surging while the US and other regions have seen a decline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Ceiling Is Kevin McCarthy&#39;s Problem to Fix, Not Joe Biden&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-is-kevin-mccarthys-problem-to-fix-not-joe-bidens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:15:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-is-kevin-mccarthys-problem-to-fix-not-joe-bidens/</guid>
      <description>In recent weeks, the U.S. debt ceiling debate has been heating up, with Speaker Kevin McCarthy finding himself in a difficult position. The New York Times reports that McCarthy is facing a dilemma as he tries to navigate the competing interests of his Republican caucus and the Biden administration[^1].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Want a Break From the FDIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banks-want-a-break-from-the-fdic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:15:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banks-want-a-break-from-the-fdic/</guid>
      <description>In the wake of the recent regional banking crisis, banks are seeking relief from the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC), according to an article by Bloomberg [^1^][4]. The crisis has put a spotlight on the FDIC, which has been forced to rescue failed banks at a high cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Leave Curbing Inflation to the ECB: Opinion</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/dont-leave-curbing-inflation-to-the-ecb-opinion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 17:03:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/dont-leave-curbing-inflation-to-the-ecb-opinion/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t Leave Curbing Inflation to the ECB: Opinion The European Central Bank (ECB) is facing a difficult task in trying to curb inflation without causing a recession. The ECB has already raised interest rates, but it is not clear if this will be enough to bring inflation under control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBS&#39;s Sweet Deal for Credit Suisse Is Looking Even Sweeter</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ubss-sweet-deal-for-credit-suisse-is-looking-even-sweeter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 13:50:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ubss-sweet-deal-for-credit-suisse-is-looking-even-sweeter/</guid>
      <description>UBS&amp;rsquo;s Sweet Deal for Credit Suisse Is Looking Even Sweeter UBS&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Credit Suisse is looking like a better deal for UBS as the value of Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s assets has declined. UBS is expected to pay around $3.5 billion for Credit Suisse, which is a fraction of the $20 billion that Credit Suisse was worth just a few years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Regulation: OpenAI&#39;s Sam Altman Is the Wrong Person to Ask</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ai-regulation-openais-sam-altman-is-the-wrong-person-to-ask/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 12:26:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ai-regulation-openais-sam-altman-is-the-wrong-person-to-ask/</guid>
      <description>AI Regulation: OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Sam Altman Is the Wrong Person to Ask In a recent article, Bloomberg argued that Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI, is not the right person to ask about AI regulation. The article cites several reasons for this, including Altman&amp;rsquo;s close ties to the tech industry, his lack of experience in government, and his past statements about AI regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric Vehicles Are an Imperfect Answer to Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/electric-vehicles-are-an-imperfect-answer-to-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 12:00:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/electric-vehicles-are-an-imperfect-answer-to-climate-change/</guid>
      <description>Electric Vehicles Are an Imperfect Answer to Climate Change Electric vehicles (EVs) are becoming increasingly popular as a way to reduce greenhouse gas emissions. EVs produce zero emissions while driving, which makes them a promising option for reducing our reliance on fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats Can Confirm More Judges by Ditching the Blue Slip</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-can-confirm-more-judges-by-ditching-the-blue-slip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:30:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-can-confirm-more-judges-by-ditching-the-blue-slip/</guid>
      <description>Democrats Can Confirm More Judges by Ditching the Blue Slip The blue slip is a Senate tradition that allows home-state senators to block judicial nominees. Democrats have been unable to confirm many of their judicial nominees because of the blue slip. Democrats can confirm more judges by getting rid of the blue slip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Writers’ Strike, AI and a Silly Hollywood Myth</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-writers-strike-ai-and-a-silly-hollywood-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 11:00:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-writers-strike-ai-and-a-silly-hollywood-myth/</guid>
      <description>The Writers’ Strike, AI, and a Silly Hollywood Myth In 2007, Hollywood writers went on strike, shutting down production on many TV shows and movies. The strike was caused by a dispute between the writers and the studios over payment for new media, such as streaming and DVD sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mammogram Recommendations for Women Under 50</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mammogram-recommendations-for-women-under-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 10:30:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mammogram-recommendations-for-women-under-50/</guid>
      <description>![](news photo about mammograms,breast cancer,women&amp;rsquo;s health &amp;ndash;ar 2:11.webp)
Mammogram Recommendations for Women Under 50 Mammogram screening is a controversial topic, especially for women under 50. The American Cancer Society (ACS) recommends that women start getting mammograms at age 45, while the U.S. Preventive Services Task Force (USPSTF) recommends that women start getting mammograms at age 50.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quirky Federal Spending Speeds Up Debt-Ceiling Clash</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/quirky-federal-spending-speeds-up-debt-ceiling-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/quirky-federal-spending-speeds-up-debt-ceiling-clash/</guid>
      <description>Quirky Federal Spending Speeds Up Debt-Ceiling Clash A bigger-than-anticipated federal deficit has pushed up the deadline for dealing with the US debt ceiling from sometime in the third quarter to any day now, according to a recent article published on Bloomberg Opinion ^1^.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq 100 Rally Shows the Bears Got Up Too Early</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nasdaq-100-rally-shows-the-bears-got-up-too-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nasdaq-100-rally-shows-the-bears-got-up-too-early/</guid>
      <description>The Nasdaq 100 Index has been making headlines lately with its impressive performance this year, gaining 23% and edging close to a 52-week high. This has caused some to question the validity of earlier predictions of a bear market, and has led to discussions on the importance of timing in stock market predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Ukraine, Technology Only Thickens the Fog of War</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/in-ukraine-technology-only-thickens-the-fog-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/in-ukraine-technology-only-thickens-the-fog-of-war/</guid>
      <description>The conflict in Ukraine has been ongoing for years, with no clear end in sight. As technology advances, it has become increasingly intertwined with the conflict, with both sides utilizing it to gain an advantage.
On May 17, 2023, Bloomberg published an article titled &amp;ldquo;In Ukraine, Technology Only Thickens the Fog of War&amp;rdquo; by Leonid Bershidsky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling Failed With EMs and Will Again With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/decoupling-failed-with-ems-and-will-again-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/decoupling-failed-with-ems-and-will-again-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Decoupling, or the idea of disentangling one country&amp;rsquo;s economy from another&amp;rsquo;s, has been a topic of much debate in recent years, particularly in regards to China. Some argue that decoupling from China is necessary to protect national security and intellectual property, while others believe it would be detrimental to global trade and economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo, Blackstone See Opportunities in Banks&#39; Troubles</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-blackstone-see-opportunities-in-banks-troubles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-blackstone-see-opportunities-in-banks-troubles/</guid>
      <description>In recent news, Apollo, Blackstone, and other private credit funds have expressed interest in the banking industry as banks face struggles in the current economic climate. According to Bloomberg, Apollo and Blackstone are among firms pitching private debt to public companies, while also bidding for assets from Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) [1][2][3][4][5].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Iran, Venezuela Confound Oil Output Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russia-iran-venezuela-confound-oil-output-forecasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russia-iran-venezuela-confound-oil-output-forecasts/</guid>
      <description>The International Energy Agency (IEA) has lifted its forecast for Russian, Iranian, and Venezuelan output in 2023 by a combined 1.3 million barrels a day, reaching an annual average of 14.3 million barrels a day, according to a recent article on Bloomberg 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Wants to Become a Heat-Pump Billionaire?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/who-wants-to-become-a-heat-pump-billionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/who-wants-to-become-a-heat-pump-billionaire/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The energy transition is a hot topic in today&amp;rsquo;s world, and with good reason. As we move towards a more sustainable future, there are many opportunities for investors to profit from this shift. One such opportunity is in the field of heat pumps, which are becoming an increasingly popular way to heat and cool homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Pursuing Peace, Japan&#39;s Leader Must Also Prepare for War</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/in-pursuing-peace-japans-leader-must-also-prepare-for-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/in-pursuing-peace-japans-leader-must-also-prepare-for-war/</guid>
      <description>On May 16th, 2023, The Washington Post published an article titled &amp;ldquo;In Pursuing Peace, Japan&amp;rsquo;s Leader Must Also Prepare for War&amp;rdquo; by an unknown author[^1^][1]. The article talks about how Fumio Kishida, Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader, is working towards nuclear disarmament while simultaneously moving the nation closer to being the world&amp;rsquo;s largest nuclear power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Shouldn&#39;t Dismiss China&#39;s Ukraine Peace Bid</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-shouldnt-dismiss-chinas-ukraine-peace-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:00:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-shouldnt-dismiss-chinas-ukraine-peace-bid/</guid>
      <description>On May 16, 2023, Bloomberg published an op-ed titled &amp;ldquo;US Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t Dismiss China&amp;rsquo;s Ukraine Peace Bid,&amp;rdquo; which argues that the United States and its allies should not dismiss China&amp;rsquo;s proposal for a ceasefire in Ukraine. Instead, the US should engage with China to turn its rhetoric of peace into action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
