<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ultron Bloom on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/author/ultron-bloom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ultron Bloom on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:16:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/author/ultron-bloom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Travel Hell Is Wreaking Havoc for Low-Cost Airlines, Too</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/travel-hell-is-wreaking-havoc-for-low-cost-airlines-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:16:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/travel-hell-is-wreaking-havoc-for-low-cost-airlines-too/</guid>
      <description>2023 has been a year of mixed fortunes for the airline industry. On one hand, there are signs of strong demand for summer travel, particularly in Asia, as reported by Bloomberg [1]. On the other hand, there have been high-profile incidents of flight cancellations and service meltdowns, such as the one experienced by Southwest Airlines in December 2022, as reported by CNN [2].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renewables: No Country Will Be the Saudi Arabia of Green Hydrogen</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/renewables-no-country-will-be-the-saudi-arabia-of-green-hydrogen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:13:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/renewables-no-country-will-be-the-saudi-arabia-of-green-hydrogen/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent article on Moneycontrol, the green hydrogen trade will not have a dominant country because hydrogen will be used close to where it is produced. This means that countries rich in cheap renewables, such as Australia, Brazil, and Chile, hope to become hydrogen hubs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden&#39;s Economic Decoupling Plan With China Won&#39;t Work</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bidens-economic-decoupling-plan-with-china-wont-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:09:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bidens-economic-decoupling-plan-with-china-wont-work/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The economic relationship between the United States and China has been fraught with tension for some time now, with both countries imposing tariffs and other trade restrictions on each other. Recently, President Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has taken steps towards what they call &amp;ldquo;economic decoupling&amp;rdquo; with China, a policy aimed at reducing the US&amp;rsquo;s dependence on China&amp;rsquo;s economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Wants to Become a Heat-Pump Billionaire?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/who-wants-to-become-a-heat-pump-billionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:04:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/who-wants-to-become-a-heat-pump-billionaire/</guid>
      <description>Heat pumps are quickly becoming a popular solution for reducing carbon emissions, and according to a Bloomberg report, they could also be a lucrative investment opportunity for those looking to profit from the energy transition.
The report by Chris Bryant^1^ discusses the growing demand for heat pumps, which are devices that use electricity to move heat from one place to another, thereby heating or cooling a space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Shouldn&#39;t Dismiss China&#39;s Ukraine Peace Bid</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-shouldnt-dismiss-chinas-ukraine-peace-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:55:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-shouldnt-dismiss-chinas-ukraine-peace-bid/</guid>
      <description>In a recent article published on Bloomberg, the author argues that the US and its allies should not dismiss China&amp;rsquo;s calls for a ceasefire in Ukraine. Despite continuing to ship weapons to Ukraine, the author suggests that the US and its European allies should be encouraging deeper Chinese engagement in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Pursuing Peace, Japan&#39;s Leader Must Also Prepare for War</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/in-pursuing-peace-japans-leader-must-also-prepare-for-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:43:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/in-pursuing-peace-japans-leader-must-also-prepare-for-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The G-7 meeting in Hiroshima has brought attention to Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader, Fumio Kishida, and his pursuit of peace while also preparing for war. In a recent article published on Bloomberg, the author discusses the delicate balance that Kishida must strike in order to achieve his life&amp;rsquo;s goal of nuclear disarmament while also moving Japan closer to being the world&amp;rsquo;s largest nuclear power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Worry, Food Prices Will Stop Going Up Soon</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/dont-worry-food-prices-will-stop-going-up-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:22:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/dont-worry-food-prices-will-stop-going-up-soon/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bloomberg.com recently published an analysis titled &amp;quot;Don&#39;t Worry, Food Prices Will Stop Going Up Soon&amp;quot; [^1^][^2^][^4^]. In this article, the author suggests that supermarkets have started to trim prices, indicating that the upward trend in food prices may soon come to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo, Blackstone See Opportunities in Banks&#39; Troubles</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-blackstone-see-opportunities-in-banks-troubles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:19:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-blackstone-see-opportunities-in-banks-troubles/</guid>
      <description>Private lenders Apollo Global Management and Blackstone Inc. are exploring financing options with publicly listed companies in Europe as borrowing costs spiked and equity valuations fell. This move comes amid growing concerns about the banking industry as traditional banks struggle with a range of issues, including low interest rates, rising competition from fintech startups, and mounting regulatory pressures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Iran, Venezuela Confound Oil Output Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russia-iran-venezuela-confound-oil-output-forecasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:16:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russia-iran-venezuela-confound-oil-output-forecasts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The oil market is facing uncertainty due to the unpredictable behavior of Russia, Iran, and Venezuela. According to recent reports1[2^], the International Energy Agency (IEA) has been revising its forecast for oil output from these countries, confounding experts&amp;rsquo; predictions. The following blog post examines the current situation in the oil market and the reasons behind the unexpected changes in oil output from Russia, Iran, and Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling Failed With EMs and Will Again With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/decoupling-failed-with-ems-and-will-again-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:12:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/decoupling-failed-with-ems-and-will-again-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is where you introduce the topic of your blog post and provide some context. ## Section 1 This is where you can start diving into the details of your topic. You can use subheadings to break up your post into sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Ukraine, Technology Only Thickens the Fog of War</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/in-ukraine-technology-only-thickens-the-fog-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:10:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/in-ukraine-technology-only-thickens-the-fog-of-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The ongoing conflict between Russia and Ukraine has been making headlines for years now. With the advent of technology, one would expect the conflict to become more transparent, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. In the article titled &amp;ldquo;In Ukraine, Technology Only Thickens the Fog of War&amp;rdquo; by Leonid Bershidsky on Bloomberg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Consumers Have Some $500 Billion of Excess Savings to Spend</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-consumers-have-some-500-billion-of-excess-savings-to-spend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:52:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-consumers-have-some-500-billion-of-excess-savings-to-spend/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent report by the San Francisco Federal Reserve, US households still have approximately $500 billion in excess savings compared to before the COVID-19 pandemic. This surplus could support consumer spending late into this year and beyond.
The Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco estimated that there is still a significant amount of excess savings in the economy, which is over and above what people would normally save.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
