<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>REITs on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/reits/</link>
    <description>Recent content in REITs on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:03:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/reits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:112
Chances: Investors looking to own winning stocks need to know which sectors are outperforming other sectors when making purchase decisions. The upheavals of 2023 rattled the housing market, witnessing soaring mortgage rates and stalled sales. A silver lining emerges with mortgage rates finally relenting and a subtle yet promising upswing in home sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/drh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/drh/</guid>
      <description>score:-68
Chances: Wolfe Research initiated coverage of four hotel REITs this week, indicating potential opportunity in the sector. DiamondRock Hospitality Company is set to report financial results for the fourth quarter, providing insight into its performance. Comparable total revenues for DiamondRock Hospitality remain flat to 2022 and 12% higher than 2019, indicating potential stability and growth in the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:86
Chances: Recovery in group and business transient travel demand, capital-recycling efforts and healthy balance sheet strength are likely to drive Host Hotels&amp;rsquo; performance in the quarters ahead. The pause in interest rate hikes and the likelihood of interest rate cuts in 2024 have generated strong appreciation of REITs, including Host Hotels, across multiple subsectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-132
Chances: Realty Income Corp. is acquiring Spirit Realty Capital, which indicates potential for growth and expansion in its real estate portfolio. The Federal Open Market Committee&amp;rsquo;s dovish outlook and prediction of rate cuts could benefit Realty Income Corp. as a real estate company with a focus on generating dependable monthly cash dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:294
Chances: AGNC Investment (AGNC) is a wise investment option at present due to an active portfolio-management strategy, decent liquidity and an attractive ROE. MPLX should have plenty of fuel to continue growing its big-time payout. Compared to this past year, 2024 is expected to be much better for the economy, and that means it will look even better for the stock market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
