<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Streaming on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/streaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Streaming on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/streaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CMCSA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cmcsa/</guid>
      <description>score:-75
Chances: Comcast&amp;rsquo;s (CMCSA) fourth-quarter earnings reflect a continued strength in wireless subscribers, offset by a declining broadband subscriber base. The company also added around 3 million subscribers to its streaming platform Peacock, a 50% year-over-year gain. Risks: While the top- and bottom-line numbers for Comcast (CMCSA) give a sense of how the business performed, it could be worth looking at how some of its key metrics compare to Wall Street estimates and year-ago values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:22
Chances: Disney&amp;rsquo;s business segments including entertainment, ESPN, and parks, experiences, and products provide a diverse revenue stream. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into direct-to-consumer services and international markets presents growth opportunities. Potential for positive impact from new board members and shareholder activism. Risks: Cancellation of the planned merger with Sony Group Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wbd/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: The merger between Warner Bros. Discovery and Paramount Global could result in a stronger position in the streaming world due to potential reshaping and reevaluation of portfolios Future mergers in the media and entertainment industry could lead to a lot of activity and potential bundling and deconsolidation of assets The opportunity for consumers to choose their own bundles in the future could be a positive development for the industry Risks: The disappointing box office performance of Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom raises concerns about the industry&amp;rsquo;s understanding of audience preferences Cord cutting, tough ad environment, and pressure to turn profits pose challenges for companies in the media and entertainment sector The unpredictability of box office performance and the potential impact on theater revenues may create uncertainty in the short term Score:27 chances characters count - risks characters count = 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nflx/</guid>
      <description>score:115
Chances: Netflix (NFLX) stock has continued its robust rally off its mid-2022 lows. With Squid Game: The Challenge reality series leaning on the strength of its impressive Squid Game franchise and new plans for its video game business, it’s hard not to feel better about the company’s growth story moving into 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
