<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stock Price on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stock-price/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stock Price on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stock-price/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DIS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dis/</guid>
      <description>score:221
Chances: Peltz&amp;rsquo;s pressure did help spur some change at Disney, not to mention, boost the stock price Shareholders stuck with Iger and Disney over Peltz for preserving the Disney brand, liking Bob Iger, and Peltz not having entertainment experience Activists will continue to circle The Walt Disney Company unless the share price keeps going up, putting pressure on Bob Iger until 2026 The fight may not be over for Disney, and succession planning, cost-cutting, and revenue growth are urgent needs Risks: Pressure on Bob Iger until 2026 when his contract expires will stay really tight Peltz&amp;rsquo;s involvement could continue to create uncertainty and push for more changes at Disney Potential deal for Paramount (PARA) could impact Disney&amp;rsquo;s position in the entertainment industry Score:221 chances characters count - risks characters count = 221</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:291
Chances: Rivian stock has dropped around 50% to begin 2024, after surging to end 2023, and is now 80% below its IPO price of $78. Earlier this month, the electric-car maker Rivian announced its new SUV, the R2 — a $45,000 family hauler that will get more than 300 miles in range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lbrt/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: The stock price of Liberty Energy Inc. (LBRT) is up by 14% this week, indicating positive momentum. The company announced full year and fourth quarter 2023 financial and operational results, suggesting potential growth and stability. The Board of Directors has increased its share repurchase authorization to $750 million, indicating confidence in the company&amp;rsquo;s future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
