<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mexico on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/mexico/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mexico on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:11:12 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/mexico/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:11:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</guid>
      <description>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time Mexico&amp;rsquo;s central bank, Banxico, has signaled that it will keep interest rates high for a long period of time in order to tame inflation.
The bank&amp;rsquo;s decision comes as inflation in Mexico has reached a 20-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Pitches Automakers GM, Toyota on Developing Southern States</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mexico-pitches-automakers-gm-toyota-on-developing-southern-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mexico-pitches-automakers-gm-toyota-on-developing-southern-states/</guid>
      <description>Mexico Pitches Automakers GM, Toyota on Developing Southern States Mexico is in talks with General Motors (GM) and Toyota Motor Corporation (TMC) about investing in a narrow strip of land in southern Mexico. The government is hoping to attract investment to the region, which has been lagging behind the rest of the country in terms of economic development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popocatépetl Volcano in Mexico: What We Know About Eruption Alert Level</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/popocat%C3%A9petl-volcano-in-mexico-what-we-know-about-eruption-alert-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 15:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/popocat%C3%A9petl-volcano-in-mexico-what-we-know-about-eruption-alert-level/</guid>
      <description>Popocatépetl Volcano in Mexico: Increased Activity and Eruption Alert Level Popocatépetl, a volcano near Mexico City, has been exhibiting increased activity in recent weeks. This includes increased ashfall and seismic activity. As a result, authorities have raised the eruption alert level to Yellow Phase 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
