<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Banking on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/banking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Banking on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/banking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IBN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: ICICI Bank Ltd. is well positioned for above-average growth in financials. Efforts to bolster fee income, domestic loan dependence, and digitization of banking services will support ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s financials. Risks: Concerns related to higher restructuring costs may pose a risk for ICICI Bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Investors seeking high dividend-yielding stocks may find New York Community Bancorp (NYCB) attractive The joint venture between Blackstone and CPPIB winning a stake in the commercial property loans portfolio is a positive development for NYCB Banco Santander&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a 20% stake in a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
