<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Banking on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/banking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Banking on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:05:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/banking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: Increased operating revenues and managerial financial margin are partially offset by escalating costs for Itau Unibanco (ITUB) in fourth-quarter 2023. Itaú Unibanco Holding S.A. (NYSE:ITUB) recently announced a dividend of $0.23 per share, payable on 2024-03-15, with the ex-dividend date set for 2024-02-22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:-75
Chances: Bank Bradesco SA is one of the largest banks in Brazil, providing financial and insurance services across the country. The company&amp;rsquo;s diverse portfolio includes banking activities, insurance products, and pension plans. Latin American stocks and currencies have been climbing, indicating a positive market trend for companies like Bank Bradesco SA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cm/</guid>
      <description>score:149
Chances: CIBC has provided growth financing to InsightRX, a software company leveraging quantitative pharmacology and AI to improve therapeutic decision-making, indicating the bank&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and investment in emerging technologies. The smaller-than-expected increase in US crude stockpiles has added to signs of a tightening physical market, which could positively impact the bank&amp;rsquo;s capital markets and direct financial services segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: ICICI Bank Ltd. is well positioned for above-average growth in financials. Efforts to bolster fee income, domestic loan dependence, and digitization of banking services will support ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s financials. Risks: Concerns related to higher restructuring costs may pose a risk for ICICI Bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
