<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Call on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Call on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Revenues rise in Q2 2023 despite stock slide. Positive impact of new partnership to research hypersonic travel. Boeing awarded military contract for Spirit-tied P-8 aircraft trainers. Expectation of ramping up 737 Max production by more than 20% by Boeing. Striking workers at a key Boeing supplier approve a new contract and will return to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
