<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Call on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Call on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:636
Chances: Increase in Kinross&amp;rsquo; production in Q2 due to higher grades and recoveries at specific locations. Announcement of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and transcript. Renewal of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s normal course issuer bid (NCIB) program. Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s delivery of positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:1601
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line (NCL) welcomes the first guests aboard the all-new Norwegian Viva, marking an important milestone. Discussing the inclusion of Carnival, Norwegian Cruise Line, and Gentherm in the Zacks Screen of the Week article. Exploring the strong performance of travel stocks due to consumers&amp;rsquo; confidence in travel despite economic concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VALE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vale/</guid>
      <description>score:153
Chances: Investment fund Engine No. 1&amp;rsquo;s interest in Vale SA&amp;rsquo;s base metals business suggests potential for strategic deals in critical minerals. Vale&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the mining industry, especially in base metals, positions it for potential growth and partnerships. Vale&amp;rsquo;s earnings call provides insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance during the second quarter, offering investors valuable information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
