<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings call on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings call on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:22:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Revenues rise in Q2 2023 despite stock slide. Positive impact of new partnership to research hypersonic travel. Boeing awarded military contract for Spirit-tied P-8 aircraft trainers. Expectation of ramping up 737 Max production by more than 20% by Boeing. Striking workers at a key Boeing supplier approve a new contract and will return to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:-42
Chances: Surprise Q2 profit reported by Paramount Global. Revenues beat expectations in Q2 2023. Positive impact of subscriber growth on earnings. Company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to ending strikes and adjusting fall lineup. Paramount Global to sell Simon &amp;amp; Schuster in a $1.62 billion deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Positive earnings call and financial results for Q2 2023. Potential for Bilibili to beat earnings estimates. Bilibili stock recently breaking out above key moving averages. Recent gains and improved sentiment among institutional owners. Publishing of positive environmental, social, and governance report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Ambev S.A. sees higher Q4 net profit, indicating growth in the company&amp;rsquo;s financials. Ambev&amp;rsquo;s market share gains are positively viewed, signaling potential business strength. ABEV&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2023 earnings call transcript is available, offering insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. Positive performance of Boston Beer (SAM) could impact ABEV&amp;rsquo;s growth strategies positively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
