<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Call on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Call on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:27:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-call/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1084 KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:1084
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper appointed Monique Oxender as Interim Chief Corporate Affairs Officer, which could bring positive changes and strengthen corporate responsibility. The company&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results showed increases in sales and earnings, driven by continued brand strength and significant pricing, indicating positive business performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0929 VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:929
Chances: V.F. Corp reported a daily gain of 3.78% with an EPS of $0.3, which could indicate positive market sentiment and earnings performance. VF Corp&amp;rsquo;s First Quarter 2024 Earnings Call indicated that the company beat earnings expectations, which could boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0791 GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:791
Chances: Goodyear India reported a higher quarterly profit as a drop in raw material prices helped make up for its first revenue fall in 12 quarters. The Goodyear Tire &amp;amp; Rubber Company reported results for the second quarter 2023 in an Investor Letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1006 MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:1006
Chances: Investors are looking to buy Marvell Technology stock as it is considered a relatively cheap AI stock, which could attract more investment. Marvell Technology is a top AI chip stock and a key player in the AI industry, which is experiencing a surge in stock values due to AI advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1177 GSAT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gsat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gsat/</guid>
      <description>score:1177
Chances: Globalstar delivered earnings and revenue surprises of 100% and 6.75%, respectively, for the quarter ended June 2023, indicating positive financial performance. Globalstar announced its engagement with Jason Bernstein to provide strategic advice on investor relations and outreach, showing efforts to strengthen investor relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0898 CFLT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cflt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cflt/</guid>
      <description>score:898
Chances: Confluent reported a strong set of beats on second-quarter numbers and provided strong guidance, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to navigate the tough economic climate. Rohan Sivaram has been named Confluent&amp;rsquo;s Chief Financial Officer, which could bring positive changes to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial management and strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1044 COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:1044
Chances: Coinbase Global reported improved losses in the second quarter, and its stock price target was raised, indicating potential positive developments for the company. Coinbase is creating diverse revenue streams, which may contribute to its future growth if the crypto industry experiences positive developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0889 SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:889
Chances: Despite Shopify posting better-than-expected second-quarter revenue and adjusted earnings per share, analysts upgraded their 12-month price targets for the stock after digesting the solid results. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter results benefited from growth in merchant solutions revenues and an expanding merchant base. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s President, Harley Finkelstein, discussed how the e-commerce company is approaching a potential U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
