<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisitions on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisitions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisitions on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:02:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisitions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oln/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oln/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Olin Corp. announces shakeup in C-suite Olin Announces CEO Transition Plan Olin (OLN) Acquires White Flyer Targets to Grow Winchester Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Julie Piggott Appointed to Olin&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors Risks: Why Olin Stock Is Down Today Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Olin (OLN) Misses Q1 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Olin (OLN) to Close Epoxy Facilities in Restructuring Program An Intrinsic Calculation For Olin Corporation (NYSE:OLN) Suggests It&amp;rsquo;s 49% Undervalued Score:-43 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Schwab Q3 trader sentiment survey indicates improving outlook. Bond investors show confidence in Schwab after cost-cutting. Acquisitions to aid Schwab&amp;rsquo;s top line amid cost woes. Schwab&amp;rsquo;s asset growth slows down. Crypto exchange EDX Markets taps Anchorage as custody provider. Risks: Schwab caught up in banking selloff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: Newmont receives clearance from regulatory authorities for acquisitions. Positive analysis of Newmont&amp;rsquo;s potential value and growth. Market edge highlights Newmont&amp;rsquo;s performance and potential. Strategic acquisitions and clearances enhance Newmont&amp;rsquo;s position. Upgrade to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; recommendation due to positive factors. Risks: Missed earnings estimates due to disruptions and higher costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
