<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisitions on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisitions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisitions on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:54:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisitions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: An intrinsic calculation suggests that Occidental Petroleum Corporation (OXY) is potentially undervalued by 32%, which could present a buying opportunity for investors. Occidental Petroleum offers dividends, making it an attractive option for income-focused investors. The company is making acquisitions and investments, such as the acquisition of Carbon Engineering, indicating a strategic focus on growth and innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jci/</guid>
      <description>score:13
Chances: Johnson Controls has reported strong revenue and EPS growth in Q3, which could indicate a positive outlook for the company. The acquisition of FM:Systems for $455 million shows the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its digital buildings capabilities. Johnson Controls is the winner of the 2023 Microsoft Global Independent Software Vendor Partner of the Year, highlighting its industry recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLVT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clvt/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Clarivate&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the data and analytics sector positions it well to capitalize on growing demand for research and information services. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships and acquisitions, such as the integration of ProQuest Dissertations and Theses Global, enhance its offerings and market reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TLRY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tlry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tlry/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: The DEA&amp;rsquo;s recommendation for the rescheduling of marijuana suggests potential progress towards legalization. Tilray&amp;rsquo;s expansion of its cannabis portfolio with new Redecan products in Canada may drive growth. Acquiring 8 big beer brands from Anheuser-Busch could have a positive impact on Tilray&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oln/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oln/</guid>
      <description>score:-43
Chances: Olin Corp. announces shakeup in C-suite Olin Announces CEO Transition Plan Olin (OLN) Acquires White Flyer Targets to Grow Winchester Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Julie Piggott Appointed to Olin&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors Risks: Why Olin Stock Is Down Today Olin Updates Second Quarter 2023 Outlook and Announces Additional Epoxy Restructuring Actions Olin (OLN) Misses Q1 Earnings and Revenue Estimates Olin (OLN) to Close Epoxy Facilities in Restructuring Program An Intrinsic Calculation For Olin Corporation (NYSE:OLN) Suggests It&amp;rsquo;s 49% Undervalued Score:-43 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HWM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hwm/</guid>
      <description>score:1110
Chances: Howmet Aerospace&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strength in commercial and defense aerospace, raising earnings guidance for 2023. Howmet Aerospace raises full-year profit and revenue forecast due to high demand for jet parts as plane manufacturers increase production. Positive outlook supported by extraordinary backlog of aircraft orders at Airbus and Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
