<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nvidia on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/nvidia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nvidia on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:06:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/nvidia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/soun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/soun/</guid>
      <description>score:142
Chances: SoundHound AI Inc. (NASDAQ: SOUN) reported substantial year-over-year gains in its recent financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2023. The company announced an innovative in-vehicle voice assistant using a large language model completely on the edge while running on the NVIDIA DRIVE platform, showcasing technological advancements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arm/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Nvidia has become the undisputed leader in a stock market powered by AI hopes. Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s blowout earnings show the fear of missing out in the stock market rally is alive and well. Shares of Asian chip makers rose after strong earnings from Nvidia buttressed expectations of booming global demand for semiconductors used in artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:121
Chances: Micron Technology, Inc. is experiencing a significant increase in demand for its memory and storage solutions, particularly with the incorporation of its high-performance LPDDR5X and UFS 4.0 into Samsung’s flagship Galaxy S24 series. The company has also started mass production of its HBM3E memory chips for Nvidia’s latest chip for artificial intelligence, which is expected to contribute to a boost in performance and reduce data center operating costs by consuming about 30% less power than competing offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
