<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 09:03:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 09:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:141
Chances: The average brokerage recommendation for Schlumberger (SLB) is equivalent to a Buy, indicating positive sentiment among analysts. According to recent Q4 2023 results, companies beat market expectations, suggesting a solid outlook for corporate earnings and potential upside for SLB. Elite blue-chip stocks like SLB can provide downside protection and substantial upside amid geopolitical and macroeconomic uncertainties in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: ET engages in natural gas pipeline transportation and transmission services Higher oil production and reduction in marketing purchases aid Q4 earnings The average brokerage recommendation for ET is equivalent to a Buy Investors may keep a tab on stocks like ET that have higher dividend yields compared to the industry Risks: Effectiveness of overly optimistic recommendations of Wall Street analysts is questionable Lower commodity price realizations affecting Q4 earnings Potential challenges in finding the right dividend stocks to invest in The overly optimistic recommendations of Wall Street analysts make the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric questionable Score:-33 chances characters count - risks characters count = -33</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: AppLovin has been hot, and the run higher might have some momentum. AppLovin (APP) has been upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reflecting growing optimism about the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings prospects. Risks: It&amp;rsquo;s always important to assess the risk involved in investing in a company, especially in the volatile tech sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/azn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/azn/</guid>
      <description>score:-135
Chances: AstraZeneca (AZN) closed at $65.95, indicating a +1.77% shift from the previous trading day. AstraZeneca (AZN) announces that it is buying vaccine company, Icosavax. The additional supply of RSV shot for infants by AstraZeneca and Sanofi indicates a positive outlook for meeting winter demand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
