<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>recession on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/recession/</link>
    <description>Recent content in recession on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:16:38 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/recession/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rates Latest: Inflation Hop, Policy Skip May Set Dissent Jump</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-inflation-hop-policy-skip-may-set-dissent-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:16:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-inflation-hop-policy-skip-may-set-dissent-jump/</guid>
      <description>Fed Faces Difficult Balancing Act as Inflation Rises
The Federal Reserve is facing a difficult balancing act as it tries to bring down inflation without causing a recession.
In recent months, the Fed has raised interest rates in an effort to cool the economy and bring down inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Global Economy Is Headed for a Hard Landing</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-global-economy-is-headed-for-a-hard-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-global-economy-is-headed-for-a-hard-landing/</guid>
      <description>The Global Economy Is Headed for a Hard Landing The global economy is facing a number of challenges, including rising inflation, interest rate hikes, and the war in Ukraine. These factors are raising concerns about a potential recession.
Inflation is at a 40-year high in the United States, and it is also rising in other parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Economy Remains &#39;Very, Very Hot,&#39; Larry Summers Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-economy-remains-very-very-hot-larry-summers-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-economy-remains-very-very-hot-larry-summers-says/</guid>
      <description>US Economy: Is a Recession Coming? Former US Treasury Secretary Larry Summers has warned that the US economy is &amp;ldquo;very, very hot&amp;rdquo; and that there is a risk of a recession. Summers said that the Federal Reserve needs to take aggressive action to cool the economy, including raising interest rates by more than 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Economy: Will There Be a Recession in 2023?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-economy-will-there-be-a-recession-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-economy-will-there-be-a-recession-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>UK Economy: Will There Be a Recession in 2023? The UK economy is facing a number of headwinds, including rising inflation, the war in Ukraine, and the cost of living crisis. Economists are increasingly concerned that the UK could enter a recession in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Coming &#39;Balance-Sheet Recession&#39;: New Economy Saturday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:45:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Coming Balance-Sheet Recession China&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing a number of challenges, including a slowdown in growth, rising debt, and a property market crisis. These challenges are likely to lead to a &amp;ldquo;balance-sheet recession&amp;rdquo; in China, which is a recession caused by a decline in corporate and household balance sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia&#39;s Crashing Yield Curve Doubts RBA Hope of No Recession</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australias-crashing-yield-curve-doubts-rba-hope-of-no-recession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:13:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australias-crashing-yield-curve-doubts-rba-hope-of-no-recession/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Yield Curve Invert, Recession Fears Rise
The yield curve in Australia has inverted, with short-term interest rates rising above long-term rates. This is a sign that investors are expecting a recession in the near future.
The Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA) has said that it does not expect a recession, but the inverted yield curve is casting doubt on that view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Weekend Reading: With Debt Debacle Done, It&#39;s Back to Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Inflation: The Fed&amp;rsquo;s Tough Balancing Act The Federal Reserve has signaled that it will begin to raise interest rates in March, which is likely to lead to higher borrowing costs for businesses and consumers. Inflation is still running at a high level, and there is a risk that it could get worse if the Fed raises rates too quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy-Biden Debt Deal Reached</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mccarthy-biden-debt-deal-reached/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:32:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mccarthy-biden-debt-deal-reached/</guid>
      <description>McCarthy-Biden Debt Deal Reached, Averting Potential Default House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) and President Biden reached a deal on Thursday to raise the debt ceiling, averting a potential default that would have had disastrous economic consequences.
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, enough to cover the government&amp;rsquo;s borrowing needs through December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:35:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</guid>
      <description>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year According to Moody&amp;rsquo;s, the UK is headed for a &amp;ldquo;mild recession&amp;rdquo; this year. The recession is expected to be caused by higher-than-expected inflation and rising interest rates. Inflation in the UK is currently at a 40-year high, and interest rates have been raised four times since December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEC&#43; Faces Oil Market Torn by Demand Rebound and Recession Risks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/opec&#43;-faces-oil-market-torn-by-demand-rebound-and-recession-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:29:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/opec&#43;-faces-oil-market-torn-by-demand-rebound-and-recession-risks/</guid>
      <description>OPEC+ Faces Oil Market Torn by Demand Rebound and Recession Risks OPEC+ is facing a difficult balancing act as the oil market is torn between demand rebounding from the COVID-19 pandemic and recession risks.
The International Energy Agency (IEA) has warned that the global oil market could be in a deficit of 1 million barrels per day (bpd) in the third quarter of 2023, if Russian output falls by 3 million bpd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germany&#39;s Sneeze May Give European Stocks a Cold</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</guid>
      <description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s Recession Could Hurt the Eurozone Germany, the eurozone&amp;rsquo;s largest economy, is in recession. The country&amp;rsquo;s GDP shrank by 0.3% in the first quarter of 2023, following a 0.5% decline in the fourth quarter of 2022.
The recession is being driven by a number of factors, including the global slowdown, the trade war between the United States and China, and the Brexit uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
