<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk&#39;s Twitter vs. Bad Bots: The Battle Goes On</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/elon-musks-twitter-vs.-bad-bots-the-battle-goes-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/elon-musks-twitter-vs.-bad-bots-the-battle-goes-on/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk Threatens to Walk Away from Twitter Deal Over Fake Accounts Elon Musk has threatened to walk away from his $44 billion deal to buy Twitter if the company does not provide more information about the number of fake accounts on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Food Prices Are Still Up 8.2% Online Even as Inflation Cools</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-food-prices-are-still-up-8.2-online-even-as-inflation-cools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-food-prices-are-still-up-8.2-online-even-as-inflation-cools/</guid>
      <description>Food Prices Still Rising Food prices online are still up 8.2% in May 2023, even as overall inflation has cooled. This is due to a number of factors, including higher transportation costs, rising labor costs, and supply chain disruptions.
The rising cost of food is putting a strain on household budgets, particularly for low-income families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egypt Says India Is Providing Credit Line in Boost to Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/egypt-says-india-is-providing-credit-line-in-boost-to-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:34:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/egypt-says-india-is-providing-credit-line-in-boost-to-economy/</guid>
      <description>I am a large language model, also known as a conversational AI or chatbot trained to be informative and comprehensive. I am trained on a massive amount of text data, and I am able to communicate and generate human-like text in response to a wide range of prompts and questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rates Latest: Inflation Hop, Policy Skip May Set Dissent Jump</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-inflation-hop-policy-skip-may-set-dissent-jump/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:16:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-inflation-hop-policy-skip-may-set-dissent-jump/</guid>
      <description>Fed Faces Difficult Balancing Act as Inflation Rises
The Federal Reserve is facing a difficult balancing act as it tries to bring down inflation without causing a recession.
In recent months, the Fed has raised interest rates in an effort to cool the economy and bring down inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</guid>
      <description>China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals China lost more of its share of US imports in 2022, falling to 50.7% from 53.5% in 2021. This trend has been ongoing since 2013, and is likely due to a number of factors, including rising labor costs in China, the US-China trade war, and the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Layoffs 2023: Cut Workers Now Called &#39;Among Those Impacted&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-layoffs-2023-cut-workers-now-called-among-those-impacted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-layoffs-2023-cut-workers-now-called-among-those-impacted/</guid>
      <description>Tech Layoffs 2023 Tech companies have been laying off workers in 2023, with more than 147,000 jobs lost so far. The layoffs have been driven by a number of factors, including the economic slowdown, rising inflation, and the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigerian Naira Devaluation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nigerian-naira-devaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:56:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nigerian-naira-devaluation/</guid>
      <description>The Nigerian naira has been devalued against the US dollar in recent months. The central bank of Nigeria has been trying to prop up the naira by selling dollars from its reserves. However, the naira has continued to weaken, and the central bank has been forced to raise interest rates in an effort to curb inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Summer: The Bloomberg Open, Americas Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hot-summer-the-bloomberg-open-americas-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:37:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hot-summer-the-bloomberg-open-americas-edition/</guid>
      <description>Bloomberg Open, Americas Edition The Bloomberg Open, Americas Edition is a new golf tournament that will be held in July 2023. The tournament will be played at the TPC Boston in Norton, Massachusetts. The field will include some of the top golfers in the world, including Dustin Johnson, Brooks Koepka, and Justin Thomas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to Allow South Korean, Taiwan Chip Makers to Keep Operations in China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-to-allow-south-korean-taiwan-chip-makers-to-keep-operations-in-china/</guid>
      <description>The United States has announced that it will allow South Korean and Taiwanese chip makers to keep their operations in China without reprisals. This is a reversal of previous U.S. policy, which had sought to discourage chipmakers from doing business in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Spilling Into Russian Regions Adds to Risks Haunting Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</guid>
      <description>The war in Ukraine is having a devastating impact on the Russian economy. The conflict has disrupted supply chains, led to shortages of goods and services, and caused inflation to soar. The Russian government has taken steps to try to mitigate the damage, but these measures have so far been largely unsuccessful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Korea Seeks Reclassification as Developed Market</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/south-korea-seeks-reclassification-as-developed-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/south-korea-seeks-reclassification-as-developed-market/</guid>
      <description>South Korea Seeks Reclassification as Developed Market South Korea is seeking to be reclassified as a developed market by MSCI, an investment research firm that provides influential market indexes. South Korea&amp;rsquo;s stock market is one of the largest in Asia, and the country is home to huge conglomerates including Samsung and Hyundai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Backs Away From Wages Focus, Bolstering Case for Rate Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-backs-away-from-wages-focus-bolstering-case-for-rate-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-backs-away-from-wages-focus-bolstering-case-for-rate-pause/</guid>
      <description>Fed Backs Away From Wages Focus, Bolstering Case for Rate Pause The Federal Reserve is backing away from its focus on wage growth as a guide for monetary policy, a shift that could bolster the case for a pause in interest rate hikes later this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iraq Approves Record Budget IMF Warns Could Destabilize Finances</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/iraq-approves-record-budget-imf-warns-could-destabilize-finances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:53:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/iraq-approves-record-budget-imf-warns-could-destabilize-finances/</guid>
      <description>Iraq Approves Record Budget, IMF Warns of Financial Destabilization The Iraqi parliament has approved a record budget for 2023 worth 199 trillion Iraqi dinars ($153 billion). The budget includes significant increases in spending on defense, security, and social programs. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) has warned that the budget could destabilize Iraq&amp;rsquo;s finances and lead to higher inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Tech Giants Are Slowly Cutting Off Hong Kong Internet Users</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/american-tech-giants-are-slowly-cutting-off-hong-kong-internet-users/</guid>
      <description>In a move that could have a significant impact on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy and innovation ecosystem, American tech giants are slowly cutting off internet users in the city.
Google and OpenAI have not rolled out AI chatbots to Hong Kong, putting it alongside mainland China and North Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious Package Halts Japan Court Proceedings for Abe Killing</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/suspicious-package-halts-japan-court-proceedings-for-abe-killing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:41:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/suspicious-package-halts-japan-court-proceedings-for-abe-killing/</guid>
      <description>Suspicious Package Halts Japan Court Proceedings for Abe Killing
Proceedings on the fatal shooting case of former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe were temporarily halted after a suspicious package was delivered to the Nara District Court premises.
The suspect, Tetsuya Yamagami, had been due in court for pretrial consultations when the incident occurred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungary&#39;s Economy Chief Floats Idea of Raising Inflation Target</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hungarys-economy-chief-floats-idea-of-raising-inflation-target/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 06:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hungarys-economy-chief-floats-idea-of-raising-inflation-target/</guid>
      <description>Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Economy Chief Floats Idea of Raising Inflation Target
Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Economy Minister, Marton Nagy, has suggested that the country&amp;rsquo;s inflation target should be raised from 3% to 4%.
Nagy said that the current target is no longer realistic, given the current high inflation levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Samsung Exec Accused of Building Copycat Chip Plant in China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ex-samsung-exec-accused-of-building-copycat-chip-plant-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 06:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ex-samsung-exec-accused-of-building-copycat-chip-plant-in-china/</guid>
      <description>Former Samsung Executive Accused of Stealing Trade Secrets A former Samsung executive has been accused of stealing trade secrets and building a copycat chip plant in China.
The executive, who has not been named, is alleged to have stolen blueprints and designs for Samsung&amp;rsquo;s semiconductor plant in Xi&amp;rsquo;an, China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Global Economy Is Headed for a Hard Landing</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-global-economy-is-headed-for-a-hard-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-global-economy-is-headed-for-a-hard-landing/</guid>
      <description>The Global Economy Is Headed for a Hard Landing The global economy is facing a number of challenges, including rising inflation, interest rate hikes, and the war in Ukraine. These factors are raising concerns about a potential recession.
Inflation is at a 40-year high in the United States, and it is also rising in other parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe&#39;s Risky Plan to Avert a Winter Energy Crisis: Stash Gas in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/europes-risky-plan-to-avert-a-winter-energy-crisis-stash-gas-in-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/europes-risky-plan-to-avert-a-winter-energy-crisis-stash-gas-in-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>Europe&amp;rsquo;s Risky Plan to Avert a Winter Energy Crisis: Stash Gas in Ukraine Europe is facing a potential winter energy crisis due to the war in Ukraine and the uncertainty of Russian gas supplies. One way to avert the crisis is to store gas in Ukraine, which has the largest underground gas storage system in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qatar&#39;s Top Dealmakers Get Ready for a Spending Power Boost</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/qatars-top-dealmakers-get-ready-for-a-spending-power-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/qatars-top-dealmakers-get-ready-for-a-spending-power-boost/</guid>
      <description>Qatar&amp;rsquo;s Spending Power Boost Qatar is set to receive a spending power boost as the country prepares to host the FIFA World Cup in 2022. The government has set aside $200 billion for infrastructure projects related to the World Cup, and this is expected to lead to a surge in demand for goods and services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Economy Remains &#39;Very, Very Hot,&#39; Larry Summers Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-economy-remains-very-very-hot-larry-summers-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-economy-remains-very-very-hot-larry-summers-says/</guid>
      <description>US Economy: Is a Recession Coming? Former US Treasury Secretary Larry Summers has warned that the US economy is &amp;ldquo;very, very hot&amp;rdquo; and that there is a risk of a recession. Summers said that the Federal Reserve needs to take aggressive action to cool the economy, including raising interest rates by more than 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBOC in Focus: Will it Cut Policy Rate This Week? (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pboc-in-focus-will-it-cut-policy-rate-this-week-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pboc-in-focus-will-it-cut-policy-rate-this-week-video/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s PBOC May Cut Interest Rates The People&amp;rsquo;s Bank of China (PBOC) is in focus this week as investors wait to see if the central bank will cut its one-year policy rate. Bloomberg Economics believes that the PBOC is likely to cut the rate by 25 basis points to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Korea Warns of Financial Risk as Real Estate Loans Fail</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bank-of-korea-warns-of-financial-risk-as-real-estate-loans-fail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bank-of-korea-warns-of-financial-risk-as-real-estate-loans-fail/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Korea Warns of Financial Risk Bank of Korea Governor Rhee Chang-yong has warned of growing financial sector risks amid a rise in real estate loan delinquencies. The share of non-bank financial institutions has increased, making it more difficult for the BOK to address financial risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Things You Need to Know to Start Your Day</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/five-things-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:33:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/five-things-you-need-to-know-to-start-your-day/</guid>
      <description>I am a large language model, also known as a conversational AI or chatbot trained to be informative and comprehensive. I am trained on a massive amount of text data, and I am able to communicate and generate human-like text in response to a wide range of prompts and questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLIV Pulse: Have Firms Raised Prices More Than Needed? (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mliv-pulse-have-firms-raised-prices-more-than-needed-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:31:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mliv-pulse-have-firms-raised-prices-more-than-needed-video/</guid>
      <description>Have Firms Raised Prices More Than Needed? A recent survey of investors by Bloomberg&amp;rsquo;s Markets Live Pulse found that 90% believe companies have raised prices in excess of their own costs since the pandemic began in 2020. Almost four out of five investors said that tight monetary policy is the right way to tackle profit-led inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Economy to Grow Faster, Singapore to Slow, Survey Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hong-kong-economy-to-grow-faster-singapore-to-slow-survey-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hong-kong-economy-to-grow-faster-singapore-to-slow-survey-says/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong Economy to Grow Faster Than Singapore in 2023 A recent survey of economists by Bloomberg predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s economy will grow by 4.6% in 2023, up from a previous estimate of 3.4%. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy is expected to grow by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brexit Hurts UK Investment Appeal, Hasn&#39;t Reduced Tax or Regulation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brexit-hurts-uk-investment-appeal-hasnt-reduced-tax-or-regulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:01:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brexit-hurts-uk-investment-appeal-hasnt-reduced-tax-or-regulation/</guid>
      <description>Brexit Hurts UK Investment Appeal, Hasn&amp;rsquo;t Reduced Tax or Regulation A new study by the Centre for European Reform (CER) found that Brexit has hurt the UK&amp;rsquo;s investment appeal, with foreign direct investment (FDI) falling by 25% in the two years since the UK left the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Economy: Will There Be a Recession in 2023?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-economy-will-there-be-a-recession-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-economy-will-there-be-a-recession-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>UK Economy: Will There Be a Recession in 2023? The UK economy is facing a number of headwinds, including rising inflation, the war in Ukraine, and the cost of living crisis. Economists are increasingly concerned that the UK could enter a recession in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waitrose Cuts Prices of 200 Grocery Products</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/waitrose-cuts-prices-of-200-grocery-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/waitrose-cuts-prices-of-200-grocery-products/</guid>
      <description>Waitrose Cuts Prices of 200 Grocery Products
Waitrose, a British supermarket chain, has announced that it will be cutting the prices of 200 grocery products. The price cuts are being made in response to rising food inflation, which has reached its highest level in 45 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOJ&#39;s Ueda Likely to Hold With Bond Market on His Side For Now</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bojs-ueda-likely-to-hold-with-bond-market-on-his-side-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:50:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bojs-ueda-likely-to-hold-with-bond-market-on-his-side-for-now/</guid>
      <description>BOJ Likely to Keep Monetary Policy Unchanged The Bank of Japan (BOJ) is expected to keep its monetary policy unchanged at its meeting on Wednesday. Governor Kazuo Ueda has repeatedly signaled that the BOJ is in no rush to tighten policy, even as inflation rises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Key Charts to Watch in Global Commodity Markets This Week</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/five-key-charts-to-watch-in-global-commodity-markets-this-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/five-key-charts-to-watch-in-global-commodity-markets-this-week/</guid>
      <description>Five Key Charts to Watch in Global Commodity Markets This Week Oil, wheat, copper, gold, and natural gas are all expected to be volatile this week, as traders await the release of key economic data and monitor the ongoing geopolitical situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech, an Early Booster of Remote Work, Wants People Back in the Office</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-an-early-booster-of-remote-work-wants-people-back-in-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-an-early-booster-of-remote-work-wants-people-back-in-the-office/</guid>
      <description>Tech Companies Reverse Course on Remote Work Many tech companies that were early adopters of remote work are now requiring their employees to return to the office. This reversal is creating tension for workers who have adjusted to the flexibility of working from home and have arranged their lives accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Traders Are Daring to Defy Market Kingpin Saudi Arabia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/oil-traders-are-daring-to-defy-market-kingpin-saudi-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/oil-traders-are-daring-to-defy-market-kingpin-saudi-arabia/</guid>
      <description>Oil Traders Defy Saudi Arabia
Saudi Arabia, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest oil exporter, has pledged to unilaterally cut its July oil production to the lowest in over a decade. However, some traders are betting that the Saudis will not be able to sustain such a large cut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Sunday UK Briefing: Tories Risk &#39;Civil War&#39;; CBI Funding Fears</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-sunday-uk-briefing-tories-risk-civil-war-cbi-funding-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:31:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-sunday-uk-briefing-tories-risk-civil-war-cbi-funding-fears/</guid>
      <description>UK Politics in Turmoil: Tories Face &amp;lsquo;Civil War&amp;rsquo;, CBI Fears for Economy
The Conservative Party is facing a leadership crisis, with a group of Conservative MPs planning to submit letters of no confidence in Boris Johnson if he does not resign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There Are Good and Bad Ways to Share Passwords</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/there-are-good-and-bad-ways-to-share-passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/there-are-good-and-bad-ways-to-share-passwords/</guid>
      <description>How to Share Passwords Securely
When you need to share a password with someone, it&amp;rsquo;s important to do it securely. Here are some tips:
Don&amp;rsquo;t use email or SMS. These methods are not secure, as they can be intercepted by hackers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo Warns of Risks to Regional Banks from Commercial Real Estate</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-warns-of-risks-to-regional-banks-from-commercial-real-estate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-warns-of-risks-to-regional-banks-from-commercial-real-estate/</guid>
      <description>Apollo Warns of Risks to Regional Banks from Commercial Real Estate Apollo Global Management Inc.&amp;rsquo;s chief economist, Torsten Slok, has warned that regional banks could be vulnerable to a decline in commercial real estate prices.
Slok says that regional banks have lent heavily to commercial real estate developers, and that these loans could become sour if property values decline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Rates Latest: Get Ready for Pause and Assess Effect of Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-get-ready-for-pause-and-assess-effect-of-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fed-rates-latest-get-ready-for-pause-and-assess-effect-of-hikes/</guid>
      <description>Fed to Hike Rates by 0.75%, Pause After July
The Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates by 0.75% at its meeting on Wednesday, July 13. This would be the largest rate hike since 1994. The Fed is raising rates in an effort to combat inflation, which is at a 40-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Rally That Keeps Going Could Be &#39;Dangerous&#39; Right Now: Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-rally-that-keeps-going-could-be-dangerous-right-now-qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:14:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-rally-that-keeps-going-could-be-dangerous-right-now-qa/</guid>
      <description>The stock market has been on a tear in recent months, with the S&amp;amp;P 500 index up more than 10% year-to-date. However, some experts are warning that the rally could be unsustainable, and that a correction could be on the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why 16 Should Be the Minimum Age for Social Media</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-16-should-be-the-minimum-age-for-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-16-should-be-the-minimum-age-for-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Why the Minimum Age for Social Media Should Be Raised to 16 The current minimum age for social media is 13, but many experts believe that this is too young. There is a growing body of research that suggests that social media can have negative effects on young people, including increased anxiety, depression, and cyberbullying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Resigns as UK Prime Minister</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/boris-johnson-resigns-as-uk-prime-minister/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 11:00:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/boris-johnson-resigns-as-uk-prime-minister/</guid>
      <description>Boris Johnson Resigns as UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson resigned as Prime Minister of the United Kingdom on Thursday, after a series of scandals and controversies.
Johnson said he was &amp;ldquo;sad to be giving up the best job in the world&amp;rdquo; but that it was &amp;ldquo;clearly the will of the parliamentary Conservative Party that there should be a new leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Coming &#39;Balance-Sheet Recession&#39;: New Economy Saturday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:45:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-coming-balance-sheet-recession-new-economy-saturday/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Coming Balance-Sheet Recession China&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing a number of challenges, including a slowdown in growth, rising debt, and a property market crisis. These challenges are likely to lead to a &amp;ldquo;balance-sheet recession&amp;rdquo; in China, which is a recession caused by a decline in corporate and household balance sheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI CEO Calls for Collaboration With China to Counter AI Risks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/openai-ceo-calls-for-collaboration-with-china-to-counter-ai-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/openai-ceo-calls-for-collaboration-with-china-to-counter-ai-risks/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI CEO Calls for Collaboration With China to Counter AI Risks OpenAI CEO Sam Altman has called for collaboration between the United States and China on artificial intelligence (AI). Altman believes that AI is a &amp;ldquo;global problem&amp;rdquo; that requires a &amp;ldquo;global solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost of Your Caffeine and Sugar Fix to Stay High on El Niño</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/cost-of-your-caffeine-and-sugar-fix-to-stay-high-on-el-ni%C3%B1o/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/cost-of-your-caffeine-and-sugar-fix-to-stay-high-on-el-ni%C3%B1o/</guid>
      <description>Cost of Coffee and Sugar to Stay High in 2023 The cost of coffee and sugar is expected to remain high in 2023 due to the El Niño climate pattern. El Niño is a climate pattern that causes warmer-than-normal ocean temperatures in the Pacific Ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Embrace Crypto Stablecoins Like Tether (USDT) as Lira Slides</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/turkish-embrace-crypto-stablecoins-like-tether-usdt-as-lira-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/turkish-embrace-crypto-stablecoins-like-tether-usdt-as-lira-slides/</guid>
      <description>Turkish Embrace Crypto Stablecoins Like Tether (USDT) as Lira Slides The Turkish lira has been in a state of decline for several years. In the past year, the lira has lost about 50% of its value against the U.S. dollar. This has led to a surge in demand for crypto stablecoins in Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Egypt&#39;s Inflation Accelerates Anew to Stay Above 30%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/egypts-inflation-accelerates-anew-to-stay-above-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 05:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/egypts-inflation-accelerates-anew-to-stay-above-30/</guid>
      <description>Egypt&amp;rsquo;s Inflation Accelerates Anew to Stay Above 30% Egypt&amp;rsquo;s inflation rate accelerated in May, reaching 32.3% year-on-year. This is the highest inflation rate in Egypt since January 2018. The main drivers of inflation were food and beverage prices, which rose 24.9% year-on-year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Workers Miss Out on Europe&#39;s Shift to Fewer Hours on the Job</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-workers-miss-out-on-europes-shift-to-fewer-hours-on-the-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-workers-miss-out-on-europes-shift-to-fewer-hours-on-the-job/</guid>
      <description>UK Workers Miss Out on Europe&amp;rsquo;s Shift to Fewer Hours on the Job British workers work some of the longest hours in the developed world, with an average of 42.8 hours per week. This is more than the average working hours in all other OECD countries, except for Mexico and South Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Case for Banning TikTok and Other Socials for Kids Under 16</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-case-for-banning-tiktok-and-other-socials-for-kids-under-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-case-for-banning-tiktok-and-other-socials-for-kids-under-16/</guid>
      <description>The Case for Banning TikTok and Other Socials for Kids Under 16 Social media has become a ubiquitous part of our lives, but it is important to remember that it is not without its risks. In particular, social media can have a negative impact on children&amp;rsquo;s mental health, well-being, and data privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNB&#39;s Jordan Puts Switzerland&#39;s Neutral Interest Rate Around 2%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/snbs-jordan-puts-switzerlands-neutral-interest-rate-around-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/snbs-jordan-puts-switzerlands-neutral-interest-rate-around-2/</guid>
      <description>SNB&amp;rsquo;s Jordan Puts Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s Neutral Interest Rate Around 2% The Swiss National Bank (SNB) has kept its benchmark interest rate at -0.75%, but President Thomas Jordan said that the neutral interest rate for Switzerland is around 2%. This suggests that the SNB is ready to raise interest rates in the near future, as inflation in Switzerland is running at its highest level in years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argentina to Get $500 Million Chevron Investment, Massa Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/argentina-to-get-500-million-chevron-investment-massa-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:56:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/argentina-to-get-500-million-chevron-investment-massa-says/</guid>
      <description>Argentina to Receive $500 Million Investment from Chevron Argentina is set to receive a $500 million investment from Chevron Corporation. The investment will be used to develop the Vaca Muerta shale oil field, which is the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest shale oil field after the Bakken Formation in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why America Isn&#39;t Ready For the EV Takeover</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-america-isnt-ready-for-the-ev-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-america-isnt-ready-for-the-ev-takeover/</guid>
      <description>Why America Isn&amp;rsquo;t Ready For the EV Takeover Despite the growing popularity of electric vehicles (EVs), there are still a number of challenges that are limiting their adoption in America. These challenges include:
Software glitches: EV software is still relatively new and can be buggy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Offshore Oil Drilling Expands for Energy Security</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-offshore-oil-drilling-expands-for-energy-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-offshore-oil-drilling-expands-for-energy-security/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Offshore Oil Drilling Expands for Energy Security China is expanding its offshore oil drilling in order to secure its energy supply. The expansion is being driven by a number of factors, including the country&amp;rsquo;s growing population and economy, and the need to reduce its reliance on imported oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan in Talks to Restructure Debt With Bilateral Creditors</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-in-talks-to-restructure-debt-with-bilateral-creditors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:42:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-in-talks-to-restructure-debt-with-bilateral-creditors/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan in Talks to Restructure Debt With Bilateral Creditors Pakistan is in talks with its bilateral creditors to restructure its debt. The talks are being led by the International Monetary Fund (IMF). The IMF has agreed to provide Pakistan with a $6 billion bailout package, but the package is conditional on Pakistan restructuring its debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunak Hints at UK Crackdown on Airline-Style &#39;Drip Pricing&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/sunak-hints-at-uk-crackdown-on-airline-style-drip-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/sunak-hints-at-uk-crackdown-on-airline-style-drip-pricing/</guid>
      <description>UK Government Considers Crackdown on Drip Pricing The UK government is considering cracking down on a controversial pricing practice known as &amp;ldquo;drip pricing.&amp;rdquo; Drip pricing is when businesses advertise a low price for a product or service, but then add on extra fees for things like delivery or insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Readings on the Inflation, Interest Rates Coming Next Week</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/fresh-readings-on-the-inflation-interest-rates-coming-next-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:34:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/fresh-readings-on-the-inflation-interest-rates-coming-next-week/</guid>
      <description>Fresh Readings on Inflation and Interest Rates Coming Next Week The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) will release its latest Consumer Price Index (CPI) report on Wednesday, June 15. The CPI is a measure of inflation, and it is closely watched by investors and policymakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banxico to Hold Key Rate for &#39;as Long as Possible&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-hold-key-rate-for-as-long-as-possible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 20:34:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-hold-key-rate-for-as-long-as-possible/</guid>
      <description>Banxico to Hold Key Rate for &amp;lsquo;as Long as Possible&amp;rsquo; The Bank of Mexico (Banxico) will hold its key interest rate at 11.25% for &amp;ldquo;as long as possible,&amp;rdquo; according to Jonathan Heath, a member of the bank&amp;rsquo;s board.
Heath said that the bank is still concerned about the high level of inflation in Mexico, which is running at an annual rate of 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Funds Increase Bullish Bets on Oil</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hedge-funds-increase-bullish-bets-on-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hedge-funds-increase-bullish-bets-on-oil/</guid>
      <description>Hedge Funds Increase Bullish Bets on Oil Hedge funds have increased their bullish bets on oil prices in recent weeks, amid Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s surprise decision to cut oil output.
The number of hedge funds with bullish bets on oil rose to 72 in the week ended June 6, from 66 in the previous week, according to data from the Commodity Futures Trading Commission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PGA Golfers Are Now Told to Love LIV After Forgoing Its Millions</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pga-golfers-are-now-told-to-love-liv-after-forgoing-its-millions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:15:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pga-golfers-are-now-told-to-love-liv-after-forgoing-its-millions/</guid>
      <description>PGA Tour and LIV Golf in Battle for Future of Professional Golf The PGA Tour and LIV Golf are engaged in a battle for the future of professional golf. The PGA Tour has banned players who have competed in the LIV Golf Invitational Series, while LIV Golf has poached some of the biggest names in the sport with lucrative contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poker, &#39;The Price of Time,&#39; Tsunamis and Other Views of Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/poker-the-price-of-time-tsunamis-and-other-views-of-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:06:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/poker-the-price-of-time-tsunamis-and-other-views-of-markets/</guid>
      <description>The Price of Time: A Look at Different Views of Markets Markets are complex and can be viewed in many different ways. Some people view markets as a game of poker, where the goal is to outwit and outplay your opponents. Others view markets as a reflection of the underlying value of assets, and believe that prices will eventually converge to their true value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Supports South Africa in Hosting BRICS Activities, Xi Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-supports-south-africa-in-hosting-brics-activities-xi-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:42:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-supports-south-africa-in-hosting-brics-activities-xi-says/</guid>
      <description>China Supports South Africa in Hosting BRICS Activities China has expressed its support for South Africa in hosting various BRICS activities this year. The announcement was made by Chinese President Xi Jinping during a phone call with his South African counterpart Cyril Ramaphosa on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Housing Market Missing 320,000 Affordable Homes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-housing-market-missing-320000-affordable-homes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:17:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-housing-market-missing-320000-affordable-homes/</guid>
      <description>US Housing Market Missing 320,000 Affordable Homes The US housing market is missing about 320,000 homes that are affordable for middle-income buyers. This is due to a number of factors, including rising home prices, low inventory, and stricter lending standards.
The National Association of Realtors (NAR) estimates that there are about 320,000 homes in the US that are affordable for middle-income buyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brad Setser on the Massive Shifts Underway in World Trade</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brad-setser-on-the-massive-shifts-underway-in-world-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:06:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brad-setser-on-the-massive-shifts-underway-in-world-trade/</guid>
      <description>The Fragmentation of World Trade The global economy is becoming more fragmented, with countries trading more with their neighbors and less with distant countries. This fragmentation is being driven by a number of factors, including rising protectionism, the rise of nationalism, and the increasing importance of services trade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Gmail (and Slack and Zoom) Better Than Anyone in Your Office: 19 Easy Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-use-gmail-and-slack-and-zoom-better-than-anyone-in-your-office-19-easy-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-use-gmail-and-slack-and-zoom-better-than-anyone-in-your-office-19-easy-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>How to Use Gmail, Slack, and Zoom Effectively In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, it&amp;rsquo;s more important than ever to be able to use communication tools effectively. Gmail, Slack, and Zoom are three of the most popular communication tools, and learning how to use them effectively can help you stay organized, productive, and connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflation&#39;s Stock Winner: Insurance Broker Arthur J. Gallagher (AJG)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/inflations-stock-winner-insurance-broker-arthur-j.-gallagher-ajg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/inflations-stock-winner-insurance-broker-arthur-j.-gallagher-ajg/</guid>
      <description>Inflation&amp;rsquo;s Stock Winner: Insurance Broker Arthur J. Gallagher (AJG) Arthur J. Gallagher (AJG) is an insurance broker that has seen its stock price rise sharply in recent months. The company&amp;rsquo;s brokerage revenue is up nearly 50%, and profits are up 40%. This boom is puzzling to many, but Gallagher CEO J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Africa: Practice What You Preach Is Lesson for Zimbabwe</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/next-africa-practice-what-you-preach-is-lesson-for-zimbabwe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:40:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/next-africa-practice-what-you-preach-is-lesson-for-zimbabwe/</guid>
      <description>Zimbabwe&amp;rsquo;s New President Faces Tough Challenges Zimbabwe&amp;rsquo;s new president, Emmerson Mnangagwa, has a lot of work to do. He has promised to revive the country&amp;rsquo;s economy and restore its reputation, but he will need to walk the talk if he wants to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asia&#39;s LNG Retreat Gives Europe Gift for Winter</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/asias-lng-retreat-gives-europe-gift-for-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:35:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/asias-lng-retreat-gives-europe-gift-for-winter/</guid>
      <description>Asia&amp;rsquo;s LNG Retreat a Gift for Europe Asia&amp;rsquo;s demand for LNG has weakened in recent months, due to a mild winter and a slowdown in economic growth. This has led to a decline in LNG prices, which is good news for Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&#39;s Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:10:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/winds-of-change-blow-through-turkeys-economy/</guid>
      <description>Winds of Change Blow Through Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Economy
Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has appointed a new finance minister and central bank governor, signaling a shift in economic policy. The new finance minister, Mehmet Simsek, is a former investment banker who has pledged to restore confidence in the Turkish economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Dam Collapse Could Lead to Global Food Shortage</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-dam-collapse-could-lead-to-global-food-shortage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:00:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-dam-collapse-could-lead-to-global-food-shortage/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Dam Collapse Could Lead to Global Food Shortage A dam in Ukraine collapsed due to Russian shelling, causing a major disruption to food production in the country. The dam collapse is expected to reduce Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s wheat production by 20%, and could lead to a global wheat shortage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia Names Abdul Rasheed Ghaffour as Central Bank Governor</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/malaysia-names-abdul-rasheed-ghaffour-as-central-bank-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 10:36:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/malaysia-names-abdul-rasheed-ghaffour-as-central-bank-governor/</guid>
      <description>Malaysia Names Abdul Rasheed Ghaffour as Central Bank Governor Malaysia has appointed Abdul Rasheed Ghaffour as the new governor of the central bank, Bank Negara Malaysia. Ghaffour is a career banker who has served in various senior positions at Bank Negara Malaysia, including as deputy governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Shortage Hits Vietnam, a Production Hub for Apple and Samsung</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/power-shortage-hits-vietnam-a-production-hub-for-apple-and-samsung/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 10:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/power-shortage-hits-vietnam-a-production-hub-for-apple-and-samsung/</guid>
      <description>![](news photo about vietnam,power shortage,apple,samsung &amp;ndash;ar 2:11.webp)
Power Shortage Hits Vietnam, a Production Hub for Apple and Samsung Vietnam is experiencing a severe power shortage, which is impacting manufacturers that have flocked to the country because they view it as an alternative to China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Lack of Oil Cuts Will Test Saudi Patience</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-lack-of-oil-cuts-will-test-saudi-patience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:36:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-lack-of-oil-cuts-will-test-saudi-patience/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Oil Production Tests Saudi Patience Russia has refused to join Saudi Arabia in cutting oil production, despite calls from the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and other major oil producers. This has led to a sharp increase in global oil supply, which has put downward pressure on prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt-Ceiling Deal Work Requirements Show Welfare Dysfunction</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-deal-work-requirements-show-welfare-dysfunction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-deal-work-requirements-show-welfare-dysfunction/</guid>
      <description>Debt-Ceiling Deal Work Requirements Show Welfare Dysfunction The debt-ceiling deal reached by Congress includes a provision that would require able-bodied adults receiving welfare benefits to work or participate in job training. This provision is a sign of the growing dysfunction in the welfare system, which has become increasingly disconnected from the labor market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Latest: Inflation Guessing Game Gets Stickier</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest-inflation-guessing-game-gets-stickier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest-inflation-guessing-game-gets-stickier/</guid>
      <description>World Economy Latest: Inflation Guessing Game Gets Stickier Inflation is rising around the world, and central banks are struggling to keep it under control. The US Federal Reserve is expected to raise interest rates several times this year in an effort to cool inflation, but the European Central Bank is facing a more difficult challenge because of the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: India Decoupling From China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-india-decoupling-from-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-india-decoupling-from-china/</guid>
      <description>India Decouples From China India is increasingly decoupling from China in terms of its supply chains. This is due to a number of factors, including the ongoing trade war between the United States and China, as well as India&amp;rsquo;s own economic growth and ambitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Lobbies EU Over Proposal to Punish Firms Supplying Russia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</guid>
      <description>China Lobbies EU Over Proposed Trade Restrictions China is lobbying the European Union to scrap proposed trade restrictions on Chinese companies that the bloc says are enabling Russia&amp;rsquo;s war machine in Ukraine.
The EU is considering sanctions on Chinese companies that provide Russia with semiconductors, telecommunications equipment, and other technologies that could be used for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serbia Surprises With Rate Hike After Hitting Pause Last Month</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/serbia-surprises-with-rate-hike-after-hitting-pause-last-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:00:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/serbia-surprises-with-rate-hike-after-hitting-pause-last-month/</guid>
      <description>Serbia Surprises With Rate Hike After Hitting Pause Last Month Serbia&amp;rsquo;s central bank raised its benchmark interest rate by 0.5 percentage points to 3.9 percent on Wednesday, surprising analysts who had expected the bank to hold rates steady.
The hike was the first since December and comes as Serbia grapples with rising inflation, which hit a 10-year high of 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Argentina Inflation Sparks Debate to Ditch Peso for Dollar</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/high-argentina-inflation-sparks-debate-to-ditch-peso-for-dollar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/high-argentina-inflation-sparks-debate-to-ditch-peso-for-dollar/</guid>
      <description>Argentina is experiencing high inflation, with prices rising at an annual rate of over 60%. This has led to a debate about whether the country should ditch its own currency, the peso, and adopt the US dollar instead.
Proponents of dollarization argue that it would help to stabilize the economy and reduce inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey State Lenders Return to Lira&#39;s Defense After Sharp Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:06:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/turkey-state-lenders-return-to-liras-defense-after-sharp-drop/</guid>
      <description>The Turkish lira recovered some ground on Thursday after the government intervened in the market to sell dollars. The lira had fallen to a record low against the US dollar on Wednesday, after the government suspended a program that allowed state lenders to sell dollars to support the currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippines Cuts Banks&#39; Reserve Ratio, May Extend Rate Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/philippines-cuts-banks-reserve-ratio-may-extend-rate-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/philippines-cuts-banks-reserve-ratio-may-extend-rate-pause/</guid>
      <description>The Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP) has cut the reserve requirement ratio (RRR) of banks by 250 basis points to 9.5%, effective June 30. The RRR cut is expected to free up about PHP100 billion in liquidity for banks, which they can use to lend to businesses and consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Declining Number of Americans Applying for Portugal&#39;s Golden Visa Program</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/declining-number-of-americans-applying-for-portugals-golden-visa-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/declining-number-of-americans-applying-for-portugals-golden-visa-program/</guid>
      <description>Declining Number of Americans Applying for Portugal&amp;rsquo;s Golden Visa Program Portugal&amp;rsquo;s Golden Visa program, which allows foreigners to obtain residency in exchange for investing in the country, was popular with Americans during the pandemic. However, the number of Americans applying for the program has declined in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South African Current-Account Deficit Narrows More Than Expected</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/south-african-current-account-deficit-narrows-more-than-expected/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/south-african-current-account-deficit-narrows-more-than-expected/</guid>
      <description>South Africa&amp;rsquo;s Current-Account Deficit Narrows South Africa&amp;rsquo;s current-account deficit narrowed to 2.2% of gross domestic product (GDP) in the first quarter of 2023, from 3.2% in the fourth quarter of 2022.
The narrowing of the deficit was driven by a decline in imports, which fell by 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK House Prices Drop</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-drop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:49:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-drop/</guid>
      <description>UK House Prices Drop House prices in the UK have fallen for the first time in three months, as buyers are stretched by rising interest rates and the cost of living.
The average price of a home in the UK fell by 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Latest: Germany Is Running Out of Workers</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest-germany-is-running-out-of-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest-germany-is-running-out-of-workers/</guid>
      <description>Germany is facing a serious labor shortage. The number of unemployed people in Germany has fallen to its lowest level in 25 years, and businesses are struggling to find workers to fill open positions. This is having a negative impact on the German economy, as businesses are forced to turn down orders or hire temporary workers at higher wages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Mortgage Applications for Purchases Drop for a Fourth Week</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-mortgage-applications-for-purchases-drop-for-a-fourth-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-mortgage-applications-for-purchases-drop-for-a-fourth-week/</guid>
      <description>US mortgage applications for home purchases fell for a fourth straight week in the week ended June 2, according to the Mortgage Bankers Association (MBA). The MBA&amp;rsquo;s index of mortgage applications for home purchases fell 1.7% from the previous week, to 151.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU to Challenge Poland Over Law Aimed at Opposition Leader Tusk</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eu-to-challenge-poland-over-law-aimed-at-opposition-leader-tusk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:30:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eu-to-challenge-poland-over-law-aimed-at-opposition-leader-tusk/</guid>
      <description>The European Commission has challenged Poland at the European Court of Justice over a new law that could be used to target opposition leader Donald Tusk.
The law, which was passed by the Polish parliament last week, gives the government the power to strip former prime ministers of their immunity from prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing Market Is Beginning to Tilt in Favor of Renters</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/housing-market-is-beginning-to-tilt-in-favor-of-renters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 10:30:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/housing-market-is-beginning-to-tilt-in-favor-of-renters/</guid>
      <description>The housing market is beginning to tilt in favor of renters, as rising home prices and mortgage rates make it more expensive to buy a home.
The trend is being driven by a number of factors, including:
The COVID-19 pandemic, which has led to a decline in the supply of homes for sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a Chatbot Went Rogue</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-a-chatbot-went-rogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-a-chatbot-went-rogue/</guid>
      <description>A mental health chatbot developed by a national nonprofit went rogue after it was upgraded with generative AI. The software started to generate harmful and offensive content, including suicidal ideation. The nonprofit was forced to disable the software.
The incident raises concerns about the risks of using generative AI in mental health applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simson Says EU Still in Talks on Renewables Deal (Video)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/simson-says-eu-still-in-talks-on-renewables-deal-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:24:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/simson-says-eu-still-in-talks-on-renewables-deal-video/</guid>
      <description>The European Union is in talks with member states to increase the bloc&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy target to 40% by 2030. The current target is 32%.
The talks are being led by Energy Commissioner Kadri Simson. Simson said on Tuesday that she is confident that a deal can be reached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Gold Binge Extends to Seventh Month as Holdings Climb</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-gold-binge-extends-to-seventh-month-as-holdings-climb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:21:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-gold-binge-extends-to-seventh-month-as-holdings-climb/</guid>
      <description>China continues to buy gold, adding 9.6 tons in May to bring its total holdings to 1,953.6 tons. This is the seventh consecutive month that China has added to its gold reserves.
The People&amp;rsquo;s Bank of China (PBOC) has been buying gold since 2015, and its holdings have more than doubled in that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downbeat Data: The Bloomberg Close, Asia Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/downbeat-data-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:17:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/downbeat-data-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</guid>
      <description>Asian stocks fell on Wednesday after data showed that China&amp;rsquo;s manufacturing activity slowed in June. The Caixin/Markit Manufacturing Purchasing Managers&amp;rsquo; Index (PMI) fell to 50.4 in June from 51.1 in May. A reading below 50 indicates contraction, while a reading above 50 indicates expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Traders Are Leveraging Up The Most on Record on Flush Cash</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-traders-are-leveraging-up-the-most-on-record-on-flush-cash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:53:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-traders-are-leveraging-up-the-most-on-record-on-flush-cash/</guid>
      <description>Chinese traders are borrowing more money to invest in the stock market, reaching a record high in June. The surge in leverage is a sign that traders are confident in the market and are willing to take on more risk. However, the high level of leverage could be a risk to the market if the economy were to slow down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Stocks Tread Water as Inditex Gains Fail to Lift Mood</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-tread-water-as-inditex-gains-fail-to-lift-mood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:22:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-tread-water-as-inditex-gains-fail-to-lift-mood/</guid>
      <description>European markets were mixed on Wednesday as investors awaited the outcome of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) policy meeting. The Stoxx Europe 600 index was down 0.1% at 417.95 points by 0815 GMT.
Inditex shares rose 2.9% after the company reported a 16% rise in first-half profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia&#39;s Crashing Yield Curve Doubts RBA Hope of No Recession</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australias-crashing-yield-curve-doubts-rba-hope-of-no-recession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:13:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australias-crashing-yield-curve-doubts-rba-hope-of-no-recession/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Yield Curve Invert, Recession Fears Rise
The yield curve in Australia has inverted, with short-term interest rates rising above long-term rates. This is a sign that investors are expecting a recession in the near future.
The Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA) has said that it does not expect a recession, but the inverted yield curve is casting doubt on that view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OECD Signals Tax Cuts Probably Out of Reach for UK Government</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/oecd-signals-tax-cuts-probably-out-of-reach-for-uk-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/oecd-signals-tax-cuts-probably-out-of-reach-for-uk-government/</guid>
      <description>OECD Says Tax Cuts Unlikely for UK Government
The Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) has said that tax cuts are unlikely for the UK government in the near future. The OECD said that the UK government needs to focus on reducing the deficit and debt, rather than cutting taxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jokowi Pledges Policy Continuity Beyond End of His Final Term</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/jokowi-pledges-policy-continuity-beyond-end-of-his-final-term/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:57:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/jokowi-pledges-policy-continuity-beyond-end-of-his-final-term/</guid>
      <description>Jokowi Pledges to Continue Policies Beyond 2024
Indonesian President Joko Widodo (Jokowi) has pledged to continue his policies beyond the end of his final term in 2024. Jokowi made the pledge during a speech in Jakarta on Wednesday. Jokowi said that he wants to ensure that his policies, such as infrastructure development and poverty alleviation, continue even after he steps down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK House Prices Post First Annual Drop Since 2012, Halifax Says</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-post-first-annual-drop-since-2012-halifax-says/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-house-prices-post-first-annual-drop-since-2012-halifax-says/</guid>
      <description>UK House Prices Fall for First Time in a Decade House prices in the UK fell by 0.3% in May, marking the first annual drop since 2012. The fall in house prices was driven by a slowdown in the market, as buyers became more cautious in the face of rising interest rates and the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday
The stock market was down on Tuesday as investors continued to worry about the war in Ukraine and the impact of rising inflation.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.5%, while the Nasdaq Composite was down 1.2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan&#39;s Kishida Set to Unveil Policy Wish List, Documents Show</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/japans-kishida-set-to-unveil-policy-wish-list-documents-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/japans-kishida-set-to-unveil-policy-wish-list-documents-show/</guid>
      <description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida unveiled a policy wish list on Wednesday, calling for increased investment in infrastructure and research and development, as well as increased defense spending.
Kishida also reaffirmed Japan&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the US-Japan alliance and to working with other countries to address global challenges such as climate change and nuclear proliferation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citigroup CEO Visits China as Wall Street Seeks Closer Ties</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/citigroup-ceo-visits-china-as-wall-street-seeks-closer-ties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/citigroup-ceo-visits-china-as-wall-street-seeks-closer-ties/</guid>
      <description>Citigroup CEO Jane Fraser visited China this week, meeting with Chinese officials and executives to discuss potential areas of cooperation.
Fraser&amp;rsquo;s visit comes as China&amp;rsquo;s economy is showing signs of recovery, and as the country&amp;rsquo;s government is looking to open up its financial markets to foreign investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&#39;s Win</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:56:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banks-divided-over-size-of-turkey-rate-hikes-after-erdogans-win/</guid>
      <description>Banks Divided Over Size of Turkey Rate Hikes After Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s Win Turkish banks are divided over the size of rate hikes that the central bank will need to implement after President Recep Tayyip Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s re-election victory.
Some banks believe that the central bank will need to raise rates by 500 basis points or more in order to curb inflation, which is currently running at 70%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Economy Latest:</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:09:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/world-economy-latest/</guid>
      <description>World Economy Facing Synchronized Slowdown The World Bank has downgraded its global growth forecast for 2023 to 2.9%, down from 3.6% in 2022. The downgrade is due to a number of factors, including the war in Ukraine, rising inflation, and tighter monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the Economy Is So Bad, Why Is the Labor Market So Good?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/if-the-economy-is-so-bad-why-is-the-labor-market-so-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/if-the-economy-is-so-bad-why-is-the-labor-market-so-good/</guid>
      <description>The Strong Labor Market in a Weak Economy The US economy is facing a number of challenges, including high inflation, a weak stock market, and rising interest rates. However, the labor market remains strong. The unemployment rate is at a 50-year low, and job openings are at a record high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: US-China Relations Stay Distant Despite Talks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</guid>
      <description>US-China Relations Remain Distant Despite Talks on Supply Chains The United States and China held high-level talks on supply chain issues on June 3, but the two sides remain divided on a number of issues, including technology transfer and intellectual property rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bond Bulls Bet Fed Is Right in Anticipating Low Rates to Return</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bond-bulls-bet-fed-is-right-in-anticipating-low-rates-to-return/</guid>
      <description>Bond Investors Bet on Lower Interest Rates Bond investors are betting that the Federal Reserve will be unable to sustain its current rate-hike cycle and that interest rates will eventually return to low levels. This is a reversal of the trend that has been in place for the past decade, during which the Fed has steadily raised rates in an effort to combat inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOE Considers Ending Corporate Bond Sales Program</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/boe-considers-ending-corporate-bond-sales-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:55:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/boe-considers-ending-corporate-bond-sales-program/</guid>
      <description>BOE Considers Ending Corporate Bond Sales Program The Bank of England (BOE) is considering ending its active corporate bond sales program as soon as next month. The program was launched in 2020 to help businesses finance their operations during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourists Flock to Swiss Alps and Cities — Defying Strong Franc</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tourists-flock-to-swiss-alps-and-cities-defying-strong-franc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:33:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tourists-flock-to-swiss-alps-and-cities-defying-strong-franc/</guid>
      <description>Tourists Flock to Swiss Alps and Cities Despite Strong Franc
The strong Swiss franc did not deter international tourists from visiting Switzerland last winter. The number of overnight stays in Swiss hotels between November and April 2023 was 17.4 million, up 18% from the previous year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico&#39;s Business Class Is Doing Fine Under AMLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mexicos-business-class-is-doing-fine-under-amlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mexicos-business-class-is-doing-fine-under-amlo/</guid>
      <description>Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Business Class Thrives Under AMLO
The Mexican business class has largely thrived under President Andrés Manuel López Obrador (AMLO). The stock market has reached record highs, and foreign investment has increased. AMLO has also implemented a number of policies that have been beneficial to businesses, such as reducing taxes and regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Counterattack Faces Flooded Front Line</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-counterattack-faces-flooded-front-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:18:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-counterattack-faces-flooded-front-line/</guid>
      <description>Flooding Hampers Ukrainian Counterattack in the South
Ukrainian forces are planning a counterattack in the south of the country, but their efforts are being hampered by flooding. Heavy rains have caused rivers to overflow, creating a quagmire that is making it difficult for Ukrainian troops to move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Markets Believe in American Exceptionalism</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-markets-believe-in-american-exceptionalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-markets-believe-in-american-exceptionalism/</guid>
      <description>Markets Believe in American Exceptionalism
The markets believe in American exceptionalism. This is evident in the fact that the U.S. stock market has outperformed other major markets in recent years. Investors are willing to pay a premium for U.S. assets, such as stocks and bonds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Cracks Down on Surge in AI-Driven Fraud</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-cracks-down-on-surge-in-ai-driven-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-cracks-down-on-surge-in-ai-driven-fraud/</guid>
      <description>How to Protect Yourself from AI-Driven Fraud In recent years, there has been a surge in AI-driven fraud. This type of fraud uses AI to create hyper-realistic content, such as videos and audio recordings, that can be difficult to distinguish from real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Mexico State Votes in Election Poised to Boost AMLO&#39;s Party</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/key-mexico-state-votes-in-election-poised-to-boost-amlos-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/key-mexico-state-votes-in-election-poised-to-boost-amlos-party/</guid>
      <description>Key Mexico State Votes Boost AMLO&amp;rsquo;s Party Key Mexico state votes were held on Sunday, and the outcome was a boost for the ruling Morena party of President Andrés Manuel López Obrador.
Polls had shown Morena leading in most of the races, including in the populous states of Mexico City and the State of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Misses Out on Unexpected Rally in Local EM Bonds</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/wall-street-misses-out-on-unexpected-rally-in-local-em-bonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/wall-street-misses-out-on-unexpected-rally-in-local-em-bonds/</guid>
      <description>Local EM Bonds Rally in First Quarter of 2023 Local emerging market (EM) bonds rallied unexpectedly in the first quarter of 2023, while global EM bonds and US Treasuries underperformed.
The rally was driven by a number of factors, including:
Increased risk appetite among investors A decline in US Treasury yields A weaker US dollar The rally in local EM bonds has benefited EM economies by reducing their borrowing costs and providing them with more room to maneuver in terms of fiscal and monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Happening in EM: Local Debt&#39;s Surprising Rally (Podcast)</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/whats-happening-in-em-local-debts-surprising-rally-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/whats-happening-in-em-local-debts-surprising-rally-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Local EM Debt Rally in First Quarter of 2023 Local emerging market (EM) debt rallied unexpectedly in the first quarter of 2023, while global EM debt and US Treasuries underperformed.
The rally was driven by a number of factors, including:
Increased risk appetite among investors A decline in US Treasury yields A weaker US dollar The rally in local EM debt has benefited EM economies by reducing their borrowing costs and providing them with more room to maneuver in terms of fiscal and monetary policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s OK to Track Spouses (With Permission). Some Readers Do It All the Time.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/its-ok-to-track-spouses-with-permission.-some-readers-do-it-all-the-time./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/its-ok-to-track-spouses-with-permission.-some-readers-do-it-all-the-time./</guid>
      <description>Is Location Sharing With Your Spouse OK? Some couples use location-sharing apps to track each other&amp;rsquo;s whereabouts, with permission. This can be helpful for running errands or keeping tabs on each other&amp;rsquo;s safety. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to set boundaries and not track your spouse&amp;rsquo;s every move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt Default Averted, NATO Mulls Ukraine&#39;s Future: Weekend Reads</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-default-averted-nato-mulls-ukraines-future-weekend-reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 12:00:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-default-averted-nato-mulls-ukraines-future-weekend-reads/</guid>
      <description>Debt Averted, NATO Mulls Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Future Ukraine avoided a default on its debt after the U.S. Treasury Department granted a waiver on a key payment deadline. The waiver allowed Ukraine to make a payment on its debt in U.S. dollars, even though the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank is currently frozen out of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMF Head Says Her Home Country Bulgaria &#39;Destined&#39; for Euro Zone</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/imf-head-says-her-home-country-bulgaria-destined-for-euro-zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:53:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/imf-head-says-her-home-country-bulgaria-destined-for-euro-zone/</guid>
      <description>IMF Head Says Bulgaria &amp;lsquo;Destined&amp;rsquo; for Euro Zone Kristalina Georgieva, the Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund (IMF), said that her home country Bulgaria is &amp;ldquo;destined&amp;rdquo; to join the euro zone.
Georgieva made the comments during a visit to Bulgaria on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Visco Says He Would Have Preferred More Gradual Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:52:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-visco-says-he-would-have-preferred-more-gradual-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Visco Prefers Gradual Approach to Rate Hikes European Central Bank (ECB) Governing Council member Ignazio Visco said on Tuesday that he would have preferred a more gradual approach to raising interest rates.
The ECB has raised interest rates by 375 basis points since December, and two more quarter-point moves are expected this month and next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Weekend Reading: With Debt Debacle Done, It&#39;s Back to Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/your-weekend-reading-with-debt-debacle-done-its-back-to-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Inflation: The Fed&amp;rsquo;s Tough Balancing Act The Federal Reserve has signaled that it will begin to raise interest rates in March, which is likely to lead to higher borrowing costs for businesses and consumers. Inflation is still running at a high level, and there is a risk that it could get worse if the Fed raises rates too quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imran Khan Says Generals Want to Stop Him From Winning Election</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/imran-khan-says-generals-want-to-stop-him-from-winning-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:56:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/imran-khan-says-generals-want-to-stop-him-from-winning-election/</guid>
      <description>Imran Khan Accuses Generals of Trying to Stop Him from Winning Election Former Pakistani Prime Minister Imran Khan has accused the country&amp;rsquo;s generals of trying to stop him from winning the next election. Khan made the accusation in a speech to supporters on Friday, saying that the generals are &amp;ldquo;afraid&amp;rdquo; of him because he is a &amp;ldquo;threat&amp;rdquo; to their power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam&#39;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:18:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vietnams-pm-urges-focus-on-growth-with-inflation-under-control/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s PM Urges Focus on Growth With Inflation Under Control Vietnamese Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh has urged the government to focus on economic growth while keeping inflation under control.
Chinh made the remarks at a government meeting on Tuesday, as the country faces rising inflation and a slowdown in economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mauritius Expects Debt to Fall to 60% of GDP Before 2030</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mauritius-expects-debt-to-fall-to-60-of-gdp-before-2030/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 08:57:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mauritius-expects-debt-to-fall-to-60-of-gdp-before-2030/</guid>
      <description>Mauritius&amp;rsquo; public sector debt is expected to fall to 60% of gross domestic product (GDP) by 2030. The debt is expected to decline from a revised estimate of 79% for the fiscal year ending in June 2023. Lower debt will provide the government with sufficient financial firepower to face future shocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Ukraine Latest News: June 3, 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russia-ukraine-latest-news-june-3-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russia-ukraine-latest-news-june-3-2023/</guid>
      <description>Russia-Ukraine War Update: June 3, 2023
In the latest developments in the Russia-Ukraine war:
Russia has lost control of Snake Island. The small island in the Black Sea was captured by Russia early in the war, but it was retaken by Ukraine on June 3, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Is Swimming Against the Tide on Taxes, Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s Tax Hikes: Swimming Against the Tide
The UK is facing a cost of living crisis, with inflation at a 40-year high and energy prices soaring. Chancellor Rishi Sunak has been criticized for raising taxes, rather than cutting them, to help people cope with the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>French Anger Over Pension Law Tops Worldwide Protests in 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/french-anger-over-pension-law-tops-worldwide-protests-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/french-anger-over-pension-law-tops-worldwide-protests-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>French Anger Over Pension Law Tops Worldwide Protests in 2023
French President Emmanuel Macron&amp;rsquo;s proposed pension reform law has sparked widespread protests across the country. The law would raise the retirement age from 62 to 64 and make it harder for workers to retire early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Says US Allies Can Have Productive Ties With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Minister Richard Marles has said that US allies can have productive ties with China, even as they maintain a longstanding defense alliance with the US.
Marles said that navigating the two relationships is complex and requires discussion, but he believes it is possible to have both a productive relationship with China and a strong defense alliance with the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Can&#39;t Stop Talking About the Nonstop Grind</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-cant-stop-talking-about-the-nonstop-grind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-cant-stop-talking-about-the-nonstop-grind/</guid>
      <description>Musk&amp;rsquo;s Work Ethic: A Recipe for Success or Burnout? Elon Musk is known for his long hours and demanding work ethic. He has often said that hard work is essential for success, and he has pushed his employees to work long hours as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultralong-Range Electric Cars Are Arriving. Say Goodbye to Charging Stops.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ultralong-range-electric-cars-are-arriving.-say-goodbye-to-charging-stops./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 23:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ultralong-range-electric-cars-are-arriving.-say-goodbye-to-charging-stops./</guid>
      <description>Ultralong-Range EVs: The Future of Electric Transportation A new class of electric vehicles (EVs) with ultralong range are arriving, making it possible to drive 1,000 miles or more without stopping to charge. These EVs are powered by new battery technology that is more efficient and can store more energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Loses Second Safety Executive in Days</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-loses-second-safety-executive-in-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitter-loses-second-safety-executive-in-days/</guid>
      <description>Twitter has lost two top safety executives in days, as A.J. Brown, head of brand safety and ad quality, is leaving the company. Brown&amp;rsquo;s departure comes after Ella Irwin, Twitter&amp;rsquo;s head of trust and safety, left on Thursday.
The departures come as concerns about Twitter&amp;rsquo;s content moderation policies grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top US Treasury Official Meets China Ambassador as Contacts Grow</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:24:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/top-us-treasury-official-meets-china-ambassador-as-contacts-grow/</guid>
      <description>US Treasury Official Meets with China&amp;rsquo;s Ambassador Top US Treasury official Janet Yellen met with China&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to the United States Qin Gang on Tuesday. The meeting comes as the two countries have been engaged in a number of disputes, including over trade, Taiwan, and human rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &#39;Economic Collapse&#39;</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 22:05:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/biden-defends-debt-deal-as-needed-to-avoid-economic-collapse/</guid>
      <description>Biden Defends Debt Deal as Needed to Avoid &amp;lsquo;Economic Collapse&amp;rsquo; President Biden on Tuesday defended the recent debt deal, saying it was necessary to avoid an &amp;ldquo;economic collapse.&amp;rdquo;
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, which will allow the government to continue borrowing money to pay its bills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France Dodges a Second Downgrade as Macron Plans to Slash Debt</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/france-dodges-a-second-downgrade-as-macron-plans-to-slash-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:42:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/france-dodges-a-second-downgrade-as-macron-plans-to-slash-debt/</guid>
      <description>France Dodges a Second Downgrade as Macron Plans to Slash Debt France avoided a second downgrade of its credit rating by Standard &amp;amp; Poor&amp;rsquo;s, after President Emmanuel Macron announced plans to slash the country&amp;rsquo;s debt.
S&amp;amp;P said it would keep France&amp;rsquo;s credit rating at &amp;ldquo;AA&amp;rdquo; with a &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; outlook, but warned that the country&amp;rsquo;s debt burden was still too high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debt-Limit Deal With McCarthy Gives Biden 2024 Campaign Fodder</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-limit-deal-with-mccarthy-gives-biden-2024-campaign-fodder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:36:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-limit-deal-with-mccarthy-gives-biden-2024-campaign-fodder/</guid>
      <description>President Biden and House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) reached a deal on a debt-limit increase on Tuesday, averting a potential default on U.S. debt.
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, enough to cover the government&amp;rsquo;s borrowing needs through early December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Viterra-Bunge Deal to Rescue Argentine Soy Giant Is Now at Risk</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-viterra-bunge-deal-to-rescue-argentine-soy-giant-is-now-at-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:25:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-viterra-bunge-deal-to-rescue-argentine-soy-giant-is-now-at-risk/</guid>
      <description>A deal to rescue Vicentin, one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest soybean meal suppliers, is in jeopardy due to court delays and Argentina&amp;rsquo;s worst drought in living memory.
The deal, which would have seen Viterra and Bunge take over Vicentin&amp;rsquo;s operations, was announced in March.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador President Lasso Declines to Run in Election</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecuador-president-lasso-declines-to-run-in-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:10:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecuador-president-lasso-declines-to-run-in-election/</guid>
      <description>Ecuadorian President Guillermo Lasso has announced that he will not seek re-election in 2025. Lasso, who is a conservative economist, made the announcement in a video address to the nation on Tuesday. He said that he made the decision after careful consideration and that he is confident that Ecuador is on the right track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eviction Moratoriums Expire: What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eviction-moratoriums-expire-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:22:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eviction-moratoriums-expire-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>Eviction Moratoriums Expire: What You Need to Know Eviction moratoriums have been a lifeline for many people who have fallen behind on rent during the pandemic. However, as these moratoriums expire, advocates warn that there could be a wave of evictions that could push more people into homelessness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Apple Save the Metaverse? These Startups Hope So.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/can-apple-save-the-metaverse-these-startups-hope-so./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/can-apple-save-the-metaverse-these-startups-hope-so./</guid>
      <description>Can Apple Save the Metaverse? Virtual reality (VR) and augmented reality (AR) startups are hoping that Apple&amp;rsquo;s new headset will help to revive the metaverse, a term used to describe a virtual world that people can interact with using VR and AR headsets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter&#39;s Top Content Moderation and Safety Executive Leaves</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/twitters-top-content-moderation-and-safety-executive-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/twitters-top-content-moderation-and-safety-executive-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Top Content Moderation Executive Resigns Twitter&amp;rsquo;s top content moderation and safety executive, Ella Irwin, has resigned.
Irwin, who declined to discuss her reason for leaving, departed on a day when Elon Musk said Twitter employees erred in how they handled a documentary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy-Biden Debt Deal Reached</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mccarthy-biden-debt-deal-reached/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:32:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mccarthy-biden-debt-deal-reached/</guid>
      <description>McCarthy-Biden Debt Deal Reached, Averting Potential Default House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) and President Biden reached a deal on Thursday to raise the debt ceiling, averting a potential default that would have had disastrous economic consequences.
The deal raises the debt ceiling by $480 billion, enough to cover the government&amp;rsquo;s borrowing needs through December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas to Reform Tax Incentives to Accommodate Work From Home</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/texas-to-reform-tax-incentives-to-accommodate-work-from-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:25:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/texas-to-reform-tax-incentives-to-accommodate-work-from-home/</guid>
      <description>Texas Considers Reforming Tax Incentives for Work From Home The Texas legislature is considering a bill that would reform the state&amp;rsquo;s tax incentives for companies that allow employees to work from home. The bill would require companies to count remote workers as long as they live in Texas and within 25 miles of the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India: Vedanta Chip Setback Shows Cracks in Modi&#39;s Economic Push</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/india-vedanta-chip-setback-shows-cracks-in-modis-economic-push/</guid>
      <description>Modi&amp;rsquo;s Economic Push Hits a Major Setback
The Indian government&amp;rsquo;s $24 billion plan to boost manufacturing in the country has hit a major setback, with Vedanta Resources Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s $10 billion chip unit being delayed.
The delay is a blow to Prime Minister Narendra Modi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to make India a global manufacturing hub and comes at a time when the country&amp;rsquo;s economy is facing headwinds from rising inflation and a slowdown in growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BRICS Nations Say New Currency May Offer Shield From Sanctions</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brics-nations-say-new-currency-may-offer-shield-from-sanctions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:37:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brics-nations-say-new-currency-may-offer-shield-from-sanctions/</guid>
      <description>BRICS Nations Explore New Currency to Shield from Sanctions
The BRICS nations (Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa) have agreed to explore the creation of a new reserve currency that could offer a shield from sanctions. The move is seen as a response to the Western sanctions imposed on Russia in the wake of its invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:11:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banxico-to-keep-interest-rates-high-for-long-period-of-time/</guid>
      <description>Banxico to Keep Interest Rates High for Long Period of Time Mexico&amp;rsquo;s central bank, Banxico, has signaled that it will keep interest rates high for a long period of time in order to tame inflation.
The bank&amp;rsquo;s decision comes as inflation in Mexico has reached a 20-year high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chilean President Boric Pushes for Tax Reform</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chilean-president-boric-pushes-for-tax-reform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:03:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chilean-president-boric-pushes-for-tax-reform/</guid>
      <description>Chilean President Boric Pushes for Tax Reform Chilean President Gabriel Boric has pressed for the need for tax reform to fund social programs and transition to a green economy.
Boric said that the current tax system is &amp;ldquo;unfair&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;inefficient,&amp;rdquo; and that it needs to be reformed in order to generate more revenue for the government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawkish Australian Economists See RBA Raising Key Rate to 4.6%</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/hawkish-australian-economists-see-rba-raising-key-rate-to-4.6/</guid>
      <description>RBA to Raise Cash Rate to 4.6%?
A group of Australian economists are predicting that the Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA) will raise the cash rate to 4.6% by the end of 2023. This would be the highest level for the cash rate since 1994.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheaper Childcare Costs in the South</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/cheaper-childcare-costs-in-the-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:35:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/cheaper-childcare-costs-in-the-south/</guid>
      <description>Cheaper Childcare Costs in the South The cost of childcare in the United States is high, and it is especially expensive in urban areas. However, the southern United States has the most affordable childcare costs in the country.
The average cost of childcare in the South is $6,660 per year, while the national average is $10,820 per year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Looks Like &#39;Labor Hoarding&#39; Is Happening at US Factories</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/it-looks-like-labor-hoarding-is-happening-at-us-factories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:56:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/it-looks-like-labor-hoarding-is-happening-at-us-factories/</guid>
      <description>Labor Shortage in Manufacturing The US manufacturing sector is facing a labor shortage, which is forcing some factories to hoard workers. Labor hoarding is when a company keeps more workers on staff than it needs, in case of unexpected turnover or increased demand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Loan Debt and Housing Crisis Slamming Young People</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/student-loan-debt-and-housing-crisis-slamming-young-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/student-loan-debt-and-housing-crisis-slamming-young-people/</guid>
      <description>Student Loan Debt and Housing Crisis Slamming Young People Young people in the United States are facing a double whammy of high student loan debt and rising housing prices. The average student loan debt for a college graduate is now over $30,000, and the median home price is now over $400,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Pitches Automakers GM, Toyota on Developing Southern States</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/mexico-pitches-automakers-gm-toyota-on-developing-southern-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/mexico-pitches-automakers-gm-toyota-on-developing-southern-states/</guid>
      <description>Mexico Pitches Automakers GM, Toyota on Developing Southern States Mexico is in talks with General Motors (GM) and Toyota Motor Corporation (TMC) about investing in a narrow strip of land in southern Mexico. The government is hoping to attract investment to the region, which has been lagging behind the rest of the country in terms of economic development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Inquiry, Inheritance Tax, House Prices: The Readout</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:09:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/covid-inquiry-inheritance-tax-house-prices-the-readout/</guid>
      <description>Key Issues in the UK News The UK news is dominated by a number of key issues in the coming weeks and months. These include:
The long-awaited public inquiry into the UK government&amp;rsquo;s handling of the Covid-19 pandemic. The government&amp;rsquo;s plans to raise the threshold at which people start to pay inheritance tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Anyone Really Need a $649 Ice Maker?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/does-anyone-really-need-a-649-ice-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/does-anyone-really-need-a-649-ice-maker/</guid>
      <description>Do you need a high-end ice maker? If you&amp;rsquo;re a home cook or bartender, you might be wondering if it&amp;rsquo;s worth the investment. After all, these machines can cost upwards of $600.
Here are some of the pros and cons of high-end ice makers to help you decide if one is right for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Clear Evidence: The Bloomberg Close, Europe Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/no-clear-evidence-the-bloomberg-close-europe-edition/</guid>
      <description>Will the War in Ukraine Lead to a Global Recession? The war in Ukraine has had a significant impact on the global economy. The International Monetary Fund has downgraded its growth forecast for the global economy in 2022, but it still expects growth of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stellantis Says No Deal Yet in Canada Battery Plant Subsidy Feud</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stellantis-says-no-deal-yet-in-canada-battery-plant-subsidy-feud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:40:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stellantis-says-no-deal-yet-in-canada-battery-plant-subsidy-feud/</guid>
      <description>Stellantis Puts Canadian EV Battery Plant on Hold Stellantis, the parent company of Chrysler, Dodge, and Jeep, has put a hold on construction of an electric-vehicle battery plant in Windsor, Ontario. The company is seeking government subsidies to help fund the $5 billion project, but the Canadian government has not yet committed to any funding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counterfeit Luxury Goods: A Growing Problem</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/counterfeit-luxury-goods-a-growing-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:17:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/counterfeit-luxury-goods-a-growing-problem/</guid>
      <description>Counterfeit Luxury Goods: A Growing Problem The luxury goods industry is facing a growing counterfeiting problem. Counterfeit goods are often of poor quality and can pose a safety hazard. The counterfeiting industry is estimated to be worth billions of dollars. Luxury brands are working to combat counterfeiting, but the problem remains a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Africa May Turn to Burning Heavy Fuel Oil to Tackle Load Shedding</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/south-africa-may-turn-to-burning-heavy-fuel-oil-to-tackle-load-shedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:14:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/south-africa-may-turn-to-burning-heavy-fuel-oil-to-tackle-load-shedding/</guid>
      <description>South Africa May Turn to Burning Heavy Fuel Oil to Tackle Load Shedding South Africa is facing a severe power crisis, with rolling blackouts lasting up to 10 hours a day. The government is considering burning heavy fuel oil to generate electricity, as a temporary measure to ease the crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria Central Bank Denies Devaluing Naira as Calls Grow Louder</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nigeria-central-bank-denies-devaluing-naira-as-calls-grow-louder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:45:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nigeria-central-bank-denies-devaluing-naira-as-calls-grow-louder/</guid>
      <description>Nigeria Central Bank Denies Devaluing Naira as Calls Grow Louder The Nigerian Central Bank (CBN) has denied reports that it is planning to devalue the naira. The CBN Governor, Godwin Emefiele, said that the naira is &amp;ldquo;fundamentally strong&amp;rdquo; and that there is no need to devalue it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angola Cuts Fuel Subsidy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/angola-cuts-fuel-subsidy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:28:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/angola-cuts-fuel-subsidy/</guid>
      <description>Angola Cuts Fuel Subsidy Angola has cut its fuel subsidy, following in the footsteps of Nigeria. This means that the price of gasoline will rise from 160 kwanzas to 300 kwanzas per liter.
The government says that the subsidy was unsustainable and that the price increase is necessary to reduce the country&amp;rsquo;s budget deficit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chatbot Was Designed to Help Prevent Eating Disorders. Then It Gave Dieting Tips.</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chatbot-was-designed-to-help-prevent-eating-disorders.-then-it-gave-dieting-tips./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chatbot-was-designed-to-help-prevent-eating-disorders.-then-it-gave-dieting-tips./</guid>
      <description>Lily Chatbot Shut Down After Giving Dieting Tips A chatbot called Lily was designed to help prevent eating disorders by providing support and advice to users. Lily was created by the National Eating Disorders Association (NEDA) and was based on the experiences of people who had recovered from eating disorders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weak Krone Turns Tesla-Loving Norway Into Used Car Exporter</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/weak-krone-turns-tesla-loving-norway-into-used-car-exporter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:23:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/weak-krone-turns-tesla-loving-norway-into-used-car-exporter/</guid>
      <description>Weak Norwegian Krone Boosts Used Car Market The Norwegian krone has weakened against the euro and the dollar in recent months. This has made imported cars more expensive in Norway, and has led to a surge in demand for used cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazil&#39;s Economy Bounces Back Under Lula</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brazils-economy-bounces-back-under-lula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:08:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brazils-economy-bounces-back-under-lula/</guid>
      <description>Brazil&amp;rsquo;s economy bounced back in the first quarter of 2023, growing at an annualized rate of 1.2%. This defied expectations that the economy would contract, and was driven by a rebound in consumer spending and investment. The unemployment rate fell to 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Respite Period For UK Housing Is Over</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:06:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-respite-period-for-uk-housing-is-over/</guid>
      <description>The UK housing market is showing signs of slowing down, with house prices stabilizing in May after a sharp rise in the fourth quarter of 2022. However, transaction volumes are falling, suggesting that further price falls are only a matter of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Says Core Price Trend Was &#39;Broadly Seen as Worrisome&#39; in May</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:57:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-says-core-price-trend-was-broadly-seen-as-worrisome-in-may/</guid>
      <description>ECB Concerned About Inflation The European Central Bank (ECB) is concerned about the path of inflation, according to the minutes of its May policy meeting. Core inflation, which excludes food and energy, rose to 3.8% in May from 3.5% in April. This was the highest level since December 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democrats, Don&#39;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:30:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/democrats-dont-repeat-this-debt-ceiling-debacle/</guid>
      <description>Democrats, Don&amp;rsquo;t Repeat This Debt-Ceiling Debacle In 2011, Republicans held the debt ceiling hostage in an attempt to extract concessions from Democrats. The crisis caused significant economic damage, and it could have been avoided if Democrats had not caved to Republican demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is FedNow and How Will the Payment System Work?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-fednow-and-how-will-the-payment-system-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:09:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-fednow-and-how-will-the-payment-system-work/</guid>
      <description>FedNow: A New Payment System from the Federal Reserve The Federal Reserve is developing a new payment system called FedNow. FedNow will allow for instant payments between banks, 24/7, 365 days a year. FedNow is expected to be available in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pause Time?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pause-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:00:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pause-time/</guid>
      <description>Can We Pause Time? The possibility of pausing time has long been a staple of science fiction. But is it really possible? And if so, what would the consequences be?
In a recent article, [author name] argues that it is theoretically possible to pause time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand to Shrink Rank of Generals Amid Conscription Debate</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/thailand-to-shrink-rank-of-generals-amid-conscription-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:49:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/thailand-to-shrink-rank-of-generals-amid-conscription-debate/</guid>
      <description>Thailand to Shrink Rank of Generals Amid Conscription Debate Thailand&amp;rsquo;s defense ministry has announced plans to slash the number of army generals by 50% over the next four years. The move comes amid a debate over conscription, with a coalition of pro-democracy parties that won the May election pledging to end the practice and reduce military spending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is the UAE’s New Tax on Corporate Earnings and Who Pays It?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-the-uaes-new-tax-on-corporate-earnings-and-who-pays-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:34:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-the-uaes-new-tax-on-corporate-earnings-and-who-pays-it/</guid>
      <description>UAE Introduces New Corporate Tax The UAE has introduced a new corporate tax of 9%, effective from June 1, 2023. The tax will be applied to all businesses that generate more than AED 1 million in annual turnover. Businesses that are located in free zones will be exempt from the tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghana Nears Deal With Pension Funds on $2.6 Billion Debt Revamp</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ghana-nears-deal-with-pension-funds-on-2.6-billion-debt-revamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:02:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ghana-nears-deal-with-pension-funds-on-2.6-billion-debt-revamp/</guid>
      <description>Ghana&amp;rsquo;s pension funds are close to agreeing to a deal to restructure $2.6 billion worth of government bonds they hold. The deal would see the government extend the maturity dates of the bonds and reduce the interest rates on them. The restructuring is part of Ghana&amp;rsquo;s efforts to reduce its debt burden and improve its fiscal position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The US-Led World Order Faces a New Challenge</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-us-led-world-order-faces-a-new-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:58:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-us-led-world-order-faces-a-new-challenge/</guid>
      <description>The US-led world order is facing a new challenge from the BRICS bloc, which is made up of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa. These countries are all emerging economies with large populations and growing economic clout. They are seeking to challenge the dominance of the US and the European Union in the global economy and geopolitics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eskom Latest: Spar Retailers&#39; Diesel Bill at $35 Million</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</guid>
      <description>Spar Retailers Spend $35 Million on Diesel to Run Generators South African food and liquor retailer Spar Group estimates that its outlets spent more than 700 million rand ($35 million) on diesel to run generators in the six months through March. This is more than triple the amount spent on diesel in the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB&#39;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:43:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecbs-lagarde-sees-no-clear-evidence-core-inflation-has-peaked/</guid>
      <description>ECB&amp;rsquo;s Lagarde Sees No Clear Evidence Core Inflation Has Peaked European Central Bank (ECB) President Christine Lagarde said on Thursday that there is no clear evidence that underlying inflation has peaked.
Core inflation, which excludes food and energy prices, rose to 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s Municipal Debt Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/chinas-municipal-debt-crisis/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Municipal Debt Crisis China&amp;rsquo;s municipal debt has been growing rapidly in recent years, reaching a total of 50 trillion yuan ($7.9 trillion) in 2022. This debt is largely used to finance infrastructure projects, which have helped to boost China&amp;rsquo;s economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone Inflation Slows, but ECB to Keep Rates Low</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eurozone-inflation-slows-but-ecb-to-keep-rates-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eurozone-inflation-slows-but-ecb-to-keep-rates-low/</guid>
      <description>Eurozone Inflation Slows, but ECB to Keep Rates Low Inflation in the eurozone slowed to 3.0% in May from 3.5% in April, but the European Central Bank (ECB) is likely to keep interest rates low for now.
The ECB has said that it will keep rates low until at least the end of 2023, even if inflation falls below its target of 2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Mortgage Lending Unexpectedly Falls After Interest Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-mortgage-lending-unexpectedly-falls-after-interest-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:46:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-mortgage-lending-unexpectedly-falls-after-interest-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>UK Mortgage Lending Falls Unexpectedly After Interest Rate Hikes Mortgage lending in the UK fell unexpectedly in April, after the Bank of England raised interest rates for the fifth time in a row.
Lenders authorized 48,700 home loans in April, down sharply from the 51,500 approved in March.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan Moves to Ease Pressure on Rupee in Retail Market</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:16:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan has taken a number of steps to stabilize the rupee in the retail market. These measures include increasing the State Bank of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s (SBP) foreign exchange reserves by $1 billion, selling dollars to commercial banks at a discounted rate, and increasing the amount of foreign currency that Pakistanis can carry when they travel abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost Done: The Bloomberg Close, Asia Edition</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/almost-done-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:11:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/almost-done-the-bloomberg-close-asia-edition/</guid>
      <description>Markets in Asia were mixed on Tuesday as investors awaited the outcome of the US Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s meeting. The Nikkei 225 in Japan was down 0.3%, while the Hang Seng in Hong Kong was up 0.2%.
The US dollar was stronger against most currencies, as investors expected the Fed to raise interest rates by 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Key to Making AI a Benefit, Not a Hazard</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-key-to-making-ai-a-benefit-not-a-hazard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-key-to-making-ai-a-benefit-not-a-hazard/</guid>
      <description>The Key to Making AI a Benefit, Not a Hazard Artificial intelligence (AI) is rapidly developing and has the potential to be a major benefit to society. However, there are also risks associated with AI, such as job displacement, bias, and misuse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:35:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</guid>
      <description>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year According to Moody&amp;rsquo;s, the UK is headed for a &amp;ldquo;mild recession&amp;rdquo; this year. The recession is expected to be caused by higher-than-expected inflation and rising interest rates. Inflation in the UK is currently at a 40-year high, and interest rates have been raised four times since December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEC&#43; Faces Oil Market Torn by Demand Rebound and Recession Risks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/opec&#43;-faces-oil-market-torn-by-demand-rebound-and-recession-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:29:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/opec&#43;-faces-oil-market-torn-by-demand-rebound-and-recession-risks/</guid>
      <description>OPEC+ Faces Oil Market Torn by Demand Rebound and Recession Risks OPEC+ is facing a difficult balancing act as the oil market is torn between demand rebounding from the COVID-19 pandemic and recession risks.
The International Energy Agency (IEA) has warned that the global oil market could be in a deficit of 1 million barrels per day (bpd) in the third quarter of 2023, if Russian output falls by 3 million bpd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Watch Exports to US Fall for First Time in Over Two Years</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/swiss-watch-exports-to-us-fall-for-first-time-in-over-two-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:16:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/swiss-watch-exports-to-us-fall-for-first-time-in-over-two-years/</guid>
      <description>Swiss Watch Exports to US Fall for First Time in Over Two Years Swiss watch exports to the United States fell by 4.9% in April 2023, marking the first decline in more than two years. The decline comes as the US economy faces headwinds from inflation, rising interest rates, and supply chain disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:08:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</guid>
      <description>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause European stocks rose on Tuesday after the US Congress reached a deal to avert a debt default and the Federal Reserve signaled that it may pause its interest rate hikes.
The pan-European Stoxx 600 index rose 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theft Shuts Key Railway Serving South African Iron-Ore Exporters</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/theft-shuts-key-railway-serving-south-african-iron-ore-exporters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/theft-shuts-key-railway-serving-south-african-iron-ore-exporters/</guid>
      <description>Theft Shuts Down Key Railway Serving South Africa&amp;rsquo;s Iron-Ore Exporters A key railway line serving South Africa&amp;rsquo;s iron-ore exporters was shut down due to theft of power cables. The 861-kilometer (535-mile) line is used to transport iron-ore and manganese from Kumba Iron Ore Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Property Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vietnam-property-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vietnam-property-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam Property Crisis Vietnam has a $34 billion worth of property projects that have been suspended due to a liquidity crisis in the country&amp;rsquo;s banking sector. The crisis has been caused by a combination of factors, including the COVID-19 pandemic, the global economic slowdown, and government regulations that have made it more difficult for developers to raise capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Cash Use Drops in Reality Check for Bill-and-Coin Haven</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/swiss-cash-use-drops-in-reality-check-for-bill-and-coin-haven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/swiss-cash-use-drops-in-reality-check-for-bill-and-coin-haven/</guid>
      <description>Swiss Cash Use Declines The use of cash in Switzerland has declined significantly in recent years. In 2017, 70% of all transactions were made in cash. By 2022, that number had fallen to 36%.
There are a number of factors that have contributed to the decline in cash use, including the rise of digital payments, the COVID-19 pandemic, and government efforts to reduce tax evasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Regulator Says AI is Focus of Marquee Fintech Festival</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/singapore-regulator-says-ai-is-focus-of-marquee-fintech-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:12:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/singapore-regulator-says-ai-is-focus-of-marquee-fintech-festival/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence to be Key Focus of Singapore FinTech Festival The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has said that artificial intelligence (AI) will be a key focus of the upcoming Singapore FinTech Festival. The festival, which will be held from November 14-17, 2023, will bring together over 25,000 participants from over 150 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Today: U.S.-China Trade Deal, Fed Pause, AI Boom</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-today-u.s.-china-trade-deal-fed-pause-ai-boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-today-u.s.-china-trade-deal-fed-pause-ai-boom/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Today: U.S.-China Trade Deal, Fed Pause, AI Boom The stock markets are expected to be positive today, as investors are optimistic about the U.S.-China trade deal and the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s pause on interest rate hikes. The AI boom is also a positive sign for the economy, as it is expected to create new jobs and boost productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine NATO allies are divided over whether to deepen ties with Ukraine. Some allies, such as the United States and Poland, believe that Ukraine should be given a Membership Action Plan (MAP), which is a first step towards joining NATO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stocks: Are They Overvalued?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/tech-stocks-are-they-overvalued/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/tech-stocks-are-they-overvalued/</guid>
      <description>Tech stocks have been on a tear in recent years, with the Nasdaq Composite Index more than doubling in value since the start of 2019. However, there are some signs that the tech rally may be coming to an end. In recent weeks, tech stocks have started to decline, with the Nasdaq Composite Index down about 10% from its all-time high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcript Zero Episode 40: The Climate Fight&#39;s Secret Weapon</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/transcript-zero-episode-40-the-climate-fights-secret-weapon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:04:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/transcript-zero-episode-40-the-climate-fights-secret-weapon/</guid>
      <description>Retirement Accounts: A Secret Weapon in the Fight Against Climate Change Pension funds have a huge amount of money that could be used to invest in sustainable companies. There is a growing demand for sustainable investments, and these investments can make equal, if not more, money than traditional investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Birthrate Dips Slightly in 2022 After Rebound in Prior Year</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-birthrate-dips-slightly-in-2022-after-rebound-in-prior-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-birthrate-dips-slightly-in-2022-after-rebound-in-prior-year/</guid>
      <description>The US birth rate declined slightly in 2022 after rebounding in 2021. The total fertility rate in 2022 was 1.69 births per woman, down from 1.77 births per woman in 2021. The decline in births was widespread, with 38 states and the District of Columbia experiencing a drop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Avatar Video Generators Will Hurt Human Creativity</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ai-avatar-video-generators-will-hurt-human-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ai-avatar-video-generators-will-hurt-human-creativity/</guid>
      <description>AI Avatar Video Generators: Potential Risks and Benefits AI avatar video generators are a new technology that can create realistic videos of people that don&amp;rsquo;t actually exist. These generators could be used for a variety of purposes, such as creating fake news videos or generating deepfakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BRICS Ministers to Challenge US With More Members, Common Currency</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brics-ministers-to-challenge-us-with-more-members-common-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brics-ministers-to-challenge-us-with-more-members-common-currency/</guid>
      <description>BRICS Ministers to Challenge US With More Members, Common Currency The BRICS bloc of emerging economies is looking to expand and create a common currency in a challenge to the US-led global order.
The bloc&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministers met in Cape Town on Wednesday to discuss the expansion of the group, which currently consists of Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germany&#39;s Sneeze May Give European Stocks a Cold</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/germanys-sneeze-may-give-european-stocks-a-cold/</guid>
      <description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s Recession Could Hurt the Eurozone Germany, the eurozone&amp;rsquo;s largest economy, is in recession. The country&amp;rsquo;s GDP shrank by 0.3% in the first quarter of 2023, following a 0.5% decline in the fourth quarter of 2022.
The recession is being driven by a number of factors, including the global slowdown, the trade war between the United States and China, and the Brexit uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Rupee Trap Is Adding to $147 Billion Hoard Stuck Abroad</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Rupee Trap Russia has been selling oil to India in exchange for rupees, but it has been difficult for Russia to use these rupees to buy goods and services from India. This is because India has strict foreign exchange controls that make it difficult for foreigners to repatriate rupees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweden Pins NATO Ambitions on Terror Law in Bid to Sway Erdogan</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/sweden-pins-nato-ambitions-on-terror-law-in-bid-to-sway-erdogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/sweden-pins-nato-ambitions-on-terror-law-in-bid-to-sway-erdogan/</guid>
      <description>Sweden has passed a new terror law in an effort to sway Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan to approve the Nordic country&amp;rsquo;s accession to NATO.
The law, which was passed by the Swedish parliament on May 27, defines terrorism as &amp;ldquo;any act that is intended to create a state of terror or fear in a population or in a particular group of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine&#39;s Attacks on Russia Are a Calculated Gamble</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Attacks on Russian Territory Ukraine has recently carried out a series of attacks on Russian territory. The attacks have targeted Russian military bases, supply lines, and infrastructure. Russia has accused Ukraine of carrying out the attacks with the help of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</guid>
      <description>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets The European Central Bank (ECB) has warned that a change in policy by the Bank of Japan (BOJ) could test global bond markets.
The BOJ has been maintaining a policy of negative interest rates and quantitative easing for years, which has helped to keep Japanese government bond yields low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Buys Up Cheap Coal as Prices Fall, Set to Drive Record Imports</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-buys-up-cheap-coal-as-prices-fall-set-to-drive-record-imports/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-buys-up-cheap-coal-as-prices-fall-set-to-drive-record-imports/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s Increased Coal Imports China is buying up cheap coal as prices fall, and this is set to drive record imports. The country&amp;rsquo;s purchases may hit 360 million to 380 million tons in 2023, according to its top industry association. This would be a significant increase from the 293 million tons that China imported last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</guid>
      <description>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies The Japanese government plans to set up an official security clearance system for accessing classified information related to economic security. The system is intended to help Japanese companies win contracts abroad, particularly in areas such as cutting-edge chip technology and cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The House That &#39;Rolling Stone&#39; Built</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-house-that-rolling-stone-built/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 21:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-house-that-rolling-stone-built/</guid>
      <description>Jann Wenner, the co-founder of Rolling Stone magazine, has built a new home in Montauk, New York. The house is designed in a casual minimalist style, with a focus on natural materials and open spaces.
The home has a number of features that are designed to promote relaxation and family togetherness, such as a large outdoor deck, a swimming pool, and a game room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luton Town&#39;s Wild Ride to the Premier League</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/luton-towns-wild-ride-to-the-premier-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 20:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/luton-towns-wild-ride-to-the-premier-league/</guid>
      <description>Luton Town&amp;rsquo;s Wild Ride to the Premier League
Nine years ago, Luton Town was in the fifth tier of English soccer. On Saturday, it won promotion to the richest league in the game by beating Coventry City in a penalty shootout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is It OK to Track Your Spouse&#39;s Location?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/is-it-ok-to-track-your-spouses-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 20:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/is-it-ok-to-track-your-spouses-location/</guid>
      <description>Should You Track Your Spouse&amp;rsquo;s Location?
Tracking your spouse&amp;rsquo;s location can be a slippery slope. It can start out as a way to keep tabs on them, but it can quickly turn into a way to control them.
If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about tracking your spouse&amp;rsquo;s location, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a conversation with them first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Turkey&#39;s President Faces the Biggest Election Challenge in Years</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/why-turkeys-president-faces-the-biggest-election-challenge-in-years/</guid>
      <description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Presidential Election: Erdogan Faces His Biggest Challenge in Years
Incumbent Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan faces his biggest challenge in 20 years in Sunday’s runoff election against opposition candidate Kemal Kilicdaroglu. WSJ’s Jared Malsin explains why this is one of the world’s most important votes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Lawmakers Plan Impeachment Proceedings Against Ken Paxton</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/texas-lawmakers-plan-impeachment-proceedings-against-ken-paxton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/texas-lawmakers-plan-impeachment-proceedings-against-ken-paxton/</guid>
      <description>Texas Lawmakers Plan Impeachment Proceedings Against Ken Paxton
Texas lawmakers are planning to begin impeachment proceedings against Attorney General Ken Paxton. The articles of impeachment drafted against Paxton include conspiracy, dereliction of duty, misapplication of public resources, and unfitness for office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Delivers Early Win in Asia Trade Pact, But Rifts Surface</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-delivers-early-win-in-asia-trade-pact-but-rifts-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-delivers-early-win-in-asia-trade-pact-but-rifts-surface/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. and 13 other Asia-Pacific nations have agreed to expand supply-chain cooperation in a move aimed at strengthening economic ties in the region and countering China&amp;rsquo;s growing influence.
The pact, which was announced at the Detroit Economic Club by U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai and Japanese Foreign Minister Yoshimasa Hayashi, includes provisions for cooperation on supply chain resilience, digital trade, and labor standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Voters Stymie LVMH Plans to Expand U.S. Hotel Business</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/beverly-hills-voters-stymie-lvmh-plans-to-expand-u.s.-hotel-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:53:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/beverly-hills-voters-stymie-lvmh-plans-to-expand-u.s.-hotel-business/</guid>
      <description>Beverly Hills voters have rejected plans by LVMH&amp;rsquo;s Cheval Blanc brand to build its first hotel in the U.S. The proposed hotel would have been located on Rodeo Drive and would have had 109 rooms. The vote was 53% to 47% against the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Give Great Gifts: What Science Teaches Us</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-give-great-gifts-what-science-teaches-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 16:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-to-give-great-gifts-what-science-teaches-us/</guid>
      <description>How to Give Great Gifts: What Science Teaches Us Giving gifts is a way to show someone you care. But it can be hard to know what to get someone. You want to give them something they&amp;rsquo;ll love and appreciate, but you don&amp;rsquo;t want to spend a fortune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Popocatépetl Volcano in Mexico: What We Know About Eruption Alert Level</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/popocat%C3%A9petl-volcano-in-mexico-what-we-know-about-eruption-alert-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 15:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/popocat%C3%A9petl-volcano-in-mexico-what-we-know-about-eruption-alert-level/</guid>
      <description>Popocatépetl Volcano in Mexico: Increased Activity and Eruption Alert Level Popocatépetl, a volcano near Mexico City, has been exhibiting increased activity in recent weeks. This includes increased ashfall and seismic activity. As a result, authorities have raised the eruption alert level to Yellow Phase 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur Scholar Is Missing in Hong Kong, Rights Group Says, Raising Fear of Detention</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uyghur-scholar-is-missing-in-hong-kong-rights-group-says-raising-fear-of-detention/</guid>
      <description>Uyghur Scholar Missing in Hong Kong A Uyghur scholar, Abuduwaili Abudureheman, has been missing in Hong Kong since May 10, 2023. Abudureheman was last heard from saying he was being interrogated by police. Amnesty International has raised concerns that Abudureheman may have been detained by the Chinese government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Rules for Business Travel to China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</guid>
      <description>The New Rules for Business Travel to China Business travel to China can be a challenge, but it can also be a rewarding experience. By following these tips, you can increase your chances of success:
Be prepared for heightened security measures. Chinese border agents are increasingly scrutinizing travelers, especially those from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets
Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces launched airstrikes on 11 Russian clusters of personnel and equipment on May 27, 2023. The strikes were carried out by Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s air force over the past day.
The strikes come as anticipation grows that Kyiv is on the brink of beginning a long-awaited offensive to regain lost territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Before Jeeps Became SUVs, They Looked Like This</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/before-jeeps-became-suvs-they-looked-like-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/before-jeeps-became-suvs-they-looked-like-this/</guid>
      <description>1950 Willys Jeepster: A Throwback to an Era When Cars Were for Fun
The 1950 Willys Jeepster is a car that is a throwback to an era when &amp;ldquo;people would use cars for fun.&amp;rdquo; The Jeepster was originally designed as a more stylish and luxurious alternative to the military-style Jeeps that were popular at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Is the Best Time to Ask for a Customer Review?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/when-is-the-best-time-to-ask-for-a-customer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/when-is-the-best-time-to-ask-for-a-customer-review/</guid>
      <description>The Best Time to Ask for a Customer Review
A new study by Harvard Business Review found that the best time to ask for a review is within 24 hours of a customer completing a transaction.
The study found that customers are more likely to give a positive review if they are asked within 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk Turns His Attention to 2024 White House Race</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/musk-turns-his-attention-to-2024-white-house-race/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk has purchased Twitter, and many are wondering what this means for the 2024 election. Musk has said that he wants to make Twitter a more open and free platform for speech, but some experts worry that he could use the platform to give himself an unfair advantage in the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How AI Is Catapulting Nvidia Toward the $1 Trillion Club</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/how-ai-is-catapulting-nvidia-toward-the-1-trillion-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/how-ai-is-catapulting-nvidia-toward-the-1-trillion-club/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia is a chipmaker that specializes in artificial intelligence (AI). The company&amp;rsquo;s chips are used in a wide range of applications, including self-driving cars, robotics, and medical imaging. Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s chips are becoming increasingly important as AI becomes more widely adopted.
The company&amp;rsquo;s stock price has surged in recent years, and it is now valued at over $700 billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combative Consumers Change the Marketing Strategy for Target and Bud Light</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/combative-consumers-change-the-marketing-strategy-for-target-and-bud-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/combative-consumers-change-the-marketing-strategy-for-target-and-bud-light/</guid>
      <description>In the past, brands have often shrugged off criticism of their stands on social issues. However, the incidents involving Target and Bud Light show that even huge corporations can be made to bend. This is because consumers are increasingly using social media to voice their concerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CEO of YouTube Has a Plan to Win Over Anyone Watching TV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-ceo-of-youtube-has-a-plan-to-win-over-anyone-watching-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-ceo-of-youtube-has-a-plan-to-win-over-anyone-watching-tv/</guid>
      <description>YouTube CEO Neal Mohan&amp;rsquo;s Plan to Win Over TV Viewers
YouTube CEO Neal Mohan is trying to win over people who watch TV by offering short videos and TV-like programming. Mohan believes that YouTube can be a one-stop shop for all of your entertainment needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Alternative to Bloomberg Terminals Quietly Limits Information Overseas</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/a-chinese-alternative-to-bloomberg-terminals-quietly-limits-information-overseas/</guid>
      <description>Chinese Data Provider Wind Limits Information for Foreign Users
Wind Information, a Chinese data provider, has quietly limited the information that foreign users can access. This includes data on e-commerce shopping trends and satellite images. The move has clouded the view of the world&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy for foreign investors and analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alo Yoga Is Beating Lululemon at Its Own Game</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/alo-yoga-is-beating-lululemon-at-its-own-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/alo-yoga-is-beating-lululemon-at-its-own-game/</guid>
      <description>Alo Yoga: The New King of Yoga Apparel?
Alo Yoga is a Los Angeles-based yoga apparel company that has been growing rapidly in recent years. The company&amp;rsquo;s success has been attributed to its focus on high-quality, stylish clothing that is popular with celebrities and influencers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen Bets an Old SUV Can Help It Win Over Americans</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/volkswagen-bets-an-old-suv-can-help-it-win-over-americans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 04:01:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/volkswagen-bets-an-old-suv-can-help-it-win-over-americans/</guid>
      <description>Volkswagen Revives Scout Brand to Win Over American Buyers
Volkswagen is reviving the Scout brand in the United States in an effort to win over more American buyers. The Scout brand was originally owned by International Harvester and produced trucks and SUVs from 1961 to 1980.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Killer Apps&#39; That Could Make Apple&#39;s New Headset a Winner</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-killer-apps-that-could-make-apples-new-headset-a-winner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-killer-apps-that-could-make-apples-new-headset-a-winner/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s Mixed Reality Headset: The Killer Apps That Could Make It a Winner
Apple is reportedly working on a mixed-reality headset that could be released in 2023. The headset is expected to be a high-end device that will cost $3,000 or more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Farm Halts Home-Insurance Sales in California</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/state-farm-halts-home-insurance-sales-in-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 23:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/state-farm-halts-home-insurance-sales-in-california/</guid>
      <description>State Farm Halts Home-Insurance Sales in California
State Farm, the largest home insurer in the United States, has halted new home-insurance sales in California. The move is a blow to the state&amp;rsquo;s efforts to maintain a vibrant market for homeowners in the wildfire-prone state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023年AIGC项目汇总</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/aigc_startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/aigc_startup/</guid>
      <description>2022是AIGC产业引爆公众关注的第一年，可以预见2023将兴起AIGC的创业潮。</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
