<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:15:09 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Debt Ceiling Is Kevin McCarthy&#39;s Problem to Fix, Not Joe Biden&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-is-kevin-mccarthys-problem-to-fix-not-joe-bidens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 19:15:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/debt-ceiling-is-kevin-mccarthys-problem-to-fix-not-joe-bidens/</guid>
      <description>In recent weeks, the U.S. debt ceiling debate has been heating up, with Speaker Kevin McCarthy finding himself in a difficult position. The New York Times reports that McCarthy is facing a dilemma as he tries to navigate the competing interests of his Republican caucus and the Biden administration[^1].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teens Can Now Ride Ubers Solo---With Parents&#39; Credit Cards</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/teens-can-now-ride-ubers-solo---with-parents-credit-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/teens-can-now-ride-ubers-solo---with-parents-credit-cards/</guid>
      <description>According to the Wall Street Journal, Uber is now offering a solution for parents who need help driving kids around by allowing 13- to 17-year-olds parent-supervised accounts for rides and food delivery. This is the first time teenagers as young as 13 years old will be able to have Uber accounts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banks Want a Break From the FDIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/banks-want-a-break-from-the-fdic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:15:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/banks-want-a-break-from-the-fdic/</guid>
      <description>In the wake of the recent regional banking crisis, banks are seeking relief from the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC), according to an article by Bloomberg [^1^][4]. The crisis has put a spotlight on the FDIC, which has been forced to rescue failed banks at a high cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quirky Federal Spending Speeds Up Debt-Ceiling Clash</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/quirky-federal-spending-speeds-up-debt-ceiling-clash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/quirky-federal-spending-speeds-up-debt-ceiling-clash/</guid>
      <description>Quirky Federal Spending Speeds Up Debt-Ceiling Clash A bigger-than-anticipated federal deficit has pushed up the deadline for dealing with the US debt ceiling from sometime in the third quarter to any day now, according to a recent article published on Bloomberg Opinion ^1^.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Apple Headset Is Coming. Can It Be More Than a Nerd Helmet?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/an-apple-headset-is-coming.-can-it-be-more-than-a-nerd-helmet/</guid>
      <description>Apple is rumored to be releasing a mixed reality headset as a precursor to their AR glasses. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we know so far:
The headset will allow users to switch between viewing the real world and virtual reality with a physical dial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq 100 Rally Shows the Bears Got Up Too Early</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nasdaq-100-rally-shows-the-bears-got-up-too-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nasdaq-100-rally-shows-the-bears-got-up-too-early/</guid>
      <description>The Nasdaq 100 Index has been making headlines lately with its impressive performance this year, gaining 23% and edging close to a 52-week high. This has caused some to question the validity of earlier predictions of a bear market, and has led to discussions on the importance of timing in stock market predictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Ukraine, Technology Only Thickens the Fog of War</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/in-ukraine-technology-only-thickens-the-fog-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/in-ukraine-technology-only-thickens-the-fog-of-war/</guid>
      <description>The conflict in Ukraine has been ongoing for years, with no clear end in sight. As technology advances, it has become increasingly intertwined with the conflict, with both sides utilizing it to gain an advantage.
On May 17, 2023, Bloomberg published an article titled &amp;ldquo;In Ukraine, Technology Only Thickens the Fog of War&amp;rdquo; by Leonid Bershidsky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling Failed With EMs and Will Again With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/decoupling-failed-with-ems-and-will-again-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/decoupling-failed-with-ems-and-will-again-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Decoupling, or the idea of disentangling one country&amp;rsquo;s economy from another&amp;rsquo;s, has been a topic of much debate in recent years, particularly in regards to China. Some argue that decoupling from China is necessary to protect national security and intellectual property, while others believe it would be detrimental to global trade and economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apollo, Blackstone See Opportunities in Banks&#39; Troubles</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-blackstone-see-opportunities-in-banks-troubles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/apollo-blackstone-see-opportunities-in-banks-troubles/</guid>
      <description>In recent news, Apollo, Blackstone, and other private credit funds have expressed interest in the banking industry as banks face struggles in the current economic climate. According to Bloomberg, Apollo and Blackstone are among firms pitching private debt to public companies, while also bidding for assets from Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) [1][2][3][4][5].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Iran, Venezuela Confound Oil Output Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russia-iran-venezuela-confound-oil-output-forecasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russia-iran-venezuela-confound-oil-output-forecasts/</guid>
      <description>The International Energy Agency (IEA) has lifted its forecast for Russian, Iranian, and Venezuelan output in 2023 by a combined 1.3 million barrels a day, reaching an annual average of 14.3 million barrels a day, according to a recent article on Bloomberg 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Wants to Become a Heat-Pump Billionaire?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/who-wants-to-become-a-heat-pump-billionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/who-wants-to-become-a-heat-pump-billionaire/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The energy transition is a hot topic in today&amp;rsquo;s world, and with good reason. As we move towards a more sustainable future, there are many opportunities for investors to profit from this shift. One such opportunity is in the field of heat pumps, which are becoming an increasingly popular way to heat and cool homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Pursuing Peace, Japan&#39;s Leader Must Also Prepare for War</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/in-pursuing-peace-japans-leader-must-also-prepare-for-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/in-pursuing-peace-japans-leader-must-also-prepare-for-war/</guid>
      <description>On May 16th, 2023, The Washington Post published an article titled &amp;ldquo;In Pursuing Peace, Japan&amp;rsquo;s Leader Must Also Prepare for War&amp;rdquo; by an unknown author[^1^][1]. The article talks about how Fumio Kishida, Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader, is working towards nuclear disarmament while simultaneously moving the nation closer to being the world&amp;rsquo;s largest nuclear power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is ChatGPT? What to Know About the AI Chatbot</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-chatgpt-what-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT: The Next-Generation AI Chatbot Revolutionizing Industries
ChatGPT is an AI chatbot that has caused a stir in the world of technology and is set to transform industries and the future of work. Built on a family of large language models (LLMs) known as GPT-3, ChatGPT can understand and generate human-like answers to text prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Shouldn&#39;t Dismiss China&#39;s Ukraine Peace Bid</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/us-shouldnt-dismiss-chinas-ukraine-peace-bid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:00:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/us-shouldnt-dismiss-chinas-ukraine-peace-bid/</guid>
      <description>On May 16, 2023, Bloomberg published an op-ed titled &amp;ldquo;US Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t Dismiss China&amp;rsquo;s Ukraine Peace Bid,&amp;rdquo; which argues that the United States and its allies should not dismiss China&amp;rsquo;s proposal for a ceasefire in Ukraine. Instead, the US should engage with China to turn its rhetoric of peace into action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023年AIGC项目汇总</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/aigc_startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/aigc_startup/</guid>
      <description>2022是AIGC产业引爆公众关注的第一年，可以预见2023将兴起AIGC的创业潮。</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
