<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:48:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ecrett Music: Using AI for Composing Game Music</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecrett-music-using-ai-for-composing-game-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:48:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecrett-music-using-ai-for-composing-game-music/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Ecrett Music is a service that uses simple inputs to create tracks that fit the exact type of mood required. It is re-defining the generation of functional music that enhances another medium. The service is equipped to deliver royalty-free background music for videos, games and podcasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pros and Cons of VC Funding for AI Startups: A Review of the Crunchbase Megadeals Board</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-pros-and-cons-of-vc-funding-for-ai-startups-a-review-of-the-crunchbase-megadeals-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:44:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-pros-and-cons-of-vc-funding-for-ai-startups-a-review-of-the-crunchbase-megadeals-board/</guid>
      <description>The Crunchbase Megadeals Board is a useful resource for traders and investors who want to keep track of the latest trends in VC funding for AI startups. This board tracks announced venture funding deals in 2023 of $100 million or more in the Crunchbase database that were raised by U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub and OpenAI Release Copilot: An AI Pair Programmer</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/github-and-openai-release-copilot-an-ai-pair-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:36:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/github-and-openai-release-copilot-an-ai-pair-programmer/</guid>
      <description>GitHub and OpenAI have recently released Copilot, an AI-powered pair programmer that can help programmers write code faster and with less work. This revolutionary new system is powered by OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Codex, which is based on the GPT-3 architecture. Copilot can generate code within mainstream development environments such as VS Code and Neovim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open-Source LLMs: Benefits and Concerns</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/open-source-llms-benefits-and-concerns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:34:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/open-source-llms-benefits-and-concerns/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The topic of open-source LLMs (large language models) has been gaining attention on social media platforms like Twitter and Reddit. The push for open-source LLMs to become the dominant product is aimed at preventing a future where one or two companies control the information the world receives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of AI on Reddit: A Look at AI Interaction and Business Models</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-impact-of-ai-on-reddit-a-look-at-ai-interaction-and-business-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:33:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-impact-of-ai-on-reddit-a-look-at-ai-interaction-and-business-models/</guid>
      <description>As AI technology continues to advance, it is having a significant impact on various industries, including social media. One platform that has been influenced by AI is Reddit. In this blog post, we will examine how AI is changing the way users interact on Reddit and how it is affecting the platform&amp;rsquo;s business model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Music Composing Software for Game Developers</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/recommended-music-composing-software-for-game-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:30:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/recommended-music-composing-software-for-game-developers/</guid>
      <description>If you are a game developer looking for easy-to-use music composing software, you may want to check out these recommendations from Reddit&amp;rsquo;s gamedev subreddit.
Bosca Ceoil - Bosca Ceoil is a free and open-source music creation tool that is designed to be easy to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Websites for Market Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/top-websites-for-market-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:26:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/top-websites-for-market-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to analyze market data for your investment decisions, there are several websites that can provide valuable information. Here are a few of the top websites for market data analysis:
Yahoo Finance: Yahoo Finance is a popular website for tracking stock prices and market news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Intersection of Generative AI and UI Design: Insights from Reddit&#39;s UI Design Subreddit</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/exploring-the-intersection-of-generative-ai-and-ui-design-insights-from-reddits-ui-design-subreddit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:23:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/exploring-the-intersection-of-generative-ai-and-ui-design-insights-from-reddits-ui-design-subreddit/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The field of UI design has been enhanced by the use of generative AI, as discussed in a recent post on Reddit&amp;rsquo;s UI Design subreddit. This intersection of AI and design has the potential to revolutionize the way designers approach their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code-Generating AI Models and APIs: A Hot Topic in Programming</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/code-generating-ai-models-and-apis-a-hot-topic-in-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:19:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/code-generating-ai-models-and-apis-a-hot-topic-in-programming/</guid>
      <description>Code-generating AI models and AI-friendly APIs are gaining popularity in the programming community. Forbes recently published an article discussing five AI tools that can generate code to assist programmers. These tools are designed to help developers automate repetitive coding tasks and improve productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Open-Source LLMs: A Comparison to ChatGPT and GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-rise-of-open-source-llms-a-comparison-to-chatgpt-and-gpt-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:15:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-rise-of-open-source-llms-a-comparison-to-chatgpt-and-gpt-4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In recent discussions on Reddit and Twitter, there has been a lot of talk about Open-Source LLMs (Large Language Models). These discussions have included confusion about their differences and computing costs compared to ChatGPT, as well as claims about their capabilities compared to GPT-4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2023年AIGC项目汇总</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/aigc_startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/aigc_startup/</guid>
      <description>2022是AIGC产业引爆公众关注的第一年，可以预见2023将兴起AIGC的创业潮。</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
