<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dividend stock on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stock/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dividend stock on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-stock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Quality dividend stock with potential for growth when down. Positive earnings surprise and beats earnings expectations. Interest from insiders buying the stock. Diverse offerings catering to dividends or explosive growth. Strong performance in the reliable healthcare sector. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BAC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bac/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Bank of America&amp;rsquo;s stock has garnered significant attention, indicating investor interest. Strong influence of institutions due to substantial holdings could impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s direction. Bank of America is considered an attractive dividend stock in the current market. Risks: Moody&amp;rsquo;s downgrade and credit rating reviews for multiple banks, including Bank of America, may affect the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Impressive second-quarter earnings and revenue beat ratios in the healthcare sector highlight positive performance. Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dividend stock could attract investors looking for consistent income. FDA approval for antibody-based therapy Talvey indicates potential for innovation in difficult-to-treat blood cancer treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KMI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kmi/</guid>
      <description>score:1043
Chances: Pipeline giant Kinder Morgan (NYSE: KMI) is a high-yield dividend stock with a yield of 6.2%. Kinder Morgan has spent the last eight years reviving its image after dividend cut in 2015. Kinder Morgan&amp;rsquo;s ability to secure high-return expansion projects to grow cash flow is a positive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
