<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Autonomous Vehicles on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/autonomous-vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Autonomous Vehicles on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:04:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/autonomous-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 09:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-100
Chances: General Motors&amp;rsquo; Cruise unit is set to resume testing its robotaxis with safety drivers in Phoenix, marking an important step in restarting the autonomous vehicle business. GM is entering the EV truck business with a splash. The company has been working on software-enabled services and subscriptions, which could drive future growth and revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBLY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mbly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mbly/</guid>
      <description>score:-35
Chances: Shares of self-driving technology company Mobileye jumped on Wednesday after comments management made to investors at a conference. Three emerging leaders in advanced driver-assist systems, and Qualcomm is smashing expectations. There are three high-powered artificial intelligence (AI) stocks that could leave Nvidia in the dust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Aurora Innovation, Inc. has reported strong progress towards commercial launch with an Autonomy Readiness Measure (ARM) of 84% in Q3 2023 The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in industry conferences and events indicates a commitment to showcasing its technology and engaging with potential investors The opening of the industry’s first lane for driverless trucks supported by commercial-ready terminals in Dallas and Houston demonstrates Aurora&amp;rsquo;s advancement in autonomous vehicle technology Risks: The company&amp;rsquo;s significant net loss of US$414.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
