<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Support on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/community-support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community Support on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:04:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/community-support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 09:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:164
Chances: The company is actively supporting STEM education through its scholarship program, showcasing a commitment to future talent development and innovation. PG&amp;amp;E&amp;rsquo;s contribution of $55 million to the Dollar Energy Fund demonstrates a strong commitment to supporting customers in paying their energy bills during times of crisis, which can enhance customer loyalty and reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/exc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/exc/</guid>
      <description>score:130
Chances: ComEd was recognized for its outstanding emergency recovery and assistance efforts in 2023 by The Edison Electric Institute and the Midwest Energy Efficiency Alliance. Exelon has been providing incentives for the development of energy-efficient affordable housing units across northern Illinois, showing a commitment to sustainability and community support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:284
Chances: Regions Bank services designed to help people impacted by recent storms in Tennessee and Kentucky. Bank stocks are enjoying the chatter about potential interest-rate cuts at the Fed, which could benefit Regions Financial Corp. Initiatives to support veterans, equip family business owners, and teach financial literacy are creating positive community impact and potential long-term customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
