<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partnerships on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/partnerships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partnerships on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:03:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/partnerships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: IonQ and BearingPoint Bring Quantum Consulting to the European Market IonQ Signs Agreement With South Korea’s Ministry of Science and ICT to Cultivate Regional Quantum Computing Ecosystem IonQ Raises 2023 Bookings Expectations to $50M at Midpoint, Anticipates Doubling Bookings from Prior Year IonQ Forte Launched For Commercial Use, Making #AQ 29 Available for Customers Worldwide IonQ Demonstrates World-First Quantum Cognition Models Risks: While shareholders of IonQ (NYSE:IONQ) are in the black over 1 year, those who bought a week ago aren&amp;rsquo;t so fortunate IonQ Poised for Aggressive Commercial Growth in 2023, Sets Date to Report on Momentum and Fourth Quarter 2022 Financial Results IonQ and Hyundai Motor Company Expand Quantum Computing Partnership, Continuing Pursuit of Automotive Innovation IonQ Announces Third Quarter 2022 Financial Results IonQ Chief Scientist to Presen&amp;hellip; Score:-7 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:90
Chances: Exacta Bioscience and Ginkgo Bioworks Announce Partnership to Optimize Exacta&amp;rsquo;s Crop Protection Product Ginkgo Bioworks and Google Cloud Partner to Build Next Generation AI Platform for Biological Engineering and Biosecurity Ginkgo Bioworks Announces Collaboration with Merck to Improve Biologic Manufacturing Ginkgo Bioworks and Sumitomo Chemical Announce Expanded Partnership To Develop Functional Chemicals with Synthetic Biology Ginkgo Bioworks Advances Collaboration with Novo Nordisk on Expression Systems for Pharmaceutical Products Risks: Ginkgo Bioworks Awarded DARPA Contract to Reimagine the Manufacturing of Complex Therapeutic Proteins Ginkgo Bioworks and the Ministry of Health of the Republic of Botswana Announce Pathogen Monitoring Program at Key Ports of Entry Ginkgo Bioworks Announces Participation in Goldman Sachs 44th Annual Global Healthcare Conference Ginkgo Bioworks Reports First Quarter 2023 Financial Results Ginkgo Bioworks Previews Today&amp;rsquo;s Annual Ferment Conference Score:90 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Amazon&amp;rsquo;s CAPEX to Exceed $50 Billion in 2023, Partly to Support AI Amazon Adds Cloud Executives, Zoox Chief to Jassy’s Senior Team Like Amazon And Google, Salesforce Is Optimistic About The Remaining Half Of The Year Amazon (AMZN) Integrates Buy With Prime Into Shopify Stores This Is a Huge Win for Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Healthcare Business Risks: Apollo Tries to Salvage Amazon Aggregator Investment With Sale Walgreens CEO out, Amazon&amp;rsquo;s One Medical CEO to depart Amazon stock up $423 billion in market cap amid longest monthly winning streak since 2011 Amazon shareholder sues board, Bezos over Blue Origin launch contracts Amazon Rides High Amid Challenges In Cloud Computing, E-Commerce And FTC Probe Score:-28 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Positive earnings results with EPS beating expectations and strong Q2 performance. Expansion of collaboration with PG&amp;amp;E and readiness for emergency demand response program. Partnerships with housing organizations to provide solar installations for renters. Growing interest and investments in renewable energy stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STLA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stla/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Stellantis collaborates with AGI to electrify US dealerships. Launch of SPOTiCAR in the US by Stellantis. Positive developments in EV initiatives and partnerships. Stellantis invests over $100 million in California lithium project. Jeep brand&amp;rsquo;s strong performance and enhanced packages for enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/umc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/umc/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Positive Q2 2023 results reported. Announcement of 40nm RFSOI platform for 5G mmWave applications. Collaboration with Cadence on 3D-IC Hybrid Bonding Reference Flow. Leadership in semiconductor foundries as per Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. Partnership extension with Infineon for 40nm eNVM Microcontroller Production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Expansion into new markets, such as opening casinos and online gaming products. Positive analyst outlook and investment recommendations. Potential growth in the sports betting and gambling industry. Partnership announcements with major media companies like ESPN. Strong investor interest and bullish sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Announcements of leadership changes and updates. Participation in community programs and innovation awards. Strategic ties and partnerships with other financial institutions. Strong institutional investor ownership. Positive initiatives in affordable housing and clean water technology. Risks: Declines in stock price due to industry crisis and rising costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gm/</guid>
      <description>score:-24
Chances: Positive potential for rebound after recent earnings report decline. Collaboration with battery materials startup for EV battery technology. Partnership with Hyundai Motor to scale up Indian operations. Investment in EV battery startup to shift future focus to cheaper materials. Interest and investment in EV market amid potential value increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:-77
Chances: JetBlue&amp;rsquo;s strong Q2 earnings beating estimates. Partnerships and collaborations to reinforce commitment to customers. Positive moves in response to customer needs such as fare changes. JetBlue Plus Card receiving awards and recognition. Expansions and programs targeting specific customer segments. Risks: Potential loss in Q3 due to ending a deal with American Airlines and flight disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Cruise operators plan to hike prices as demand for cruises swells. New partnerships and themed cruise offerings contribute to customer attraction. Carnival announces successful bond offerings and secured term loan facilities for refinancing. Princess Cruises season sale for South America and Antarctica shows growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Luminar reported Q2 2023 results in line with expectations and maintains full-year financial guidance. Luminar delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with automakers like Polestar and Nissan indicate growth prospects. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s focus on advanced semiconductor capabilities and AI technologies is positioning it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PENN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/penn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/penn/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Penn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s partnership with ESPN for the launch of ESPN Bet indicates a significant investment and potential growth in the sports betting market. The $2 billion deal with Penn Entertainment to launch ESPN Bet showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to diversify and capitalize on the growing sports betting industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Intel to create a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s technological capabilities and competitiveness. Cradlepoint&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Ericsson in modernizing network infrastructure for Los Angeles County showcases Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s involvement in innovative and impactful projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
