<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>partnerships on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/partnerships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in partnerships on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/partnerships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LAZR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lazr/</guid>
      <description>score:174
Chances: Luminar reported Q2 2023 results in line with expectations and maintains full-year financial guidance. Luminar delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with automakers like Polestar and Nissan indicate growth prospects. Luminar&amp;rsquo;s focus on advanced semiconductor capabilities and AI technologies is positioning it well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PENN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/penn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/penn/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Penn Entertainment&amp;rsquo;s partnership with ESPN for the launch of ESPN Bet indicates a significant investment and potential growth in the sports betting market. The $2 billion deal with Penn Entertainment to launch ESPN Bet showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s efforts to diversify and capitalize on the growing sports betting industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E&amp;rsquo;s initiatives for National 811 Day and energy incentive programs highlight its commitment to safety and clean energy goals. Partnerships like the one with Sunrun to share excess solar energy demonstrate efforts to enhance grid resiliency. Beat in adjusted earnings and revenue growth in recent quarters indicate some positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: Ginkgo Bioworks&amp;rsquo; collaborations with industry leaders like Merck and Sumitomo Chemical highlight its potential for expanding its biomanufacturing capabilities and advancing synthetic biology. Participation in conferences and panels, such as the UBS MedTech, Tools and Genomics Summit, showcases Ginkgo&amp;rsquo;s position as a leading player in the field of cell programming and biosecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s plans to introduce in-app ads and in-car services could enhance its revenue potential by creating new streams of income and a more personalized experience for users. Partnerships with technology companies like Rokt to offer personalized and relevant offers to riders might attract more engagement and improve user satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ccl/</guid>
      <description>score:-13
Chances: Carnival has experienced a stunning comeback from cancelled cruises, surpassing previous sales records and achieving growth. Record quarterly bookings and increasing demand have contributed to Carnival&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory. Exclusive partnerships with renowned chefs and new gourmet dining experiences could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s appeal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IONQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ionq/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: IonQ&amp;rsquo;s increased bookings expectations and the expansion of its quantum computer availability indicate potential growth in demand and revenue. Partnerships with entities like South Korea’s Ministry of Science and ICT and QuantumBasel suggest IonQ&amp;rsquo;s efforts to collaborate and promote quantum science and technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:983
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Intel to create a custom chip for 5G networking gear using advanced manufacturing technology could enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s technological capabilities and competitiveness. Cradlepoint&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Ericsson in modernizing network infrastructure for Los Angeles County showcases Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s involvement in innovative and impactful projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
