<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:34:50 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is the UAE’s New Tax on Corporate Earnings and Who Pays It?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-the-uaes-new-tax-on-corporate-earnings-and-who-pays-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:34:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/what-is-the-uaes-new-tax-on-corporate-earnings-and-who-pays-it/</guid>
      <description>UAE Introduces New Corporate Tax The UAE has introduced a new corporate tax of 9%, effective from June 1, 2023. The tax will be applied to all businesses that generate more than AED 1 million in annual turnover. Businesses that are located in free zones will be exempt from the tax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eskom Latest: Spar Retailers&#39; Diesel Bill at $35 Million</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/eskom-latest-spar-retailers-diesel-bill-at-35-million/</guid>
      <description>Spar Retailers Spend $35 Million on Diesel to Run Generators South African food and liquor retailer Spar Group estimates that its outlets spent more than 700 million rand ($35 million) on diesel to run generators in the six months through March. This is more than triple the amount spent on diesel in the same period last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Rules for Business Travel to China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/the-new-rules-for-business-travel-to-china/</guid>
      <description>The New Rules for Business Travel to China Business travel to China can be a challenge, but it can also be a rewarding experience. By following these tips, you can increase your chances of success:
Be prepared for heightened security measures. Chinese border agents are increasingly scrutinizing travelers, especially those from the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Is the Best Time to Ask for a Customer Review?</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/when-is-the-best-time-to-ask-for-a-customer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/when-is-the-best-time-to-ask-for-a-customer-review/</guid>
      <description>The Best Time to Ask for a Customer Review
A new study by Harvard Business Review found that the best time to ask for a review is within 24 hours of a customer completing a transaction.
The study found that customers are more likely to give a positive review if they are asked within 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
