<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japan on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/japan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Japan on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:41:26 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious Package Halts Japan Court Proceedings for Abe Killing</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/suspicious-package-halts-japan-court-proceedings-for-abe-killing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:41:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/suspicious-package-halts-japan-court-proceedings-for-abe-killing/</guid>
      <description>Suspicious Package Halts Japan Court Proceedings for Abe Killing
Proceedings on the fatal shooting case of former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe were temporarily halted after a suspicious package was delivered to the Nara District Court premises.
The suspect, Tetsuya Yamagami, had been due in court for pretrial consultations when the incident occurred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOJ&#39;s Ueda Likely to Hold With Bond Market on His Side For Now</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bojs-ueda-likely-to-hold-with-bond-market-on-his-side-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:50:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bojs-ueda-likely-to-hold-with-bond-market-on-his-side-for-now/</guid>
      <description>BOJ Likely to Keep Monetary Policy Unchanged The Bank of Japan (BOJ) is expected to keep its monetary policy unchanged at its meeting on Wednesday. Governor Kazuo Ueda has repeatedly signaled that the BOJ is in no rush to tighten policy, even as inflation rises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan&#39;s Kishida Set to Unveil Policy Wish List, Documents Show</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/japans-kishida-set-to-unveil-policy-wish-list-documents-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/japans-kishida-set-to-unveil-policy-wish-list-documents-show/</guid>
      <description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s Prime Minister Fumio Kishida unveiled a policy wish list on Wednesday, calling for increased investment in infrastructure and research and development, as well as increased defense spending.
Kishida also reaffirmed Japan&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the US-Japan alliance and to working with other countries to address global challenges such as climate change and nuclear proliferation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/japan-seeks-security-clearance-system-in-line-with-us-allies/</guid>
      <description>Japan Seeks Security Clearance System in Line With US Allies The Japanese government plans to set up an official security clearance system for accessing classified information related to economic security. The system is intended to help Japanese companies win contracts abroad, particularly in areas such as cutting-edge chip technology and cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
