<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>revenue growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in revenue growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sea Limited reports strong revenue growth despite missing estimates. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and upside according to Wall Street. Investing in Sea five years ago would have delivered a significant gain. TikTok signs payment pact with Atome for Malaysia e-commerce. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s intrinsic value is potentially 50% above its share price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hln/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hln/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Haleon has raised its annual organic revenue growth forecast, indicating a positive outlook for demand in essential healthcare products. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on essential, over-the-counter respiratory and oral health products has led to growing volumes and consumer spending. Haleon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Halodoc in Indonesia to provide mobile clinic services showcases its commitment to improving medical care access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
