<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>revenue growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in revenue growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:04:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: Coca-Cola has shown outstanding performance in its recent earnings report, with the ability to grow revenue in a way that remains elusive to competitors. The company has increased its quarterly payout to 48.5 cents a share, demonstrating confidence in its financial position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Nike, Inc. is aiming to cut costs and reinvest its savings into big growth areas like sport, health, and wellness. The company&amp;rsquo;s Global Brand Divisions represent its NIKE Brand licensing businesses, which could be a significant source of revenue and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DASH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 09:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dash/</guid>
      <description>score:-62
Chances: DoorDash has reported a 31% increase in revenue for FY 2023, indicating strong growth in its food delivery and logistics platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion into new verticals such as groceries and convenience stores shows potential for further revenue growth. DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Wolt brings expertise in managing logistics and micrologistics of restaurant delivery, which could enhance its operational efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALKS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alks/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Alkermes stock saw its Relative Strength Rating improve from 69 to 75, indicating a potential rebound in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenues outpaced estimates in the fourth quarter of 2023, driven by strong growth in proprietary products. Robust revenue growth and strategic focus are likely to propel Alkermes into 2024, indicating positive prospects for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings report indicates a stable performance, with revenue climbing 15% and operating income surging 37% The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend history, yield, and growth rates show potential for sustainable returns for investors The Food and Support Services United States (FSS United States) segment continues to offer food, hospitality and facility services for various institutions and venues, indicating a steady revenue stream Risks: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2024 earnings call is approaching, and it&amp;rsquo;s essential to closely monitor key metrics and compare them with Wall Street estimates and year-ago numbers for any potential areas of concern While the company has seen decent share price growth, the economic environment can significantly impact its performance, posing a potential risk The company may face challenges related to specialized dietary and support services provided by the Food and Support Services International (FSS International) segment Score:-74 chances characters count - risks characters count = -74</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVGO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/avgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/avgo/</guid>
      <description>score:-28
Chances: Broadcom, Inc. shares are surging, ripping 9% year to date. The semiconductor powerhouse enjoyed a solid rally in 2023. Goldman Sachs analyst anticipates robust growth in Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s AI-related businesses, especially in high-speed networking and custom compute segments. TSMC projected 2024 revenue growth of more than 20% on booming demand for high-end chips used in artificial-intelligence applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
