<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revenue Growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revenue Growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:1202
Chances: B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call discussed operational and financial results, including total gold production and performance highlights. B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 revenues increased year-over-year due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. B2Gold delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, indicating a potential positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</guid>
      <description>score:957
Chances: Boston Scientific&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings saw organic and operational revenue growth in core business segments and geographies. Continued strength in BD&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences segment&amp;rsquo;s base business is expected to benefit Q3 sales. Boston Scientific stock rose as hospital procedures stabilized after the Covid pandemic, contributing to a 20% rise in earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:1139
Chances: Shopify is considered to have growth potential alongside other stocks like Visa and Roku. Shopify President, Harley Finkelstein, discusses the company&amp;rsquo;s approach to potential U.S. recession. Shopify posted better-than-expected Q2 revenue and adjusted earnings per share. Despite recent decline, several analysts have raised their price targets for Shopify stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:919
Chances: DraftKings&amp;rsquo; stock has nearly tripled from its December lows, driven by better-than-hoped financials, including a surprising profit last quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s revenue outlook for the second quarter has been hoisted for the second time in a row, indicating strong growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
