<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revenue Growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revenue Growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:34:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:94
Chances: Schlumberger&amp;rsquo;s resilient performance with rising revenue and earnings could indicate strong prospects for the company. Positive earnings surprises and better-than-expected adjusted earnings in the second quarter might suggest favorable operational efficiency. Price target upgrades by UBS analysts and maintenance of a buy rating could indicate positive sentiment towards SLB&amp;rsquo;s future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:-35
Chances: Tencent Music reported strong revenue growth from online music services, driving total revenue up 5.5% year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s online music platform surpassed estimates, indicating strong demand and positive sentiment among investors. Tencent Music&amp;rsquo;s strategic adjustments to its live-streaming business show its proactive approach to managing potential risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HLN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hln/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hln/</guid>
      <description>score:44
Chances: Haleon has raised its annual organic revenue growth forecast, indicating a positive outlook for demand in essential healthcare products. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on essential, over-the-counter respiratory and oral health products has led to growing volumes and consumer spending. Haleon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Halodoc in Indonesia to provide mobile clinic services showcases its commitment to improving medical care access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BABA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/baba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/baba/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s update to Alipay&amp;rsquo;s international interface to support overseas travelers and facilitate credit card purchases could enhance user experience and drive growth. Separating the DingTalk office communication platform from the cloud division might be a strategic move that unlocks value for Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s business units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Nu Holdings Ltd. beat earnings expectations with reported EPS of $0.05, surpassing the expected $0.04. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid revenue growth and customer expansion could indicate positive prospects. Nu Holdings is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest digital financial services platforms, which could lead to further growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
