<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revenue growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revenue growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CHWY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chwy/</guid>
      <description>score:343
Chances: Chewy stock has reached a three-month high after breaking out of a double bottom pattern, indicating potential for further price appreciation. Jefferies has initiated coverage on Chewy with a &amp;ldquo;Buy&amp;rdquo; rating, signaling positive sentiment from analysts and potential for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PATH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/path/</guid>
      <description>score:713
Chances: UiPath is well positioned to have a phenomenal decade. UiPath and CrowdStrike will continue their 2023 success into the new year. UiPath did an excellent job in 2023, accelerating revenue and controlling costs. Both of these stocks are massive holdings for Ark Invest, but Wood likes one better at current prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:-73
Chances: Shopify (SHOP) is benefiting from an expanding clientele and a robust portfolio. The e-commerce software provider is finally generating a profit. Snowflake and Shopify expect to grow revenues quickly in the coming decade, creating substantial value for shareholders. Risks: In an environment of low market interest rates, growth stocks, especially in the technology sector, such as NDVA, INTC, CRWD, META and SHOP, tend to thrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 09:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: Fortinet Inc provides a comprehensive suite of cybersecurity solutions catering to various businesses including enterprises, communication service providers, and small businesses. The company operates through multiple segments including Network Security, Infrastructure Security, Cloud Security, and Endpoint Protection, Internet of Things and Operational Technology, indicating a diversified product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docu/</guid>
      <description>score:78
Chances: DocuSign&amp;rsquo;s stock is incredibly cheap at the moment going by two traditional valuation metrics, so it might be an enticing buying opportunity for investors. Insightful Analysis of DocuSign Inc&amp;rsquo;s Financial Health and Strategic Position Shares of e-signature company DocuSign (DOCU) jumped 4.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
