<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revenue Growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revenue Growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cx/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Announcement of significant milestone in developing solar-driven cement production technology. Double-digit price hikes and strong peso contributing to a slight rise in second-quarter net profit. Positive growth in revenue, up by 13% in the second quarter. Cemex&amp;rsquo;s focus on scaling technology for solar-driven cement production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ttd/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Better-than-expected revenue, adjusted earnings, and guidance reported in Q2 2023. Strong customer retention and innovative product pipeline contributing to gains. Management&amp;rsquo;s guidance suggests strong double-digit revenue growth persisting in Q3 and beyond. Potential benefits from the growing Connected TV (CTV) momentum and Unified ID 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:-44
Chances: Reported growth in monthly active user (MAU) base, up 8% YoY in Q2. Rebound potential with a return to user growth and focus on building better ad tools. Rise in revenue due to increasing user base, strength in emerging verticals, and AI integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:109
Chances: Stronger-than-expected second-quarter earnings indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s financial strength. Positive results from clinical trials and collaborations in the healthcare sector. Rise in revenue and better full-year sales forecast driven by strong Keytruda cancer-drug sales. Expansion of ongoing Phase 1 dose escalation trial for breast cancer vaccine in collaboration with Cleveland Clinic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hal/</guid>
      <description>score:1
Chances: Positive revenue growth with year-over-year increases. Strength shown in the oil and gas services industry. Optimistic recommendations from analysts. Interest in multi-bagger potential. Potential valuation mismatches in the energy sector. Risks: Dependency on oil and gas industry trends and energy sector shifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1061
Chances: Discussing the top stock picks of ARK Invest and Unity&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the portfolio. Reviewing Unity&amp;rsquo;s latest quarterly update and evaluating its potential as an AI stock investment. Highlighting the year-over-year improvement in Unity&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results in terms of revenue and earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Nu Holdings&amp;rsquo; expected increase in second-quarter 2023 revenues could positively impact the stock. Partnership with Hopper to power Nubank&amp;rsquo;s travel portal could lead to growth in customer engagement. Surpassing 80 million customers in Brazil and Latin America indicates strong customer base expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-57
Chances: Despite the recent stock price decline, Upstart&amp;rsquo;s long-term growth potential remains promising due to its AI-powered lending marketplace. Upstart generated revenue growth, reaching $136 million in the last quarter, indicating its ability to generate strong sales in its niche. The company&amp;rsquo;s performance in the second quarter was better than feared, with better-than-expected Q2 results and revenue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Plug Power reported record revenue in its second-quarter results, reaffirming its full-year sales estimate. Despite recent losses and challenges, Plug Power remains one of the most hyped hydrogen stocks with potential. The hydrogen technology company has hydrogen production plants in various states, contributing to its revenue drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sofi/</guid>
      <description>score:252
Chances: SoFi&amp;rsquo;s differentiation in the fintech space through low fees and an extensive suite of digital financial services is resonating with customers. SoFi&amp;rsquo;s strong revenue growth and significant increase in its member base showcase the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for expansion. The positive earnings report and revenue growth have contributed to a more than 100% increase in SOFI stock in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/net/</guid>
      <description>score:1022
Chances: Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report showed a 32% YoY revenue increase to $308 million, leading to an 8% jump in stock price. Cloudflare reported positive adjusted operating income and free cash flow in Q2 2023. Cloudflare raised its full-year 2023 outlook and exceeded estimates in its second-quarter results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</guid>
      <description>score:957
Chances: Boston Scientific&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings saw organic and operational revenue growth in core business segments and geographies. Continued strength in BD&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences segment&amp;rsquo;s base business is expected to benefit Q3 sales. Boston Scientific stock rose as hospital procedures stabilized after the Covid pandemic, contributing to a 20% rise in earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
