<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revenue Growth on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Revenue Growth on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/revenue-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1220 FSLY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsly/</guid>
      <description>score:1220
Chances: Fastly delivered significantly stronger-than-expected second-quarter results, with revenue climbing 20% year over year to $122.8 million, well above guidance and analysts&amp;rsquo; estimates. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic initiatives to simplify its go-to-market, increase innovation velocity, and drive operational rigor and cost control are expected to contribute to its growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1071 JCI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jci/</guid>
      <description>score:1071
Chances: Johnson Controls&amp;rsquo; fiscal Q3 results show strength in the HVAC &amp;amp; Controls and Fire &amp;amp; Security businesses. The company reported solid quarterly numbers, including a record backlog, which indicates positive performance. Cost-control measures and improving supply chains are likely to have aided Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1169 GEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gen/</guid>
      <description>score:1169
Chances: Gen Digital Inc experienced a 6.44% gain recently, with a positive Earnings Per Share (EPS) of 2.12. Q1 results reflect strong customer growth and benefits from global business expansion and the Avast acquisition, leading to year-over-year growth in revenues and bookings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 IPG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: The Interpublic Group of Companies Inc (IPG) gained 4.25% daily, indicating investor interest in the stock. The company&amp;rsquo;s Earnings Per Share (EPS) of $2.41 adds to the positive sentiment among investors. As one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest advertising holding companies, IPG generates revenue from various advertising services, including traditional and digital services, which could potentially lead to future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
