<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biopharmaceutical on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/biopharmaceutical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Biopharmaceutical on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/biopharmaceutical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IOVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iova/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Iovance&amp;rsquo;s surges on the anticipated FDA approval for its lead pipeline drug as the first individualized, one-time cell therapy for certain patients with melanoma. These biotech innovators have what it takes to soar. Risks: Iovance shares have dropped by double digits over the past three years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Immunovant, Inc. announced that results from the initial cohort of patients in the Phase 2 clinical trial of batoclimab in Graves’ disease exceeded 50% response rates, indicating promising potential for the drug Risks: Oral brepocitinib failed to meet its primary endpoint of Systemic Lupus Erythematosus Responder Index (SRI-4) change of 4 at Week 52, indicating a setback in the drug&amp;rsquo;s development for this specific indication Score:2 chances characters count - risks characters count = 2</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
