<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>biopharmaceutical on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/biopharmaceutical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in biopharmaceutical on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:02:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/biopharmaceutical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:239
Chances: Bristol Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s Krazati, in combination with cetuximab, demonstrates clinically meaningful activity as a targeted treatment option for patients with previously treated KRASG12C-mutated colorectal cancer. Bristol Myers wins FDA approval for CAR T cell immunotherapy, Abecma, in earlier lines of treatment for patients with relapsed or refractory multiple myeloma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROIV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 09:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roiv/</guid>
      <description>score:14
Chances: Roivant Sciences Ltd. has shown impressive financial growth, with a 118% increase in revenue in the third quarter of 2024. The completion of the sale of Telavant to Roche for $7.1B with an additional $150M in cash payable upon the completion of a near-term milestone shows strong financial achievements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iova/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iova/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Iovance Biotherapeutics&amp;rsquo; revenue is set to grow, indicating potential for increased stock value. The FDA has lifted a partial clinical hold on Iovance&amp;rsquo;s mid-stage study, showing positive regulatory progress. Risks: Iovance Biotherapeutics reported a net loss of $116.4 million in Q4, reflecting financial risk and potential impact on stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:113
Chances: TG Therapeutics, Inc. has announced the presentation of data from the ULTIMATE I &amp;amp; II Phase 3 trials evaluating BRIUMVI® in patients with relapsing forms of multiple sclerosis, indicating potential positive outcomes from the trials. The company has reported strong financial results, with BRIUMVI U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARDX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 09:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ardx/</guid>
      <description>score:112
Chances: Strong commercial performance of IBSRELA and XPHOZAH drive revenue surge for Ardelyx, Inc. The positive outlook for the U.S. economy and widespread analyst upgrades across various sectors reflect confidence in the economic backdrop. The global biotech market is set to experience exponential growth, providing a unique opportunity for savvy investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRSP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crsp/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: CRISPR Therapeutics has shown improving price performance, earning an upgrade to its IBD Relative Strength Rating. The company is focused on creating transformative gene-based medicines for serious diseases, and has announced conditional marketing authorization for its gene edited therapy, CASGEVY. Risks: The company doesn&amp;rsquo;t possess the right combination of the two key ingredients for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ALKS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/alks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/alks/</guid>
      <description>score:-21
Chances: Alkermes stock saw its Relative Strength Rating improve from 69 to 75, indicating a potential rebound in the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s earnings and revenues outpaced estimates in the fourth quarter of 2023, driven by strong growth in proprietary products. Robust revenue growth and strategic focus are likely to propel Alkermes into 2024, indicating positive prospects for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARWR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/arwr/</guid>
      <description>score:114
Chances: The company has successfully priced an underwritten registered offering, indicating strong investor interest and potential for significant capital influx. The filing of an application for clearance to initiate a Phase 1/2a clinical trial of ARO-CFB demonstrates progress in the company’s pipeline development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
