<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory Compliance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-compliance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory Compliance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:55:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-compliance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> WFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1097
Chances: Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s CEO expresses confidence despite the second downgrade of the US credit rating, indicating potential resilience in the face of credit challenges. Wells Fargo&amp;rsquo;s support for nonprofit organization Concordance&amp;rsquo;s national expansion to promote financial health and stability reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to community development and positive social impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BKI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bki/</guid>
      <description>score:1173
Chances: Black Knight&amp;rsquo;s Data &amp;amp; Analytics division releases August 2023 Mortgage Monitor Report highlighting the heating housing market and rising home prices. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) dismisses federal court case against Intercontinental Exchange&amp;rsquo;s proposed acquisition of Black Knight, clearing the regulatory path for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:1058
Chances: Itaú Unibanco releases revised projections for 2023, complying with regulatory requirements. Positive growth in commissions, fees, insurance operations, and acquisitions supporting financials. Approval of interest on capital payment to stockholders by Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s Board of Directors. Potential divestment of operations in Argentina through preliminary negotiations with Banco Macro.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
