<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Performance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-performance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Performance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:27:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hst/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hst/</guid>
      <description>score:99
Chances: Host Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts is the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest lodging real estate investment trust, which could indicate its market influence and stability. Continued recovery in leisure demand and business transient demand might benefit HST&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings. The company&amp;rsquo;s active involvement in the lodging real estate sector positions it to benefit from the rebound in the travel and hospitality industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iq/</guid>
      <description>score:107
Chances: iQIYI&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Cinema has demonstrated its efficacy with strong box office performances for films released in July, indicating growing popularity and success of its online entertainment services. The company&amp;rsquo;s initiative to establish offline parent-child theme parks, such as the iQIYI QiBubble Space, showcases its efforts in IP commercialization and creating immersive entertainment experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aur/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Aurora Innovation (AUR) has made significant financial improvements, as evident from its narrowed net loss in the first half of 2023. Participation in industry conferences, such as the Canaccord Genuity Annual Growth Conference, showcases Aurora&amp;rsquo;s efforts to engage with investors and stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) could benefit from a bullish trendline that might drive its stock price closer to record highs. The auto and industrial chip sector&amp;rsquo;s potential for accelerating growth and profit expansion in the coming year could positively impact ON Semiconductor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CARR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/carr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/carr/</guid>
      <description>score:30
Chances: Carrier Global&amp;rsquo;s recognition for earning a Top Project of the Year Award indicates the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to deliver energy-efficient solutions in collaboration with its partners, which could positively impact its reputation and customer base. Strong financial results in the second quarter of 2023, along with raised full-year guidance for revenue and adjusted metrics, demonstrate Carrier Global&amp;rsquo;s performance resilience and its potential to capitalize on market opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BRFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/brfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/brfs/</guid>
      <description>score:63
Chances: BRF is executing a plan to improve operating efficiency and benefiting from rising chicken prices and falling grain costs. The outlook for BRF is considered benign after overcoming challenges like high corn prices and chicken supply glut. BRF&amp;rsquo;s Annual Report for 2022 has been filed with the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VTRS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vtrs/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Viatris, a generic drugmaker, serves patients and customers in over 165 countries with a diverse global business. Viatris&amp;rsquo; potential divestitures and new multiple sclerosis treatment could contribute to positive sentiment. Viatris is a stock of interest among the dividend investing community due to its stable line of business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ENVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/envx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/envx/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Enovix Corporation announced its participation in investor conferences, indicating efforts to engage with the investment community. Enovix made significant progress in scaling operations during the second quarter, producing more units than planned. Enovix&amp;rsquo;s advanced battery modeling and machine learning efforts in India could accelerate the company&amp;rsquo;s product development roadmap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:-47
Chances: RLX Technology Inc. is a leading branded e-vapor company in China, which positions it in the growing e-cigarette market. Strong financial results and consistent announcements of unaudited financial results demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s transparency and performance. Chinese stocks, including RLX Technology, have experienced significant share movement, indicating potential for price appreciation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dependable dividend payer makes it attractive to income-focused investors seeking stable income over time. Strong financial performance, including robust revenue growth and consecutive dividend increases, adds confidence to Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s investment potential. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s resilience and innovation are highlighted, showcasing the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to thrive and adapt in changing market conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Despite challenges in the renewable energy sector, Sunrun has shown growth in revenue and networked storage capacity, indicating potential for expansion. Strong performance in the electric vehicle market and increased demand for charging could positively impact Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s business. Growing storage attachment rates and networked storage capacity highlight Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s ability to adapt to market trends and offer value-added services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ua/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ua/</guid>
      <description>score:5
Chances: Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s first-quarter fiscal 2024 results beat revenue and earnings estimates, showcasing its ability to navigate challenges in the market. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on direct-to-consumer revenues and e-commerce demand indicates its adaptability to changing consumer preferences. The launch of the &amp;lsquo;UA Rewards&amp;rsquo; loyalty program demonstrates Under Armour&amp;rsquo;s efforts to engage and retain loyal customers, potentially driving brand loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: Truist&amp;rsquo;s commitment to support affordable housing in Charlotte and career development programs could enhance its community engagement and social responsibility image. Participation in initiatives like the MIT Solve challenge showcases Truist&amp;rsquo;s dedication to fostering innovation and collaboration in addressing societal challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: AGNC Investment Corp.&amp;rsquo;s commitment to reposition its portfolio in the current volatile interest rate scenario could optimize performance. Consistent dividend distribution and a focus on monthly dividend stocks make AGNC Investment Corp. attractive to income-seeking investors. AGNC&amp;rsquo;s potential for optimizing performance in the current volatile interest rate scenario suggests a chance for improved financial results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce dominance in Southeast Asia and Taiwan positions it as a key player in a fast-growing market. Solid uptick in e-commerce and digital financial services businesses positively impacted Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter 2023 results. Strategic investments in growth could lead to potential expansion and revenue generation for Sea Limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/para/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/para/</guid>
      <description>score:15
Chances: Paramount Global&amp;rsquo;s decision not to sell the majority stake of BET Media Group indicates their strategic focus on maintaining value. The consideration of ESG (Environmental, Social, and Governance) factors in content creation and delivery can be a positive aspect for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADYEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/adyey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/adyey/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: Adyen being among the first to complete testing and receive certification to utilize the FedNow(R) Service reflects its commitment to investing in the North American region. Expansion of in-person payment offering with Tap to Pay on Android can improve convenience and potentially attract more business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMCR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amcr/</guid>
      <description>score:27
Chances: Amcor&amp;rsquo;s CEO highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s proactive measures to manage inflation and reduce costs, reflecting strong strategic management. Amcor&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Phoenix Flexibles and expansion in the high-growth Indian market can contribute to its future growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s ability to return cash to shareholders and its growth in the first half of fiscal 2023 indicate positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STNE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/stne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/stne/</guid>
      <description>score:95
Chances: StoneCo&amp;rsquo;s strong top-line growth driven by expanding clientele indicates a positive growth trajectory. The consistently above-market projection results, with significant revenue and profit growth, demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s strong performance. The Financial Services segment&amp;rsquo;s revenue growth and the positive performance of the Software segment contribute to the overall success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RBLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rblx/</guid>
      <description>score:80
Chances: Roblox&amp;rsquo;s partnerships with well-known brands like Meta Platforms, Spotify, and H&amp;amp;M could lead to revenue growth through advertising and brand activations on its platform. The collaboration with Hamilton to integrate it into metaverse platforms could provide new opportunities for engagement and monetization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Petrobras&amp;rsquo; move to increase fuel prices to reduce the cost gap with international markets could please investors and improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s decision to preserve its existing ownership in Braskem and not turn it into a government-owned company could indicate strategic alignment and stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABEV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abev/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abev/</guid>
      <description>score:48
Chances: Ambev S.A. (ABEV) is being compared to other stocks like Diageo (DEO), Beyond Meat (BYND), and others in terms of value and performance. Lifeway Foods&amp;rsquo; (LWAY) Q2 results suggest positive growth driven by higher net revenues and earnings, indicating potential for similar trends in the beverage industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VZ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vz/</guid>
      <description>score:-78
Chances: Verizon Communications Inc. (VZ) is a high-yield dividend stock that can appeal to income-seeking investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnership with the Washington Commanders and being named the &amp;lsquo;Official 5G Network&amp;rsquo; suggests a focus on expanding its technology solutions. Verizon&amp;rsquo;s efforts to restore network coverage in West Maui after recent wildfires showcases its commitment to providing reliable services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:-57
Chances: Opendoor Technologies Inc. (OPEN) has attracted attention from investors, indicating potential interest in the stock. The projected fair value for Opendoor Technologies suggests a certain valuation based on free cash flow to equity. While the housing market has faced challenges, Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s role as an e-commerce platform for real estate transactions is noteworthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:185
Chances: Southwestern Energy&amp;rsquo;s declining total operating costs and expenses in Q2 have positively impacted its earnings, indicating potential cost management and efficiency improvements. The company&amp;rsquo;s positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023 could indicate a potential favorable direction for the stock, suggesting strong operational performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Marathon&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in Bitcoin mining, including record blocks and increased operational hash rate, indicates its leadership in the crypto mining sector. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic expansion, such as its mining operations in Abu Dhabi, demonstrates its commitment to diversifying and scaling its operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: Component shortages have eased, which could lead to positive developments for Cisco&amp;rsquo;s future. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s fiscal fourth-quarter results reflect strength in Secure, Agile Networks, and gross margin expansion. The company&amp;rsquo;s diverse book of business and easing supply chain challenges could benefit Cisco&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Aramark recognized as one of the &amp;lsquo;Best Companies for Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion&amp;rsquo; Positive movement in Relative Strength (RS) Rating. Strong performance in Q3 2023 results. Upcoming spin-off of Aramark Uniform Services (AUS) as an independent public company. Dividend payment announcement for August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AQN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Announcement of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s CEO Arun Banskota&amp;rsquo;s resignation and the appointment of interim CEO Christopher Huskilson. Consideration of the potential sale of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy unit as a strategic move to reduce debt. Discussion of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s dividend declarations and its financial decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:331
Chances: Discussion of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s potential as an e-commerce business compared to Amazon&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory. Upgrading of CPNG shares by TheStreet&amp;rsquo;s Quant Ratings service. Coverage of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and its financial performance. Explanation of Coupang&amp;rsquo;s quarterly profit streak and factors contributing to improved margins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-191
Chances: V.F. Corporation (VFC) reported a daily gain of 3.78% with positive Earnings Per Share (EPS) results, indicating potential growth. VF Corporation beats earnings expectations, with reported EPS exceeding expectations in the first quarter of fiscal year 2024. Although V.F. (VFC) delivered lower-than-expected earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, the company&amp;rsquo;s performance might be worth considering compared to the year-ago numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> GT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gt/</guid>
      <description>score:700
Chances: Goodyear India reported higher profit due to a drop in raw material prices, which could potentially improve the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position. Goodyear is taking steps to enhance its Board of Directors and undergo a strategic and operational review, which could lead to positive changes for the company&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:981
Chances: TAL Education Group share price has gained 56% in the last period. TAL Education Group announces unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. TAL Education Group to release unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. Chinese hedge funds add TAL Education Group to their portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1010
Chances: Regions Bank introduces digital solutions for business clients to manage billing and communications. Appointment of Alison Rand to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Bank increases prime lending rate to 8.50%. Enhancement of Treasury Management suite of products and services to meet customer needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NVST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nvst/</guid>
      <description>score:1237
Chances: Envista announces successful pricing of $435 million Convertible Senior Notes offering. Consistent growth in Specialty Products &amp;amp; Technologies and Equipment &amp;amp; Consumables segments drive Q2 revenues. Envista delivers positive Q2 2023 earnings and revenue surprises. Envista Smile Project completes mission trip to the Dominican Republic, providing dental care to underserved patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MNST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mnst/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Monster Beverage Corporation reported record second-quarter net sales, rising 12.1% to $1.85 billion, driven by gains in brand performance, innovation, product launches, and pricing actions. Monster Beverage&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results are expected to reflect gains from continued strength in the energy drinks category and robust product innovation plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FLR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/flr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/flr/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Fluor Corporation successfully priced $500 million aggregate principal amount of Convertible Senior Notes due 2029. Fluor reported outstanding financial results, leading to a significant rating upgrade and positive market sentiment. Fluor announced its intention to offer Convertible Senior Notes due 2029, potentially raising capital for future operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KOS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kos/</guid>
      <description>score:1056
Chances: Kosmos Energy reports positive financial and operating results for Q2 2023, generating net income of $23 million. Successful start-up of Jubilee South East (JSE) project offshore Ghana in partnership with Tullow Oil and others. Adjusted net income and diluted earnings per share figures indicate a favorable financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ELAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/elan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/elan/</guid>
      <description>score:923
Chances: Elanco Animal Health reports strong financial results for Q2 2023 and raises guidance for the full year. Approval of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s Seresto flea and tick collar by the EPA and FDA contributes to stock surge. Elanco releases Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Report highlighting enhanced governance and transparency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
