<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EV Market on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/ev-market/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EV Market on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/ev-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>VFS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vfs/</guid>
      <description>score:-216
Chances: What is VinFast bringing to the table in the EV market? Why VinFast Auto Stock Jumped Again Today Why New IPO Stock VinFast Surged 94% Today VinFast stock rebounds on Star Group&amp;rsquo;s plans to open Vietnamese plant Risks: Why VinFast Auto Stock Crashed This Week &amp;ndash; and Could Keep Falling VinFast Auto Stock Is Down 50% This Week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Lucid announces plans for Gravity SUV reveal in November, potentially boosting interest. Lucid&amp;rsquo;s Air EV price cuts are well received by the market, indicating positive response. Lucid remains on track for annual production guidance of over 10,000 vehicles. Lucid strikes EV technology deal with Aston Martin, leading to partnership and stock jump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FSR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fsr/</guid>
      <description>score:960
Chances: Fisker Inc. announced a new line of vehicles, including a pickup truck, targeting a popular segment in the U.S. market. The Fisker Alaska pickup truck, priced at $45,400 before incentives, is expected to capitalize on demand for affordable electric trucks. The company&amp;rsquo;s decision to manufacture cars in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
