<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>product launches on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/product-launches/</link>
    <description>Recent content in product launches on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:19:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/product-launches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sq/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: Square&amp;rsquo;s innovative products like Cash App and Square Credit Card gaining popularity. Positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts and investors. Strong institutional ownership, indicating confidence in the company. Potential for growth in the fintech and blockchain sectors. Recent product launches and expansions showing positive signs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: SentinelOne leads the way in XDR. SentinelOne and Netskope team up to secure modern workforce. SentinelOne streamlines vulnerability management with Singularity™ Ranger Insights. SentinelOne launches cloud data security product line. SentinelOne bolsters India’s cyber defenses. Risks: Cybersecurity startup Wiz considers potential bid for SentinelOne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TWNK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/twnk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/twnk/</guid>
      <description>score:-7
Chances: Hostess Brands reports strong Q2 earnings, beating estimates. Positive performance and earnings beat in Q1 2023. Hostess Brands completes refinancing transaction, enhancing financial position. Launch of new products like Hostess &amp;lsquo;Mashup&amp;rsquo; and Zero Sugar Mini Wafers. Participation at investor conferences and corporate responsibility efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
