<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pakistan on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/pakistan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pakistan on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:42:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/pakistan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan in Talks to Restructure Debt With Bilateral Creditors</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-in-talks-to-restructure-debt-with-bilateral-creditors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:42:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-in-talks-to-restructure-debt-with-bilateral-creditors/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan in Talks to Restructure Debt With Bilateral Creditors Pakistan is in talks with its bilateral creditors to restructure its debt. The talks are being led by the International Monetary Fund (IMF). The IMF has agreed to provide Pakistan with a $6 billion bailout package, but the package is conditional on Pakistan restructuring its debt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imran Khan Says Generals Want to Stop Him From Winning Election</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/imran-khan-says-generals-want-to-stop-him-from-winning-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:56:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/imran-khan-says-generals-want-to-stop-him-from-winning-election/</guid>
      <description>Imran Khan Accuses Generals of Trying to Stop Him from Winning Election Former Pakistani Prime Minister Imran Khan has accused the country&amp;rsquo;s generals of trying to stop him from winning the next election. Khan made the accusation in a speech to supporters on Friday, saying that the generals are &amp;ldquo;afraid&amp;rdquo; of him because he is a &amp;ldquo;threat&amp;rdquo; to their power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan Moves to Ease Pressure on Rupee in Retail Market</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:16:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/pakistan-moves-to-ease-pressure-on-rupee-in-retail-market/</guid>
      <description>Pakistan has taken a number of steps to stabilize the rupee in the retail market. These measures include increasing the State Bank of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s (SBP) foreign exchange reserves by $1 billion, selling dollars to commercial banks at a discounted rate, and increasing the amount of foreign currency that Pakistanis can carry when they travel abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
