<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Renewable Energy on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/renewable-energy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Renewable Energy on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:35:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/renewable-energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1005 NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Evergy&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings are better than expected, which could indicate positive performance for utility companies like NextEra Energy. IDACORP&amp;rsquo;s second-quarter earnings benefited from customer additions and plans to add more hydropower generation to its portfolio, which might also be favorable for NextEra Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0939 PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:939
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E encourages customers to enroll in an energy incentive program to help lower energy costs and support the state&amp;rsquo;s clean energy goals, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s reputation and customer loyalty. Sunrun customers in California sharing excess solar energy with their neighbors through an exclusive partnership with PG&amp;amp;E could increase grid resiliency and improve the company&amp;rsquo;s standing in the renewable energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0887 RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:887
Chances: Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s reported earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023 suggest potential positive performance in the future. Sales activities outside of California have been robust, growing 25% year-over-year, indicating potential growth in other markets. Sunrun customers in California sharing excess solar energy with their neighbors may increase grid resiliency and enhance the company&amp;rsquo;s reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
