<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Renewable energy on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/renewable-energy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Renewable energy on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/renewable-energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: NextEra Energy owns the largest renewables business in the U.S. Positive opportunity presented by the stock&amp;rsquo;s selloff. Expected gains from ongoing capital investments and acquisitions. Dividend income potential from utility stocks for retirees. Strategic plans for strengthening transmission and distribution network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bp/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: Expansion of EV charging network through joint venture indicates growth potential for BP&amp;rsquo;s Indian operations. BP&amp;rsquo;s consideration of offshore wind farm construction without government assistance shows commitment to renewable energy. Positive outlook for BP&amp;rsquo;s dividend and earnings potential, with a focus on improving profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ENPH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enph/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enph/</guid>
      <description>score:1020
Chances: Enphase Energy is strategically expanding its presence in the renewable energy market, particularly in Europe where sales are growing. The global alternative energy market is showing strong growth, offering significant investment opportunities for Enphase Energy. Solar energy is projected to become the largest source of power globally by 2027, providing a favorable outlook for Enphase Energy&amp;rsquo;s solar-based solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
