<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>renewable energy on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/renewable-energy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in renewable energy on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/renewable-energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ENPH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enph/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Enphase Energy (ENPH) has been expanding its footprint in the global market, with recent shipments of its latest microinverter, IQ8P, in various countries. The company is leading the way in solar and battery systems technology, positioning itself as a key player in the renewable energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 09:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/be/</guid>
      <description>score:110
Chances: Bloom Energy has seen solid earnings estimate revision activity over the past month. One analyst believes that powering data centers will help the company charge higher. The demand for better environmental tech continues to ramp up. Investors watching artificial intelligence are turning to power plant companies, which could benefit Bloom Energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: SolarEdge Technologies, Inc. has a strong track record in the energy technology sector, offering inverter solutions and a range of other products and services. The company&amp;rsquo;s Solar segment, which includes inverter solutions designed to maximize power generation, shows potential for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
