<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acquisition Strategy on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/acquisition-strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acquisition Strategy on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:41:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/acquisition-strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hl/</guid>
      <description>score:-171
Chances: Hecla Mining&amp;rsquo;s strong silver production and its target to produce 17 million ounces of silver in 2023 could indicate potential growth opportunities. The acquisition of ATAC Resources Ltd. and the investment in Cascadia Minerals Ltd. might enhance Hecla Mining&amp;rsquo;s exploration capabilities and diversify its portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Crestwood Equity Partners enhances its operations and cash flow, supporting its distribution growth strategy. The reduction in Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s debt and its efforts to improve credit ratings indicate a positive financial management approach. The acquisition of Crestwood Equity Partners expands Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s pipeline network, positioning it for further growth in the fuel infrastructure business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aapl/</guid>
      <description>score:-90
Chances: Apple considering acquiring ESPN from Disney could diversify its offerings and boost its streaming services. Growth of premium and ultra-premium sales, along with the upcoming iPhone 15 launch, could drive Apple&amp;rsquo;s unit sales. Synopsys&amp;rsquo; AI impact on chip demand could be positive for Apple&amp;rsquo;s semiconductor needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
