<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Services on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Services on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:05:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Growth stock investors could be in for an excellent year in 2024. Although it&amp;rsquo;s battling intense competition, there is still much that can work in Sea&amp;rsquo;s favor. If you missed the tenfold return in Amazon stock since 2013, this other e-commerce stock might give you another chance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 09:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: CNH Industrial NV has been recognized for its innovative and customer-inspired products, winning multiple awards in the agricultural industry.The company is making efforts to educate and support the next generation of farmers through partnerships with educational institutions. Risks: The delisting of the company’s common shares from Euronext Milan may result in decreased trading activity and potential loss of investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:161
Chances: Pure Storage is leveraging its all-flash storage platform to deliver reliable, always-on digital financial services to its growing customer base. The company was named a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Container Data Management 2023 Vendor Assessment, highlighting its competitive fitness in the container data management space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
