<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial services on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial services on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:05:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:144
Chances: CNH Industrial has completed its voluntary delisting of shares from Euronext Milan and is now solely listed on the New York Stock Exchange, which may result in increased visibility and access for investors. The company has also completed the €400 million component of its $1 billion share buyback program, indicating strong financial stability and commitment to return value to shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:203
Chances: First Horizon Corp. operates as a financial holding company providing a range of financial products and services to individuals and businesses. The company has been recognized for its commitments to employee health and well-being, as well as its contributions to diversity and inclusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:161
Chances: Pure Storage is leveraging its all-flash storage platform to deliver reliable, always-on digital financial services to its growing customer base. The company was named a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Container Data Management 2023 Vendor Assessment, highlighting its competitive fitness in the container data management space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
