<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Services on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Services on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:208
Chances: Sea Ltd. is a diversified internet and mobile platform company with strong growth potential in its Digital Entertainment, E-Commerce, and Digital Financial Services segments. The company&amp;rsquo;s E-Commerce segment, Shopee, has the potential for significant growth as it connects buyers and sellers in a third-party marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FHN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fhn/</guid>
      <description>score:84
Chances: First Horizon Corp. operates as a financial holding company, providing a range of financial products and services to individuals and businesses. The company has received multiple recognitions and awards for its commitments to employee health and well-being, diversity and inclusion, and adoption-friendly workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
