<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial services on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial services on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:04:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HOOD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hood/</guid>
      <description>score:123
Chances: Robinhood Markets, Inc. (HOOD) closed at $19.20, marking a -1.08% move from the previous day. According to eMarketer, credit cards will remain the most popular payment method for US consumers through next year, with total credit card transactional value to reach $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 09:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Brazil&amp;rsquo;s hugely popular Pix payment system has become the country&amp;rsquo;s favorite way to pay, replacing cash and wire transfers in many cases and now threatening the dominance of credit cards in the booming e-commerce sector. The controlling shareholders of Brazilian payments firm Cielo have reached an agreement with some minority shareholders to raise the price of a tender offer to take the company private.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vly/</guid>
      <description>score:-83
Chances: Valley National Bancorp has been performing well in 2023, with revenue increasing by 1.7% from the previous year. The company has announced a new share repurchase program, indicating confidence in its financial position and sustainability in the long run. Risks: The recent unexpected losses reported by New York Community Bancorp have put regional banks on high alert, raising concerns about the potential impact on Valley National Bancorp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 09:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd. has been operating a technology-empowered personal financial services platform since 2005, offering personal lending and wealth management solutions. The company recently announced its unaudited financial results for the fourth quarter and full year, showing potential for growth and profitability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:41
Chances: The recent overhaul of the management team and the raised $1 billion in equity capital shows a potential for positive change and growth for New York Community Bancorp. Risks: The bank&amp;rsquo;s reliance on a blacklisted broker for many of its loans could pose a risk to its financial stability and reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibn/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: ICICI Bank Ltd. is well positioned for above-average growth in financials. Efforts to bolster fee income, domestic loan dependence, and digitization of banking services will support ICICI Bank&amp;rsquo;s financials. Risks: Concerns related to higher restructuring costs may pose a risk for ICICI Bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
