<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Services on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Services on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:59:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ms/</guid>
      <description>score:-36
Chances: Morgan Stanley plans to launch an AI chatbot to enhance its services for wealthy clients, which could lead to improved customer engagement and satisfaction. The global wealth management industry is experiencing growth, and Morgan Stanley aims to capitalize on this trend by attracting investor attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCHW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/schw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/schw/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Charles Schwab experienced a successful weekend, converting TD Ameritrade clients and advisors, potentially leading to increased assets under management. Bond investors are showing confidence in Schwab after its cost-cutting measures, which may boost the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health. Schwab&amp;rsquo;s trader survey indicates that recession fears are receding, suggesting positive sentiment among traders and investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: KeyBank provided a $5 million line of credit to advance small businesses, indicating support for growth. KeyBank celebrated the opening of a new, full-service branch, demonstrating expansion efforts. KeyCorp is paying a dividend of $0.205, offering a 7.1% dividend yield, which may attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUTU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/futu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/futu/</guid>
      <description>score:11
Chances: S&amp;amp;P Expects A Steady Increase in Futu&amp;rsquo;s Overseas Client Base, Reaffirms Its BBB- Rating Futu Holdings Stock Shows Improved Relative Price Strength Futu Announces Plan for App Removal in Mainland China App Stores Moomoo Expands Into Malaysia Following Success In Singapore Futu Ranks #2 on Fortune&amp;rsquo;s 100 Fastest-Growing Companies List For 2022 Risks: Futu Announces Proposed Dual Primary Listing on The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong Limited Futu Provides Regulatory Update in China Futu Holdings Records Solid Growth in Q3 with US$247.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
