<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Services on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Services on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/financial-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PSTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pstg/</guid>
      <description>score:260
Chances: Pure Storage Inc. (PSTG) will replace Patterson Companies Inc. (NASD:PDCO) in the S&amp;amp;P MidCap 400, and Patterson Companies will replace Chico&amp;rsquo;s FAS Inc. (NYSE:CHS) in the S&amp;amp;P SmallCap 600 effective prior to the opening of trading on Friday, January 5. Pure Storage&amp;rsquo;s all-flash storage platform being leveraged by Toss Bank in South Korea for reliable digital financial services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 09:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:231
Chances: CNHI has completed the voluntary delisting of its shares from Euronext Milan and is now solely listed on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), which may lead to increased visibility and access for American investors. The company has been simplifying its operations, as seen in the completion of the €400 million component of its $1 billion share buyback program, which could indicate a positive outlook for shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mfc/</guid>
      <description>score:246
Chances: Manulife Financial Corp. has recently announced a reinsurance transaction with Global Atlantic, indicating a strategic move to de-risk its long-term care business and release capital for potential shareholder activities. The company&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the Dow Jones Sustainability North America Index reflects its leading sustainable business practices and long-term shareholder value creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:73
Chances: Lufax Holding Ltd is a leading financial services enabler for small business owners in China The company announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter, showing promising performance The change in the ADS Ratio could potentially benefit the company and its investors Risks: The reduction in dividend payment from the previous year raises concerns about the company&amp;rsquo;s financial health The potential US China war and rise of China could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth prospects Score:73 chances characters count - risks characters count = -927</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
