<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dividend income on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-income/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dividend income on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-income/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NEE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nee/</guid>
      <description>score:35
Chances: NextEra Energy owns the largest renewables business in the U.S. Positive opportunity presented by the stock&amp;rsquo;s selloff. Expected gains from ongoing capital investments and acquisitions. Dividend income potential from utility stocks for retirees. Strategic plans for strengthening transmission and distribution network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:-115
Chances: Huntington Bancshares Incorporated&amp;rsquo;s investors are due to receive a dividend payment per share, which could attract investors looking for income. Huntington Bancshares beat Wall Street estimates for second-quarter profit, earning more from rising interest rates and experiencing strong demand for commercial loans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Cisco&amp;rsquo;s stock has been moving higher and On-Balance-Volume (OBV) line suggests aggressive buying. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s earnings report next week is expected to beat peers Arista and Juniper, according to Citi. Juniper Networks CEO highlights growth driven by AI innovation and differentiation in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:1057
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reliable and stable performance makes it an attractive stock for long-term gains. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment model and Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s portfolio receive widespread attention for long-term performance. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s diverse product portfolio includes well-known brands like Coke, Sprite, Dasani water, Costa Coffee, and Minute Maid juices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
