<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend Income on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend-income/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend Income on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend-income/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> KO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ko/</guid>
      <description>score:1057
Chances: Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s reliable and stable performance makes it an attractive stock for long-term gains. Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s investment model and Berkshire Hathaway&amp;rsquo;s portfolio receive widespread attention for long-term performance. Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s diverse product portfolio includes well-known brands like Coke, Sprite, Dasani water, Costa Coffee, and Minute Maid juices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:1194
Chances: Aramark is introducing innovative ordering technologies and food concepts for college campuses, aiming to engage and ground students through dining programs tailored to industry and campus-specific data. The company&amp;rsquo;s partnership with BLK &amp;amp; Bold, the first Black-owned nationally distributed coffee brand, expands its coffee offerings to Aramark Refreshments clients, potentially boosting revenue and customer engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:1066
Chances: Marathon Oil reported positive earnings surprises in the second quarter, with net income of $287 million and adjusted net income of $295 million. The company&amp;rsquo;s solid production profile could have contributed to somewhat favorable Q2 results despite lower commodity realizations and higher costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:1014
Chances: Truist Financial Corporation is set to pay a dividend of $0.52 per share, indicating a potential income opportunity for investors. Truist Ventures led an $18 million Series A funding round for GoTab, showcasing potential strategic investments and partnerships. Truist Foundation&amp;rsquo;s grant of $1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
