<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Utility Stocks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/utility-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Utility Stocks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/utility-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aes/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: AES is focusing on renewable energy investments, which could provide growth opportunities in the future. The company has announced positive momentum in its first-quarter results, reaffirming its 2023 guidance. AES recently acquired the largest permitted solar-plus-storage project in the United States, positioning itself in the renewable energy sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/d/</guid>
      <description>score:100
Chances: Dominion Energy is set to sell its gas distribution companies to Enbridge in a $14 billion deal, which could fuel its high-yielding payout and create new growth opportunities. The company is advancing its business with strategic agreements and initiatives, such as building a solar farm in Dulles Airport and investing in renewable energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Companhia Energética de Minas Gerais (CIG) reported its Q2 2023 earnings, and the details can be found in the earnings call transcript. CEMIG Geração e Transmissão S.A. announced early tender date results for its cash tender offer for senior notes due 2024, which could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
