<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Collaboration on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/collaboration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Collaboration on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/collaboration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PSNY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/psny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/psny/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Polestar reported record deliveries in the second quarter, growing 36% year-on-year, indicating strong momentum. Polestar is collaborating with Mobileye to build an integrated driver assist solution for its electric SUV coupé, Polestar 4. Polestar plans to adopt the North American Charging Standard to enable access to Tesla Supercharger network in the USA and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/infy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/infy/</guid>
      <description>score:208
Chances: Infosys welcomes tennis world No.1 Iga Świątek and tennis icon Rafael Nadal as brand ambassadors, enhancing global brand presence. Infosys Foundation USA invests $200,000 to boost tech careers through collaboration, reflecting corporate social responsibility. Infosys expands strategic collaboration with Liberty Global to bring AI-powered digital entertainment to customers worldwide, indicating growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:0
Chances: HP CEO discusses the potential impact of the AI boom on computers, hinting at future innovations. Miro and HP collaborate to accelerate collaboration and innovation, which may drive business growth. HP matches Q3 earnings estimates, indicating a degree of stability and meeting investor expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Sunrun has been upgraded and is well-positioned to navigate a potentially volatile solar market. The company reported better-than-expected Q2 2023 earnings with an earnings per share (EPS) beat, which is a positive sign for investors. Sunrun has expanded its collaboration with PG&amp;amp;E to share critical solar energy with California&amp;rsquo;s grid, which can enhance its market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABCM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abcm/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Danaher (DHR) to Acquire Abcam, Boost Life Sciences Unit Danaher Buys Abcam for $5.7 Billion to Expand Its Product Offerings Here’s Why Abcam plc (ABCM) Outperformed in Q2 Abcam Highlights Successful Execution of Strategic Priorities to Drive Shareholder Value NanoString and Abcam Expand Collaboration to Advance Spatial Multiomics Research Risks: Abcam shares fall after $5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:-30
Chances: United Airlines&amp;rsquo; plans to resume daily flights between San Francisco and Beijing, as well as increase flights to Shanghai, could indicate a potential for increased revenue. Collaboration with TSA PreCheck enrollment provider IDEMIA Identity and Security for an enrollment initiative at Denver International Airport could enhance customer experience and convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
