<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:51:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DNA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dna/</guid>
      <description>score:90
Chances: Exacta Bioscience and Ginkgo Bioworks Announce Partnership to Optimize Exacta&amp;rsquo;s Crop Protection Product Ginkgo Bioworks and Google Cloud Partner to Build Next Generation AI Platform for Biological Engineering and Biosecurity Ginkgo Bioworks Announces Collaboration with Merck to Improve Biologic Manufacturing Ginkgo Bioworks and Sumitomo Chemical Announce Expanded Partnership To Develop Functional Chemicals with Synthetic Biology Ginkgo Bioworks Advances Collaboration with Novo Nordisk on Expression Systems for Pharmaceutical Products Risks: Ginkgo Bioworks Awarded DARPA Contract to Reimagine the Manufacturing of Complex Therapeutic Proteins Ginkgo Bioworks and the Ministry of Health of the Republic of Botswana Announce Pathogen Monitoring Program at Key Ports of Entry Ginkgo Bioworks Announces Participation in Goldman Sachs 44th Annual Global Healthcare Conference Ginkgo Bioworks Reports First Quarter 2023 Financial Results Ginkgo Bioworks Previews Today&amp;rsquo;s Annual Ferment Conference Score:90 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Merck&amp;rsquo;s Phase 3 trial for WELIREG met the primary endpoint of PFS in certain advanced RCC patients. Merck&amp;rsquo;s impressive financial results, robust product portfolio, and commitment to R&amp;amp;D make it a potential consideration. Healthcare sector performance suggests potential for growth in healthcare stocks like Merck.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
