<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:104
Chances: Merck&amp;rsquo;s (MRK) stock has shown a 7.0% increase over the past three months, indicating positive growth potential. Early-stage study data shows positive clinical response for Moderna&amp;rsquo;s (MRNA) experimental cancer therapy, potentially boosting the healthcare industry. Merck (MRK) has initiated a Phase 3 clinical trial for its investigational oral selective KRAS G12C inhibitor, indicating a strong pipeline for future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cbay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cbay/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Gilead Sciences, Inc. has completed the acquisition of CymaBay Therapeutics, Inc. for $4.3 billion in total equity value, adding to its liver portfolio and aligning with its commitment to liver health. CymaBay’s lead product candidate, seladelpar, for the treatment of primary biliary cholangitis (PBC) including pruritus, has shown promising results in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Organon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence shows a proactive approach to patient care and may lead to increased sales. The company&amp;rsquo;s exclusive distribution of Emgality and RAYVOW in Europe presents a significant opportunity for revenue growth in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
