<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:06:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ABT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/abt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/abt/</guid>
      <description>score:82
Chances: Abbott Laboratories is expected to post stellar quarterly growth when they report Q4 results on January 24. The company is seeing favorable earnings estimate revision activity and has a positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season. The strength of the Pharmacy &amp;amp; Consumer Wellness and Health Services segments is likely to reflect positively on CVS Health&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter 2023 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:72
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s spin-off of its consumer health division may lead to increased focus and growth in its pharmaceutical and medtech segments The addition of serious warnings for cancer therapies may lead to increased caution and monitoring for potential adverse effects, which could impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:93
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co., Inc. continues to deliver positive news with the FDA approval of Keytruda for cervical cancer treatment. The Pharmaceutical segment of the company includes human health pharmaceutical and vaccine products, which positions it well in the current healthcare market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Organon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence shows a proactive approach to patient care and may lead to increased sales. The company&amp;rsquo;s exclusive distribution of Emgality and RAYVOW in Europe presents a significant opportunity for revenue growth in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/azn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/azn/</guid>
      <description>score:-135
Chances: AstraZeneca (AZN) closed at $65.95, indicating a +1.77% shift from the previous trading day. AstraZeneca (AZN) announces that it is buying vaccine company, Icosavax. The additional supply of RSV shot for infants by AstraZeneca and Sanofi indicates a positive outlook for meeting winter demand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
