<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pharmaceuticals on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/pharmaceuticals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson recently completed the separation of Kenvue, which could lead to better focus and growth opportunities in the pharmaceutical and medical tech sectors. The company forecasts double-digit earnings growth after the Kenvue spin-off, indicating a positive outlook. J&amp;amp;J continues to generate strong free cash flow, supporting its dividend decisions and financial stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:93
Chances: Bristol-Myers Squibb&amp;rsquo;s investigational LPA1 antagonist shows promise in reducing lung function decline in a Phase 2 study, which could lead to a potential breakthrough in pulmonary fibrosis treatment. Bristol-Myers Squibb celebrates a decade of its Coast 2 Coast 4 Cancer cross-country bike ride in support of the V Foundation for Cancer Research, showcasing its commitment to corporate social responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PFE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pfe/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: Pfizer Inc. (PFE) is a trending stock, indicating strong market interest. Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s COVID-era growth may influence investment decisions. Pfizer and BioNTech receive positive CHMP opinion for Omicron XBB.1.5-adapted COVID-19 vaccine in the European Union, indicating potential market expansion. Risks: Big Pharma&amp;rsquo;s battle with the Biden administration could have long-lasting consequences, posing regulatory risks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
