<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Russia on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/russia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Russia on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:13:06 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unipec and TotalEnergies Face Off in Battle for Russian Oil</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/unipec-and-totalenergies-face-off-in-battle-for-russian-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:13:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/unipec-and-totalenergies-face-off-in-battle-for-russian-oil/</guid>
      <description>Unipec and TotalEnergies Face Off in Battle for Russian Oil Unipec, the trading arm of China&amp;rsquo;s Sinopec, and TotalEnergies, the French oil major, are locked in a battle for Russian oil cargoes. Unipec is offering to pay a premium of $10 per barrel above the market price for Russian Urals crude oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s War in Ukraine Latest News Updates on June 13, 2023</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-war-in-ukraine-latest-news-updates-on-june-13-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:03:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-war-in-ukraine-latest-news-updates-on-june-13-2023/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s War in Ukraine Update: June 13, 2023
The war in Ukraine continues, with heavy fighting reported in the eastern Donbas region. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has called for more weapons from the West, saying that his country is facing a &amp;ldquo;critical moment&amp;rdquo; in the war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War in Ukraine So Far Favors the Defense</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/war-in-ukraine-so-far-favors-the-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/war-in-ukraine-so-far-favors-the-defense/</guid>
      <description>War in Ukraine So Far Favors the Defense The war in Ukraine has been raging for over two months now, and it is clear that the defense has been favored so far. The Russian military has failed to achieve its initial objectives, and has suffered heavy losses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>War Spilling Into Russian Regions Adds to Risks Haunting Economy</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/war-spilling-into-russian-regions-adds-to-risks-haunting-economy/</guid>
      <description>The war in Ukraine is having a devastating impact on the Russian economy. The conflict has disrupted supply chains, led to shortages of goods and services, and caused inflation to soar. The Russian government has taken steps to try to mitigate the damage, but these measures have so far been largely unsuccessful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe&#39;s Risky Plan to Avert a Winter Energy Crisis: Stash Gas in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/europes-risky-plan-to-avert-a-winter-energy-crisis-stash-gas-in-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/europes-risky-plan-to-avert-a-winter-energy-crisis-stash-gas-in-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>Europe&amp;rsquo;s Risky Plan to Avert a Winter Energy Crisis: Stash Gas in Ukraine Europe is facing a potential winter energy crisis due to the war in Ukraine and the uncertainty of Russian gas supplies. One way to avert the crisis is to store gas in Ukraine, which has the largest underground gas storage system in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Lack of Oil Cuts Will Test Saudi Patience</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-lack-of-oil-cuts-will-test-saudi-patience/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:36:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-lack-of-oil-cuts-will-test-saudi-patience/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Oil Production Tests Saudi Patience Russia has refused to join Saudi Arabia in cutting oil production, despite calls from the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and other major oil producers. This has led to a sharp increase in global oil supply, which has put downward pressure on prices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China Lobbies EU Over Proposal to Punish Firms Supplying Russia</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:31:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/china-lobbies-eu-over-proposal-to-punish-firms-supplying-russia/</guid>
      <description>China Lobbies EU Over Proposed Trade Restrictions China is lobbying the European Union to scrap proposed trade restrictions on Chinese companies that the bloc says are enabling Russia&amp;rsquo;s war machine in Ukraine.
The EU is considering sanctions on Chinese companies that provide Russia with semiconductors, telecommunications equipment, and other technologies that could be used for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-down-on-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Down on Tuesday
The stock market was down on Tuesday as investors continued to worry about the war in Ukraine and the impact of rising inflation.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 was down 0.5%, while the Nasdaq Composite was down 1.2%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nato-allies-wrestle-over-deepening-ties-with-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>NATO Allies Wrestle Over Deepening Ties With Ukraine NATO allies are divided over whether to deepen ties with Ukraine. Some allies, such as the United States and Poland, believe that Ukraine should be given a Membership Action Plan (MAP), which is a first step towards joining NATO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia&#39;s Rupee Trap Is Adding to $147 Billion Hoard Stuck Abroad</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/russias-rupee-trap-is-adding-to-147-billion-hoard-stuck-abroad/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Rupee Trap Russia has been selling oil to India in exchange for rupees, but it has been difficult for Russia to use these rupees to buy goods and services from India. This is because India has strict foreign exchange controls that make it difficult for foreigners to repatriate rupees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine&#39;s Attacks on Russia Are a Calculated Gamble</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraines-attacks-on-russia-are-a-calculated-gamble/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Attacks on Russian Territory Ukraine has recently carried out a series of attacks on Russian territory. The attacks have targeted Russian military bases, supply lines, and infrastructure. Russia has accused Ukraine of carrying out the attacks with the help of the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 14:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ukraine-launches-airstrikes-on-russian-held-targets/</guid>
      <description>Ukraine Launches Airstrikes on Russian-Held Targets
Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces launched airstrikes on 11 Russian clusters of personnel and equipment on May 27, 2023. The strikes were carried out by Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s air force over the past day.
The strikes come as anticipation grows that Kyiv is on the brink of beginning a long-awaited offensive to regain lost territory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
