<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economics on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economics on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rishi Sunak Is Swimming Against the Tide on Taxes, Inflation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/rishi-sunak-is-swimming-against-the-tide-on-taxes-inflation/</guid>
      <description>Rishi Sunak&amp;rsquo;s Tax Hikes: Swimming Against the Tide
The UK is facing a cost of living crisis, with inflation at a 40-year high and energy prices soaring. Chancellor Rishi Sunak has been criticized for raising taxes, rather than cutting them, to help people cope with the cost of living crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:35:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/uk-headed-for-mild-recession-this-year/</guid>
      <description>UK Headed for Mild Recession This Year According to Moody&amp;rsquo;s, the UK is headed for a &amp;ldquo;mild recession&amp;rdquo; this year. The recession is expected to be caused by higher-than-expected inflation and rising interest rates. Inflation in the UK is currently at a 40-year high, and interest rates have been raised four times since December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Property Crisis</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/vietnam-property-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/vietnam-property-crisis/</guid>
      <description>Vietnam Property Crisis Vietnam has a $34 billion worth of property projects that have been suspended due to a liquidity crisis in the country&amp;rsquo;s banking sector. The crisis has been caused by a combination of factors, including the COVID-19 pandemic, the global economic slowdown, and government regulations that have made it more difficult for developers to raise capital.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
