<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology Innovation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/technology-innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology Innovation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:50:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/technology-innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>INTC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/intc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/intc/</guid>
      <description>score:-142
Chances: Intel adds a layer of protection to edge computing Intel&amp;rsquo;s Gaudi 2 Beats Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s H100 in Certain AI Tasks Intel to Accelerate Arizona Fab Build Out After Getting Large Customer Order Intel Rallies on CEO Gelsinger’s Optimistic Comments Intel&amp;rsquo;s Efficient 144-Core Monster Is Coming Next Year Risks: Intel (INTC)&amp;rsquo;s True Worth: Is It Overpriced?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COHR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cohr/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: Coherent Corp. being a global leader in materials, networking, and lasers positions it well in innovative technology segments. Upgrades from analysts and positive performance by the U.S. oil &amp;amp; gas sector indicate some positive sentiment in the market. Investor interest in the company&amp;rsquo;s shareholder letter and updated presentation could imply a focus on transparency and strategic direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rtx/</guid>
      <description>score:1070
Chances: Ukraine reports significant results from U.S. Patriot and German IRIS-T defense systems against attacks by Russia. RTX faces quality and durability concerns with its single-aisle jetliner bet in the aerospace and defense sector. RTX beats Q2 earnings estimates with organic sales growth of 12% year over year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
