<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Airline Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/airline-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Airline Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/airline-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:113
Chances: Delta Air Lines is expanding its flights to tourist-friendly destinations in Latin America and the Caribbean, indicating potential growth in those markets. The commercial aerospace recovery is expected to continue in 2024, making it a good sector to invest in. American Express and Delta Air Lines are revamping their co-branded credit cards, offering new rewards and benefits that could attract more customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Southwest Airlines Co. invites you to listen to a live webcast of its fourth quarter 2023 financial results, indicating transparency and potential positive news for investors. The future of the U.S. economy is promising, marked by a robust recovery in the travel sector, which could benefit Southwest Airlines and its stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: United Airlines is a founding member of Star Alliance, a global aviation partnership, which could provide the company with valuable market access and customer loyalty. The U.S. Transportation Department&amp;rsquo;s scrutiny of airline loyalty programs could lead to increased transparency and benefits for frequent fliers, potentially boosting customer satisfaction and retention for United Airlines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
