<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>airline industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/airline-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in airline industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/airline-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:-76
Chances: The termination of the merger with Spirit Airlines allows JetBlue to refocus on its own operations and growth strategies. Spirit Airlines can now pursue its own expansion and market strategies without being tied to a failed merger with JetBlue. The decision to terminate the merger reflects JetBlue and Spirit Airlines&amp;rsquo; commitment to upholding competition and consumer benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 09:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dal/</guid>
      <description>score:74
Chances: Delta Air Lines closed at $41.57 in the latest trading session, marking a -1.4% move from the prior day. SkyWest aims to operate 278 E175s by 2026-end, which could potentially drive growth for the airline industry. Delta Air Lines has been one of the stocks most watched by Zacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ual/</guid>
      <description>score:-87
Chances: United Airlines plans to resume flights to Israel next month, potentially increasing revenue and market share The company reported a 1.36% positive shift in stock value in the most recent trading session Risks: The forced emergency landing of a United Airlines flight due to a bomb threat and other incidents may impact consumer confidence The ongoing investigation by the Federal Aviation Administration into an emergency landing of a United Airlines Boeing 757 flight could lead to regulatory issues Score:-87 chances characters count - risks characters count = -87</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LUV</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/luv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 09:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/luv/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Southwest Airlines Co. invites you to listen to a live webcast of its fourth quarter 2023 financial results, indicating transparency and potential positive news for investors. The future of the U.S. economy is promising, marked by a robust recovery in the travel sector, which could benefit Southwest Airlines and its stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
