<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings surprises on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprises/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings surprises on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:43:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprises/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Increase in revenues due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Operational and financial results in-line with expectations for Q2 2023. Positive outlook for penny stocks, including BTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:636
Chances: Increase in Kinross&amp;rsquo; production in Q2 due to higher grades and recoveries at specific locations. Announcement of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and transcript. Renewal of Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s normal course issuer bid (NCIB) program. Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s delivery of positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:792
Chances: Announcement of Credo Technology Group Holding&amp;rsquo;s conference call to discuss financial results for the fiscal first quarter. Credo&amp;rsquo;s participation in OCP China Day to showcase its HiWire AEC technology. Discussion about share price drop and potential concerns among shareholders. Earnings and revenue surprises reported for the quarter ended April 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:-172
Chances: Transocean expects adjusted contract drilling revenues of $720 million in Q3 2023, indicating potential revenue growth. Total adjusted contract drilling revenues showed an increase in Q2 2023 compared to the first quarter, which might suggest improving business performance. The global demand for energy presents an opportunity for energy stocks, including Transocean, to capitalize on the need for various energy sources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
