<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings surprises on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprises/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings surprises on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-surprises/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Barclays Global Consumer Staples Conference on September 6th provides an opportunity for the company&amp;rsquo;s leadership to share insights and strategies, potentially influencing investor sentiment. Continued market share growth, strength in the cold beverages segment, and effective pricing actions have positively impacted Keurig Dr Pepper&amp;rsquo;s performance, highlighting its ability to navigate competitive markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Increase in revenues due to higher average realized gold prices and increased gold ounces sold. Earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023. Operational and financial results in-line with expectations for Q2 2023. Positive outlook for penny stocks, including BTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRDO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crdo/</guid>
      <description>score:792
Chances: Announcement of Credo Technology Group Holding&amp;rsquo;s conference call to discuss financial results for the fiscal first quarter. Credo&amp;rsquo;s participation in OCP China Day to showcase its HiWire AEC technology. Discussion about share price drop and potential concerns among shareholders. Earnings and revenue surprises reported for the quarter ended April 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
