<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory Approval on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-approval/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory Approval on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:08:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-approval/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gh/</guid>
      <description>score:298
Chances: Guardant Health to Participate in the Morgan Stanley 21st Annual Global Healthcare Conference Guardant Health Stock Sees Renewed Technical Strength Guardant Health (GH) Reports Solid Q2 Results Guardant Health Receives Regulatory Approval from Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Health Sciences Authority for Guardant360® CDx blood test Guardant Health Secures Coverage From Major US Commercial Health Insurers for Guardant360® Blood Test for Comprehensive Genomic Profiling Risks: Further weakness as Guardant Health (NASDAQ:GH) drops 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIDIY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/didiy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/didiy/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: XPeng inks $744M deal with ride-share giant Didi, linking two of China&amp;rsquo;s biggest tech names XPeng Shares Rise after Announcing Strategic Partnership with DiDi Risks: Disney defends Bob Iger, Didi gets approval to register users, FAA investigates near-crash at JFK&amp;hellip; Score:61 investment score = chances characters count - risks characters count</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOBY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/joby/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/joby/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Release of operational and financial results for the second quarter, showcasing progress. Company&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing all-electric aircraft for commercial passenger service. Submission of Certification Plans to the FAA, marking progress towards aircraft certification. Annual release of Environmental, Social, Governance (ESG) report, highlighting responsible practices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
