<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory Approval on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-approval/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory Approval on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:02:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-approval/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GERN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gern/</guid>
      <description>score:178
Chances: Geron Corporation has received positive regulatory and study updates, indicating potential growth in the near future. The FDA&amp;rsquo;s potential expansion of use for Geron&amp;rsquo;s multiple myeloma cell therapies and Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s gene therapy work could lead to increased market opportunities. The FDA&amp;rsquo;s backing of Geron&amp;rsquo;s pipeline candidate, imetelstat, for the treatment of transfusion-dependent anemia is a significant positive development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ibrx/</guid>
      <description>score:153
Chances: Recent publication of preclinical data in the online issue of Science, First Release indicating potential for managing HIV without antiretroviral treatment Phase 1 pilot study showing potential for reducing viral load in people living with HIV Completion of safety portions of clinical trial studying investigational cancer vaccine for participants with Lynch syndrome Risks: Need for further clinical trials to validate the potential of N-803 and natural killer cells for managing HIV Uncertainty around regulatory approval for commercialization efforts despite significant financial resources Score:153 chances characters count - risks characters count = 153</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBAY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cbay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cbay/</guid>
      <description>score:96
Chances: Gilead Sciences, Inc. has completed the acquisition of CymaBay Therapeutics, Inc. for $4.3 billion in total equity value, adding to its liver portfolio and aligning with its commitment to liver health. CymaBay’s lead product candidate, seladelpar, for the treatment of primary biliary cholangitis (PBC) including pruritus, has shown promising results in clinical trials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OGN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ogn/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Organon&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Sempre Health to improve medication adherence shows a proactive approach to patient care and may lead to increased sales. The company&amp;rsquo;s exclusive distribution of Emgality and RAYVOW in Europe presents a significant opportunity for revenue growth in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
