<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Innovation on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/tech-innovation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech Innovation on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/tech-innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PINS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pins/</guid>
      <description>score:-171
Chances: A growing partnership with Amazon and strengthening advertising business make Pinterest a standout stock for 2024, according to RBC Powered by artificial intelligence, Pinterest is using tech to increase body representation on its platform, showing potential for innovation and growth Risks: Smaller social media stocks are slowly winning over analysts as the outlook for the advertising industry improves, indicating potential competition Impulse purchases aren’t going away any time soon, which could lead to increased reliance on Pinterest for shopping, but also potential for market saturation Activist investor Elliott Investment Management has recommended various changes for Crown Castle, showing potential for disruption in the industry Score:-171 chances characters count - risks characters count = -1171</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/s/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: SentinelOne&amp;rsquo;s joint go-to-market program with Secureworks is expected to accelerate organizational cyber resilience and simplify risk management. The company&amp;rsquo;s recent rebound in stock price, positive financial results, and strong third-quarter earnings indicate a potential upward trend in the market for SentinelOne.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
