<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory Changes on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-changes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory Changes on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:32:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-changes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TFC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tfc/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: Truist&amp;rsquo;s commitment to support affordable housing in Charlotte and career development programs could enhance its community engagement and social responsibility image. Participation in initiatives like the MIT Solve challenge showcases Truist&amp;rsquo;s dedication to fostering innovation and collaboration in addressing societal challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:-35
Chances: Tencent Music reported strong revenue growth from online music services, driving total revenue up 5.5% year over year. The company&amp;rsquo;s online music platform surpassed estimates, indicating strong demand and positive sentiment among investors. Tencent Music&amp;rsquo;s strategic adjustments to its live-streaming business show its proactive approach to managing potential risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bbd/</guid>
      <description>score:90
Chances: Banco Bradesco&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 Earnings Call Transcript suggests an opportunity for investors to understand the bank&amp;rsquo;s performance and strategies. The reduction in delinquency rates following the central bank&amp;rsquo;s easing cycle could positively impact Banco Bradesco&amp;rsquo;s financial performance. The partnership with Amazon to launch a credit card offering in Brazil indicates Banco Bradesco&amp;rsquo;s expansion into fintech and potential revenue growth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
