<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings analysis on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings analysis on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:32:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:939
Chances: Discussing the impact of higher interest rates on Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s business valuation and the changing outlook. Reviewing Sunrun&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings call and the missed earnings expectations. Analyzing the performance of renewable energy stocks, including the impact of interest rates and EV market strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1061
Chances: Discussing the top stock picks of ARK Invest and Unity&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the portfolio. Reviewing Unity&amp;rsquo;s latest quarterly update and evaluating its potential as an AI stock investment. Highlighting the year-over-year improvement in Unity&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results in terms of revenue and earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BILI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bili/</guid>
      <description>score:1024
Chances: Highlighting the use of Zacks Earnings ESP to find stocks expected to beat quarterly earnings estimates. Discussing Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s potential for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report and the key expectations. Announcing the scheduled earnings call and unaudited financial results reporting for Bilibili&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:1065
Chances: Highlighting high-yield dividend stocks with rapid growth, where UWM Holdings ranks as a leading mortgage lender. Announcing the hiring of Michele Celestino as EVP and Head of Commercial and Private Banking, Southeast at Flagstar Bank, N.A., a subsidiary of NYCB. Announcing the successful completion of Flagstar Bank&amp;rsquo;s MortgageTech Accelerator program by fintech graduates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BMY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bmy/</guid>
      <description>score:972
Chances: Bristol Myers Squibb has a history of consistently paying dividends for the last 90 years. Pharmaceutical company AbbVie reports better-than-expected Q2 sales for its arthritis medication Humira. Discounted blue-chip stocks with potential upside may offer investment opportunities in a market with some lagging stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bsx/</guid>
      <description>score:957
Chances: Boston Scientific&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings saw organic and operational revenue growth in core business segments and geographies. Continued strength in BD&amp;rsquo;s Life Sciences segment&amp;rsquo;s base business is expected to benefit Q3 sales. Boston Scientific stock rose as hospital procedures stabilized after the Covid pandemic, contributing to a 20% rise in earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
