<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steel Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/steel-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steel Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/steel-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TECK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teck/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Teck Resources collaborates with NORDEN to reduce carbon emissions in its steelmaking coal supply chain. Teck Resources works on reducing carbon dioxide emissions in the steelmaking coal supply chain through a partnership with NORDEN. Teck Resources aims to reduce annual emissions from its shipments handled by NORDEN by 25%, contributing to environmental sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:51
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;rsquo; proposed deal to acquire United States Steel holds the potential to create an American steel champion and counter Chinese dominance in the steel industry. The assignment of the United Steelworkers&amp;rsquo; right to bid to Cleveland-Cliffs gives the company an exclusive position as a potential buyer for United States Steel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: The proposed acquisition of United States Steel by Cleveland-Cliffs has the potential to create a strong American steel champion, which could compete against Chinese dominance in the steel industry. Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;rsquo; acquisition of the United Steelworkers&amp;rsquo; right to bid on the sale of United States Steel indicates that the former is positioning itself as a strong contender for the acquisition, potentially leading to a favorable outcome for Cleveland-Cliffs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
