<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steel Industry on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/steel-industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steel Industry on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:04:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/steel-industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>X</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/x/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs signs a tentative labor agreement with USW, potentially stabilizing labor relations. U.S. Steel explores strategic alternatives amid acquisition proposals, indicating potential growth opportunities. Steelworkers&amp;rsquo; support for Cleveland-Cliffs&amp;rsquo; bid for U.S. Steel could tip the scales in favor of the acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Gerdau introduced recyclable steel into Formula 1 São Paulo Grand Prix, indicating its innovative approach and market presence. The company has been upgraded to a &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; rating, suggesting potential positive momentum for investors. Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock recently crossed above the 50-day moving average and the 200-day moving average, which can be a bullish indicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/clf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/clf/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: Cleveland-Cliffs has ratified a new labor contract with the United Steelworkers for its Northshore Mining Operations, ensuring labor stability. The company is actively involved in bid attempts and negotiations, indicating an interest in strategic expansion. Cleveland-Cliffs has the exclusive rights to bid for U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TECK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/teck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/teck/</guid>
      <description>score:18
Chances: Teck Resources collaborates with NORDEN to reduce carbon emissions in its steelmaking coal supply chain. Teck Resources works on reducing carbon dioxide emissions in the steelmaking coal supply chain through a partnership with NORDEN. Teck Resources aims to reduce annual emissions from its shipments handled by NORDEN by 25%, contributing to environmental sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
