<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividends on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividends on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Energy Transfer LP has announced an increase in its quarterly cash distribution for the fourth quarter of 2023, indicating positive financial performance. The average brokerage recommendation for Energy Transfer LP suggests that it should be added to one&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, indicating positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NYCB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nycb/</guid>
      <description>score:361
Chances: An increase in expenses and deteriorated asset quality are major near-term headwinds for New York Community (NYCB). Amid the uncertain macroeconomic backdrop, it becomes difficult for investors to generate robust returns. So, they should keep an eye on high dividend-yielding stocks like New York Community (NYCB).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:139
Chances: Permian Resources Corp. is engaging in an underwritten public offering, indicating a potential increase in capital and growth opportunities. The company&amp;rsquo;s consistent focus on responsible acquisition and development of crude oil suggests a sustainable approach to driving returns. The declaration of quarterly cash dividends reflects a commitment to delivering value to shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
