<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividends on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividends on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:34:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T is issuing dividends, attracting income-focused investors looking for high-yield dividend stocks. T-Mobile is issuing its first dividend, potentially making it a more attractive investment option. AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s CEO sees potential in the drone business, indicating diversification and growth opportunities. Some cable sites show no public health risk, potentially reducing concerns and liabilities for AT&amp;amp;T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csx/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: CSX is expanding its intermodal service in partnership with Georgia Ports Authority, potentially increasing revenue streams. CSX has affirmed its dividend of $0.11, which may be attractive to income-focused investors. CSX is committed to improving conductor training and safety after recent incidents, which could enhance its reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:-17
Chances: Kenvue becomes a fully independent company following the separation from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, which could lead to growth opportunities. Kenvue is set to join the S&amp;amp;P 500, indicating positive recognition in the market. Strong second-quarter 2023 results and a positive annual profit forecast may boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/td/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/td/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Announcement of common share repurchase up to 90 million shares. Declaration of dividends and positive third quarter financial results. Positive customer satisfaction ranking for banking mobile app. Regulatory approval for normal course issuer bid. Expansion plans with new branch openings and appointments to board.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
