<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividends on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividends on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:03:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MMM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mmm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mmm/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: 3M Co. has reached record corporate dividends in 2023, largely due to substantial contributions from banks, indicating a strong financial performance. The appointment of aerospace veteran William Brown as the new CEO signals a potential fresh direction for the company, which may boost investor confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vly/</guid>
      <description>score:-167
Chances: Valley National Bancorp has reported an increase in revenue of 1.7% from FY2022 to FY2023. The company has announced a new share repurchase program, indicating confidence in its long-term sustainability. Valley National Bancorp has declared regular preferred and common dividends, demonstrating financial stability and shareholder value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:-33
Chances: ET engages in natural gas pipeline transportation and transmission services Higher oil production and reduction in marketing purchases aid Q4 earnings The average brokerage recommendation for ET is equivalent to a Buy Investors may keep a tab on stocks like ET that have higher dividend yields compared to the industry Risks: Effectiveness of overly optimistic recommendations of Wall Street analysts is questionable Lower commodity price realizations affecting Q4 earnings Potential challenges in finding the right dividend stocks to invest in The overly optimistic recommendations of Wall Street analysts make the effectiveness of this highly sought-after metric questionable Score:-33 chances characters count - risks characters count = -33</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ppl/</guid>
      <description>score:6
Chances: PPL&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter earnings are better than estimates and the company continues to make substantial investment to further strengthen its existing operations. Robust Capital Investment Plan and Dividend Growth Announced PPL&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$20.44 based on Dividend Discount Model Risks: PPL Corporation misses on earnings expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
