<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment opportunity on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investment-opportunity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment opportunity on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:05:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investment-opportunity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:158
Chances: PayPal Holdings, Inc. recently announced the appointment of Carmine Di Sibio, outgoing Global Chairman and CEO of EY, to its Board as an independent director. Follow-on buy points are important areas to add shares or make new stock purchases, and PayPal stock has made two good ones during its run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:130
Chances: The expanded partnership with Cross Screen Media will provide a significant opportunity for Roku to accurately measure spend on its inventory and leverage ACR viewership data for precise audience targeting. Roku is experiencing pressure now, but this might just be an excellent opportunity for investors to enter the market and capitalize on its potential comeback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:47
Chances: North American gold mining companies remain sound choices for investors Oversold stocks can be an opportunity for shrewd investors B2Gold reports consolidated gold production of 2,70,611 ounces in the fourth quarter of 2023 Risks: Mines can get played out and expected deposits may fail to materialize The price of gold can be volatile B2Gold Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 09:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:16
Chances: Toast received an upgrade from &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; by Goldman Sachs analysts There is optimism about the restaurant software provider&amp;rsquo;s ability to gain market share in 2024 Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies Risks: Etsy stock declined after Goldman Sachs downgraded it from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Charles Schwab shares came under pressure after a downgrade from &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; to &amp;lsquo;Neutral&amp;rsquo; Elena Gomez, CFO of Toast Inc, executed a sale of company shares Score:16 chances characters count - risks characters count = 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/onon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/onon/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: On Holding had another great quarter, and it has big plans for the next few years. The company is on a mission to double sales over the next three years. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. On Holding AG raised full-year sales guidance after posting another record quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
