<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>investment opportunity on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/investment-opportunity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in investment opportunity on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/investment-opportunity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TGTX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tgtx/</guid>
      <description>score:77
Chances: TG Therapeutics stock saw a welcome improvement to its Relative Strength (RS) Rating on Thursday, rising from 87 to 93. The average of price targets set by Wall Street analysts indicates a potential upside of 127.8% in TG Therapeutics (TGTX). The positive trend in earnings estimate revisions might translate into an upside in the stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ONON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/onon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/onon/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: On Holding had another great quarter, and it has big plans for the next few years. The company is on a mission to double sales over the next three years. High growth and low risk are a compelling combination. On Holding AG raised full-year sales guidance after posting another record quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:43
Chances: Recent revenue results and global market trends help solidify Roku as a strong investment opportunity. Several stocks soared in November on increasing signs that the Federal Reserve could be done raising interest rates as well as rising speculation that rates could even start coming down in the first half of 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOCU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/docu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 13:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/docu/</guid>
      <description>score:78
Chances: DocuSign&amp;rsquo;s stock is incredibly cheap at the moment going by two traditional valuation metrics, so it might be an enticing buying opportunity for investors. Insightful Analysis of DocuSign Inc&amp;rsquo;s Financial Health and Strategic Position Shares of e-signature company DocuSign (DOCU) jumped 4.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
