<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>finance on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in finance on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:56:11 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nigerian Naira Devaluation</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/nigerian-naira-devaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:56:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/nigerian-naira-devaluation/</guid>
      <description>The Nigerian naira has been devalued against the US dollar in recent months. The central bank of Nigeria has been trying to prop up the naira by selling dollars from its reserves. However, the naira has continued to weaken, and the central bank has been forced to raise interest rates in an effort to curb inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Korea Warns of Financial Risk as Real Estate Loans Fail</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/bank-of-korea-warns-of-financial-risk-as-real-estate-loans-fail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/bank-of-korea-warns-of-financial-risk-as-real-estate-loans-fail/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Korea Warns of Financial Risk Bank of Korea Governor Rhee Chang-yong has warned of growing financial sector risks amid a rise in real estate loan delinquencies. The share of non-bank financial institutions has increased, making it more difficult for the BOK to address financial risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:08:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/european-stocks-gain-after-us-debt-deal-fed-signaling-pause/</guid>
      <description>European Stocks Gain After US Debt Deal, Fed Signaling Pause European stocks rose on Tuesday after the US Congress reached a deal to avert a debt default and the Federal Reserve signaled that it may pause its interest rate hikes.
The pan-European Stoxx 600 index rose 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Markets Today: U.S.-China Trade Deal, Fed Pause, AI Boom</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-today-u.s.-china-trade-deal-fed-pause-ai-boom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/stock-markets-today-u.s.-china-trade-deal-fed-pause-ai-boom/</guid>
      <description>Stock Markets Today: U.S.-China Trade Deal, Fed Pause, AI Boom The stock markets are expected to be positive today, as investors are optimistic about the U.S.-China trade deal and the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s pause on interest rate hikes. The AI boom is also a positive sign for the economy, as it is expected to create new jobs and boost productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/ecb-warns-boj-policy-change-could-test-global-bond-markets/</guid>
      <description>ECB Warns BOJ Policy Change Could Test Global Bond Markets The European Central Bank (ECB) has warned that a change in policy by the Bank of Japan (BOJ) could test global bond markets.
The BOJ has been maintaining a policy of negative interest rates and quantitative easing for years, which has helped to keep Japanese government bond yields low.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
