<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>earnings decline on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-decline/</link>
    <description>Recent content in earnings decline on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-decline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>USB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/usb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/usb/</guid>
      <description>score:-31
Chances: U.S. Bancorp is experiencing revenue growth despite high costs, which could be seen as a positive sign for investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s business banking segment, Elavon, has launched a new product called Talech Terminal, indicating innovation and potential market expansion. U.S. Bancorp has strong institutional backing, with 76% ownership, which may instill confidence in investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:-25
Chances: TAL Education Group beats earnings expectations for full year 2023. Institutional investors show interest with a significant ownership stake. TAL Education Group files its annual report on Form 20-F. TAL Education Group&amp;rsquo;s strong week for shareholders doesn&amp;rsquo;t alleviate long-term losses. Top-line decline in Q3 attributed to seasonality and forex fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/afrm/</guid>
      <description>score:-37
Chances: Affirm shares soar on higher-than-expected forecast as delinquencies decline. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s strong performance is attributed to growth in customer transaction volumes. Affirm is well-positioned to harness changes in consumer behavior, according to the CFO. Affirm&amp;rsquo;s stock pops following analyst note on Debit+ card, indicating market optimism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GFI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gfi/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: Gold Fields reported earnings decline for the first half of the year due to lower volumes sold and higher operating costs. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on pursuing growth by building new mines and searching for new gold deposits indicates a strategic approach to expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
