<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trade on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/trade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trade on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/trade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-china-loses-us-import-share-to-asia-rivals/</guid>
      <description>China Loses US Import Share to Asia Rivals China lost more of its share of US imports in 2022, falling to 50.7% from 53.5% in 2021. This trend has been ongoing since 2013, and is likely due to a number of factors, including rising labor costs in China, the US-China trade war, and the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brad Setser on the Massive Shifts Underway in World Trade</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/brad-setser-on-the-massive-shifts-underway-in-world-trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:06:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/brad-setser-on-the-massive-shifts-underway-in-world-trade/</guid>
      <description>The Fragmentation of World Trade The global economy is becoming more fragmented, with countries trading more with their neighbors and less with distant countries. This fragmentation is being driven by a number of factors, including rising protectionism, the rise of nationalism, and the increasing importance of services trade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Latest: US-China Relations Stay Distant Despite Talks</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/supply-chain-latest-us-china-relations-stay-distant-despite-talks/</guid>
      <description>US-China Relations Remain Distant Despite Talks on Supply Chains The United States and China held high-level talks on supply chain issues on June 3, but the two sides remain divided on a number of issues, including technology transfer and intellectual property rights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Says US Allies Can Have Productive Ties With China</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/australia-says-us-allies-can-have-productive-ties-with-china/</guid>
      <description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Minister Richard Marles has said that US allies can have productive ties with China, even as they maintain a longstanding defense alliance with the US.
Marles said that navigating the two relationships is complex and requires discussion, but he believes it is possible to have both a productive relationship with China and a strong defense alliance with the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Delivers Early Win in Asia Trade Pact, But Rifts Surface</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-delivers-early-win-in-asia-trade-pact-but-rifts-surface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 17:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/posts/u.s.-delivers-early-win-in-asia-trade-pact-but-rifts-surface/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. and 13 other Asia-Pacific nations have agreed to expand supply-chain cooperation in a move aimed at strengthening economic ties in the region and countering China&amp;rsquo;s growing influence.
The pact, which was announced at the Detroit Economic Club by U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai and Japanese Foreign Minister Yoshimasa Hayashi, includes provisions for cooperation on supply chain resilience, digital trade, and labor standards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
