<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:53:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/wu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/wu/</guid>
      <description>score:-22
Chances: Western Union is paying a dividend of $0.235, which can be attractive to income-focused investors. The company has opened its first-ever concept store in Jordan, which could potentially enhance its presence in the region and attract new customers. Western Union reported strong Q2 earnings, beating estimates and raising its annual profit outlook, indicating positive growth in its core business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:-63
Chances: Kinross Gold announced positive earnings and revenue beats in the last quarter, leading to a 7.6% increase in stock price. The company was granted the right to earn a 70% interest in Launi East, potentially unlocking new growth opportunities. Kinross Gold declared a quarterly dividend, offering returns to its shareholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Permian Resources announced a $500.0 million private placement of senior notes due in 2032, indicating its ability to raise capital. The company is set to acquire Earthstone Energy in an all-stock transaction, creating a $14 billion premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P, which may lead to growth opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fti/</guid>
      <description>score:160
Chances: TechnipFMC has clinched a significant contract for the Girassol Life Extension Project, indicating growth potential in the oil and gas sector. The company announced the initiation of a quarterly dividend and an additional $400 million share repurchase authorization, which may attract income and value investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s has announced a quarterly dividend, which could attract income-focused investors. Collaborations with brands like Gap on a sleepwear collection suggest potential for increased sales and brand partnerships. Despite challenges, consumers are spending, and there is optimism for a potential rebound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KEY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/key/</guid>
      <description>score:-8
Chances: KeyBank provided a $5 million line of credit to advance small businesses, indicating support for growth. KeyBank celebrated the opening of a new, full-service branch, demonstrating expansion efforts. KeyCorp is paying a dividend of $0.205, offering a 7.1% dividend yield, which may attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Lufax Holding reported Q2 2023 earnings that topped estimates, indicating potential growth. Despite recent earnings declines, Lufax Holding could bounce back, as public companies are its largest shareholders. Lufax Holding Ltd successfully listed on the Main Board of The Stock Exchange of Hong Kong, which could open up new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GSK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gsk/</guid>
      <description>score:-20
Chances: GSK&amp;rsquo;s value is being questioned, but it may be undervalued, making it an attractive investment option. GSK announces availability of AREXVY, its Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) vaccine, at all major US retail pharmacies. Settling the first Zantac cancer lawsuit could soothe investors and impact GSK&amp;rsquo;s stock positively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HBAN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hban/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hban/</guid>
      <description>score:40
Chances: Huntington Bancshares is paying out a dividend of $0.155, which may attract income-focused investors. The bank&amp;rsquo;s focus on transforming medical billing with software could lead to revenue growth in the healthcare industry. Huntington National Bank ranks No. 1 among regional banks in the J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XEL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xel/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Xcel Energy declared dividend on common stock. XEL surpasses 50% carbon-free electricity generation companywide. Intrinsic value potentially 49% above share price. Positive growth potential in utility sector. XEL is favored by institutional ownership. Risks: Q2 earnings and revenue lagged estimates. Impact of regulatory changes in the energy industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Strong contender in the media industry with good outperformance potential. Positive Q2 earnings match and potential growth. Dividend declaration and positive financial results. Recent stock price surge and analyst upgrades. Participation in important industry conferences. Risks: Stock price volatility and short-squeeze focus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
