<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BCS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 03:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bcs/</guid>
      <description>score:23
Chances: Barclays Sets Aside Balance Sheet Cash for Private Debt Push Barclays appoints two new senior leaders into its Technology Investment Banking team Barclays Hires Moelis’s Lee Counselman for Tech Investment Banking Barclays appoints James Edmonds as Global Head of Sustainable Project Finance There&amp;rsquo;s A Lot To Like About Barclays&amp;rsquo; (LON:BARC) Upcoming UK£0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/beke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/beke/</guid>
      <description>score:46
Chances: KE Holdings Inc. Announces Upsizing and Extension of Share Repurchase Program and a Special Cash Dividend KE Holdings Stock Sees Rising Market Leadership; Earns 83 RS Rating Beike Joined &amp;lsquo;1t.org&amp;rsquo; China Action Even though KE Holdings (NYSE:BEKE) has lost US$1.9b market cap in last 7 days, shareholders are still up 24% over 1 year Bears are Losing Control Over KE Holdings Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Announcement of upcoming Q3 earnings release. Positive institutional ownership of 68%. Successful PC shipments in a challenging market. Declared dividend and cash tender offer. Collaboration with Wrexham AFC for technology partnership. Risks: Potential struggles in allocating capital. Legal claims and lawsuits affecting brand reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XEL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xel/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Xcel Energy declared dividend on common stock. XEL surpasses 50% carbon-free electricity generation companywide. Intrinsic value potentially 49% above share price. Positive growth potential in utility sector. XEL is favored by institutional ownership. Risks: Q2 earnings and revenue lagged estimates. Impact of regulatory changes in the energy industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIRI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/siri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/siri/</guid>
      <description>score:-16
Chances: Strong contender in the media industry with good outperformance potential. Positive Q2 earnings match and potential growth. Dividend declaration and positive financial results. Recent stock price surge and analyst upgrades. Participation in important industry conferences. Risks: Stock price volatility and short-squeeze focus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
