<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:37:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1003 MWA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mwa/</guid>
      <description>score:1003
Chances: Mueller Water Products achieved net sales of $326.6 million in the third quarter, which may indicate positive revenue performance. Mueller Water Products announced a quarterly dividend of 6.10 cents per share, which could attract income-focused investors. The stock increased significantly by 22% over a specific period, suggesting potential positive momentum in MWA&amp;rsquo;s stock price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1038 MPW</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mpw/</guid>
      <description>score:1038
Chances: Medical Properties Trust (MPW) is a real estate investment trust (REIT) that invests in hospitals, which could benefit from the potential recovery in the healthcare sector post-pandemic. Investors seeking high dividend yields may consider Medical Properties Trust (MPW), as it currently offers a dividend yield of about 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1035 RF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rf/</guid>
      <description>score:1035
Chances: Alison Rand has been appointed to the boards of Regions Financial Corp. and its subsidiary, Regions Bank. Regions Financial Corporation announced an increase in its dividend from last year&amp;rsquo;s. Higher NII on the back of decent loan demand and rising rates supported Regions Financial&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 AES</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 12:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aes/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: AES&amp;rsquo; Q2 revenues of $3,027 million beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 5.2%. The AES Corporation reported financial results for Q2 2023. The company&amp;rsquo;s GF Value suggests that it&amp;rsquo;s modestly undervalued. AES declared a quarterly common stock dividend of $0.1659 per share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1346 BTE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bte/</guid>
      <description>score:1346
Chances: Baytex Energy Corp. released its 2022 Environment, Social and Governance (ESG) Report, demonstrating a commitment to transparency and accountability, and managing the environmental and social impacts of its business. Baytex Energy Corp. reports its operating and financial results for the three and six months ended June 30, 2023, following the Ranger transaction, positioning the company as a well-capitalized and diversified North American exploration and production company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0951 IPG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ipg/</guid>
      <description>score:951
Chances: The Interpublic Group of Companies Inc (IPG) gained 4.25% daily, indicating investor interest in the stock. The company&amp;rsquo;s Earnings Per Share (EPS) of $2.41 adds to the positive sentiment among investors. As one of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest advertising holding companies, IPG generates revenue from various advertising services, including traditional and digital services, which could potentially lead to future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0993 ENB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/enb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/enb/</guid>
      <description>score:993
Chances: Enbridge reported higher second-quarter profit due to increased oil volumes, which could positively impact the stock. Enbridge&amp;rsquo;s favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Zacks Earnings ESP heading into earnings season suggest a potential opportunity for the stock. The company reaffirming its 2023 financial outlook indicates confidence in its future performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1077 PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:1077
Chances: Permian Resources Corporation announced its second quarter 2023 financial and operational results, which may provide insights into the company&amp;rsquo;s performance. The declaration of a quarterly base and variable cash dividend by Permian Resources may attract income-seeking investors. Investors may find interest in participating in the earnings conference call to gain more insights into Permian Resources&amp;rsquo; performance and future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0953 MCHP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mchp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mchp/</guid>
      <description>score:953
Chances: Microchip&amp;rsquo;s first-quarter fiscal 2024 results reflect continued momentum in the mixed signal microcontroller business, indicating growth opportunities. Record net sales and strong financial performance in the quarter ended June 2023 may positively impact the stock&amp;rsquo;s performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s initiation of quarterly cash dividend payments may attract income-seeking investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1005 MRO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mro/</guid>
      <description>score:1005
Chances: Marathon Oil reported second quarter 2023 net income of $287 million or $0.47 per diluted share, and adjusted net income was $295 million or $0.48 per diluted share. The company delivered earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, indicating positive financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0969 KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:969
Chances: Kinross Gold delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for the quarter ended June 2023, which may boost investor confidence. The Toronto Stock Exchange accepting the notice filed by Kinross Gold to renew its normal course issuer bid program could indicate the company&amp;rsquo;s confidence in its stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1153 KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:1153
Chances: Kenvue reported strong quarterly earnings, beating analyst estimates on both the top and bottom lines. The surge in heart procedures and higher demand for cold and flu medicines contributed to Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s solid gains in revenue and profit, which could also benefit Kenvue as its former consumer health unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0858 T</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 09:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/t/</guid>
      <description>score:858
Chances: AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s total returns over the past decade have lagged behind the overall market, but at current prices, the stock is considered a bargain that may be too good to pass up. AT&amp;amp;T pays a high dividend that yields 7.6%, making it attractive to investors seeking passive income.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
