<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dividend on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/dividend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dividend on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/dividend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:62
Chances: Nike (NKE) concluded the recent trading session at $103.79, signifying a +1.15% move from its prior day&amp;rsquo;s close. Barclays is reiterating its Overweight rating and $142 per share price target on Nike (NKE). The company has declared a quarterly cash dividend of $0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lu/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Investors are jubilant after the Fed’s clear signal that it would begin cutting interest rates in 2024. US stock markets jumped recently as investors cheered the much-awaited Nvidia’s results which showed the chip company enjoying strong sales. Risks: America’s position as a globally dominant force is under threat due to divisive politics and potential US China war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARMK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/armk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/armk/</guid>
      <description>score:-74
Chances: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q4 2023 earnings report indicates a stable performance, with revenue climbing 15% and operating income surging 37% The company&amp;rsquo;s dividend history, yield, and growth rates show potential for sustainable returns for investors The Food and Support Services United States (FSS United States) segment continues to offer food, hospitality and facility services for various institutions and venues, indicating a steady revenue stream Risks: Aramark&amp;rsquo;s Q1 2024 earnings call is approaching, and it&amp;rsquo;s essential to closely monitor key metrics and compare them with Wall Street estimates and year-ago numbers for any potential areas of concern While the company has seen decent share price growth, the economic environment can significantly impact its performance, posing a potential risk The company may face challenges related to specialized dietary and support services provided by the Food and Support Services International (FSS International) segment Score:-74 chances characters count - risks characters count = -74</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
