<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory risks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory risks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:07:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 09:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-150
Chances: Meta stock is trading tightly near a high after the earnings gap-up. Meta Platforms said it will stop paying Australian news publishers for content that appears on Facebook, setting up a fresh battle with Canberra. Among the Magnificent Seven stocks to buy and watch, Apple, Nvidia and Tesla stock are in new buy areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Valero Energy Corp&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings beat Wall Street estimates, indicating operational strength amid market challenges. The company&amp;rsquo;s premium refining operations have shown resilience, even in a carbon-constrained business operating environment. Lower refinery maintenance and ethanol production have positively impacted the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings in Q4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bti/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: The company&amp;rsquo;s geographical segmentation provides diversified revenue streams and market exposure. High-yield dividend stocks are offering potential bargain-bin prices for value investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s brands like Kent, Dunhill, Lucky Strike, and Pall Mall continue to resonate with consumers globally. Risks: Revenue decline and guidance cuts by the company raise concerns about its financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
