<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory Risks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory Risks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:55:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:111
Chances: PagSeguro Digital is expected to have the right combination of key factors for a likely earnings beat in its upcoming report. Increasing sales figures and vertical market growth could positively impact PagSeguro Digital&amp;rsquo;s business in 2023. The positive trend in earnings estimate revisions suggests a potential upside in PagSeguro Digital&amp;rsquo;s stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvx/</guid>
      <description>score:-1
Chances: Chevron&amp;rsquo;s share price increased due to an uptick in oil prices, contributing to positive investor sentiment. Analysts have upgraded Chevron&amp;rsquo;s stock and raised price targets, noting its constructive performance within the Oil &amp;amp; Gas sector. Chevron&amp;rsquo;s energy projects play a significant role in supplying a portion of the global LNG market, which could positively impact its earnings potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:-47
Chances: RLX Technology Inc. is a leading branded e-vapor company in China, which positions it in the growing e-cigarette market. Strong financial results and consistent announcements of unaudited financial results demonstrate the company&amp;rsquo;s transparency and performance. Chinese stocks, including RLX Technology, have experienced significant share movement, indicating potential for price appreciation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>META</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/meta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/meta/</guid>
      <description>score:-61
Chances: Meta Platforms, along with other AI-focused companies like Nvidia and Tesla, has experienced significant investor enthusiasm in 2023, driven by the potential of AI. The company&amp;rsquo;s involvement in artificial intelligence and generative AI projects could contribute to its growth and value appreciation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIOT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/riot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/riot/</guid>
      <description>score:59
Chances: Riot Platforms has shown impressive performance in 2023, with a 332% increase in its stock price due to the appreciation in Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s price and the scale of its current Bitcoin mining operations. The company reported strong financial results, including a record hash rate capacity of 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
