<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulatory risks on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-risks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulatory risks on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:03:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/regulatory-risks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LYFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lyft/</guid>
      <description>score:-39
Chances: Lyft&amp;rsquo;s estimated fair value is US$35.37 based on 2 Stage Free Cash Flow to Equity LYFT is set to thrive in the growing rideshare market, buoyed by competitive pricing and cost-cutting measures Lyft shares more than doubled over the last year, indicating strong potential for growth Risks: Shares of ride sharing service Lyft fell 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/spr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/spr/</guid>
      <description>score:-26
Chances: Spirit AeroSystems&amp;rsquo; strong position as a key supplier to Boeing and Airbus gives it a significant chance for long-term growth and stability. The company&amp;rsquo;s focus on quality and safety will be crucial in regaining the trust of regulators, customers, and the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VLO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vlo/</guid>
      <description>score:-14
Chances: Valero Energy Corp&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings beat Wall Street estimates, indicating operational strength amid market challenges. The company&amp;rsquo;s premium refining operations have shown resilience, even in a carbon-constrained business operating environment. Lower refinery maintenance and ethanol production have positively impacted the company&amp;rsquo;s earnings in Q4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bti/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: The company&amp;rsquo;s geographical segmentation provides diversified revenue streams and market exposure. High-yield dividend stocks are offering potential bargain-bin prices for value investors. The company&amp;rsquo;s brands like Kent, Dunhill, Lucky Strike, and Pall Mall continue to resonate with consumers globally. Risks: Revenue decline and guidance cuts by the company raise concerns about its financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
