<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sustainability on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/sustainability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sustainability on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ASX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/asx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/asx/</guid>
      <description>score:175
Chances: ASE Technology Holding achieves the best overall performance on the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices. ASE&amp;rsquo;s Bumping Factory in Kaohsiung, Taiwan inducted into the World Economic Forum’s Global Lighthouse Network. ASE announces advancements under the VIPack™ Platform. ASX reports positive Q2 2023 earnings results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ba/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Resumption of 737 Max deliveries to China after a 4-year halt. Boeing&amp;rsquo;s focus on sustainability and hiring &amp;lsquo;Elon Musk engineers&amp;rsquo; for green initiatives. Positive recognition of Boeing&amp;rsquo;s top-performing suppliers. Securing an order for Dreamliner jets from Qantas. Potential rebound after a 7% drop since the last earnings report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Strong performance with positive earnings and revenue growth. Investor confidence due to Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI potential and cheap valuation. Successful sustainability efforts and focus on AI technology. Trending stock with potential for growth and long-term investment. Positive industry outlook and potential for technology sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRAB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/grab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/grab/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Grab advances break-even timeline on boost from cost cuts and strong demand. Grab reports positive second quarter 2023 results. Initiatives to achieve zero packaging waste by 2040 show Grab&amp;rsquo;s sustainability focus. Positive revenue forecast and achieving break-even in the delivery business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITUB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/itub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/itub/</guid>
      <description>score:87
Chances: Strategic buyouts and acquisitions contribute positively to Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s growth amid cost challenges. Increased earnings and revenues reported in recent quarters indicate a favorable trend. Recognition in sustainability indices demonstrates Itaú Unibanco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to corporate responsibility. Positive projections and inclusion in major indices highlight potential growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UNVR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/unvr/</guid>
      <description>score:1087
Chances: Univar Solutions has completed an acquisition by Apollo Funds, maintaining its global presence under the Univar Solutions name and brand. The company has expanded its distribution relationship with Kalsec Inc. for hop ingredients in the United States, enhancing its specialty ingredient offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
