<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainability on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/sustainability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustainability on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:04:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KDP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kdp/</guid>
      <description>score:190
Chances: Keurig Dr Pepper Inc (KDP) recently announced a dividend of $0.22 per share, payable on 2024-04-12 The company&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio runs broad across the beverage space after several acquisitions over the years, from soft drinks like Snapple and Dr. Pepper to its Keurig K-Cup coffee pods and even chocolate milk staple Yoo-Hoo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNHI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnhi/</guid>
      <description>score:165
Chances: CNH Industrial&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability and innovation is a positive sign for potential performance in the upcoming quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong showing in the S&amp;amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment indicates a solid foundation for future growth. Recent product innovations and awards from agricultural and construction industry forums reflect a forward-thinking approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XRX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/xrx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/xrx/</guid>
      <description>score:66
Chances: Xerox reported a surge in full-year free cash flow, indicating improved operational efficiency. The company&amp;rsquo;s announcement of a new operating model and organizational structure shows a commitment to reinvention and adaptation. JPMorgan named Xerox as a top hardware stock to own, indicating positive market sentiment towards the company&amp;rsquo;s potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YUMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Yum China (YUMC) has been ranked number one globally for the Restaurant &amp;amp; Leisure Facilities Industry in the S&amp;amp;P Global 2023 Corporate Sustainability Assessment, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability. Yum China&amp;rsquo;s KFC unveiled its 10,000th store in Hangzhou, indicating strategic growth and solidifying leadership in China&amp;rsquo;s dynamic restaurant market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
