<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainability on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/sustainability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustainability on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:10:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/sustainability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CSCO</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/csco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/csco/</guid>
      <description>score:199
Chances: Cisco Systems has a long-standing priority of embracing sustainability and reducing environmental footprint, which could be seen as a positive indicator for the company&amp;rsquo;s future growth potential. The company recently announced a dividend of $0.39 per share, payable on 2024-01-24, highlighting its commitment to rewarding investors and providing a steady income stream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YUMC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/yumc/</guid>
      <description>score:-5
Chances: Yum China (YUMC) has been ranked number one globally for the Restaurant &amp;amp; Leisure Facilities Industry in the S&amp;amp;P Global 2023 Corporate Sustainability Assessment, reflecting the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability. Yum China&amp;rsquo;s KFC unveiled its 10,000th store in Hangzhou, indicating strategic growth and solidifying leadership in China&amp;rsquo;s dynamic restaurant market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pcg/</guid>
      <description>score:124
Chances: PG&amp;amp;E Corp. is focused on sustainability and affordable energy for customers, which could drive long-term growth The company is exploring emerging technologies such as unmanned aerial systems for utility operations, showing a commitment to innovation The biggest US convertible bond issue in nearly two years confirms the comeback of convertible bonds as a cost-effective debt option for companies Risks: The energy sector has been going through significant volatility over the past few years, which could impact PG&amp;amp;E Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
