<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cvs/</guid>
      <description>score:39
Chances: Quality dividend stock with potential for growth when down. Positive earnings surprise and beats earnings expectations. Interest from insiders buying the stock. Diverse offerings catering to dividends or explosive growth. Strong performance in the reliable healthcare sector. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHPT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/chpt/</guid>
      <description>score:102
Chances: ChargePoint announced it will release its Q2 fiscal year 2024 financial results on September 6, 2023. Significant investment in technology to deliver nearly 100% charging station reliability. Positive outlook for the EV charging landscape in the second half of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vips/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Vipshop is a leading online discount retailer for brands in China. Strong position in China&amp;rsquo;s competitive e-commerce market. Anticipated release of second quarter 2023 financial results. Risks: Volatility in the stock price due to market movements. Competitive nature of China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Earnings ESP. Positive stock price performance, up 17% in the last quarter. Key appointment of Chief Financial Officer, Tim Stone. Leading global platform for the luxury fashion industry. Risks: Vulnerability of stock price to institutions due to large stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DISH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dish/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Merging with EchoStar creates a new kind of satellite and wireless data services company. Merger aims to give financial flexibility to build a nationwide wireless network. Share price saw a 10% increase after the merger announcement. Creation of a larger wireless network to compete with AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:32
Chances: Marvell Technology is outlining its strategy for optimizing storage and memory technologies for AI and data-intensive cloud workloads, indicating a focus on innovation and technology advancement. Investors looking for relatively cheap AI stocks may consider Marvell Technology, suggesting potential value and growth prospects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LI</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/li/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Li Auto&amp;rsquo;s strong delivery outlook and aim to outsell premium car brands in China by 2024 could boost investor confidence. Significant revenue growth in the second quarter and positive earnings performance could contribute to stock growth. Launch of Li Auto&amp;rsquo;s first pure battery electric model &amp;lsquo;MEGA&amp;rsquo; and its expected popularity could drive sales and market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:-12
Chances: Nu Holdings&amp;rsquo; expected increase in second-quarter 2023 revenues could positively impact the stock. Partnership with Hopper to power Nubank&amp;rsquo;s travel portal could lead to growth in customer engagement. Surpassing 80 million customers in Brazil and Latin America indicates strong customer base expansion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:3
Chances: Marathon Digital Holdings reported mining a record number of blocks and producing significant amounts of BTC, indicating strong operational performance. The company&amp;rsquo;s unrestricted cash and Bitcoin holdings have increased, which could potentially provide financial stability and investment opportunities. Undervalued blockchain stocks, including Marathon Digital, have rebounded in line with the resurgence of the cryptocurrency sector, presenting investment potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LCID</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lcid/</guid>
      <description>score:134
Chances: Lucid Group raised its production guidance for the year after a better-than-expected second quarter. Despite an earnings miss and falling short of EV deliveries, Lucid Group&amp;rsquo;s stock is still seeing positive movement. The unveiling of final production specs for the Lucid Air Sapphire model showcases the company&amp;rsquo;s innovation in electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLUG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/plug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/plug/</guid>
      <description>score:70
Chances: Plug Power reported record revenue in its second-quarter results, reaffirming its full-year sales estimate. Despite recent losses and challenges, Plug Power remains one of the most hyped hydrogen stocks with potential. The hydrogen technology company has hydrogen production plants in various states, contributing to its revenue drivers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:12
Chances: Impressive second-quarter earnings and revenue beat ratios in the healthcare sector highlight positive performance. Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson&amp;rsquo;s reputation as a dividend stock could attract investors looking for consistent income. FDA approval for antibody-based therapy Talvey indicates potential for innovation in difficult-to-treat blood cancer treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMZN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/amzn/</guid>
      <description>score:68
Chances: Amazon&amp;rsquo;s potential to become a central ID system for various aspects of people&amp;rsquo;s lives could lead to increased customer engagement and loyalty. Strong interest from prominent investors like Baupost Group and Fidelity indicates positive market sentiment and potential growth. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s focus on executing big solutions in large markets and the continued resilience of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Kenvue&amp;rsquo;s inclusion in the S&amp;amp;P 500 index could boost its visibility and potentially attract more investors. Strong quarterly earnings and positive outlook signal potential growth and market confidence in Kenvue&amp;rsquo;s business. Spin-off from Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and successful IPO indicate a level of independence and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLTR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pltr/</guid>
      <description>score:61
Chances: Palantir&amp;rsquo;s track record of success in AI and data mining positions it well in the current artificial intelligence boom. Despite recent stock price fluctuations, Palantir has achieved adjusted net profitability and GAAP profitability, indicating positive financial performance. Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s Ark Investment Management&amp;rsquo;s estimation of significant economic gains from AI software could indirectly benefit Palantir&amp;rsquo;s AI-focused activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:981
Chances: TAL Education Group share price has gained 56% in the last period. TAL Education Group announces unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. TAL Education Group to release unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. Chinese hedge funds add TAL Education Group to their portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Energy Transfer reports strong performance in operations with record volumes, including NGL exports. Ares Capital offers a high dividend yield of nearly 9.7%, attracting investors seeking income. Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s expanded operations in the Permian Basin and strong export volumes likely benefit Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
