<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:06:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ERIC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/eric/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Ericsson&amp;rsquo;s financial report for the fourth quarter 2024 will be published soon, which could potentially have a positive impact on the stock. The company is actively involved in 5G infrastructure, which is a positive catalyst for its growth. Recent partnerships and awards, such as winning the National Innovation Award, indicate positive developments for the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/crm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/crm/</guid>
      <description>score:172
Chances: Tech stocks were the talk of Wall Street in 2023 centering around Magnificent Seven and AI drivers, and it looks like that will continue in 2024. Companies placing major investments in AI across their respective business models may signal a paradigm shift, which could have a positive impact on Salesforce, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cnm/</guid>
      <description>score:15
Chances: Core &amp;amp; Main, Inc. has announced an upsizing of its secondary offering, indicating potential investor interest and confidence in the company. The company has seen significant stock growth, indicating positive market sentiment and potential for future gains. The acquisition of assets from a provider of water, wastewater, and storm drainage products signals a commitment to expansion and diversification of the company’s offerings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:-118
Chances: The market is feeling much better about businesses in Toast&amp;rsquo;s industry. Toast may turn the tide of a growth drop-off with cutting-edge digital solutions and a forward-thinking approach. Interest rate cuts expected by April may benefit high-growth companies like Toast. Investors are hoping for things to take a huge turn for the better for Toast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Gold producers are raising bets on copper through deals and investments, indicating potential growth opportunities. Expectations of interest rate cuts and a weaker dollar have fueled the rise in gold prices, presenting a positive outlook for gold mining companies like Newmont Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVUE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 09:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kvue/</guid>
      <description>score:-39
Chances: Kenvue Inc. stock saw a 1.4% increase at the end of the after-hours trading session on December 13.The company reported a total dividend expense of $383 million from January to September. The favorable court ruling in a product-liability case resulted in a nearly 5% rise in Kenvue shares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
