<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:00:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/td/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/td/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Announcement of common share repurchase up to 90 million shares. Declaration of dividends and positive third quarter financial results. Positive customer satisfaction ranking for banking mobile app. Regulatory approval for normal course issuer bid. Expansion plans with new branch openings and appointments to board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpq/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Announcement of upcoming Q3 earnings release. Positive institutional ownership of 68%. Successful PC shipments in a challenging market. Declared dividend and cash tender offer. Collaboration with Wrexham AFC for technology partnership. Risks: Potential struggles in allocating capital. Legal claims and lawsuits affecting brand reputation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Positive Q2 and Q1 earnings results announced. Announcement of unaudited financial results and transcripts. Stock upgraded to &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; by MSCI ESG Rating. CEO&amp;rsquo;s holdings reduced by 13%, but still a significant shareholder. Risks: Declining stock performance over the past year. Volatility and fluctuations in stock value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Positive earnings results with EPS beating expectations and strong Q2 performance. Expansion of collaboration with PG&amp;amp;E and readiness for emergency demand response program. Partnerships with housing organizations to provide solar installations for renters. Growing interest and investments in renewable energy stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pr/</guid>
      <description>score:85
Chances: Permian Resources announces acquisition of Earthstone Energy, creating a premier Delaware Basin independent E&amp;amp;P. Positive announcements of quarterly cash dividends and portfolio optimization transactions. Improvement in 2023 guidance and potential for growth in the energy sector. Senior leadership changes and improved performance indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: B2Gold reports strong Q2 2023 operating results and positions to achieve annual guidance. Positive exploration drilling results from the Fekola regional area. Company&amp;rsquo;s projects and assets positioning it for growth. Increase in mineral resource estimate for the Anaconda area near Fekola Mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Selected by Farmers Insurance Federal Credit Union for personal lending. Potential for significant upside due to AI technology in the financial sector. Stock&amp;rsquo;s impressive rally of over 400% since May 2023. Strong performance among the best performing stocks in the last 3 and 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Coupang sustains profit streak, sees logistics investments pay off. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat estimates. Coupang stock clears key benchmark, hitting 80-plus RS rating. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s sales beat estimates after big spending pays off. Positive momentum and growth trends in Coupang&amp;rsquo;s returns on capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGNC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/agnc/</guid>
      <description>score:-4
Chances: Monthly dividend payments providing attractive income to investors. Strong Q2 earnings beat on net spread and dollar roll. Positive outlook for AGNC Investment Corp. as a high-dividend stock. Bullish views from Wall Street analysts. Consistent dividend declarations and monthly common stock dividends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/fcx/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Stellar returns of 211% over the past three years for FCX investors. Strong Q2 earnings and revenue beats despite international obstacles. Positive outlook for the mining sector and commodity stocks. Potential growth opportunities in the electrification and EV trend. Strategic importance of copper in various industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: RS rating upgrade for Micron Technology stock. Expansion of memory expansion module portfolio to accelerate technology adoption. Advancements in generative AI innovation through highest-capacity HBM. Positive performance and leadership in the AI sector. Potential benefits from AI-driven growth in memory semiconductor industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NKE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nke/</guid>
      <description>score:29
Chances: Strong performance of Jordan brand contributing to resilience. Positive outlook as Wall Street analysts express optimism. Expanding offerings and addressing consumer demands. Elevated interest in soccer jerseys and merchandise. Focus on financial metrics and competitive strengths. Risks: Market volatility impacting stock&amp;rsquo;s performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Realty Income&amp;rsquo;s consistent dividend payments and yield. Positive outlook for long-term investment. Strong financial performance and revenue surpassing estimates. Investment in Bellagio Las Vegas at a significant valuation. Stable monthly dividend declarations for years. Risks: Potential impact of rising interest rates on dividend stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IQ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/iq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/iq/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: iQIYI announces positive financial results and partnerships. Company focuses on high-quality growth and content expansion. Strategic partnerships and innovative initiatives drive growth. Positive analysis of iQIYI&amp;rsquo;s intrinsic value and returns on capital. Strong performance in AI-based content production and distribution. Risks: Decline in company earnings and investor returns over the past years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:-2
Chances: JD.com beats earnings estimates despite China&amp;rsquo;s economic challenges. Strong net profit growth in the second quarter. Partnership with Gucci and digital flagship store launch. Positive sentiment from Wall Street analysts. Investment potential in high-growth tech stocks. Risks: JD.com stock impacted by China&amp;rsquo;s economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:-10
Chances: Expansion into new markets, such as opening casinos and online gaming products. Positive analyst outlook and investment recommendations. Potential growth in the sports betting and gambling industry. Partnership announcements with major media companies like ESPN. Strong investor interest and bullish sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Positive analyst recommendations and growth potential. Strong second quarter results and raised full-year outlook. Significant surge in stock price and momentum. Participation in secondary offerings and announcements. Recognition as a strong growth stock in various lists. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KGC</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/kgc/</guid>
      <description>score:-52
Chances: Kinross Gold beats earnings and revenue estimates in Q2. Kinross granted right to earn 70% interest in Launi East. Routine renewal of NCIB and redemption of senior notes. Successful unsecured notes offering to refinance outstanding notes. Positive industry outlook highlighting Kinross Gold&amp;rsquo;s potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:37
Chances: Opendoor announces inducement grants under Nasdaq listing rule. Positive signs for Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s business and growth potential. Trending stock with potential growth opportunities. Opendoor beats revenue estimates despite reporting a Q2 loss. Strong stock performance and potential for growth in the real estate sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: Merck&amp;rsquo;s Phase 3 trial for WELIREG met the primary endpoint of PFS in certain advanced RCC patients. Merck&amp;rsquo;s impressive financial results, robust product portfolio, and commitment to R&amp;amp;D make it a potential consideration. Healthcare sector performance suggests potential for growth in healthcare stocks like Merck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-160
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing next-generation solid-state lithium-metal batteries showcases its commitment to innovative technology, which could position it well in the evolving EV industry. Despite recent fluctuations in QS stock, the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to raise significant capital through underwritten public offerings demonstrates investor interest and support for its growth initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Coinbase Global has achieved a significant milestone by winning approval to handle customers&amp;rsquo; buying and selling of crypto futures. As a major player in cryptocurrency trading, Coinbase Global benefits from the $900 billion spot trading market of cryptocurrencies. The popularity of decentralized finance (DeFi) and Ethereum&amp;rsquo;s leadership in the space could positively impact Coinbase&amp;rsquo;s position in the crypto market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Marathon&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in Bitcoin mining, including record blocks and increased operational hash rate, indicates its leadership in the crypto mining sector. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic expansion, such as its mining operations in Abu Dhabi, demonstrates its commitment to diversifying and scaling its operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vips/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Vipshop is a leading online discount retailer for brands in China. Strong position in China&amp;rsquo;s competitive e-commerce market. Anticipated release of second quarter 2023 financial results. Risks: Volatility in the stock price due to market movements. Competitive nature of China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Earnings ESP. Positive stock price performance, up 17% in the last quarter. Key appointment of Chief Financial Officer, Tim Stone. Leading global platform for the luxury fashion industry. Risks: Vulnerability of stock price to institutions due to large stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
