<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Market Volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Market Volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:14:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> M</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/m/</guid>
      <description>score:1034
Chances: Macy&amp;rsquo;s is set to report its second quarter 2023 sales and earnings results, with a call and webcast hosted by company executives. Retailers like Macy&amp;rsquo;s are expanding their use of &amp;lsquo;breathable&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cooling&amp;rsquo; fabrics to boost sales amid high demand for heat-relief clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TAL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tal/</guid>
      <description>score:981
Chances: TAL Education Group share price has gained 56% in the last period. TAL Education Group announces unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. TAL Education Group to release unaudited financial results for Q1 of fiscal year 2024. Chinese hedge funds add TAL Education Group to their portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:990
Chances: Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s recent appointment of Tim Stone as Chief Financial Officer is a positive move that could contribute to the company&amp;rsquo;s financial management and strategic direction. Riding Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s love for innovative tech businesses, Farfetch&amp;rsquo;s stock had soared in the past, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s potential for growth and investor interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> OXY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/oxy/</guid>
      <description>score:999
Chances: Occidental Petroleum reported a surprise profit in Q2 2023 despite the impact of soft commodity prices. Permian Basin production remains strong, contributing to Occidental&amp;rsquo;s production volumes for the year. Sunrise&amp;rsquo;s surprise profit, DXC&amp;rsquo;s guidance, and Wayfair&amp;rsquo;s performance could provide insights into Occidental&amp;rsquo;s industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/hpe/</guid>
      <description>score:1112
Chances: Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) announces a transition plan for CFO Tarek Robbiati, who will assume an external CEO role. HPE expands its Bare Metal Cloud platform with cloud-native HPE ProLiant RL300 Gen11 servers, enhancing AI inferencing and cloud-native workloads. ZoomInfo delivered positive earnings and revenue surprises for Q2 2023, potentially impacting HPE&amp;rsquo;s stock and market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ET</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/et/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/et/</guid>
      <description>score:890
Chances: Energy Transfer reports strong performance in operations with record volumes, including NGL exports. Ares Capital offers a high dividend yield of nearly 9.7%, attracting investors seeking income. Energy Transfer&amp;rsquo;s expanded operations in the Permian Basin and strong export volumes likely benefit Q2 earnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MSFT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/msft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/msft/</guid>
      <description>score:1004
Chances: Microsoft is seeking to patent a &amp;lsquo;high-sensitivity&amp;rsquo; facial recognition technology, indicating the company&amp;rsquo;s focus on innovative advancements. Rising corporate spending on digital transformation projects has positively impacted CRM stock, with completed merger synergies from the Slack deal being a key driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:1139
Chances: Upstart, a consumer lender using AI for creditworthiness, experienced a significant stock rally, driven by a short squeeze, improving macro environment, AI excitement, and positive earnings report. Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 performance likely benefited from new product additions amid a challenging macro environment and support from funding partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> NU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nu/</guid>
      <description>score:1054
Chances: Nu Holdings, a Brazilian digital bank backed by Berkshire Hathaway, is focusing on high-yield savings accounts to drive growth in Latin America&amp;rsquo;s second-largest economy. Nu Holdings has surpassed 80 million customers in Brazil and expanded operations to Mexico and Colombia, indicating rapid customer acquisition and potential growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JNJ</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jnj/</guid>
      <description>score:1071
Chances: Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson is allowing shareholders to swap for shares of Kenvue, which has brands like Tylenol, at a discount. Dividend stocks like Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson (JNJ) are considered a stable investment option, especially for risk-averse investors. Boasting brands like Band-Aid and Benadryl, Kenvue has become the largest pure-play consumer health company, offering potential opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PBR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr/</guid>
      <description>score:1040
Chances: Petrobras considers increasing investments in the next five-year plan, possibly by up to 10% over the previous one. The increase may include inflation adjustments and funding for new projects, supporting the company&amp;rsquo;s growth. President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva aims to use Petrobras to drive a green transition and increase investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PYPL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pypl/</guid>
      <description>score:1002
Chances: PayPal launches its own U.S. dollar-backed stablecoin, PYUSD, for payments and transfers. PYPL stock surges on the news of the stablecoin launch in the cryptocurrency market. Introduction of stablecoin by a major fintech firm like PayPal can drive further cryptocurrency adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> JBLU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jblu/</guid>
      <description>score:883
Chances: Airlines adapting routes to cater to changing travel preferences between leisure and business travelers. JetBlue and Allegiant Travel&amp;rsquo;s Q2 results benefit from strong air travel demand. JetBlue partners with Air Serbia for codeshare agreement to expand flight availability. Risks: Dependence on recovery of business travel demand, which has been slower to rebound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PBR-A</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pbr-a/</guid>
      <description>score:1205
Chances: Petrobras&amp;rsquo; potential increase in investments and capital expenditures in its next five-year business plan reflects a commitment to growth and expansion, supported by President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva&amp;rsquo;s focus on driving a green transition. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategy to raise the average capacity use of its refineries and break production records for diesel showcases operational efficiency and the ability to adapt to market demands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:1032
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s decision to raise $300 million through a public offering of shares could provide a significant influx of cash for the company&amp;rsquo;s operations and growth. Shares of QuantumScape have experienced a more than 50% increase in the past three months, indicating positive investor sentiment and potential demand for the company&amp;rsquo;s innovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:919
Chances: DraftKings&amp;rsquo; stock has nearly tripled from its December lows, driven by better-than-hoped financials, including a surprising profit last quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s revenue outlook for the second quarter has been hoisted for the second time in a row, indicating strong growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> U</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/u/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/u/</guid>
      <description>score:1114
Chances: Unity Software reported strong Q2 2023 results with an 11% year-over-year revenue increase to $533 million, exceeding analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations by $16 million. The company&amp;rsquo;s Unity Wētā Tools division aims to reshape the digital entertainment landscape and provide solutions for artists to collaborate and create 2D and 3D content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
