<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:53
Chances: Schlumberger (SLB) concluded the recent trading session at $54.48, signifying a +1.97% move from its prior day&amp;rsquo;s close. De-risking the Welchau play in Austria may not just be a big step toward Austrian energy independence, it may also ease Europe&amp;rsquo;s $800 billion energy crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROKU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/roku/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/roku/</guid>
      <description>score:130
Chances: The expanded partnership with Cross Screen Media will provide a significant opportunity for Roku to accurately measure spend on its inventory and leverage ACR viewership data for precise audience targeting. Roku is experiencing pressure now, but this might just be an excellent opportunity for investors to enter the market and capitalize on its potential comeback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEDG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 09:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sedg/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: SolarEdge Technologies, Inc. has a strong track record in the energy technology sector, offering inverter solutions and a range of other products and services. The company&amp;rsquo;s Solar segment, which includes inverter solutions designed to maximize power generation, shows potential for growth and revenue generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LVS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/lvs/</guid>
      <description>score:121
Chances: Las Vegas Sands Corp. has been named one of Fortune&amp;rsquo;s World&amp;rsquo;s Most Admired Companies in 2024, indicating a strong reputation and respect within the global business community. The company&amp;rsquo;s full year 2023 results show a significant increase in revenue, up 152% from FY 2022, indicating strong financial performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRK</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrk/</guid>
      <description>score:126
Chances: Merck &amp;amp; Co. has demonstrated its commitment to expanding its animal health business through the recent acquisition of Elanco&amp;rsquo;s aqua business. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong earnings report and solid guidance indicate that it is well-positioned to thrive despite potential challenges such as the expiration of its patent on Keytruda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NXT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nxt/</guid>
      <description>score:306
Chances: Nextracker (NXT) has beaten earnings expectations and lifted guidance, showing robust performance and product differentiation in the solar market. Increasing installation activities and benefits from the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA) should benefit the U.S. solar industry amid declining module pricing. Apple, Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ry/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: Royal Bank of Canada (RY) is a well-established financial institution with a strong presence in multiple segments including Personal and Commercial Banking, Wealth Management, Insurance, and Capital Markets. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion efforts, such as the proposed acquisition of HSBC Bank Canada and the RBC Training Ground program, indicate a commitment to growth and diversification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Gold producers are raising bets on copper through deals and investments, indicating potential growth opportunities. Expectations of interest rate cuts and a weaker dollar have fueled the rise in gold prices, presenting a positive outlook for gold mining companies like Newmont Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
