<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PAA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/paa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/paa/</guid>
      <description>score:100
Chances: Plains All American Pipeline (PAA) settling at $16.20, representing a -0.61% change from its previous close. The U.S. now accounts for 967.144 billion cubic meters of NGL production per year, equivalent to 42.7% of the global production, driving heightened demand for transport services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ry/</guid>
      <description>score:-49
Chances: Royal Bank of Canada (RY) is a well-established financial institution with a strong presence in multiple segments including Personal and Commercial Banking, Wealth Management, Insurance, and Capital Markets. The company&amp;rsquo;s expansion efforts, such as the proposed acquisition of HSBC Bank Canada and the RBC Training Ground program, indicate a commitment to growth and diversification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:129
Chances: Fortinet (FTNT) has been gaining attention from investors and analysts, indicating potential for growth in the stock&amp;rsquo;s prospects. The announcement of the industry’s only integrated secure networking solution with Wi-Fi 7 and the launch of a new access point and 10 Gigabit Power over Ethernet switch demonstrates Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and staying ahead in the cybersecurity market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEM</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nem/</guid>
      <description>score:42
Chances: Gold producers are raising bets on copper through deals and investments, indicating potential growth opportunities. Expectations of interest rate cuts and a weaker dollar have fueled the rise in gold prices, presenting a positive outlook for gold mining companies like Newmont Corp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ON</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/on/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/on/</guid>
      <description>score:71
Chances: ON Semiconductor Corp. (ON) is expected to capture more than 25% of the silicon carbide market by the end of 2023. The stock market is likely to be volatile in 2024, and diligent investors will find opportunities. These stocks have growth potential in 2024 and over the next decade because of megatrend tailwinds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:92
Chances: Cemig (CIG) possesses solid growth attributes, which could help it handily outperform the market. Cemig (CIG) could produce exceptional returns because of its solid growth attributes. Cemig (CIG) is well positioned to outperform the market, as it exhibits above-average growth in financials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAVA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cava/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 14:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cava/</guid>
      <description>score:58
Chances: Cava Group&amp;rsquo;s revenue jumped by 50% in the most recent quarter and analysts expect sales to rise by 33% in the fourth quarter, indicating strong growth potential. The company&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Morgan Stanley Global Consumer &amp;amp; Retail Conference shows a proactive approach to investor relations and potential for positive market impact.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
