<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>market volatility on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in market volatility on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/market-volatility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dvn/</guid>
      <description>score:26
Chances: Devon Energy is attracting investor attention, and it could be a buy for its upcoming dividend. Some oil stocks, including Devon Energy, have recently received a boost and may have potential for further growth. The company&amp;rsquo;s strong financial prospects suggest that weakness in its stock may not reflect its true value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SBRA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/sbra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/sbra/</guid>
      <description>score:52
Chances: Sabra Health Care REIT has announced its participation in several healthcare and real estate conferences, indicating an active presence in the industry. The company has published its third annual sustainability report, reflecting a commitment to sustainability and responsible business practices. Despite recent stock price declines, there&amp;rsquo;s potential for a 20% rise in dividend yields, as suggested by Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSNY</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/psny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/psny/</guid>
      <description>score:-38
Chances: Polestar reported record deliveries in the second quarter, growing 36% year-on-year, indicating strong momentum. Polestar is collaborating with Mobileye to build an integrated driver assist solution for its electric SUV coupé, Polestar 4. Polestar plans to adopt the North American Charging Standard to enable access to Tesla Supercharger network in the USA and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tost/</guid>
      <description>score:64
Chances: Toast announces the launch of a Catering &amp;amp; Events platform to help restaurants streamline event management and improve guest experience. Toast is transforming the restaurant industry with its restaurant technology platform, which could drive future growth. Toast is approved for use in Marriott Select Service Hotels in the United States and Canada, expanding its market presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tme/</guid>
      <description>score:-3
Chances: Tencent Music Entertainment reports rising quarterly revenue, although it warns of a potential decline ahead. Tencent Music&amp;rsquo;s implied volatility is surging for its stock options, indicating increased market interest. Tencent Music Entertainment sees increased revenue from paying users, which could drive future growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/jd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/jd/</guid>
      <description>score:45
Chances: JD.com reports earnings beat in the second quarter, outperforming estimates despite economic challenges in China. Gucci and JD.com announce a digital partnership and the launch of an official Gucci flagship store, indicating growth in the luxury e-commerce segment. Analysts suggest JD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COIN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/coin/</guid>
      <description>score:-18
Chances: Coinbase is outpacing stock market gains, indicating strong performance in the crypto industry. The company is expanding its services and targeting regulatory clarity for international expansion. Coinbase-backed insurance alternative OpenCover debuts on Layer 2 blockchain Base, showing innovation. Coinbase announces interim results and extension and upsizing of cash tender offer for its outstanding senior notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BTG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/btg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/btg/</guid>
      <description>score:69
Chances: B2Gold declared a dividend of $0.04 per share for the third quarter of 2023, which may attract income-oriented investors. Strong Q2 2023 operating results and lower costs position B2Gold well to achieve its 2023 annual guidance. B2Gold&amp;rsquo;s updated mineral resource estimate for the Anaconda Area in Mali indicates growth potential for the company&amp;rsquo;s operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GILD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gild/</guid>
      <description>score:60
Chances: Gilead&amp;rsquo;s Phase 2 EVOKE-02 Study of Trodelvy in Combination with KEYTRUDA demonstrates promising clinical activity in first-line metastatic non-small cell lung cancer, indicating potential growth opportunities. Gilead Sciences has a high institutional ownership of 86%, suggesting confidence from major investors. The FDA approval for Veklury to treat COVID-19 in people with hepatic impairment is a positive development for Gilead&amp;rsquo;s product portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vst/</guid>
      <description>score:17
Chances: Vistra Corp. (VST) is receiving positive attention from analysts and investors, making it a potentially favorable investment. The company has reported strong earnings and results in the second quarter of 2023, which could attract investors seeking growth. Vistra Corp. is expanding its energy storage system, positioning itself for the growing demand for clean energy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pten/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pten/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Industry analysts have upgraded Patterson-UTI Energy&amp;rsquo;s revenue forecasts by 36%, indicating positive growth prospects. The completion of the merger between Patterson-UTI Energy and NexTier Oilfield Solutions suggests potential synergies and expansion opportunities. Patterson-UTI Energy expects rig counts and completions activity to rise later this year, aligning with potential industry recovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cig/</guid>
      <description>score:31
Chances: Companhia Energética de Minas Gerais (CIG) reported its Q2 2023 earnings, and the details can be found in the earnings call transcript. CEMIG Geração e Transmissão S.A. announced early tender date results for its cash tender offer for senior notes due 2024, which could impact the company&amp;rsquo;s financial position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ggb/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Gerdau introduced recyclable steel into Formula 1 São Paulo Grand Prix, indicating its innovative approach and market presence. The company has been upgraded to a &amp;lsquo;Buy&amp;rsquo; rating, suggesting potential positive momentum for investors. Gerdau&amp;rsquo;s stock recently crossed above the 50-day moving average and the 200-day moving average, which can be a bullish indicator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RUN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/run/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Sunrun has been upgraded and is well-positioned to navigate a potentially volatile solar market. The company reported better-than-expected Q2 2023 earnings with an earnings per share (EPS) beat, which is a positive sign for investors. Sunrun has expanded its collaboration with PG&amp;amp;E to share critical solar energy with California&amp;rsquo;s grid, which can enhance its market position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BKR</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/bkr/</guid>
      <description>score:57
Chances: Baker Hughes secured a deal to supply equipment for the Driftwood LNG project, potentially contributing to revenue growth. The company signed agreements and expanded equipment supply partnerships with Venture Global, supporting its long-term expansion plans. Despite market fluctuations, Baker Hughes shareholders have earned a 38% CAGR over the last three years, indicating positive performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rig/</guid>
      <description>score:10
Chances: Transocean secured a $222 million drilling contract from ONGC, indicating a potential revenue boost. Transocean announced a $518 million ultra-deepwater drillship contract, which could contribute to future earnings. Transocean&amp;rsquo;s stock has gained 3.3% over the past week, showing positive market sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NCLH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/nclh/</guid>
      <description>score:-23
Chances: Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings has shown resilience despite market challenges. Consumer demand for travel experiences remains robust, which is positive for the company. The company reported strong second-quarter 2023 financial results and improved its full-year guidance. Risks: Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings faced a 25% drop in stock price in August, indicating market volatility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHOP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/shop/</guid>
      <description>score:21
Chances: Shopify&amp;rsquo;s landmark deal with Amazon to integrate &amp;lsquo;Buy with Prime&amp;rsquo; is expected to boost its sales and market presence. The company has been consistently growing, and its stock has outperformed the broader market in recent times. Investors are showing strong interest in Shopify as it continues to innovate and expand its partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MRVL</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mrvl/</guid>
      <description>score:19
Chances: Marvell&amp;rsquo;s AI revenue is showing promising growth, which could be a positive sign for the company&amp;rsquo;s future performance. Despite a recent pullback, institutional shareholders have seen a 7.2% return over the past year, indicating some level of confidence in Marvell. The company beat Q2 earnings and revenue estimates, which may suggest its resilience in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OPEN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/open/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/open/</guid>
      <description>score:36
Chances: Opendoor Technologies Inc. has shown significant growth potential, making it an attractive stock for investors. The company could be one of the market&amp;rsquo;s biggest winners over the next decade, indicating long-term growth prospects. Opendoor&amp;rsquo;s stock performance has been impressive, with a more than 200% increase in value this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DKNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/dkng/</guid>
      <description>score:9
Chances: DraftKings is poised to benefit from the NFL season kick-off, as millions of Americans are expected to bet on games. Analysts look optimistic about DraftKings&amp;rsquo; future prospects, suggesting it may be a good buy. DraftKings&amp;rsquo; expansion efforts, like the opening of Golden Nugget&amp;rsquo;s casino in Pennsylvania, indicate growth potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIVN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rivn/</guid>
      <description>score:33
Chances: Swiss Bank doubled down on EV stock Rivian and achieved significant gains, indicating investor interest. Battery material price easing expected in the next year could benefit Rivian&amp;rsquo;s EV production. Rivian&amp;rsquo;s participation in the Goldman Sachs Communacopia + Technology Conference suggests market engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TD</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/td/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/td/</guid>
      <description>score:28
Chances: Announcement of common share repurchase up to 90 million shares. Declaration of dividends and positive third quarter financial results. Positive customer satisfaction ranking for banking mobile app. Regulatory approval for normal course issuer bid. Expansion plans with new branch openings and appointments to board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RLX</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/rlx/</guid>
      <description>score:-6
Chances: Positive Q2 and Q1 earnings results announced. Announcement of unaudited financial results and transcripts. Stock upgraded to &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; by MSCI ESG Rating. CEO&amp;rsquo;s holdings reduced by 13%, but still a significant shareholder. Risks: Declining stock performance over the past year. Volatility and fluctuations in stock value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPST</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/upst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/upst/</guid>
      <description>score:-54
Chances: Upstart&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues surpass estimates. Selected by Farmers Insurance Federal Credit Union for personal lending. Potential for significant upside due to AI technology in the financial sector. Stock&amp;rsquo;s impressive rally of over 400% since May 2023. Strong performance among the best performing stocks in the last 3 and 6 months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPNG</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/cpng/</guid>
      <description>score:-27
Chances: Coupang sustains profit streak, sees logistics investments pay off. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s Q2 earnings and revenues beat estimates. Coupang stock clears key benchmark, hitting 80-plus RS rating. Coupang&amp;rsquo;s sales beat estimates after big spending pays off. Positive momentum and growth trends in Coupang&amp;rsquo;s returns on capital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/o/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/o/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Realty Income&amp;rsquo;s consistent dividend payments and yield. Positive outlook for long-term investment. Strong financial performance and revenue surpassing estimates. Investment in Bellagio Las Vegas at a significant valuation. Stable monthly dividend declarations for years. Risks: Potential impact of rising interest rates on dividend stocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SLB</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/slb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/slb/</guid>
      <description>score:65
Chances: Double-digit jump in revenue in Q2 2023 due to rebounding oil and gas prices. Positive Q2 earnings surprises and growth potential. Awarded a five-year contract for Petrobras&amp;rsquo; digital transformation. Strong performance in the energy sector and resilient stock. Trending stock with optimistic outlook from Wall Street analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vrt/</guid>
      <description>score:2
Chances: Positive analyst recommendations and growth potential. Strong second quarter results and raised full-year outlook. Significant surge in stock price and momentum. Participation in secondary offerings and announcements. Recognition as a strong growth stock in various lists. Risks: Market volatility affecting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/qs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/qs/</guid>
      <description>score:-160
Chances: QuantumScape&amp;rsquo;s focus on developing next-generation solid-state lithium-metal batteries showcases its commitment to innovative technology, which could position it well in the evolving EV industry. Despite recent fluctuations in QS stock, the company&amp;rsquo;s ability to raise significant capital through underwritten public offerings demonstrates investor interest and support for its growth initiatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MARA</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mara/</guid>
      <description>score:7
Chances: Marathon&amp;rsquo;s strong performance in Bitcoin mining, including record blocks and increased operational hash rate, indicates its leadership in the crypto mining sector. The company&amp;rsquo;s strategic expansion, such as its mining operations in Abu Dhabi, demonstrates its commitment to diversifying and scaling its operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIPS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/vips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/vips/</guid>
      <description>score:-32
Chances: Vipshop is a leading online discount retailer for brands in China. Strong position in China&amp;rsquo;s competitive e-commerce market. Anticipated release of second quarter 2023 financial results. Risks: Volatility in the stock price due to market movements. Competitive nature of China&amp;rsquo;s e-commerce market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTCH</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftch/</guid>
      <description>score:-9
Chances: Favorable earnings estimate revision activity and positive Earnings ESP. Positive stock price performance, up 17% in the last quarter. Key appointment of Chief Financial Officer, Tim Stone. Leading global platform for the luxury fashion industry. Risks: Vulnerability of stock price to institutions due to large stake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/app/</guid>
      <description>score:67
Chances: AppLovin beats earnings expectations, reporting higher EPS than expected. Strong second-quarter earnings report and positive third-quarter forecast. Surge in stock price (over 26%) after strong earnings report. Guidance for higher third-quarter sales than analysts&amp;rsquo; expectations. Risks: Market volatility and macroeconomic factors impacting stock performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EXPE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/expe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/expe/</guid>
      <description>score:901
Chances: Expedia Group&amp;rsquo;s Q2 2023 earnings report indicates that consumers are willing to pay higher prices for international summer travel, reflecting strong travel demand. The company beat earnings expectations in Q2 2023, with reported EPS of $2.89 compared to expectations of $2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
