<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings estimates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings estimates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:05:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PAGS</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/pags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/pags/</guid>
      <description>score:20
Chances: Expected to beat earnings estimates and move higher. Positive earnings call transcripts and potential value. Potential for strong rally and upside potential. Highlighted by analysts as a potential value stock. Positive financial results and profit beating forecasts. Risks: Stock price volatility and potential declines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/se/</guid>
      <description>score:34
Chances: Sea Limited reports strong revenue growth despite missing estimates. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and upside according to Wall Street. Investing in Sea five years ago would have delivered a significant gain. TikTok signs payment pact with Atome for Malaysia e-commerce. Sea Limited&amp;rsquo;s intrinsic value is potentially 50% above its share price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AQN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/aqn/</guid>
      <description>score:8
Chances: Announcement of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s CEO Arun Banskota&amp;rsquo;s resignation and the appointment of interim CEO Christopher Huskilson. Consideration of the potential sale of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s renewable energy unit as a strategic move to reduce debt. Discussion of Algonquin&amp;rsquo;s dividend declarations and its financial decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTNT</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ftnt/</guid>
      <description>score:75
Chances: Fortinet is expanding cybersecurity knowledge and skill sets to address the cybersecurity talent shortage. Discussion of best cybersecurity ETFs and potential opportunities in the cloud security sector. Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s top analyst calls, including upgrades and cybersecurity market trends. Focus on improving cybersecurity strategies to address vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
