<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Estimates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Estimates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MU</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/mu/</guid>
      <description>score:-15
Chances: Micron (MU) reported earnings 30 days ago. What&amp;rsquo;s next for the stock? We take a look at earnings estimates for some clues. Emerging technologies, like artificial intelligence (AI), are creating brand-new opportunities for two semiconductor companies besides Nvidia. The future of the US economy holds the potential for significant transformation, driven by technological advancements, innovation and evolving global dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gme/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: The investment landscape has been abuzz with the trend of meme stocks, a phenomenon ushered in by the remarkable and dramatic rise in GameStop’s stock in 2021. Investors know that the current expectations project rate cuts as early as March, which is a major positive for the economy overall and suggests that we have avoided a recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TRIP</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/trip/</guid>
      <description>score:-19
Chances: Tripadvisor&amp;rsquo;s RS Rating has been upgraded from 78 to 81, indicating potential for a significant climb in share price. Kristen Dalton&amp;rsquo;s appointment as President of the Tripadvisor Core business suggests a strategic transformation within the company. Cruise Critic® has recognized Tripadvisor as a winner in its Editors&amp;rsquo; Picks Awards, highlighting the company&amp;rsquo;s strength in the cruise industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
