<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Earnings Estimates on FinanClub</title>
    <link>https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Earnings Estimates on FinanClub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:03:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://finan.club/tags/earnings-estimates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SWN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/swn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/swn/</guid>
      <description>score:102
Chances: Higher oil production and reduction in marketing purchases aid Southwestern&amp;rsquo;s Q4 earnings. Uncovering the Financial and Strategic Position of Chesapeake Energy Corp. Investors looking for ways to find stocks that are set to beat quarterly earnings estimates should che&amp;hellip; The longer-term bull case for natural gas rests on expanding U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TCN</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/tcn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/tcn/</guid>
      <description>score:38
Chances: Tricon Residential Inc. has received positive recommendations from leading independent proxy advisory firms ISS and Glass Lewis, indicating strong shareholder support for the company&amp;rsquo;s plans. The company has announced its consolidated financial results for the three and twelve months ended December 31, 2023, showing positive performance and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YPF</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/ypf/</guid>
      <description>score:117
Chances: YPF SA&amp;rsquo;s plan to divest aging oil fields will free up hundreds of millions of dollars to invest in its shale push in the Vaca Muerta formation. The company has been highlighted in the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) value stocks list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GME</title>
      <link>https://finan.club/us/gme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://finan.club/us/gme/</guid>
      <description>score:147
Chances: The investment landscape has been abuzz with the trend of meme stocks, a phenomenon ushered in by the remarkable and dramatic rise in GameStop’s stock in 2021. Investors know that the current expectations project rate cuts as early as March, which is a major positive for the economy overall and suggests that we have avoided a recession.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
